<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject36</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 20:56:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Universe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 13:29:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eat the wood from the table at school. He used to scrape the table with a ruler and then eat the wooden pieces. And he did it every day, until the table had a spoon shape were he had been eating it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 12:14:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In 2019 the Event Horizon Telescope took the first "picture" of a black hole, the M87\*.  A rotating disk of ionized gas surrounds the black hole, with a diameter of 3.7×10\^12 km. To have an idea of how enormous it is, the distance from Pluto to the Sun is 5.8×10\^9 km. Therefore, the disk of the black hole is around 1000 times bigger than the distance from Pluto to the Sun. Not only that, the radius of the black hole is 120 times bigger than the distance from the Sun to Earth. Freaking big. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 10:38:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Catalonian here, this sounds so familiar...classic, "we would allow if if it was legal, but it's not, and of course law is sacred and above people" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 10:25:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would say start right now and always asap, send emails and show interest. If you ask for it, the chance will appear and will be given to you by some company </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 09:12:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know and argentinian guy with that surname! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 21:48:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lekker! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 22:45:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I must not fear.
Fear is the mind-killer.
Fear is the little-death that brings total obliteration.
I will face my fear.
I will permit it to pass over me and through me.
And when it has gone past I will turn the inner eye to see its path.
Where the fear has gone there will be nothing.
Only I will remain." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Let's roll! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 14:12:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 13:32:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would like to see the data for the west of Ireland. I have been there multiple times during summer and it just rains all the fucking time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 08:34:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This Meow'dib is surely not afraid of the box! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 11:26:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair enough haha indeed not being able to reserve a seat is fucking annoying, but in the end I still love it because the cinema is so good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 10:51:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing bad has ever happend to me personally, I can't complain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 03:54:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Phenomena has the best sound system in BCN. Also the screen quality is really good and they can show 70mm movies, so for instance you would be having the true experience Tarantino was going for in The Hateful Eight, as image matters so much.

Downside: can't reserve a seat. Sometimes this is annoying for big very well known movies, but it's usually grand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 11:02:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Recall Spanish ham, Jamón. In Spain it's not food, it's a religion. And of course many typical dishes have pork, we literally eat everything from the pig. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hybrid Minds </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 10:09:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 08:52:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dune is the mind killer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 14:40:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Super Mario Sunshine and Metroid Prime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 14:55:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I speak 3 languages and I can think in any of them, I have no trouble with it. If I am speaking English with someone I will be thinking in English. If I am alone it depends, don't ask me how I choose one or the other but I just randomly think in one and that's it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 00:44:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for your reply! Seems nice, I am glad to hear people are chill. My issue is that I don't know anybody there, so I am a bit concerned about meeting people and hanging out, but for what you say it shouldn't be super hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 23:52:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! Nice info, sounds good and like and interesting city :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 23:50:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks a lot! Sounds like a nice place. I am originally from Spain, so I was just curious to know about Dortmund. I am glad to hear people are open minded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How is life in Dortmund? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 22:54:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi all,

I will me moving to Dortmund next year, and I would like to know a bit about the city. What's the vibe there like? Is it a big city? I am from the south of Europe, what can I expect from Dortmund compared to southern cities? Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 08:54:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mate I am so glad you gave it a chance and liked it. I totally agree with you, this movie is jaw dropping, and one of the best skills of Denis is to take a cast and make them do an incredibly performance. I mean wtf, Jack's G. character and performance is out of this world, as well as H. Jackaman's (and even for the secondary characters this happens). In this sense it reminds me of Tarantino or Scorsese. The acting is just 10/10.

Tension wise he is also a master. His movies are very tense, but the point is that you feel it because his movies feel so real, even the sci-fi ones. I have this very funny story to explain what I exactly mean. Some time ago I told my gf that she should watch Arrival. One night we decided to do so, but before watching the movie we smoked a joint. Then we started watching the movie, and we literally had to stop after 30 min. The tension was too much, it felt too real, and with the high we were like omg the fucking aliens are arriving. It just felt way too real, we couldn't deal with the tension. Something I noticed in Arrival that Denis used to create tension and loved is the following. Since minute 1 in Arrival they keep saying how the aliens have arrived. You see people's reaction and stuff, but you NEVER see the spaceship for the entire first 15-20 min. The first time you see the spaceship is when the main character goes to the military base, and then you are like damn there it is, after 20 min. That is tension. So good.

Anyway, I am very happy you enjoyed the movie. I hope Dune turns out to be a good movie, all the necessary ingredients are there for sure. Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 23:34:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dafuck is wrong with you dude, you are a fucking  asshole, go fuck yourself piece of shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 16:33:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Had the same problem in the past. I used to focus on a problem, do a calculation which could take me 3 days, and then write down all the calculation. Then it would happen what you mention, I would write for days for a single problem and I used to try to improve the writing, and all of this would take me 10 days. In the end I figured out that what works for me is to write as I do the calculation, so i basically write every day and after every step of the calculation, before moving on to the next step. In this manner I write less (although I write more times because I write after every small step) and things are clearer as I move on and makes it easier to have all the steps in my head to move to the next one. When I am done with all the calculation I read what I wrote all over again and improve it, BUT ONLY ONCE. That's the final rule, only one final reread. Also try to not be super peaky about the writing, if it's not perfect it's not a problem as long as it is for you to read and have ordered in a document. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 17:25:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seven's "what's in the box" scene. Fucked up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 17:20:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Certain octopuses know how use shells in order to make an armor for themselves. Saw a video of one doing it so that a shark couldn't eat it. I thought it was incredibly smart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 12:34:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahahahaaha perdón, es que siempre todo el mundo me lo dice y me cansa, pero entiendo tú respuesta. Lo siento! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 11:52:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ya, y? Qué quieres qué te diga? No es mi culpa que sea de bcn y tú de otro sitio. Not my fucking problem xd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 10:50:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go have a look at the modernist buildings, they are really nice (in my opinion the nicest one is the Hospital de Sant Pau). Also get lost around the city center, within the small and narrow streets. Go to bars and have beers, that is what Spanish people do, we love going to bars, talk and drink beer and have some food (and yeah, we love being loud). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 10:45:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo simplemente digo que soy de Barcelona...y ya está, cada uno que piense lo que quiera. No me definiría como Español, pero tampoco como indepe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 23:54:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am happy to hear you are working on it! Remember none of it it's your own fault, 0 blame on you for being who you are. All my love and support for you dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 23:01:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you would be happy in Spain. Surely you will find some asshole from time to time, but generally speaking people will be respectful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 21:56:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice, enjoy your holidays! And please let me know what you think about the movie if you watch it, I am very curious to see what you think :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 18:48:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand, but I think you should give it a chance, specially if you like Denis so much. Do you really want to not watch it, being a Denis movie which everyone says it's amazing?

Also, let me say something about the movie, no spoilers ahead. The movie is not about child kidnapping at all. It indeed happens, but if you watch the movie you will understand that it is just an excuse and setup for the other characters to be developed in their journey. I swear to god, you have to watch this movie, give it a try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 15:46:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Man that is so awful, I am so sorry you had to suffer these kinds of behaviours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 15:42:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well my friend, welcome to thw world of physics, there are questions that make no sense. It is as if you ask me why we exist, why things are made of particles, and why protons and electrons have opposite charge. Why? Because we SEE it, bevause we can observe it and measure it and have data. Sometimes the answer to these questions are "because it is like this and that ks it". Why does spacetime curve? Who the fuck knows, we just know it does and it works. Of course this is unsatisfying, but right now we simply don't know why </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 15:09:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course, I agree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 15:04:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are confusing something. You are thinking of curvature and mass/energy as different things, but Einstein's field equations (someone else wrote them) tell us that they are the same thing. Look at the equation, it says T= G, where T is energy and mass and G curvature. They are the same thing. This of course brings up the philosophy of general relativity. Would it be possible to have empty spacetime without any bodies? Meaning, can you have an empty universe? Well that is something for another day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 14:58:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Indeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 14:25:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These people are fucking obsessed, they really have a problem with this shit. Get your shit together America, we all laugh at your constant stupidity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 14:11:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you seen Prisoners? To me it's his best movie, fucking amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 13:50:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mmm no, tú has dicho que no son mediocres en educación pero si en investigación. Yo digo que la docencia y invesitgación som buenas, independientemente de que no haya dinero. El problema es la pasta, no la docencia o investigación, que son buenas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 13:45:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, yes and no. As other people said Einstein's theory HAD TO happen, the signs where there and it was a matter of time. Still a genius of course. In my opinion we have been focusing into high energy physics a lot, and new developments and models will (and are) be developed in low energy regimes for particle physics and string theory. Also, we'll see what quantum computing could reveal about the nature of quantum info </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 10:11:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have seen a couple of "documentaries" about it. I just laugh, even if the ideas are cool, makes no sense to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 02:13:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you really believe that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 02:10:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is not a conspiracy theory, it is a fact. Trump won 2016 elections manipulating US voters, search for Cambridge Analytica and you will see how deep the rabbit hole goes. Fucked up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 01:29:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure, seems correct if you say so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 23:18:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No estoy totalmente de acuerdo, yo estoy haciendo el doctorado en física en la UB y la investigación es buena, dentro de mi campo es una uni buena en términos europeos. Y la docencia también es buena, yo fui a hacer el máster en Holanda, en una de las mejores unis de Europa, y yo era de los más bien preparados gracias a mi grado en la UB, por delante de Irlandeses, Ingleses, Griegos, Italianos, etc y estaba tan bien preparado como Alemanes y Holandeses.

La triste realidad es que las unis no son malas, lo que pasa es que no hay dinero. Eso siempre lo digo con mis compañeros de doctorado, es sorprendente y miraculoso como cobrando menos de 1000 al mes por hacer investigación, la investigación es buena. Obviamente es una situación lamentable e insostenible. La parte más triste de todo esto es que me han ofrecido una plaza de investigador en Alemania para acabar mi doctorado, y no dudaré en irme allí porque me pagan más. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 19:13:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> coño tienes razón lol perdón haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 18:42:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo entiendo que veas España muy mal, al menos en tema de unis, y haya una falta de autoestima. Obviamente hay mucho que mejorar, eso seguro. Pero también creo que aquí hay una cultura muy dañina hacía nosotros mismos, y pensamos "todo es una mierda". La realidad, creo yo, es que ni todo es una mierda, ni todo es perfecto. Yo solía pensar de forma muy negativa, pero me di cuenta que no ayuda a nadie, ni a mi país ni a mi mismo. Cualquier extremo es malo. Dicho eso, el problema que yo veo con las unis en España no es la educación en si, sino la falta de conexión entre el mundo universitario y el mundo laboral, el sistema hace poco esfuerzo para facilitar salidas laborales des de la uni. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 18:06:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lo dices por mi o por ti? Entiendo que por ti pero no me queda claro xd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 18:05:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahah ok entiendo, yo estudié física en la UB y también fue bastante duro. En parte es una mierfa sufrir tanto pero ahora lo veo como algo positivo, porque si puedo aguantar esa presión, puedo con todo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 17:30:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> La mitad de reconocimiento comparado con qué otra uni? Me gustaría saber en que basas tú afirmación. Tienes alguna fuente de datos? Que conste que yo no estudié en la UPC, no intento ser un defensor hardcore, simplemente me sorprendre tú afirmación </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 17:19:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Las unis de España no son mediocres. Obviamente hay unis mucho mejores en el mundo y se puede mejorar mucho, pero no es justo decir que son mediocres, porque no lo son. Mira las estadísticas y números antes de decir algo tan injusto (e innecesario) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 16:34:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> La UPC (Unversidad Politécnica de Cataluña) es una de las mejores en grados y investigación en ingeniería, con un gran abanico de posibilidades. Además tienen muchas colaboraciones con otras unis, como la Universidad de Barcelona. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 14:21:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice one, fuck him. I have a lot of trouble trying to understand why some people use hacks. I mean, how is it fun then? Isn't the point to try your best and if you do well you win and show you played the best game? If you use hacks you don't prove shit to anyone, and specially not to yourself. Makes no sense to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 19:53:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Visca Catalunya!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 18:47:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for sharing your experience, I hope you find a nice job in industry. You are totally right that knowing what kind of jobs I woild like to do I could start doing things that would be useful. But it is hard to do courses and stuff while doing a PhD, it is so time consuming... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 18:46:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks a lot, I really appreciate your answers. This is giving me much hope :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 17:26:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for sharing your experience. Do you think your PhD was valued then in order to get a job? I understand so. Would you say it was easy for you to find a job after the PhD? What about your colleagues who also did a PhD and went to industry, are they also happy they did the PhD? Hope you don't mind me asking so many questions :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is a PhD in physics valued/useful in industry? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 17:18:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello all,

I am currently doing a PhD in theoretical physics (no experiments, just theory and some coding to compare my theoretical results to experimental data obtained by other people). I am now 7 months into my PhD, and I am unsure if this is the right choice for my career, and I would love to hear your experiences and thoughts.

So, I am very sure that if I complete my PhD I won't stay in academia, and I would go into industry jobs. My fear is that a PhD in theoretical physics won't be valued in the industry I am keen about (tech, AI, robotics, renewable energies, data science, ... you get the idea). Is a PhD in theoretical physics valued in industry? Is it useful? I am enjoying my PhD and I like the topic, but I am very worried it won't be valued in the industry sector, specially being a theoretical work. I am very confused these days about the value of my PhD, and only knowing what other people know and say about it will help me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is a PhD in particle physics useful/valued in industry? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 17:04:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi all,

I am currently doing my PhD in particle physics (BSM phenomenology), now 7 months into it. I need some advice about the value of doing this PhD for future jobs, as I am doubting it is the right choice for my career.

I am very sure I won't stay in academia if I finish my PhD, and so I would go into industry jobs. My current concern is that such a PhD won't be valued in industry. If I wish to go work in tech companies, renewable energies, data science, etc, how useful is it for me to complete my PhD in particle physics? Is it better to just go right into industry and get experience in those areas? I like the PhD itself and the research I am doing, but I am very worried about my future and that this PhD won't be useful and won't be valued, and that other people with a more industry oriented studies will be more competent than me for the job. I would love to hear your experiences if you went to industry after your PhD! Was it worth the PhD? Did they value you for having it? Did you get a certain job because you have a PhD in particle physics? Thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 21:21:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should convince your buddy to read the book, not to watch the movie!! The real deal my friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 21:11:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have never been there yet, but would be cool to check it out. Anyway I would be up for meeting you if you like :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 17:18:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I also like techno music, and electronic music in general, specially d&b! It is indeed true that here there is not a big scene for electronic music. Also love all the tv shows you mentioned! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Need advice for future plans </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 17:23:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi all,

I am currently doing a PhD in physics, and after a year of research I am wondering if this is the correct path for me. I am quite certain I won't stay in academia if I complete my PhD, and I am worried I should just go straight to industry instead of first doing a PhD. So I was just wondering if someone had a similar experience, with a PhD in physics or a similar field and later on went to industry. Was your PhD valued? Is it worth for industry?  What can I expect with a physics PhD? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 17:15:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks I  really appreciate your encouraging message </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 12:36:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have heard so before, I have a couple of friends who worked in consulting, but they were very unhappy with it and eventually left. For what they described to me it also doesn't seem  like an option for me. Do you work in consulting? If so, what is your experience/opinion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 12:34:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks I will definitely have a look, the thing is I am in Europe, so I don't know to what extent I can trust the AIP data, but surely it will be helpful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Options after my physics PhD </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 09:20:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello,

I am currently doing my PhD in theoretical particle physics, and right now I feel I can't keep going with this. I am concerned with my possibilities after the PhD, as I am quite sure I won't stay in academia, and I would rather go to industry jobs. So I was wondering if someone here did a PhD within particle physics and went to industry afterwords, in order to have an idea of what kind of job I can get after my research period. I am mostly interested in tech industry, and even in a mathematical point of view of economics. I am so worried this PhD won't open the right doors for me...any advice?  Thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 18:03:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Smash Bros for gc! What an amazing game. Also metroid prime and metroid prime 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 15:36:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do! Not only I prefer to sit, I also think it is much cleaner and so respectful for other people, ladies basically. I always used to pee standing until I broke my leg and so for 3 months I had to sit to pee, and then I realised I prefer to sit lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 16:38:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my opinion all the options you listed are good ones. But maybe you should also look at which uni is best for the field you are going to study. What degree will you pursue? Not only the city is important, but the research quality of the uni is, specially if you are considering doing a master's or PhD afterwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 15:33:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what a nobbit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I (25M) have to choose between one of my best friends (25M) and my girlfriend (24F) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 15:11:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So, allow me to introduce the situation first. I am currently with my gf in Ireland, where she is from. I came here from Barcelona (where I am from) about a month ago, to be with her and see her. You can already imagine it was hard to make such a decision to see her with the covid situation, which is particularly bad in Spain.

In August I had planned to go back to Barcelona, actually tomorrow. Why? Well, to see my friends. Many of my friends don't live in Barcelona anymore, and so our only chance to meet and see each other is during the summer holidays. One of my best friends (I will refer to him as G) is precisely now in Barcelona, he came back from the Netherlands a few days ago, and he will stay in Barcelona until the 14th of August. My initial plan was to come back to Barcelona the 7th, and during the weekend meet my friends, and in particular G, because he would stay in my place for the weekend. We would be going to the beach, smoking some weed, playing videogames, etc. Fun stuff that I miss doing with him.

The issue is that I have been talking to my gf, and she asked me if I could stay until Sunday in Ireland, so I would go back to BCN the 9th/10th. Then we would be able to make some stuff we haven't had a chance to do (because I had to fucking quarantine for 2 weeks) like going to one of the main cities in Ireland, go to the cinema, a restaurant, etc. So, the problem is what to do. Should I stay or go? I hate these situations because I know that whatever I choose, I will feel bad for one of them. There are some important points to make that I think influence the way to think about this. For a start, with all this motherfucking covid shit my gf doesn't know if she will be able to come to BCN to visit during the summer. So I don't know when I would see her again. Not only that, we used to live together in the Netherlands but since 8 months ago we are living in different countries. So we don't see each other as much. If you ask me I truly prefer to stay with my gf, specially because in BCN the covid is going really bad now. But I also want to see G and my other friends, so if I go back on Sunday I will only see G for like 2 days. I am aware that we are talking only about a two day difference, which is a bit ridiculous, but at the same time I feel bad for G as we had planned stuff. So, what do you think? I made pretty clear in my mind that I will stay (because I actually WANT TO), but I would appreciate some advice on how to think about these situations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 22:46:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I really noticed that when I lived in Utrecht. I could even notice by just walking through the streets, they were just so clean, everything was perfect. To me, it almost seemed disturbing the level of order and perfection lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 22:36:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a Spanish, and someone who lived for three years in Utrecht, I can try to give you my opinion.

 I think spanish people see the dutch in the following way. Physically, tall people (for sure I mean holy shit they are fucking tall), blonde, classic northen european appearence in general. As how they see their personality, I would say more direct, cold, reserved. Basically, hard to get to know them. I would say that these stereotypes are kind of true (I think there is some truth to every stereotype). Personally I always found Dutch people calm, direct, not afraid of saying whay they think and yeah, more reserved in comparison to mediterranean people. Not saying it in a negative way, it is simply a different "style".

As a country, Spain sees the Netherlands as this small country in Europe that has a lot of money and where they know what they are doing. Spain has always been kind of a mess politically speaking, and we see the Dutch much more responsable with their society, jobs, money, etc. Mainly, we think you know how to make a proper society work (and I would agree to this totally). I think if I had to choose a word to define the Dutch I would choose order. Everything seems to fit perfectly, everything seems to work perfectly and everything makes sense. Of course it is not true and it is not perfect, but compared to Spain the Netherlands is the land of order and the maximum "let us build a proper country and work together" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 19:32:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Desgraciadamente tienes toda la razón. La UE ayudará a España, pero a qué precio? Ya veremos... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 18:59:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personalmente, dada my experiencia, la situación es bastante lamentable. Especialmente entre jóvenes (20-30 años). España tiene una economía basada en el turismo, comercio, hostelería, etc. No hay suficiente dinero invertido en mejorar diferentes sectores, especialmente la investigación, I+D etc. Los sueldos son bajos, y la vida es cara. Soy de Barcelona, y es totalmente terrible la relación salario/precios, simplemente no tiene ningún puto sentido estar cobrando alrededor de mil euros en Barcelona. Es demencial. Las causas de esta situación provienen de diferentes partes.

Por un lado, hay una gran cantidad de jóvenes que dejan los estudios a una edad temprana, concretamente alrededor del 30%, mientras que la media de la UE es 15%. Esto implica que haya una gran parte de la clase trabajadora poco qualificada, con más dificultad para encontrar trabajo.

En el otro extremo, hay un problema de sobrequalificación. Debido a que España se sustena en servicios, turismo, etc muchos puestos de trabajo no requieren qualificación alguna, o poca. Así que puedes tener una carrera y un máster, para acabar trabajando de camarero/camarera (no tengo nada en contra de tal trabajo, respetable como cualquier otro trabajo) y esto genera una descompensación entre educación y empleo.

Por otra parte, la politica del país. Aquí no entraré porque no tengo ni puta idea de politica, pero tengo bastante claro por lo poco que entiendo y he visto que no han hecho un buen trabajo en la economía.

Para saber un poco más del tema recomiendo leer el artículo "La empleabilidad de los jóvenes en España: Explicando el elevado desempleo juvenil durante la recesión económica", por Almudena Moreno Mínguez. Es un artículo interesante que además cita muchas fuentes en caso que uno quiera indagar un poco más en el tema.

Para finalizar, mi situación/experiencia personal. Estudié una carrera en Barcelona, y al acabar fui a Holanda a hacer un máster. Mis estudios son en física. Al acabar el máster vine de vuelta a Barcelona, donde estoy haciendo un doctorado en la uni de Barcelona. Y estoy cobrando 900 euros al mes. Cómo es esto posible? Es totalmente lamentable, no se aguanta por ningún sitio. En Holanda trabajé lavando platos para poder pagar mi alquiler, y la triste verdad es que cobro menos en Barcelona haciendo investigación en física que lavando platos en Holanda. Si, lo has leído bien. Que alguien me explique como se puede aguantar esto. Por suerte me han ofrecido una plaza en una universidad de Alemania, y no dudaré en aceptarla, pues la condiciones son mucho mejores. Lo más triste de toda esta historia es que a mi me encanta vivir en Barcelona, y me encantaría poder trabajar aquí y poner mi granito de arena para mejorar el país con mi investigación y trabajo. Pero simplemente el mercado español no me valora, ni me siento valorado, así que para vivir de forma precaria paso. Y esta situación que acabo de describir se aplica también a muchos de mis compañeros. La mitad de mis amigos estan viviendo y trabajando en otros países, Holanda, Alemania, UK, Irlanda, etc. Mucha gente válida y qualificada esta marchando del país, y de aquí 20 años será una catastrófe aún mayor para España. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 15:43:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks a lot for your advice, I will have a look at the laptop you mentioned. I have been looking a bit more into it and I have seen a possible laptop for me, the Dell inspiron 5000 13.3 5370, with the following specifics: Intel i7 8th generation,  256 GB SSD, 13,3'', 8 gb ram. Do you have an opinion on this laptop given my preferences and coding work?

Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 800 EUROS - SPAIN </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 18:23:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> * **Total budget (in local currency) and country of purchase. Please do not use USD unless purchasing in the US:**
* 800 euros (Spain)
* **Are you open to refurbs/used?**
* No
* **How would you prioritize form factor (ultrabook, 2-in-1, etc.), build quality, performance, and battery life?**
* Ultrabook
* **How important is weight and thinness to you?**
* Not very heavy
* **Do you have a preferred screen size? If indifferent, put N/A.**
* 13''
* **Are you doing any CAD/video editing/photo editing/gaming? List which programs/games you desire to run.**
* I code using Mathematica
* **If you're gaming, do you have certain games you want to play? At what settings and FPS do you want?**
* Not gaming
* **Any specific requirements such as good keyboard, reliable build quality, touch-screen, finger-print reader, optical drive or good input devices (keyboard/touchpad)?**
* Good keyboard
* **Leave any finishing thoughts here that you may feel are necessary and beneficial to the discussion.**
* I want it to have a full HD screen, minimum 8GB RAM, SSD. For my PhD I basically use it to read papers, books, write Latex documents and code with Mathematica </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
