<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject23</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 03:16:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Los españoles somos latinos en el sentido de ser territorio donde (en su momento) se habló latín y el sur de Europa, a grandes rasgos, estaba unificado bajo el Imperio Romano. En el sentido moderno de la palabra, Latino como relativo a la América Latina (la que se llevó la herencia cultural de los países originalmente hablantes de latín) no, para nada. En todo caso, a los españoles se nos puede englobar como hispanos junto a prácticamente todo el centro y sur de América (salvo Brasil y un par más de países), mientras que latinos serían ambos grupos de países americanos (incluyendo Brasil) pero no todos serían hispanos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 08:06:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1- I'd say you meant to write "guay" instead of "quay", and in that case I use that pretty often. Also bárbaro sometimes. The one I use most often tho, I'd say "mola" but it's not on the list.

2- They don't sound weird or unfamiliar, just uncommon around here. Soke of them have strong associations with Latin American communities such as chévere. Macanudo sounds a little funny and I only use it very sparsely and in a joking context, it doesn't come naturally.

3- Spanish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 07:52:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely go with Madrid. Barcelona is a tourist trap and Sevilla is far smaller and on a different scale to the other two. Plus, organizing a weekend trip/short holiday to any other place is easier from Madrid because of distance and availability of direct transportation to pretty much anywhere else in the country. You may even get to experience the three. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 04:12:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depending on context, it could also mean cute or wholesome, like "Ay, qué rico eres" =  "oh that's so sweet of you". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 18:10:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wallapop has a built in system that manages the payment and shipping part for you. Modify your listing to include dimensions and weight of the package and they'll calculate a rate which will be shown to buyers. They just have to click "Buy" and the money will be withdrawn from their card. After you've accepted the offer, pack the thing and take it to a Correos office. Show them the barcode/number on the app and they'll take it from there, shipping label and all. Once the package is in their hands, you will get your money.

&#x200B;

 It really is not that difficult to figure out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 18:01:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We're still very, very far from herd immunity. You'd need about 70-80% of the population covered for it to work, and last I read, even the most affected areas those who were infected or recovering were still around 12-15%. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 02:27:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As long as you're a resident, your nationality doesn't matter. You'll be eligible for regular mortgages which is a good thing (lower interests and bigger percentages).

The amount of money that a bank is willing to loan you for the purchase of a house depends on whether it's going to be your main residence or a secondary one (think vacation home, buying with the intent to rent, etc). As a rule of thumb, the bank will cover up to 80% in the first case and 70% in the rest; some particular cases (if you buy from the real estate agency owned by that particular bank, for example) can go up to 90% or even the full amount, but that is likely not to be your case. So, 80% of what exactly? Depends.

First of all. they need to have a look at your finances (employment history, average earnings, current live debt on credit cards/loans/etc, possible need for a guarantor, recent tax statements... The standard stuff) and greenlight you as a potential candidate for the deed. In the second stage, they will look at the property through an appraisal company and estimate the value it has for the bank. This appraisal may turn out lower, around or higher than the market value (the amount you're paying for it), and the bank decides at THAT moment what 80% they're willing to cover for. They can go for the market price (170k), the seling price (151k) or the appraisal value (which may vary), usually the lowest of them all to cover their own butts. Also, keep in mind that you may have to foot the bill for this appraisal if you end up not following through and signing the loan with the amount they're willing to give you. I know that the law changed since I bought my own flat so check with your bank.

Thirdly, you need to take into account the various expenses that come with a mortgage. The vast majority of banks in Spain will demand several additional expenses in the shape of insurance policies, opening fees, and paying the various entities involved in the process (appraisal, notary fees, processing agency costs, ITP (Impuesto de transmisiones patrimoniales, asset transfering tax) for second hand houses and VAT for first hand), which go anywhere from 10-30% the price of the property itself.

&#x200B;

Anyway, if we stick to the data we have in the post, you're gonna need that down payment. Even in the simplest of cases, if the house is valued at 170k, those 19k you deposit through your rent only amounts to 11%, and as I stated, you'll most likely need to cover at least 20-25% of the property value before anything else. I'd suggest looking into how much they're going to tax you for the purchase (varies from region to region, and you may qualify for deductions depending on various factors like age and total wealth, in my case I went from 10% to only needing to pay 3%) , and add \~3k to comfortably accomodate for "paperwork" fees (appraisal, notary, processing).  So, in the end, you should try to save up around another 25k by the end of your contract if you want to walk into the bank without a worry on your mind. Of course, the more you save up the better. Sign as small and short of a mortgage as you can, the sooner you're out the better. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 01:36:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Es parte del acento andaluz, nada más. La chica está aspirando las S (no las pronuncia), y por eso la T posterior suena mucho más fuerte. Si te fijas, te darás cuenta de que no sólo pasa con la T. En la frase "Espero que os guste", verás que "Espero" se convierte en algo más parecido a "Eh-pero" y que la S de "os" casi desaparece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 21:30:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But there is a link. You wouldn't write with a Z something you tend to pronounce with an S if it's already written with an S, because it already matches. Alternate spellings most frequently come from mixups when you lose track of how it's supposed to be pronounced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 19:21:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not really, if anything Extremadura is more likely to _seseo_ than _ceceo_. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 23:44:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One of my uni professors was named Pimentel. Nice fella. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 23:34:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Teeny tiny correction, the proper spelling for the plant (the tree, actually) would be "Aliso", meaning "alder". You may have more luck tracking down the S spelling back in Europe because Castilian Spanish does differentiate pronunciation between S, C and Z (it is not a lisp). Many regions of Latin America with _seseo_ (the homogenization of s, c and z sounds into just the S sound) have caused a lot of variant spellings over time, making those three letters interchangeable in many cases (i.e. Aliso> Alizo but also the other way around, Vázquez>Vásquez). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 06:16:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sincero, me gusta 😂😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 21:02:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A qué parte de Madrid quieres mandar a vivir al pobre OP con 50k? Si te cuesta un piso como el que quiere él en Galicia de 60 para arriba. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 12:54:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Pillo" is not an old word. At all. That's why I'm confused, I've heard a lot of nonsense obever the years about northern stereotypes but sounding old timey is a first. You family might have a flare for the dramatic but unless you talk like a _Ministerio del Tiempo_ character it's not that deep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 09:45:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Northern Spaniard here, can I just ask...? Older form...? Your family talked in _cantigas_? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 02:21:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would go with "problemas de audición" or "pérdida de audición" to describe yourself. They're pretty neutral terms in both formality and not being considered derogatory to any, they're just plain and descriptive. You can also just say "llevo audífonos" (I wear hearing aids) and be done with it.  None of the terms in your list are really offensive, "duro de oído" would be the only one I would say be careful with context, since it's very informal and not to be used to describe strangers or in like, workplace environment. "Hipoacúsico" is way too technical, save that one for your doctor. I would also rule out "dificultades para escuchar" and "no escucho bien" to convey your particular condition to others,  because these are a bit circumstancial, i.e. they may understand it as a hearing person using them to describe a loud situation or technical difficulties (like bad service over the phone). "Un poco sordo" is also fine, especially if you're just referring to yourself in casual conversation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 00:47:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fellow ASD, how do you feel about puréed stuff? I love the taste of lentils but they make me gag in their original form, but you can pry (puréed)  Spanish lentil stew from my cold, dead hands.  Same thing goes for most of the veggies I consume. Any cheap inmersion blender will do, if you don't want to make an expensive commitment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 00:32:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think this is a matter of LatAm Spanish vs Castilian Spanish. Castilian very rarely uses "Está bueno" in the context of something being okay when it comes to giving abstract opinions, we would use "bien". You could emphasize the average-ness by saying "Está bien, sin más" (It's okay, no more, no less). We only use "estar bueno" in two contexts: Discussing food (El pollo estaba bueno, la pizza estaba buenísima) and people in terms of physical attractive (Ese chico está muy bueno, esa actriz es buena y además está buena).

&#x200B;

The second part, I think you should look up the differences between "ser" and "estar" to get a better grasp, because you seem to be mixing up a couple things at a time. It doesn't have to do at all about something being comparatively more or less good, we have gradation within the adjectives for that (bueno, mejor, peor, buenísimo). If you're just stating the status, the adverb "bien" suffices. Ser and estar are quite difficult to put into words and there is an entire category destined to explain the nuances, but "ser" is used to express more permanent attributes ("Soy bueno" = "I am a good person"), and "estar" points towards things that are more subjective or impermanent ("Estoy bien"="I am \[doing\] okay") . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 20:19:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nada, típica cuestión regional. Aquí nos solemos referir a todo el conjunto como "estudios superiores", y se reserva universidad a las instituciones grandes que ofrecen un abanico grande de carreras y títulos de todas las disciplinas, y facultad a cada departamento (que puede encargarse de uno o más títulos, dependiendo de lo grande que sea la universidad). Dependiendo de la duración que tenga esta formación que quieres hacer, se puede asemejar más a una FP (Formación Profesional, 1-2 años) o a un Grado universitario (4-5 años). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 19:53:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vale, esto no es una universidad, es una escuela especializada. Te recomiendo que en este caso, busques a referentes del sector o gente que esté trabajando en donde te gustaría llegar, y que mires dónde se han formado ellos. Este tipo de estudios no regulados tiran mucho de fachada y como te toque uno malo lo único con lo que sales es con un agujero en el bolsillo. No vayas a por las apariencias, busca experiencias y testimonios. Tu objetivo es educarte, no pagarle el coche nuevo al empresaurio de turno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 19:41:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Qué universidad es? Porque "sedes en Madrid y Barcelona" suena a privada, y en general salvo casos muy MUY concretos, a las privadas se va para comprar influencias, no para aprender. Si lo que quieres es formarte vas a tirar el dinero, y si apuntas a estudiar y trabajar a la vez casi que te puedes ir olvidando. Supongo que te puedes mudar a Guadalajara si no te importa pagar en tiempo cada vez que tengas que acercarte a Madrid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 19:36:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ¿Qué banco es? A lo mejor puedes pedir que en vez de mandarla a casa, te la manden a la oficina. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 18:43:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They don't exactly convey the same. Puerto Rico is being more decisive  "se llama" making it feel like it's the only answer. Argentina's "se le llama", the use of 3rd person pronoun "le" is implying a concise "they" group, meaning that "they", presumably in Argentina, call it "mesada" but it can be different if you asked someone else outside their "they".

Third answer: En España le llamamos encimera.

"We, the Spanish, call it encimera". In this case, the "le" is referring to the subject (the kitchen counter) but I'm talking about an "us", the Spanish, through the verb in the sentence to represent myself among others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 18:25:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would say you're right but only if you're talking about the bigger cities (Madrid, Barcelona). Smaller towns are more affordable and Latino families are more integrated throughout all neighborhoods. Other times, they have been a positive factor to reintroduce services and activities in parts of the city that were previously considered as sketchy or downright dangerous and may still carry some of that association, but it no longer applies for the most part. I'm thinking of Sagrada Familia in Coruña to be precise. That place was a shitshow throughout the 80s and 90s and locals liked to look the other way. Now it's just a low income but cheap rent kind of place, not too shabby but you will still be advised not to move there, only the newcomers (mostly immigrants) do.

Every couple years or so, the fear of organized gangs (think Latin Kings) will usually pop up, and that can  also help the xenophobic narrative, but it's been relatively quiet these past few years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 04:22:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 29 años, diría que tuvo su pico de popularidad en torno a 2007 y en mi colegio/instituto se lo leyó bastante gente, pero no tuvo mucha duración. Para cuando terminamos el bachiller nadie hablaba del tema ya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 19:41:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To pile up on those who already commented, having a light source is a yes/no type of thing, while "lowest stat" is just a relative term. You can't possibly qualify for the event if you can't answer yes to the first part, regardless of whatever stats you're trying to compare. If wego meta, 9 times out of 10 that type of event asks you to drop said light source and place Fire around you if you fail your roll, so how can it possibly affect your investigator if you don't have  a light source to begin with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 17:02:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo suelo contestar "Sí?", sólo saludo o digo hola si es videoportero y puedo ver quién es. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 02:02:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> HARD disagree. Best build quality is late 80s to mid 2000s by far. 2007-2015 buildings had constructions companies still reeling and materials and finishings took a hard dive. A friend of mine has wind coming from the electrical sockets of her 2007 condo because there's no proper insulation from the outside and her street is a massive tunnel. You may get lucky with new construction but I'd still be wary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 00:27:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would say two of the biggest defects in the official app are the inability to save and resume scenarios and the dead investigator button.

-Save feature: Right now, saving your progress isn't very useful if you have to pack the game back into the box. Unless you manually keep track of each player's inventory , saving just the board is nearly useless. I also dislike how once you load a saved game you can't go back to that savepoint or start a different scenario. What if I'm playing with two groups of people, or trying to beat a scenario in a solo run while still hosting game night with friends? I think these situations are not too rare for many players.

-Dead investigator: I honestly don't know why this button even exists. As of now, you might as well just shut the app down instead of going through the trouble to find it in the menu. I feel like it shouldn't be that hard to just click it as soon as the investigator dies but make it so that it actually triggers the end scene at the right time instead of inmediately upon selecting it.

This might be a bit more out of reach, but the music can get a little repetitive after a while. I'm sure there are more royalty free tracks that could be added into the mix, or maybe even someone is willing to share their own creations as bgm. Graham Plowman and Cryo Chamber on youtube come to mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 15:45:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just got my copy of Horrific Journeys in the mail, and the back of the box clearly lists 50 clue tokens among the rest of the contents. I don't know why they felt the need but same as the fire tokens with all the other boxes, I've never felt the need for extras. The yellow/blue ones tho, I've had scenarios where they were running quite low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How many character tokens in total? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 13:45:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So, I have *some* tendencies towards organisation. I want my things neat and games are not an exception. I've been looking at how people organise their NPC tokens and I found some people recommending coin books, which I think is brilliant. However, I wouldn't like buying one that's too small and end up having to replace it further down the road, or on the contrary, overestimating the number of tokens and have a book that's only halfway full.

So my question is, does anyone know how many character tokens are there in total? Counting all expansions, and both named and unnamed ones. I don't have all the expansions yet but I plan to in the future and I would really appreciate if we could come up with a definitive list. I'll make sure to update this post with a breakdown once I get home to my current collection.

EDIT: So I finally got home to my collection and here is the partial breakdown:

BASE GAME: 22 tokens (9 generic/unnamed, 13 named characters)

SUPPRESSED MEMORIES: 4 named character tokens

RECURRING NIGHTMARES: No tokens.

BEYOND THE THRESHOLD: 7 tokens*

SANCTUM OF TWILIGHT: 10 named character tokens.

STREETS OF ARKHAM: 12 tokens (2 generic/unnamed, 10 named characters)

HORRIFIC JOURNEYS: 6 tokens*

PATH OF THE SERPENT:  5 tokens*

*These expansions I could not check for myself yet since I don't own them, but r/tavo2809 provided me with a breakdown of components. If anyone can provide more details regarding these expansions (named/unnamed characters) it would be of great help.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 19:05:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never eaten it, but looking at the recipes it doesn't seem like it *should* be gritty, not when it's well done at least. I've found a lot of sites commenting on how to get rid of the grits while working with polenta (which is also the name of the main ingredient, corn meal). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 23:14:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a bit of a wild guess, but could it be a version of Polenta? It is Italian in origin, but there's a lot of Italy in Argentina. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 06:02:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not offended. I'm just saying they are two separate recipes. I am Spanish, I am aware of Spanish recipes, and I'm just trying to point that out. As I said I meant no disrespect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 05:34:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No disrespect but gazpacho and salmorejo are two separate dishes, same ingredients yes but different technique, it's a completely different consistency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 04:06:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't lose hope! I've been looking into these two expansions quite intensely lately since I just bought a copy of the base game for myself, and more and more Spanish retailers are popping up with preorders for Suppressed Memories specifically (along with Path of the Serpent which is not surprising). Recurring Nightmares is nowhere to be seen sadly, but I managed to buy a 1E box from a friend so I'm covered at least. My optimistic mind wants to think that maybe not all of the moulds broke, or maybe they just found the incentive to get new ones, they did for other minis like the newer runs of the big ones after all.

(Also, first interaction on Reddit ever, just joined for this sub specifically). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
