<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject28</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 23:53:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My head feels clearer,  my memory isn't so foggy, and my sleeps are better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 07:14:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably going to sit at the bar with my friend who is also doing sober october and have a pitcher of huckleberry wheat ale, and smoke a dooby on his deck before we go. That, or a river beer on the kayaks doing a whitewater lap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 18:16:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vivid dreams likely to the absence of Marijuana. Mentally sharper and able to focus, i forget less shit and sleep better. Was a one or two beer a day drinker and have about 7 on a Friday night. Might not go back to the consumption I was at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 16:27:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks dude! On the bright side, I am probably in the best position to finally quit smoking cigarettes since I won't have the drunk reasoning to fight. I'm interested to see how it will be at gatherings with friends when I dont drink. Their reactions were pretty lukewarm, except one that said he did last years sober october and felt great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 16:22:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've only been asked to come for beer 4 times and had a joint put in my face twice so I guess pretty good.

Edit: been asked not even asked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 06:01:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We have to drink out of whoever rescued your boats shoe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-22 01:53:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uhh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 05:19:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just use the sidewalk. It's free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 01:13:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having the sex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-06 23:02:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You mean cigarette butts and empty beer cans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 14:41:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He is a master of reading water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 14:11:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess utopia only works when capitalism funds it from the other side of the wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 02:51:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm glad that's all you really pulled from that even though it was the smallest bit of the whole comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 21:20:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was scary at first, but now its hilarious. They are running out of food after the homeless people took it all, and they replaced police with armed individuals who don't really answer to anyone, using guns they think we should ban, and to top it off, they are building walls and demanding papers. Stupid fucking commies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 03:55:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a room in arrow heights for rent. 850 a month utilities included. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Good Vibes </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-26 05:41:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-17 20:16:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Might cost 4k a month if you're a coke addict or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 07:02:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Octopus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-01 20:58:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well fuck me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-01 18:27:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mike from canmore buying up all our guns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-01 18:22:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Let's go block a railway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-01 18:18:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who pays you to say this stupid shit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 22:31:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope they dont discover the t97 exists. Maybe itll fly under the radar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-20 19:46:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Report wrongthinkers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-07 22:58:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine is a couple that drives around. Mr and mrs canpar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-07 21:25:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My gen 1 has the flat top upper. I want that aluminum hand guard though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-07 01:25:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is the website google? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-07 01:17:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just arrived today, took it to the range. I've put about 30 shells through it and so far I like it actually. Feels decent as well. Kicks like a mule straight into your hand, as expected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-02 23:49:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My shotgun is somewhere between toronto and British Columbia on a canpar truck right now. Its racing the ups truck carrying the shells. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Intersting </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-02 18:49:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-02 18:47:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly. Also, not every landlord can afford to just not have rent coming in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-02 00:42:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trudeau is a pedophile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-01 19:44:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nobody here thinks it's a distraction except you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-01 19:39:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you ever bought from hemp and wellness it's the same owners. They are trying to keep customer base. Just text stop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 04:04:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will let you know when we decide. We have a shopping list made, but so far havent actually ordered anything yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 00:36:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah the length is just because I have shelves in a cold room converting to a grow room </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 23:56:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It wont give me a price as they dont currently deliver it here. This is what I've found:
 https://www.amazon.com/Fixture-Shaped-Integrated-Lumens-Warehouse/dp/B07YHPYQVN/ref=cm_cr_arp_d_product_top?ie=UTF8


Good or nah? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Startup Help </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 23:00:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me and a partner are nerding out working toward starting our microgreen indoor farm. Grow room already has 160 sq. Ft. Of shelf space. Was wondering if anyone could maybe point me in the best direction for materials? Lights, trays, soil. We have done our own research, and I am hoping you members in here have some helpful information for newbies on how to get going in the most cost effective way! Thank you in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 21:04:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am 26 and had mine done by one of the best surgeons in canada also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 20:36:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I figure the price reflects the fact that I'm getting simply a pistol grip short barrel pump and nothing fancy. I like the over/under rails it has though. Might just require more cleaning and lube than a higher end gun. Not expecting much, but for 250 I dont see myself having intense buyers remorse either. Its still a 12ga and that's fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 18:51:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Armsan RS-XS. Cheap so I figure I'll try it out. Reviews didnt seem too bad but I'm not expecting much from a 250 dollar shotgun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 02:58:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just ordered a shotgun lol. Did you happen to choose emt or interact? I did and it sent me a confirmation email but I haven't paid. That is quite confusing. I assume they will be contacting me tomorrow or sometime next week about payment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 02:43:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you fine sir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 20:40:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trade exchange? More info? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 20:25:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am not currently in the financial position to afford an ar15 right now, and in canada they are restricted. I dont think any transfers are going through right now either with all this shit.
I dont disagree with anything you have said. I have a neat rail mount on top now that has lowered the sight, and holds it steadier. I am off to the range today to zero it in before martial law takes effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 04:57:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Men have more back pain from carrying society. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 02:45:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I also dont like them. They are loose in the mag well and the gun doesn't always feed properly with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-20 23:21:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You sure about that? Mags are uncontrolled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-20 19:58:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Small magazines is the dumbest law second to the ar15 name ban. I use 10 round pistol mags instead anyways. They are smaller so you can carry more, and it takes 2 seconds to change a mag, especially when you dont care about dropping them. Mag capacity has no influence on damage inflicted. Crazy people are crazy, and that's all there is to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-20 19:53:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gun owners are terrible boat operators. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 13:41:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are too stupid to have this conversation with. You should get a job and we can talk in a few years. All of your comments on reddit are you looking like an ass and being a dick to people for no reason. I didn't even know you could go into the negatives with karma, yet here you are. In the nicest way possible, go fuck yourself, you uneducated sheep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 13:36:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This guy is an idiot and doesn't understand a goddamn thing. Please don't associate this retard with every other canadian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 13:21:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Canada is not a socialist country. It is very much capitalist and without capitalism, the social programs in place would never be able to exist and sustain themselves. Universal healthcare is only helpful to the people that cant afford their own health insurance. You need to stop drinking the communist koolaid. Also, I am canadian, you absolute fucking tool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 13:09:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you tell me more about how Canada is a socialist country? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 13:03:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is your mental handicap? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 13:01:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe she is in Cuba. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 04:52:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah it varies a bit but for both my knees i was walking before 4 weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 01:54:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well that right there is your problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 01:17:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you ever tried not being left handed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 01:09:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont know a ton about it other than my friend has a 10mm glock 17 and likes it. He got it as an open carry in the Bush for his job. Apparently its what a lot of people use in Alaska, it's big enough to take down bears and cheaper than .40 cal. That's about all I know sorry I can't be more help. Was kind of hoping youd have personal experience lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 22:51:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont like that your surgeon said you wont get back to that level. I would look for a different surgeon. Dont let that doctor touch your legs if he wont stand by his work. You wouldn't go to mechanic that says he can't make your engine knock stop but he will throw some heavier oil into it. My knee surgeon told me in 12 months I'll be skiing again at the level I did before and I wont think about my knees anymore. He is lumping you in with the people that DO give up and never return to sport. Hit the gym and get into strength training if you havent already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 22:40:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you think of 10mm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 22:39:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had heavy work done on both knees and I was walking a week later for one knee and 3 weeks for the other. Two acl recons and 4 different meniscus tears, 2 on each knee. It should not take 5 weeks to walk. By 6 weeks you should have almost full extension and working on a normal gait. At 8-10 weeks you should be on a bosu ball doing balance exercises and strengthening your quads and hamstrings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 15:35:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 9mm is cheaper/more readily available than .40. Also it's lighter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 06:40:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Second that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-15 22:17:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One took a while for me because they did more work on my meniscus. Acl repair is much simpler than meniscectomy or however its spelled </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-13 16:23:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude. Not true. When you have a dirty filter you get blow by because air starts going around the filter. So on top of your furnace working way harder, you are now blowing dirty, dusty air around the filter and  back into your home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-13 04:24:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shut up virgin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-12 17:42:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If only.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-12 17:17:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well yeah, but this one isnt loaded and buddy here had no reason to go off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-12 16:33:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It isnt loaded and I put it in thinking maybe that was why for some reason. Also, are you that negligent that youd even have a loaded magazine at home? Maybe youd make that fuck up, but I wouldn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-12 05:17:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah it was that... I felt real stupid when I realized why haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why wont my t97 close? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-12 02:20:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 07:39:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When are they going to throw this guy into a nursing home? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 03:44:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always wanted to take mine. The hard part for me was actually finding a course as they weren't very well advertised around me. Just a local guy that runs them out of a church. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 23:59:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have yet to take a newbie to the range and not want to get their PAL afterwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 06:19:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe you just didnt pay attention? Seems like everyone else here did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 01:22:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah but most people nowadays dont drive cars. So much so that companies are phasing them out. My small truck has an 80 liter tank. If I filled up 50 times in a year (I probably fill up about 90 times a year in reality), 4.4 cents added would cost me just under 160 dollars if I had 10 liters left every time I filled up. Factor that in with the rising cost of everything because shipping costs more, heating in storefronts cost more, and many canadians are taking a hit. Most pickups have over 120 liter tanks, just for peoples information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 00:14:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This guy unlocked tiger camo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 00:13:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bill? Is that you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 00:11:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I'm sure Bill Blair will get right on that once he gets rid of those pesky "military" rifles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 00:09:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How else is he going to have any fun guns? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 00:07:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They do have a standard for shooting skills, but yeah, being physically fit is something they cant really teach you after you're already a cadet. My friend used to work at a gun shop and said the RCMP would come in there to get their guns cleaned, and most of them didnt know anything about them other than how to shoot. And a lot of people that go to the range for fun are better shooters than cops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 00:04:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay I did those steps now when do they come teach me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 00:02:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should tell the gang bangers in my hometown that what they are doing is against the law and to stop it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 23:56:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Laser guided butt-fuckin mushroom rounds boi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 23:54:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are they going to track down our unregistered long guns or just expect us to bring them in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 23:52:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can get behind that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 23:50:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey those guns are black and dangerous, I'm telling on you! JUUSSTINNN! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 04:39:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did he put the leash on the dog? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-06 05:56:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You could move to a more affordable place. Find a job online and get there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-06 00:25:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If we were refining at the capacity we need to, we wouldn't be sending it to the states for refinement, would we? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-06 00:21:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I run a crane truck for the railway. I got lucky because I live in a town that not a lot of railroaders like living in because of all the snow, so I moved up fast. Then I was smart with my money and made some good investments in real estate.

Edit: elaborate on being smart: didnt do the typical "hookers and blow" splurges with my funds, bought things that appreciate in value instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-06 00:07:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well its normally about 5am and I check my stocks before I make myself some breakfast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 23:26:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the thing. Sometimes smart people dont choose "smart" jobs either. For me, I had good grades in high school but I hated school. I did not get grades through effort, just a good memory. I'm not a millionaire by any means, but I figured out a way to be well off without spending half a decade in college. Thing is, most people could do my job, but not many want to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 23:18:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel bad for the maritimes too. They could be way better off too if it weren't for Quebec. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 23:16:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Weird. I managed to invest money, sell those investments for a profit, buy a house, and now I make money off the house, as well as manage other people's properties, all while working a well paying job that I like. Never went to college either. I sure got scammed good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 22:15:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not about to explain everything I've ever learned in this thread dude. I actually advised against a savings account so clearly you're lacking some comprehension skills. Move along. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 21:38:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not trying to turn anything on you. I'm just proving the point I made earlier. People like him DO hire people below. And those people had to start somewhere too. You cant just solve poverty by giving poor people money. Give them the opportunity to work as hard as they want to and then they have a chance to move up. I certainly didnt come from the bottom and just suddenly end up where I am. I spent a lot of time working hard with not much to show for it. It takes time and a lot of hard work. I'm not taking a stab at anyone elses work ethic here, I just dont think handouts are the way. Saying a rich person should give his money to someone else because you think he doesn't need it is immoral, and really, it's theft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 21:27:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why dont you hire some people below you? Start your own business and hire the people who need a lift if you're doing so well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 21:13:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not at the capacity we need to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 21:09:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> China, Japan, and India are 3 of the world's top 10 in refining oil. We wound be cutting out the middle man, since the americans are balls to the wall on tankers and pipelines. We would actually get our piece of the pie. It's cheaper for asia as well to buy our oil and refine it over there. America is the only loser, and that is why there is so much american interest and pressure against our pipelines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 20:57:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well you certainly have the attitude of someone who hates on successful investors, like there is something morally wrong with securing a prosperous future for generations after you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 20:54:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They wouldn't. We could actually charge market prices. Right now the USA buys it from us for cheap and then pipes it wherever they want, and resells it a global market value. They have a lot to lose by us actually building our own pipeline. They are doing to us the same as they are doing in the middle east. Wherever oil is being moved, america wants control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 20:33:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe you should invest then. Dont work for your money, make your money work for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 20:21:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes I agree with you there. The thing is that with a pipeline we wouldn't need to sell to america at a fraction of the cost and our cost to transport would go way down, highways would be safer as well as railways. And i think the money for greener energy research is going to need to come from oil and gas, but it cant happen with a boot stomping their face into the dirt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 20:09:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah you guys enjoy your saudi oil. Many rich men get to beat on their multiple wives in mansions because of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 19:59:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No but nobody in this sub seems to know how an economy works. That or they just want shit given to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 19:33:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know you're going to downvote me and disagree with me, but most of those are not causing job loss in Saskatchewan, and the ones that did were costing us tax money to stay afloat anyways. If something is sucking money out and never giving a return, it makes no sense to shoot the money cannon at it just so some people can keep their jobs. Those people will be able to find other jobs. The alternative is to keep it going until they inevitably have to axe it anyways and then they get no money from the sale. Government shouldn't really be running industries like that anyways, and Saskatchewans small population is the only reason it has worked as long as it has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 19:12:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By years ago, I mean they talked about that when I was in 5th grade and I'm 26 now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 19:12:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They talked about that years ago when I was in grade school and it's been voted no every time. Its not gonna happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 19:11:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You think it sits there? People with that much money dont do savings accounts. That money is always moving, investing and generating more business. People with money like that keep things moving. People spending money on cheap shit from china does not do as much as you think it does for us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 19:07:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or if they could build a pipeline and sell oil at market price they still wouldn't need to tax their citizens. Alberta did great for years with no PST until they couldn't compete because they had no way to get it to the coast. What canada SHOULD do is refine it's own oil and sell to its citizens at a discounted rate, and ship all the surplus out to Asia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 19:03:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I grew up in Saskatchewan and have lived in bc for 8 years. Saskatchewan government does most things better than BC. Look at sgi, crown Corp and runs a profit every year with the cheapest rates in canada. When I moved to bc the cost of truck insurance tripled. Also, GO RIDERS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 08:00:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe by then people will grow up and get jobs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 01:24:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I went on a few dates with a girl last summer, she wasn't into guns and we kind of just quit seeing each other for various non compatibility reasons. Couple weeks ago she asks me to take her to the range. I told her "I thought you didnt like guns?"
She said she changed her mind and wants to learn about them. You really never know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-04 23:02:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont keep track and my life is better that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 22:37:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just find a job down there that will get you there. I personally have not succeeded but it would be amazing to make the move one day. Dont even need range time we can shoot in the desert! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 19:37:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cant. I asked the guy if he had the wood stock and he said he couldn't find it. The iron sights are still there as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 19:31:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get that you're trying to beat down the rifle, but I can shoot it pretty accurately right now, and I dont have an endless supply of money to change it every time someone on the internet tells me to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 19:16:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can get a chin weld on the Sks, and its sighted in. As for the riser on the other one, I'm not really sure. I just got the sight and havent played around much with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 19:14:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Magnet flashlight will be like 8 bucks and last forever. My house has a built in dehumidifier, but if you dont have that, a room dehumidifier or for 70 bucks you can  buy a uline container dri pack. Or move to Arizona? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 17:50:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't say anything racist or derogatory but go ahead and try calling the thought police instead of accepting facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 16:37:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People like to forget that black people aren't twice as likely to be shot by cops because they are black, it's because black people make up about 12% of the population, and commit almost 40% of all violent crimes, and are involved in 23% of police shootings. I'm not sure how your math is, but that debunks your whole "cops are racist" charade. Also, statistically, every ethnic group of cop is more likely to shoot their own race. You guys need to seriously research more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 16:09:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Finally, a ban that makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 15:29:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You could mount one to a PVC pipe. Let's ban all tubular sticks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 15:28:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good one. You guys are pathetic really. When you're in trouble the cops are the first people you're going to call. I'll bet you my pension this guy never gets killed by a cop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 09:39:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You still cant have as much weed as you want in canada, and if it isnt in a government duty paid container and a government strain, it's still illegal. You can still be charged for trafficking if you have vaccum sealed bags of weed in your vehicle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 09:09:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But why would you give a cop backtalk? They are just trying to do their job, and they dont pull people over for no reason. Giving people fines and arresting them is a lot if paperwork for them. I dont think you hate them, but you said you didn't want to play fast and loose with your life, so clearly you are afraid of them. Why? Has a cop ever been violent toward you? I would expect that the people I care about have enough common sense to not be an idiot if they are in a situation talking to an officer. Trust me when I say this man, arresting you for no reason just because they dont like blacks or gays, isnt worth the paperwork or the suspension. Cops dont want to kill anyone man, but they deal with dangerous people every day, and that isnt your fault or theirs, so just give them a break and dont be stupid and give them lip service if they are talking to you. Better yet, dont even give them a reason to have to approach you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 08:18:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry, just no reason for irrational fears. Cops get on the news for using necessary force against people, and you think there are cops killing people for being gay and black, and no media coverage? Absolutely no reason for this person to believe their life is in danger for that reason. If you do get killed by a cop (you wont), it won't be for those reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 08:08:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, that doesn't happen. If there was a cop out there targeting people for being black and gay, it would be everywhere. Sorry dude but the media has you too afraid. Cops care more about their jobs than the fact that you're gay or black. And whoever downvoted me for what I said, go fuck yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 07:52:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's already illegal. It actually carries a lifetime prison  sentence. If you do anything to railways that could endanger someone, life in jail, criminal offence. Too bad they wont enforce it. Sorrynotsorry. I dont want my co workers dying because some fuckhead derailed their train when they lit the ties on fire  and cause the rail to break. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 07:42:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think cops are as racist or homophobic as you think they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 07:31:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interstellar, from his daughter's point of view, dealing with her life on earth, and her brother's downward spiral while working toward seeing her father again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 05:03:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You cant get covid-19 if you dont get tested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 04:21:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just tell them you're racist and hate gay people. They will never ask you to be on jury duty again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 03:54:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You monster! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 03:46:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every Heidi I've ever met has been a huge liability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 03:42:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends who's asking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 21:29:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wrong think detected </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 21:22:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good thing my rifles dont have grenade launchers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 18:16:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The bag is right there beside it all lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 16:33:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If he likes it and it works for him then it isnt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 16:26:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It still slides backward I just cant get it out the front. I didnt clean it this time  but I hope that doesn't screw me for next time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 16:23:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think they know thats what everyone is doing if there was a collapse or bug out situation. Other than that I'm like every other person with locks coming out the ass and all the rules you gotta follow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 05:06:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Opinions=/= fact </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 04:45:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah I didnt think of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 04:25:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why non latex? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 03:34:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the info! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 02:17:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely look into one! They are 70 dollars, but the reality is that bacteria in water is super dangerous and life straws would give a lot of people false sense of safety. If you're drinking from moving water and no dead animals upstream you're probably okay, but that's not always possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 02:12:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Life straws just filter particulates, not bacteria or viruses. I dont think you can see it in the photo but I have a steri-pen. Uses UV light to kill unwanted microbes in water, and a pre filter for particles. Runs on aa batteries and can purify 8000 litres of water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 01:15:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dried food and hoppes in the bin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 01:03:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm lucky to be in a fairly remote place, and chose a spot in a secluded area. In the years I've spent there, I've only seen one old man picking huckleberries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 01:01:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the advice though I appreciate it, and it is a good point regardless if whether i think that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 01:00:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldn't call them scary. An SKS is one of the most common types of firearms and there are millions out there. I would never go aggressively looting anyone, more of a get away from any towns and wait it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 00:56:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's exactly what I'm thinking. I have the bag with everything in it, about 60 pounds and a small ammo bin with about 300 rounds, and I'd hope to return if I needed the rest. A bit heavy but if things came down to it I would need to unload unneccessary items. The ammo bin and guns are all stored close together and the bag is there too. It's a matter of throwing it all in the truck, loading myself and the dog  and out. If I got lucky and had lots of time, I'd be packing more canned goods and tools. I think if shtf there would be no perfect kit but I'm trying to do my best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 00:44:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have an 80 liter bag for essentials, like food, first aid, change of clothes, etc. I am banking on having time to load my truck. I live in a rural mountain town, so my aim is to stick around home until I need to get out, then leave to a location in the woods where I would be meeting  a few friends in town also prepared, to set up camp. Between all of us we would have our bags, guns, about 10,000 rounds of assorted ammo, and survival gear. I have a rolling ammo bin that would stay at camp locked and chained, and I have 5 magazines for one gun and 3 for the other that would be loaded on me. The Sks is for hunting if needed, and for someone else to use if necessary. The type 97 is a personal carry and defense weapon that will have a sling. I I regularily hike with a bag this big. You're right, it's a hunker down and defend a camp sort of deal, and not everything is in the picture, just the things I can carry. I'd ditch one rifle if needed. The reason for the amount of tape is  because tape goes fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 00:37:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bug out/kidnapping bag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New to the sub. Any tips? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 00:26:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-01 19:27:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my experience, it seems like once you take a girl shooting and she wont leave you alone after. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-01 03:17:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love shooting it, and my buddy with his ar15 said he would buy one over another ar since they are non restricted. I have a whole cleaning kit but it's good to know about that one so thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-01 02:50:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just had to get a whole new water heater because they dont make a 13 dollar part that takes 10 minutes to change anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-01 02:49:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also, cleaning kit inside the handle? I did not know it had this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-01 02:48:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay I'll do that next time. First time cleaning it and my Sks is much simpler to work with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Norinco T97 Gas Piston stuck? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-29 23:41:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have been able to get the adjustment knob off, but the piston and spring dont just fall out like every video I've watched. Anyone have this issue before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-29 12:18:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you ever just feel like people say things on the internet because they know that if they said it to someone in person they would get punched in the mouth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-29 11:36:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha what up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-29 04:30:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe you should demand a higher wage from your employer, or negotiate a new contract under the threat that you leave. If your employer sees your value and you come to an agreement, it will work. They will also see you are not going to be overly agreeable and that you can leave for greener pastures. Flex your muscles, dont get big brother to come fight for you. You wont learn a damn thing that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-29 02:59:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cant even see it. What is a re re? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-29 02:06:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Poverty is defined as not having enough money to afford food and shelter. The basics needed for a no frills life. The minimum. See, everything has a value. Everything you want or need, someone else gave up hours of their life to provide it to you. So you dont want to work as much, does that mean that someone else's time is worth less, or that they should provide for you? Money is a symbol of your time, efforts, products  and labour. Your want to have more for less is a bit of a selfish objective. People in the western world in poverty still have more than the people making your shoes in some far off land.
     The people that are considered 'haves' spend a lot more time working towards affording their luxuries. They do it voluntarily. I work 40 hours a week, four ten-hour-long days a week. Usually I work an extra day or plug more hours, up to 60 hours a week. I have every right in my job to leave after 10 hours and not come back until Monday. I choose to work more to afford the hobbies and things I like to enjoy in my spare time. My toys had to come from somebody else's labour, and someone else's investment, and someone elses thoughts and ideas.
      Nothing in the world is free my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-29 01:46:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you look at the data, Canada is doing okay. Yes, our economy is taking some hits and it would be nice to move forward soon, but we have it pretty good if you actually look around. Overall, we live in one of the most peaceful periods of human existence. Poverty in canada is under 10 percent of the population. Over NINETY PERCENT of our population is not living in poverty. If that doesn't give you a sense of optimism, then you are pessimistic by choice or nature, and nothing will ever be good enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-29 01:39:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My friend was telling me there is a vortex scope in the 3 or 4 hundred dollar range that he put on his rifle and he loves it. He didnt tell me what model as I'm sure he didn't think it would mean much to me. This was before I had any guns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-29 01:31:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I put a vortex crossfire red dot on the bullpup recently and I really like it. 200 dollars and it was easy to sight in. You dont need to actually line your eye up. If you can see the dot, that's where the shots going to go. Plus, vortex has lifetime unconditional warranty so even if I drop it and smash the glass I can get a new one. I know there are better ones I'm sure, but I was impressed considering I bought one of the cheapest sights in the shop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-29 01:14:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not high end at all but would be nice to use it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-29 01:13:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ncstar 35mm red dot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-28 23:14:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmm I didn't know that. Interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-28 23:04:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ...you dont? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-28 22:57:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ATI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-28 21:57:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah. I'm at the point where when I let friends shoot it I say, "The sight looks cool, the dot colors change, but dont expect to hit what you're aiming for. Best to just fold the stock and hip fire it and have fun." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-28 21:30:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks man. I know it's not for everyone and I'm learning it's kind of a hate it or love it crowd. It does turn heads at the range. Would you happen to know how i can mount the optic better and not on the dust cover? Thing wont ever stay zero and I'm about ready to go back to irons sights because of it. It's a nice optic though so if I could make use of it I would like to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-28 21:18:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I totally get the purist ideology and I'll probably get a wood stock one as well, but this is how it came and it was cheap. I asked him for the wood stock, he said when he finds it I can come get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-28 20:29:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a norinco T97. Really fun to shoot and pretty accurate. I actually bought them both from the same guy. 1700 dollars canadian for both guns, 700 rounds 7.62 and 700 rounds .223/5.56 mix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My new SKS. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-28 20:26:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 20:26:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sometimes you can hit Clay with them. Sometimes they jam. But they are fun EVERY TIME. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-25 22:07:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is so far over my head I need a telescope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-25 20:38:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been falling asleep at 830pm since I got on xeralto. Not complaining though. The night sweats from my PE and the coughing and pain made it so I was barely getting any sleep before that. It's nice to actually get some rest. Nothing wrong with a nap now and then. He should listen to his body. It is working hard to heal and process the medication at the same time. It will adjust but it's all still new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-25 04:56:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're still on crutches after 5 weeks?? Did you do any pre op training? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-25 03:35:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also, what the fuck is on your feet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-25 03:34:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My friend has the 15 and loves it. He did say that it will if you use cheap ammo or dont load it properly. His likes the cci high velocity rounds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-24 11:01:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was jumping 3 weeks after surgery, but then the scar tissue started giving me issues in my hamstring and I am currently icing my thigh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-24 10:59:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had both knees done with hamstring grafts. I was able to run 2.5 months post op. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-24 10:58:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm shocked you aren't allowed to do what you wish with your investment. Regulating markets like that is what hurts people in the long run. People that do this shit deserve to have a hard time finding a place to live. Respect people's property and your life will get easier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-24 10:56:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a joke you moron. Nobody is actually doing this. Lighten the fuck up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-24 01:05:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jesus. I'm glad I dont live there. Here in british columbia I can say no just because i dont like you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 23:32:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, but another applicant with better references and overall demeanor and responsibility will get place over some punks that show up dropping their trash on my lawn. My friends would get sent home for doing that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 22:20:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Last interview i saw the only gun those idiots could list was a mumble of ar15. They literally cant name any other gun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 22:05:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why would I feel guilty? I'm the one taking on the financial risk of owning a home and trusting them not to destroy it. They could cause thousands in damage and leave me with what, 500 dollars of a deposit? They dont need to pay to maintain the house or comply with any laws. Some days I wish I was a renter again, because it's frustrating watching tenants that dont give a fuck about my home slowly running it into the ground. Especially when I was never one of those tenants. It's in the lease that they have to shovel the driveway and they asked me to buy a snowblower. If anything I've had a swath of lazy and entitled tenants and they make me glad to take their money at the start of each month, because I know I'll need to put it back into the house as soon as they move out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 21:56:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kind of defeats the purpose of an application. You dont get a job just because you were the first to apply for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 18:46:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which was them breaking the law. You don't need to rent to them. Cite littering on the property and in the neighborhood as your reason. This isn't a hard concept at all. They dug their own grave in front of you, and you'd be crazy to think they haven't looked at half a dozen other rentals besides yours anyways. Let them be somebody else's problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 18:37:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But American tankers passing by going to and from Alaska is fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 18:33:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You may have me mixed up with the OP. Your advice was good I was just correcting the specific dosage levels. I still would stay closer and even under your recommendation of 3000mg, but it becomes legitimately dangerous above 4000mg. Just stay away from ibuprofen and naproxen as they can negatively effect the way your blood thinners work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 18:27:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I can't give you a sense of humor, so I guess I can't help you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 18:24:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely. It's the behavioral pattern. I have a tenant right now that displayed this behavior. I let her in anyways. There are boot prints in the carpet, garbage piled in the garage, even though there is weekly curbside pickup, dog piss/shit/vomit stains all over, scrapes on the walls. She is a pig and I should have taken the early signs. I guess it will be am expensive lesson for to be more careful who I rent to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 18:19:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can't you just choose someone else or am I missing something? I would straight up tell them to leave. That's littering and against the law. Bye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 07:56:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reddit uses you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 05:07:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The limit for daily use is actually 4000mg. I was originally under the impression it was half that, but my doctor corrected me. He said 4g and under is the daily ceiling for safe dosing. I still wouldn't be hitting that number daily. I try to tolerate pain as much as I can without painkillers. Regardless of safe dosage, they can have a cumulative effect on you over time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-22 03:41:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the joke went over your head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 23:40:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do agree that scheer was not appealing to anyone that wasn't already voting conservative to begin with, and even though I voted cpc, I still didn't think he was the greatest. I guess I shouldn't say he caused the loss, but Bernier also made conservatives look bad with some of his extreme views and things he said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 20:49:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This pipeline will help them though. Majority of the FN want it, it was voted on, that's how democracy works. It will bring a lot of money to the reserves. Biting the hand that feeds them. If they think they aren't part of Canada, perhaps they should stop receiving money from the feds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 20:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the problem is that now we have obvious discontent with our prime minister, and with the ppc trying to take advantage of that, all they did was split the conservative vote and leave us stuck with Justin Trudeau-Castro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 20:38:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You think preventing fellow citizens from getting to their own jobs so that they can put food on the table is going to make them stand with you? That's the problem. Nobody knows how to have a civilized debate or demonstration. How fucking dense do you have to be to protest a pipeline by blocking trains?

Edit: autocorrect was choosing other words for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 17:24:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got distracted by guns lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 16:45:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I havent but I will now. I'm pretty new and got a ton of ammo with my guns at purchase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 16:41:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If the government bans all the semi autos we are all going on a big boat trip one last time, and we are inevitably going to crash, because we are that irresponsible,  being owners of evil semi autos and all. This crash will inevitably result in us losing all our guns to the drink, thus no point in the red coats needing to come seize our guns. The great boating accident of 2020. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 16:35:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I bought a tapco SKS with an ATI extendable and foldable stock, with a red dot mounted on the dust cover. You learn pretty quick that an SKS is not an accurate gun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 16:31:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If its black and semi auto it is evil and must be seized. So basically they want all my guns and will leave me with my grandpa's Remington 870 and 270 Win. At least Justin is going to let me keep my family heirlooms... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 16:25:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont think that's true. I applied start of december and got my card in the mail start of feburary. I didn't have any boxes to check and I've been single for just over 2 years (GO ME!). Maybe you have an ex or someone that decided to be a chump and say something fucky? Best not to contact the ex about it but I'm just spitballing here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 16:17:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine took almost 3 months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 16:12:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will do! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 16:11:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just want to add, I think feeling depressed is normal. When the doctor told me I had a PE and infarction, I was overcome with sadness when he explained to me what that meant. I found out about a week ago and it took a few days to process it. I am on xeralto and it is a pretty easy medicine to take, as long as you remember to take it. Just take it easy and find other things to focus on. Talk to your friends and spend time with them. It's worse if you isolate yourself like I did at first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 16:06:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me a warm bath was what helped. Other than that maybe take some acetaminophen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 16:03:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All along was that song for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 16:02:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn. I kinda figured </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 08:39:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Listen man, you mind your own business. If I wanted to hit what I was aiming for I'd buy a Remington 700. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 08:34:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love my T97, but I use the 10 round pistol mags because it makes more noise with less effort. However, it is hard not to burn through a whole 20 box in 10 seconds sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 08:29:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just bought a couple guns and 1400 rounds in a Canadian Tire parking lot and the guy just looked at my pal and sold me them. We did get a couple weird looks from some old ladies but no other issues. We weren't waving them around and made the deal quick. He never recorded my pal or anything, and since it was my first private purchase I wasn't sure what he was required to do, other than he asked to see my pal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Palmetto State armory ship to canada? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 08:09:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sure there is an answer already somewhere but I'm wondering. Do they ship ammunition to Canada? Their prices are really good and if they do it would be nice. Any other suggestions? Specifically I buy bulk 7.62x39 and ,223/5.56 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 08:57:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Slumdog millionaire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 07:31:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am confident my roomate doesn't know where we keep the new rolls after said roomate has lived in the house for 4 months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 06:48:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really hope so. Reading stories of others here, It seems I am on the lucky side of things. Really put it into perspective and things could be worse. I feel for the ones here who had more severe cases than what mine appears to be. I didn't even know what a pulmonary embolism was when they told me I had it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 06:43:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The part the doctor isnt sure about is that I had ultrasounds on my legs and I didn't have DVT. whether they missed it and it went up to my lung before they did an ultrasound (if that's even possible) or it started in my back from being laid up for so long. I'm not familiar with what tests they do to determine the cause. They took a second set of blood tests upon discovery, but nothing came up in the tests a few days earlier, so I'm not sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 06:39:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. I plan on taking them until the doctor either says I dont need to, or if I'm on them for life, then I will look at other options. I know it isnt a death sentence, but it sure feels like my life is falling apart right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 06:35:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I took my dog for a walk yesterday and today and never felt any shortness of breath. Only limitation is just the pain because my lung is trying to heal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 04:58:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel the depression and the isolation, the fear. I was just diagnosed a few days ago. I've spent the first couple days locked away in my room. It feels like my life is over. Like I'll never get to enjoy the things I love again. I'm hoping my time on xeralto is temporary, as it was likely provoked from having 2 acl surgeries and pneumonia, but I feel alone. Talking about it makes me more depressed, like I dont want to think about that fact that this is what's happening. Walking my dog has helped. Luckily I havent felt any of the shortness of  breath, but my joints have been sore and my back is still in a bit of pain. Good luck, discovering this sub could be a very important thing for me, as I'm sure it is with a lot of people here. Nobody deserves this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New PE diagnosis </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 04:49:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey everyone. I found out a few days ago that I have a PE in my right lung. I had 2 knee surgeries in the last 3 months. I never had any pain in my leg it was just my lung. Started out as extreme back pain and night sweats, then coughing up blood. I had pneumonia and was stuck on the couch for over a week before my surgery, the  another week and a half after surgery. They are pretty sure its provoked, but they want to do more tests in the coming months. I am an avid skier, mountain biker, motorcycle rider and snowmobiler. They put me on xeralto. The way I see this is almost as a death sentence. Not physically dying, but I'm having trouble seeing how I am going to be able to live the lifestyle I want to live on these meds. Does anyone know more about if they think I will be on xeralto forever, or just 6 months. It was really hard to take the news, especially the infarction of a small portion of my lung. Looking for knowledge and advice from people who have gone through it. I dont want to be on this for life, but if it's what will keep me alive it seems I have no choice. Please help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-27 23:08:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is your job as the consumer to choose a different company if you dont like their practices. But that would be too much of an expectation for a sleeping public. Just rely on the government to solve all your problems. See where that gets you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-21 09:03:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was 24 and hooked up with a 56 year old milf who was my old landlord. Big fake tits and all. Was worth it. Almost was late to work next day, which would have cost me my job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-20 20:15:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude a semi auto ban is an awful idea. That is most modern guns. You dont even know enough about guns to know what you're banning. How can you support legislation when you know nothing about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-20 20:06:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont know why I got so many downvotes when this is exactly what I've been saying... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-19 19:31:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They would have to pay the insurance deductible and be without a vehicle while it is getting fixed. Their premiums go up as well. So yeah, they kind of are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-18 22:39:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because  the person you dont like will not be on the hook and you just ruined someone else's day, while not taking responsibility for your actions. Pretty shitty. I hope you were joking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-18 22:35:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This. As soon as people understand what free market means, they see how good it really is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-17 18:55:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wonder what all these deleted comments said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 10:28:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just like my dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 07:24:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hallucinogenics by matt maeson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 07:21:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is actually not 'we' as in canadians. Most of bc struggling has to do with bad governing, money sinkhole Gov corps, and Chinese and other foreigners buying up real estate as investments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 02:49:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who is gonna pay for that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-04 19:42:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Crazy. This is the gap between my generation and these young kids that are nerfing society. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-04 04:54:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This diagram is kind of not good in the slightest. Inb4 ok boomer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-30 02:02:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your best bet is to show the crook where you keep your expensive shit and hope said horse cops get there in under an hour.

He isnt kidding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 14:36:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Welcome to the world of rational thinkers. A lot of things dont make sense anymore. The left has gone mad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 03:16:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This subreddit is less of right cringe and more or less just people that hate trump. Aka whiny bitches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 02:49:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not in court, but i got out of a ticket by telling  a cop that it wasn't possible for him to ha e caught me going 70 in a 50 zone, because my car couldn't go that fast. He looked at my car, looked back at me, and said "alright, have a good day, no highway driving in this car." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 02:00:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There were roads and schools before there were taxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 05:55:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So just right of centre is where the most people in agreement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 00:25:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some places you need one. Living in rural bc and the lifestyle i have, you need a truck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 22:57:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You know you can buy a plane for 60k-120k and a lot of people do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 18:18:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ben Shapiro has been covering this on his show and doing a pretty good job. I would recommend it. As a Canadian following this, outstanding. It is just amazing watching this 4 year democrat impeachment goose chase, being thwarted by silly facts and nothingburgers at every corner. Very entertaining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 17:48:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People just want government to do everything for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 07:01:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It isn't just one, and it is on top of all the other violence and opposition to any type of civil discussion. We are talking about the far left here. They think communism is a good thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 04:07:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True. I'm off work for knee surgery. Never had reddit before, and facebook is a shithole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 03:55:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a bit disappointing. I had hoped this would be better than facebook for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 03:20:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is their thing now. They throw milkshakes on people they don't like because some fat chick did it. These people have no interest in talking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> It All Makes Sense </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 03:07:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't realise that it was such a far left group in there. Confused as to why every time I made a comment remotely right leaning, I got downvoted and ridiculed. I don't think anyone understood how the economy works. I joined thinking it would be intelligent discussion. Wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 02:26:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are paying tax twice on something already paid for? If you own a rental property and decide to sell, you pay gains if its value increased while you owned it. On top of that, the person buying it pays taxes on it. Same goes for when you sell your business. I support getting rid of gains tax. It is just a way for government to double dip. Government is way too big and way too involved in every part of our lives already. Maybe the divide here is that you seem to see business owners as these mega rich people hoarding loads of extra cash, while everyone that works for them is poor and scraping by. Not everyone is out to get the little guy. Many business owners barely make ends meet. Keep up with all the taxes and it will just be big corporations left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 23:46:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Check out stepcat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 23:45:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And do you think people selling their homes should have to pay a capital gains tax even though they paid hundreds of thousands in interest on it already? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 23:28:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They wont be working there if the company gets taxed out of existence. The point of the free market is that if the general populace decides they dont pay enough, they dont need to work there. Nobody is forcing you to work there. A company that cant get employees will not be in business much longer. They will be forced to raise their wages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 23:12:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think their idea is to help small business have an easier time making ends meet. Mom and pops shops. Things are tight when you run a small business. There isnt as big of a profit margin as you think. After everything is paid and you put enough away for the company to survive, the owner gets the little bit that is left. Shit isnt easy. You give your life to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 22:51:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you honestly believe that most small business owners are making excess profits? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 21:31:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not what people wear. Gangsters and wannabe thugs are losers. Comprehension..comprehension. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 19:36:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think you realize how well known it was within the elite that this was happening. When was the last time you got a foot massage from a minor on a wealthy old mans jet? Where else does that even happen? Gotta have the blinders on real tight for this one. I am not saying Groening did anything illegal, but he definitely wasn't oblivious. I was always taught that if you hang with shit, you're gonna smell like shit. He lost some standing in my books. I don't need to convince you. You have already decided you don't care anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 19:23:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is hardly tarnish by association when he was on the same plane that took so many to that evil place. Jesus dude, he even got a massage from a sex slave. I am not saying he did anything sexual to children, but in regards to what Epstein did, those who say nothing are just as evil as the ones committing the act. Nobody sits in the smoke and doesn't know there is fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 17:46:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never said it was due to employees being lazy. Just entitled.
 So someone in a small town where the current minimum wage works fine should not be in business because some hipster in vancouver wants 15 an hour to make a coffee? People wonder why rural Canada is mostly conservative and this is it. People who want to live in the concrete jungle with no specialized skills think they are entitled to things. What did the barista at starbucks do to qualify for the same wage I made when I started working with 400kv power lines? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 17:08:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I also live in British Columbia. It hasn't changeg a thing for anyone outside the lower mainland, other than make things more expensive. And imports from China and other high pollution economies went way up after the carbon tax was introduced here. You can't say you cleaned up your part of the neighbourhood just because you threw all your dog's shit into your neighbours backyard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 16:53:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All a 15/hr minimum wage will do is force small business owners to close their doors and therefore less jobs. The only people that can afford it are the big corporations that most of the 15/hr croud hates. They will automate jobs anyways, so you lose there too. How about you, as a consumer, make a concious choice to support companies that pay a liveable wage, which is different from place to place. Don't rely on the government to fix all your problems. Jesus Christ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 16:44:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How much does a fucking doctor's note cost? Mine was like 70 bucks. That or your job dude. If you really are sick it should be an easy decision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 16:41:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Except that this wont work and they will know. You will be known as the guy that got fired after he put bleach on his dick for a drug test. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 16:38:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You say it like every poor person dresses like a gangster. No. Gangsters and wannabe thugs dress like gangsters, and those people are fucking losers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 16:33:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They helped Saskatchewan after the NDP destroyed their economy. Still prosperous to this day. The PPC has also said they will abolish the capital gains tax and instead tax 10% on business profits. That helps a lot of Canadians, from me as a land owner with tenants, my friend opening up his new tour company, and every other small business owner worried about not being able to pay employees because they demand this 15/hr BS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 16:27:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They actually rose, but thanks for coming out. Try researching next time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 16:23:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like you just have a bad relationship with your family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 16:15:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://youtu.be/GMI04C74Mck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 16:08:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Come on guys. He knew what was going on with Epstein. They all did. Don't give someone a pass just because you like their work. Scum hangs with scum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 08:43:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I still message my friend every now and then. He died of a brain tumour in january. It helps me even though I know he isn't reading them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 06:17:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I found my 10mm socket while digging in a jacket pocket for change. Lost it again before I made it home to put it back in its place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 06:16:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dr Phil... You cut off the wrong leg! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 06:09:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I went there just now and Scheer announced a tax credit for renovations making homes greener. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 02:55:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Except canada. We bounce back and forth and sometimes we just switch units mid conversation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 02:48:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got it now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 01:43:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What if i dont have a pin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 01:04:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Getting a dog and buying a house. Piling a bunch of responsibilities onto myself made me a better person and better able to handle tough and stressful situations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 00:57:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is the biggest error you catch in counterfeit notes? Asking for a friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 00:53:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My friend is a radiologist. Whenever I want to piss her off, I introduce her as "this is morgan, she looks at babies," because it is really a very small part of what she does. Turns out she actually deals with shoulder injuries mostly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 07:44:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please do not refer to some of mankind's finest as "these people," you uncultured swine! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 07:31:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think weed makes anyone think differentlg. It is the different sub cultures that it forced people into. People who were already rejected by society probably don't care if it is illegal. I vote conservative typically and I smoke. I also think whoever did this is a walking sack of garbage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 08:03:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No im a fucking asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 06:49:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just some very opinionated redditors that write you off as a terrible person just for not agreeing on one thing. Grow up, there are lots of good people in the world that arent going agree with you on absolutely everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 04:47:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just do it because i like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 23:35:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It also says if tenant fails to give 30 days notice, beginning on the first and ending on the last day of the month, deposit will be held in leiu of rent. He gave 7 days notice and hasnt paid rent for october, so if i go by the lease, he has already agreed to give it up. I just dont like having to tell him that. Cant be everyones friend i guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Someone might appreciate this. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 22:50:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 20:24:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In his lease it says he needs to give a month notice or no deposit. I've just never had to deal with yet. It is all new territory for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 19:32:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just rob a bank. If you get caught claim insanity and you will get put in a nice dry place for free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Landlord CAN-BC] 7 days notice </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 18:52:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tenant is giving 7 days notice on a lease that goes until April. He wants his deposit back, and asked to stay until October 3rd because he picked up extra shifts. He wont pay Octobers rent either. How do I tell him he needs to be out on the 31 and won't get his deposit back (provided he doesnt pay for October, which he wont) in the most civil way possible? As soon as I mentioned that he needed to give 1 months notice or no deposit he accused me of  being a shitty human. This is the first tenant that has made me deal with this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tenant is giving 7 days notice </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 18:07:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 16:26:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was never just one song every time. It was just learning a new song and playing it over again when you mess up.

Edit to add that I could never stand Smoke on the Water. Fuck that song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 15:58:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Funny thing is now they ask when I learned to play like that..

When I moved out and finally had the confidence to practice again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 15:31:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sliced my hand open on a key rack at work. My boss didn't believe me when I told him why there was blood gushing from my hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 15:26:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trying to spin poi i bagged myself the worst I have ever been bagged. I almost puked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 15:23:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe he lives in a shitty neighbourhood and this happens often enough to have random gun caches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 15:22:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 'MERICA MUTHAFUCKA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 15:18:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Claymore roomba. Come out of the shower and your living room is in your kitchen, no burglar to be seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 15:10:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to get yelled at for playing the same song on guitar over and over again when i was young, learning. I feel this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 15:04:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SK! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 15:00:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If i remember correctly he was trying to get sober when he made wzrd, and you can kind of tell he had a lot on his plate. That and he had no pressure to make it or break it, so he was getting experimental. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 08:42:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 08:39:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im 26 and I loved this movie when I was 5. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 08:32:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good ol' fucking LAN parties </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 08:30:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is amazing. How many years ago was that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 08:18:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kid Cudi tends to draw us out of the woodwork. I think those are the years a lot of us look back on with affection. Maybe not to go back, but very appreciative that we have those memories at all. The years where most of us really found out who we were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 08:14:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They are all the same haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 08:07:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did we grow up in the same small saskatchewan town? Haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 07:59:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hockey rink parking lots too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 07:59:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maaan. I'm just gonna say Kid Cudi always takes me back to grade 10 and 11, and will always hold a place deep down for me. MOTM 1 and 2 man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 07:39:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a beater truck with the very basic coverage, no collision. My 45k truck costs me almost 4k a year.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 07:13:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yooo TOOL. I don't know you but your taste in music is on point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 06:56:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Canadian prairies. Similar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 06:46:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to argue with people on facebook a lot. One day i realised it just made me look like an asshole. I enjoy a good debate but facebook is not a good medium. People just want to be right, not share ideas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 06:15:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hadn't heard this song in years, then this summer I was laying on the roof of a houseboat completely wacked on shrooms, and I could hear another houseboat playing the crookers remix of this song. Immediately shot back to high school and had the most amazing good feeling. Made me miss my old friends from back then too.

Edit for typos and punctuation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 05:56:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This song is 10th grade nights blazing in a friends car sound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 05:08:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They strap you down in the coroners wagon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 05:06:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Savage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 03:59:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least you didnt play the oboe. I didnt either, i play sax, just saying. Oboe is the outcast of the whole band. Squeaky bastards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 05:16:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My husky gets excited for the leash. Thinks we are going to a new fun place. Also loves truck rides. If you want to steal my dog just open the truck door. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 01:36:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Youre out of your element </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 01:24:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I needed this years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 01:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>        I was getting frustrated at work my first year at my job. I was busting my ass while some other employees were being lazy, and whenever i tried to help or give someone advice (ive worked in similat industries my whole life), people would just get angry, tell me to fuck off and the like.
       An old guy that i really looked up to saw i wasnt happy and i blew up. He listened to me vent and let out my frustrations. He didnt tell me what to do or that i was right.
        All he said was, "It will all come out in the wash."
       I had never been hit so hard by something so simple. It made me realize i was letting small issues that really shouldnt have affected me so much ruin my time at my job. Most of those problems didnt directly need to affect me, and in time, they would work themselves out one way or another. I have since applied this to other aspects of my life when i find myself fretting over what are essentially miniscule problems and annoyances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 01:40:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lets raid the Vatican's secret library </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 23:58:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Day 4. I needed this.

Edit: I was in fact on day one when you commented, and needed it then as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 22:20:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hours of daylight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 21:00:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gets cold at night dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 20:58:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anything that says bebe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 19:59:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The same vegas that is a world renowned tourist attraction? Those hotels? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 19:55:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He did the naturo run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 19:07:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is not the fuck you mentality. The people you are broad brushing are the same people that already donate the most money to charity and effectively pay most of the taxes. You cant lift up the poor by tearing down the rich. Not every successful person is an asshole dude.
The NDP has done a great job of making people think that they NEED the government to have a good life. Government generally sucks at anything and loses money all over the goddamn place. Everyone is better off with their money in their pockets. The average canadian already pays 40-50 percent of their income in taxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 18:44:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>         I grew up in saskatchewan, and I am old enough to remember what the NDP did to that province. Nobody had much money, jobs werent there, and infrastructure was mediocre. Ever since the Saskatchewan (conservative) party took over, people have been better off pretty much across the board.
        Conservatives are a bit misunderstood when it comes to their distaste for government assistance and handout programs. Of course they want to see everyone do better and prosper, but conservatives believe that people should hone the skills and knowledge to be self sufficient and not need the government. Of course there are people who will always need help, but majority of people would actually be able to do alright for themselves if they were given the tools to help themselves. It is kind of like the old give a man a fish vs teach a man to fish. Nobody should be content living a life where they are dependant upon the government and the garnishing of other people's wages. Where is the dignity in that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 12:27:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pubg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 08:21:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People actually showed up. One guy didnt know that deserts get cold at night lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 04:27:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What if they get there prepared to fight and the guards just say yeah guys come on in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 04:19:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its all a distraction people. The games will be there after the raid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
