<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject18</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just unsubbed from r/EyeBleach </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 00:08:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally just full of karma farming accounts that repost the same shit over and over again from the early 2010s. I subbed for peoples original pictures of their pets, but instead it's just the same pics and videos over and over again that get a ton of upvotes from the Facebook Mom types that are, for some reason, on Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 18:58:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Something I'd say is very important is to encourage that while things like diet, exercise, and meditation are important in EVERYONE's mental health, many mental health issues cannot be solved by these things alone, and that sometimes various forms of therapy and/or medications may be necessary in order for someone to live their best life. I would say just to make sure to make this obvious, to make sure you don't do any medication/psychiatry-shaming, or to indicate that eating right/exercising/etc can be a fix-all to everyone's problems! As that can unfortunately cause a lot of damage.

Its also important to point out that everyone has different needs, especially in regards to dietary habits and exercise. Discussing dietary habits can be potentially triggering towards people with eating disorders. Additionally, discussing exercise can be triggering to people with chronic illnesses, particularly chronic pain, as many are not able to exercise to the "recommended amount", or they will forcefully overexert themselves in trying to reach the "recommended amount". Definitely avoid any and all discussion of BMI or weight, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 18:46:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldn't say it is "crazy" to do anything and everything possible to stop a pedo wedding. I feel sorry for the goat, yes, but...I def don't blame him for doing everything he could to help that poor girl. I imagine most people would lose their cool in such a situation and act in desperation, especially when time was of the essence. I have psychosis mind you, and some other mental illnesses, but all that aside...as somebody that suffered from CSA and knows many others who have, I probably would have lost it too in the moment and would have done anything I could.

Not to diagnose or anything, but it sounds like he is suffering from ptsd from this. And ptsd CAN make you feel lots of things like guilt, regret, you will often repeat situations over and over again in your head, it can make you feel insane - essentially gaslighting yourself in many cases.

Crazy is generally an ableist word as it is, so I would never call anyone that, even if they were suffering from things I do, like psychosis or severe OCD, etc. I think he is simply a man who experienced something very difficult, who reacted in a way induced by panic and desperation, who is now suffering ptsd in the aftermath. I really wish him the best of luck - I honestly respect him for even trying to do ANYTHING in such a horrible situation like this.

Maybe encourage him to visit an animal therapy place near you, if there are any available, or even a petting zoo. It might help to bring him some closure to interact with animals in a calming, positive environment, where he can separate what happened in India from his general feelings towards animals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 18:08:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol good question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> So many doctors/nurses/other medical professionals suck and deserve to have their licenses removed. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 17:54:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am active in many mental and physical health communities, as I have a wide variety of issues, and not even counting my own medical neglect/abuse stories, I see so so so so many people who have dealt with horrible medical professionals - most of which were disbelieving of people and the issues they were experiencing. So many doctors seem more interested in weeding out "fakers" and "pill seekers" than actually helping people. I've read so many horror stories about how people suffered and went undiagnosed for years, doctors refusing to even TEST anything...and a lot of the times this has had dire consequences, even people having near death experiences (myself included).

I'm so tired of shitty medical professionals being lazy and not actually trying to help people, and us patients being harmed, sometimes irreparably, in the process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 17:47:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Moreso for physical illnesses, and I'm from a "bless your heart" region of the United States so of course they would never Blatantly say I was faking, but when I mentioned "Hey my chronic pain flairs up sometimes and I have to miss class, can I get a doctor's note for my school's disability program" Doc said "Just...try not to miss school. Have you tried vitamins" I left him soon after, leaving a scathing Google Review.
A couple years later I get diagnosed with both fibromyalgia AND lupus AND CFS/ME. Some doctors are seriously more interested in trying to weed out "fakers" than they are in actually helping people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 17:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I broke my pelvis, my doctor even refused to prescribe me ibyprofen, I was only given muscle relaxers and a topical cream, because in her opinion "my chronic pain gave me a higher chance of getting addicted to pain meds" jokes on her i got addicted to alcohol instead to cope 🙃 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I made a don't starve sona for my cat, Asymmetry, who is very much a shadow demon </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 17:34:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What was your "two hour delay" game? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 06:30:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My car's power steering line broke and I don't have the money to get it fixed </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 01:19:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really hate doing this, I work full time in a call center as well as driving Lyft on the side, but due to constant medical issues this month, I have not been able to work hardly at all, because I've practically been bed bound. On top of this, my power steering line/pipe broke, and because my car is old they are having to special order the part in. The total cost for the replacement/their labor/etc is $273.50, and right before this I had spent my last $20 on medication I currently need. I just am so desperate for help at this point, please please help... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 12:51:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not a woman (I'm nonbinary) but as an afab person, exactly this. I have endometriosis, and even all of us that have this horrible debilitating disease, have to jump through a million hoops to get a hysterectomy that for many of us, could drastically improve our way of life. Maybe even save our lives in many cases. My friend who is nearly 35, is asexual and aromantic, who has endometriosis and even had a nearly 10 lb cyst removed, still had to be sat down and forced to watch a 30 minute video about how "serious" getting a total hysterectomy was. Even with a disease that often causes infertility, on top of it causing extreme pain and us to develop autoimmune conditions just to name a couple symptoms, we are still treated like human incubators and that we can't make decisions for ourselves. Hell, I even had a gyno once want to take me off my birth control because I am on too high of dosage for my age (22 then, 23 currently) and that it could "effect me later on". Do I look like I give a shit? I haven't had a full period since 2017. And the period I had then caused me to violently throw up for 3 hours straight and caused me to black out every time I stood up, and after going to a doctor and getting checked, she said I had probably lost the equivalent to 1 pint of blood which is what the average person can donate, AND I also had a cluster of massive cysts on my ovary.

I never want to have kids, I probably never even COULD, yet I still can't get a hysterectomy because of my age. Ffs.

Edit - in regards to the 1 pint of blood, I also get massive nosebleeds during my period, which last for hours, in addition to normal blood, which is why the amount was so big </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 00:10:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Repost. Karma farmer 🙄 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 06:10:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think its important to understand truscum/transmedicalists generally only exist in online spaces. If confronted irl, they all turn into pussies real quick, cause irl trans spaces (and lgbtq+) places in general are real accepting, and if ur not accepting ur kicked he hell out. Kalvin Garrah types would get their ass whooped in actual irl lgbtq+ spaces. Most people that are truscum are just either trolls or ignorant teens who have been brainwashed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 17:01:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I do this with youtube videos. I play ones I've seen many times before at a low volume, often things from a series like Call Me Kevin's Sims series or RTGame's City Skylines series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 09:48:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's ok, it's likely not Covid, if Covid manifested in me it would def be in lung symptoms, as my lungs are weak, I've just started a new medicine that makes me more vulnerable to sicknesses, which is likely why I'm sick right now (I have been sick all month with a variety of things).l </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 02:08:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much for your words and happy birthday! I'm still feeling pretty awful but I allowed myself to order some pho for delivery, its my bday present to myself ;;; thank you for your words, sometimes I need words like this to take a step back and take a deep breath and all that ;;; as I said happy birthday to you, and again, thank you for the kind words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> It's my birthday and I'm sick and my psychosis is worse... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 00:07:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had such a good accomplishment a few days ago, being approved to work from home. But now, I suddenly have the stomach flu, and on my bday no less. I'm young still, 23, but I kinda feel like I'm in a midlife crisis just because I feel not accomplished enough, also I have been throwing up constantly for 48 hours, and also my psychosis is getting worse, I'm hearing constant church bells which is freaking me out a bit ngl. I have a fever which is probs why everything is worse but ooooh my gosh the pain in my back + the constant digestive issues + the psychosis, all of them getting worse on my bday of all days, is having me feel some sorta way. All I really need I think rn is happy bday messages and it gets better messages to be quite frank. Normally it gets better messages annoy me but today god i really need em. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Feelin ick on my birthday </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 00:06:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had such a good accomplishment a few days ago, being approved to work from home. But now, I suddenly have the stomach flu, and on my bday no less. I'm young still, 23, but I kinda feel like I'm in a midlife crisis just because I feel not accomplished enough, also I have been throwing up constantly for 48 hours, and also my psychosis is getting worse, I'm hearing constant church bells which is freaking me out a bit ngl. I have a fever which is probs why everything is worse but ooooh my gosh the pain in my back + the constant digestive issues + the psychosis, all of them getting worse on my bday of all days, is having me feel some sorta way. All I really need I think rn is happy bday messages and it gets better messages to be quite frank. Normally it gets better messages annoy me but today god i really need em. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm sick on my birthday :( </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 23:56:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I posted here yesterday? I can't remember, I have extremely bad memory due to lots of reasons BUT ANYWAY!  Its my birthday today and I have somehow caught the stomach flu, I was supposed to work today but have hardly been able to move from my bed for any reason but to throw up, which sucks :( 23 for me feels like such a weird bday, like I feel like I'm having a midlife crisis? Which is also weird because I technically have completed all the things someone is "supposed" to do by 23 (ie graduate college, have a full time job)...I just feel idk, super weird. Anyway...I'd mainly just appreciate birthday messages and stuff atm because ya boy is struggling a bit and I just need some soft genuine positivity! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 23:49:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My 23rd birthday is today and I'm spending it bed-ridden (I have the flu bug on top of all my regular chronic illnesses, of course). Definitely message me if you need support tomorrow, it's a hard thing to celebrate your bday alone tbh... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 19:42:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have super bad insomnia, yeah. Often it is also due to my being hungry/being deficient in a certain vitamin. I would definitely try to boost your iron as best you can with foods/vitamins, as that might help at least with the shakiness, but also don't eat too close to bedtime, as that can cause additional sleeping issues (higher heart rate, digestive system keeping you awake, etc). As for the pain, a mixture of heating pads and icy hot has helped me, + things like ibuprofen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 19:37:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It really depends on the person. I know for myself, when I was in the worst of my delusions, I'd get super defensive if people claimed they weren't real, but once I had an epiphany that they weren't real, I mostly just wanted people to listen and be there for me. I would say trust your instincts, you know him better than we could ever. But if you don't really know, simply listening to him talk through these things, being supportive by simply being there for him, that is what is most important regardless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 18:14:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My advice? Not get hung up on clinical definitions cause you don't need to have dysphoria to be trans. I personally do, a lot of trans folks do, but getting hung up on that is meh. Focus instead on what you think makes you feel gender EUPHORIA, what makes you feel happy and comfortable. Also visit r/egg_irl because that reddit is honestly super helpful in a super funny, chill way.

Edit: Also never watch the big trans youtubers, they generally suck and will probably cause you bad mental health/you to adopt transmed ideals, which is no bueno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 17:27:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Begin looking into inpatient facilities tbh, as this seems like a rather serious case - the not eating or drinking is especially concerning, as well as the drug usage, on top of everything else. Contact an inpatient facility, tell them what you told us, they will be able to help you take it from there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 13:08:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gender dysphoria effects everyone, even cis people. I unfortunately do not know a lot of resources for this situation, but I truly wish you the best of luck, we support you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 13:04:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Man I loved that movie, but also had this delusion for years, it's definitely one of those movies that encourages some pretty messed up thoughts in people like us with psychosis... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 02:27:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agree with what Jane Doe said! Paying attention to the temperature in your room, what you eat and when before bed, etc, is very important. Very important to see a doctor as well, just to make sure it's nothing else. In the meantime, try melatonin gummies. Simply tell your mom they are vitamins (which they technically are) and not pills, she hopefully will allow you to take them. #1 thing, do not resort to alcohol, just trust me on that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 13:43:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Def bring this up with your doctor! Oftentimes we're told suffering from pain is normal with periods, but it kinda sounds like the level you are dealing with is worse than normal and there could be things going on like PCOS or Endometriosis! Def bring it up just to be safe!

I went on 10mg of Norethindrone in 2017, haven't had a period since! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Feeling meh, trying to "conceal don't feel" lol (vent) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 07:39:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I turn 23 on Sunday, my parents are coming to visit tomorrow. I still have to clean the whole apt because I have spent the last 24 hours throwing up every 30 minutes. Why? Who knows, take your guess, ah the joys having multiple physical and mental health conditions that can spontaneously cause things like this. Anyway, just feeling some sort of way. I'm hoping I can sleep a few hours and I'll wake up miraculously ok so I can speed clean the apt and shower and seem like a fully adjusted totally ok adult in time for the parents to arrive. Gotta say, def don't feel like I have my life enough together to be turning 23. I had my life far more together at 17 before I had the bout of pneumonia that spurred on my Fibromyalgia, my asthma, my chronic sinusitis, etc.

Ya boi feels like I'm having a midlife crisis which is also startling cause does that mean imma die at 46? Big yikes

(Sorry for all the memey talk i talk about serious issues like this to cope ahah)

Anyway, takin a couple dramamine, a shot of jim bean honey whiskey (not a product placement), and a shot of sleepy time cold medicine, happy early birthday to me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 07:27:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude yeah my weight fluctuates so rapidly because on top of having such bad inflammation I have a handful of mental health issues that cause time loss and memory issues, I literally have to set alarms to eat at some points, on top of my inflammation causing my weight to occasionally plummet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 23:44:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I s2g sometimes I wish therapists actually had the same mental illnesses as us so they could actually understand, rather than being unempathetic douchebags. I'm sorry you had to go through that, your therapist is such a shitface that doesn't deserve her license. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 16:34:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy birthday! If you want/need to chat at any point, I have the day off! Also, I'm a fellow Libra, my birthday is actually on the 11th! We're kinda birthday buddies :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 15:05:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He also killed a squirrel and brought it in to home ec to cook. It was aight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 15:04:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He hacked into my state's standardized testing system and crashed it, semi on accident. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I finally got approved to work from home! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 01:15:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> After weeks of struggling, due to a new medication I'm on (Plaquenil) I finally got approved to work from home! Not only will this keep me safe while by white blood cell count is extremely low, but it will be so much easier on my fibromyalgia, not having to walk to work every morning. I just am so happy, can't wait to begin looking for a comfy desk chair :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I finally got approved to work from home! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 22:37:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> After weeks of struggling, due to a new medication I'm on for an unrelated issue (Lupus, I'm on Plaquenil) I finally got approved to work from home! Not only will this keep me safe while by white blood cell count is extremely low, but it will be so much easier on my Fibro, not having to walk to work every morning. I just am so happy, can't wait to begin looking for a comfy desk chair :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 15:05:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you need help locating resources in Cali, let me know, I have several connections there via libraries, which generally have a lot of local info. If you are heading to Sacramento, ESPECIALLY let me know as I have several friends there in addition to some other connections. We're here for you and love you ❤️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 12:16:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean as I said, I have multiple health issues. I have chronic sinusitis, due to my fibromyalgia, which is probably why my white blood cell count is normally high, because my body is constantly fighting it. Plaquenil, according to my Rheumatologist, can cause your white blood cell count to plummet towards the beginning, which is where I'm obviously at. My white blood cell count just plummeted a bit more than what is normal, I'm working with her on this.

Idk what you're trying to say here, anyway. What do you want me to say? I have abnormal blood results because my body has multiple issues going on. I have been diagnosed with endometriosis, fibromyalgia, lupus, and cfs/me, as well as a few things that are due to these issues. And believe me, these weren't fucking easy diagnoses to get, considering my location and considering I am assigned female at birth and we are always not believed. I have been officially diagnosed from medical professionals after struggling with issues for fucking years. I just wanted to fucking vent and you are up on my ass in the comments because I don't fit into your neat little diagnosis box. Just fuck off, let me fucking vent about issues I'm struggling with due to the medication im taking for something i am fucking DIAGNOSED WITH.

Idk if you are even trying to be a fucking prick, but goddamn. I struggled for years, being in severe pain, my immune system attacking my own organs, until my kidney and liver were just about to give up. I have fucking struggled enough to be believed, I don't need some random redditor prick to be questioning me on my diagnosis in the comments of me just fucking venting. You're getting blocked because I'm over it. I just wanted to fucking vent and you decided to be a prick. Fuck you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I hate that I'm not the "normal" kind of sick (rant) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 12:03:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (for context, I have had endometriosis since I was 12, fibromyalgia and cfs/me since I was 18/19, and lupus which is genetic - due to these issues I have a lot of other health issues such as chronic sinusitis, kidney issues, and digestive issues)

It feels like anytime I vent about issues I'm having in chronic illness spaces, if I mention something that is slightly "different" for the chronic illness I'm talking about, my replies are filled with doubters. People being like "oh your white blood cell count was high before medication? wellllll with lupus its usually low" etc and it pisses me off tbh. Like its not like I'm self diagnosing myself with all this shit, I have been diagnosed Multiple times at this point by multiple doctors with shit! These fucking reddit pseudo-doctors don't fucking understand that hey! Maybe someone does not fit into a neat little box of 'typical symptoms'. Maybe someone has multiple issues causing blood results to be fucky! Maybe someone doesn't present certain symptoms!

Like jesus, I just am so tired. I thought I found spaces where I could vent about my chronic illness issues without being immediately fucking judged, but nooo every time I make a fucking post I have to hop on the defensive because I mention something atypical that I experience for the disease I'm discussing. What do these people want, tbh? Do they want the fucking phone numbers of my doctors to confirm I have stage 3 endometriosis? That I got fibromyalgia after being sick for months with pneumonia my freshman year in college? That my dad, my brother, and myself all have Lupus and it has ruined all of our lives???

I'm just fucking tired man. I wish I could just fucking vent about issues without having to try and prove that I'm 'legit' in the comments, just because I experience a few 'abnormal' things for that illness. Like...in a way, its triggering tbh, because especially with my endometriosis, my doctor didn't believe me for years. It wasn't until it had progressed into stage 3 and my doctor and mom held me down, trying to force a pap on me when I was 19, when I was sobbing because I was in so much pain, that they even tried to do blood tests. Then an ultrasound, which lit up like the fucking fourth of July.

I'm tired of not being believed. I have become a better advocate for myself, fighting doctors until they run tests until low and behold, I was fucking right about the issues I was expressing. But it pisses me off that after all this fighting, after years of struggling to obtain a diagnosis, finally fucking finally....I come to reddit chronic illness communities and its doubt doubt doubt doubt doubt. I just want to fucking vent about my issues without people jumping at my throat because I mention that I experience something slightly abnormal for a certain illness. Big shocker to all them!!!! But when you have multiple illnesses!!!!! Things may not present the fucking same!!!!!! Especially when a couple of the illnesses you have blend together and its hard to tell symptoms from one from symptoms from the other (ie, my having fibromyalgia and lupus).

Sigh sigh sigh. I'm sorry for ranting, I'm just so fucking tired. I have finally been diagnosed with shit after years of fighting, I am finally on medication that helps me somewhat, I just want to be able to vent on reddit without people who got diagnosed as easy as it is to sneeze hopping on my ass about my diagnoses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 11:32:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It normally does I think, a few of my blood tests were abnormal for Lupus because I have other health issues going on at the same time that make my complete blood counts kinda funky. However I am dxed with it as it is genetic with me (brother and dad both have it) and I show all the other physical signs, in addition to most of the blood results being spot on for Lupus. It's mainly the red and white blood cell counts that were abnormal for Lupus. Its sucks because this is why it has taken me so long to get diagnosed, it wasn't until I was having massive kidney issues due to Lupus that my doctor finally decided to officially diagnose me and start me on medication. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 05:29:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> straw 👏 berry 👏 dress 👏 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 04:45:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This feels scarily familiar, tbh. Beautiful drawing though, definitely captures a certain feeling that I am very familiar with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Plaquenil & Plummeting White Blood Cells (A very tired rant) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 04:42:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been on Plaquenil for a little over two months, but this past month has been Hell. I got a sinus infection, followed by strep throat, followed my some random scratches getting infected. I finally realized something was super off, so I contacted my Rheum, and she had blood tests ran. I used to have actually relatively high white blood cell counts, but they have abruptly plummeted to extremely low levels. She said its normal for people who have just started on Plaquenil to experience this, but also mentioned its usually not to this extreme. At her suggestion, I've basically had to try to restructure my entire life, move to only picking up groceries, working with my job to transition to working from home...I'm damn tired lmao, I really hope she's right and this is only temporary cause not being able to leave my apartment is already driving me a bit crazy. My white blood cell count is so low that my Rheum is actually getting me tested weekly just to monitor it and make sure it doesn't get worse. According to the blood tests at least my kidneys and livers are ok-ish again? Man, what a debacle. Plaquenil, please just level things out, jeas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 06:38:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The r/DID community generally welcomes questions, especially innocent ones such as that, even from people that are openly singlets (ie people that do not have DID or OSDD)! I would not worried about having a "right" to post a question there, so long as it is in good faith (ie, not posted in order to make fun of systems)! We often get people who have friends or family members diagnosed asking questions, as well as good intentioned people who are simply curious about a certain subject! Also, you don't need to fully join a group to ask a question, you can post in a group without being apart of it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 06:22:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The r/DissociaDID subreddit has a lot of info on it in regards to events that have happened. There are a few twitter accounts that have documented events such as @dissociatruth - the main youtuber I know who talks about them a lot is The Alternative System, but I don't recommend her, as she has done some nasty stuff within the community itself. I believe VangelinaSkov has maybe also made videos about the situation? But I have not looked too much into that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 06:14:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably moreso a question to ask the r/DID community, rather than a specific person just diagnosed. Def preface you are simply curious, though. As someone dxed with DID (though I have said before, feel I was misdiagnosed, though atm I'm kind of not sure if I was misdiagnosed or not due to certain recent things I won't get into BUT ANYWAY) I haven't really thought about this before. I'd be interested to see others dxed with DID's responses to this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 06:03:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem, everything was only exposed within the last year, mostly from within DID-centric spaces, so many outsiders don't know...and recent events have proved they have not changed, which is the main reason I'm bringing it up. I still hope the best for them, but the harm they have done both within the community, in addition to spreading misinformation to singlets, is immeasurable, unfortunately. As I said, still hoping for the best for them, just...really wish they were not an extremely problematic and manipulative system, esp since they are the most "well known" system atm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 05:53:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Quick note DissociaDID has been disowned from the community for multiple reasons I won't get into in depth, but it includes pedophilia, suicide-baiting, and extortion. No one with DID supports them, only singlets who are oblivious do. Definitely don't recommend them as reliable source. Multiplicity and Me is, however, a nice source, and a genuinely good person. There are also a handful of other good DID youtubers, but I'd also stay away from "The Alternative System" and obvious trolls like Trisha Paytas. Most other DID youtubers are nice and chill though! Def stay far far away from DissociaDID though. Nothing but toxicity and misinformation from them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 05:23:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree with this in a sense, as many mental illnesses masquerade as other issues, with many similar symptoms...additionally, no two people experience a mental illness the same way, so it comes down to a professional to decide.

HOWEVER. Many of the people "self diagnosing" are teenagers stuck in oppressive environments, without the resources to seek help. Many adults, even do not have the monetary resources to seek help, and many are located in areas where there are not a lot of psychiatric resources. This is speaking from experience, living in a small town in the midwest, with parents that did not believe in mental illnesses, let alone psychiatry as legitimate practice. It can feel so isolating to be experiencing things, and not have any words to place to those things, not have any resources to help you.

I think people saying "i think i have xyz mental illness" can potentially be harmful, not so much to the community, but for that individual. I think encouraging people discussing symptoms over specific mental illnesses should be encouraged more, and for people experiencing those symptoms, even without diagnosis, to be treated with the same level of seriousness as people who are diagnosed. I personally, am diagnosed with OCD, an "unspecified mood disorder" (which I generally just shorten to bipolar) and DID (tho I also doubt this diagnosis). I have experienced OCD as far back as I can remember, around 4 years old. I struggled with it for years and years, unable to obtain a diagnosis until I escaped to college.

TLDR: Its in the best interest of undiagnosed people to not identify with a certain illness, as that can cause additional issues to them. However, I believe it should be encouraged for people to discuss their specific symptoms they are struggling with, in order to obtain advice on how to handle said symptoms (examples of this are intrusive thoughts, hallucinations, physical symptoms related to mental health, etc). I frankly do not believe these people are harmful to those of us that Are diagnosed with certain things. I mean, we were all undiagnosed at one point. We were all confused and struggling, until obtaining help/a diagnosis. There is nuance to these situations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 05:07:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Privilege in general is based on a lot of different factors. Your class, your race, your gender, sexuality, disabilities...and each of these things are also impossible to compare to one another. You can't compare class and race, or disability vs gender...the fact of the matter is, regardless of the fact that I am a trans and queer disabled person who grew up poor...my whiteness was not a contributing factor to my oppression in society/general difficulties. Regardless of the disadvantages I have in life, I have white privilege. Simple as that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 04:20:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Big agree! Take it for OCD and it at least helps with the OCD-fueled hallucinations/delusions, even if it doesn't stop them completely ;;; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 01:03:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I definitely recommend checking out r/DID - I am kind of the opposite of you, being diagnosed with DID but suspecting I have schizophrenia instead. But the DID community here is very kind and accepting, they will be able to help with different ways to cope, to accept things, give you words to explain your experiences (for instance, roles, such as persecutor, which your Gabe seems to be). They are a very loving and accepting community. I wish you the best of luck friend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 00:31:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Working at their mommies and daddies businesses in our podunk hometown after dropping out of college lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 23:01:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would say in a sense, for a while, but I've kind of moreso drifted to only being comfortable dating asexual people of all genders. I just don't want to be a disappointment to anybody else I'd date, who likely would want penetrative sex at some point, either via genitals, fingers, toys, etc. I myself am not ace, I actually am quite sexual, but the idea of penetration not only terrifies me, but it's impossible atm. I just don't want to disappoint people so I kind of limit myself. Not that I have been dating much anyway, with Covid and everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 22:52:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats what I was thinking. Def sounds like she has delusions in some sense, especially if she legit believes she's a vampire/can talk to dead people (funny enough, the talking to dead people thing has been one of my biggest delusions in regards to psychosis for years). Def not a fan of the trivializing OCD though, or making her mental illnesses aesthetically pleasing, though some people Do cope that way...it just makes me uncomfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 21:30:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everyone reacts to meds differently, the most important part is for him to communicate clearly with the doctor any side effects/negative effects they may give him etc! Psych meds are very much trial and error. I wish you both luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 20:34:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does this also happen to your hands as well? Sounds a lot like Raynaud's to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 20:14:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me of that god awful "faking" post from a few days ago, how doctors apparently only take you seriously if you say 5,6,7, or 8. 🙄 the pain scale sucks esp since doctors apparently use it to rule out "fakers" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 19:21:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please don't come into my DMs harassing me about this, thanks 🙃 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 11:27:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I totally feel this tbh. I'm not vegetarian, so my general go tos aren't necessarily vegetarian, but I'll try to provide substitutions where possible!

One of my favorite go to things are things like chicken noodle soup or chicken ramen - chicken ramen can easily be substituted for vegetable ramen! I know standing and cooking at the stove can be tough during rough times, so I suggest you invest in one of those water heater kettle-looking things that plug into a wall. Pour water in, let it heat to a boil, place your ramen and the packet in a big enough dish, pour the water in, cover it and wait for 3 minutes! Or get cup of noodle, which is even easier haha!

Another go to for me is crackers and hummus. Roasted red pepper is my favorite generally, but when I'm having stomach issues, the plain is amazing. It keeps adding protein in, when dealing with beans is difficult.

The campbells sippables are also a favorite of mine. Tomato is good, especially if you have some bread or a tortilla shell to dip in it.

If you don't have issues with cheese, an easy favorite meal of mine is just take a tortilla shell, sprinkle some cheese over it, microwave it for like 30 seconds. Simple, easy on the stomach.

I also generally snack on baby carrots when i dont feel well. Sometimes i dip them in ranch or hummus, sometimes i just nibble on them. Also, those pre-cut apple packages are a godsend.

My other big simple staple for feeling icky is canned tuna, I don't really know of a good veg sub to that though, sorry.

Sometimes also, just eating toasted bread, a bit of (microwave) melted butter on it, it just really hits the spot tbh. Even just plain bread, or spread with things you can stand (nutella, peanut butter, jelly, etc) is lovely too.

Idk if any of this was helpful whatsoever, but I wish you luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 11:11:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Big agree. If someone is like "im having hallucinations like x, y, and z, and im having delusions like x, y, and z, do i have schizophrenia?" My general response is along the lines of "Those sound like they Could be some form of psychosis, but I am not a doctor, only a medical professional can diagnose and treat you."

I somewhat understand the desperation and need to have a word to describe your experiences...but in the end, if someone goes "yeah it sounds like you have schizophrenia" on a post then...what has the poster gained beyond a word? Unless they are wanting to actually go out and seek treatment, then the only thing they have to cling onto is a word that may or may not actually be describing what they have, which can be harmful in the long run. And unfortunately, I have a feeling many people do just want that word, no treatment...which can also be damaging to them. I feel for these people, I really do, they always seem so desperate, and I was once in their position when trying to get diagnosed with OCD back in high school. But in the end, encouraging them to seek treatment which is a much more effective, safe, and better relief in the long run, is better than the short temporary relief of our unprofessional opinions.

I hope that made sense its 5am and I have not slept ;;; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 10:04:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While it is very true that more attention needs brought to these issues, telling mentally ill people that they should "count their blessings because it could be worse" is not at all a good take. I highly suggest you delete this post, as it could very well trigger (especially the younger) members of this reddit who are already struggling to feel validated in their mental health issues. Make a post if you like, discussing these issues, but do NOT make comparisons, comparisons help no one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 09:55:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Obligatory "not a doctor" disclaimer...but what you're experiencing is something that many people with POCD, or Pedophilia OCD, a subset of OCD, experience. The definition of it is as follows: Pedophilia OCD, or POCD, is a subset of OCD in which a sufferer has unwanted harmful or sexual thoughts about children. This subtype often results in panic, anguish, shame and depression. People living with POCD have no desire to harm a child, yet they’re tormented by thoughts of doing so. [SOURCE](https://www.madeofmillions.com/ocd/pedophilia-ocd)

If you believe that you fit this description, I definitely would not hesitate to bring this up with a therapist, as well as possibly seeking help from online support groups (the OCD community on here, for instance, is wonderful and supportive, I am apart of this community having OCD myself).

As for what you did as a teenager, you said it right there at the end. When you're a teenager you do stupid stuff you later realize was wrong, and you feel guilty about it. It happens to all of us. You haven't had these habits for years, you don't find pleasure in those things anymore, in fact you are scared of such things...the past is in the past. Focus on the now, and getting help. Best of luck to you, truly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 09:43:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For the knocking, unfortunately no. I just have to tell myself when it is happening, that it makes no sense for it to be happening at all, I just try to ignore it to the best of my ability. For me, auditory hallucinations are some of the hardest ones for me to tell what is real vs hallucination, even after the fact. For sensory and visual, it's a bit easier to try and rationalize in my head after the fact that I couldn't have bugs crawling all over me/I couldn't be seeing shadows move wrong, etc.

I guess my best advice is to just kind of think on things as best you can: (BTW you don't need to answer any of these questions, they are just things for you to think about! This is kind of how I go through recognizing what is a hallucination and what is not)

For instance, how often was the doorbell going off? Once a day? Multiple times a day? Once could have been a census taker, door to door salesmen, religious people, etc. Multiple seems less likely to be real, unless the doorbell was malfunctioning. In that case, before you moved, did the doorbell just stop ringing one day, without you doing anything to "fix" it? In that case, it's likely that it was a hallucination, as it would not miraculously fix itself one day. Did you ever go and check to see if someone was ringing the doorbell? If you did and no one was there, same as what I said before, likely a hallucination (as I doubt even the most dedicated ding-dong-ditcher would keep this up for weeks). Another good question to ask yourself, was was that the only auditory hallucination you might have heard? Did you have any other forms of hallucinations? Prior mental health issues? Were you, at the time, currently under a great deal of stress or anxiety? Were you ill/did you have a fever? All of those things can play into hallucinations, in different ways.

I hope some of this was helpful! Best of luck to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 09:30:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We aren't medical professionals here. That being said, he likely needs some form of therapy/medication, as it is clear he is sufferring from some form of psychosis (whether it is genetic, from drug abuse, from prior abuse, spontaneous, or some combination of these, it's impossible for us to tell). I would say try bringing things up with him, but gently, like say "Maybe therapy would help with your anxiety", maybe even say that YOU are considering therapy as well for some issue. For him to get help at this point, he needs to be willing. That ALSO being said, if he is totally unreachable, inpatient might be a good idea. Look into resources in your area, Psychology Today is amazing in that regard, in finding therapists/psychiatrists that specialize in certain areas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 09:15:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even though there are supposedly laws protecting us from discrimination in the workplace and in schools, it still happens, and the people in charge get away with it. For instance, if you put down that your gender is male on a job application, but they ask for your legal name and it is a traditionally female name, you are more likely to be denied that job. Some places blatantly ask if you identify as trans, and its always a toss up on whether they will use you identifying as such to hire you as the Token Transgender tm, or if they will immediately throw your application out.

Speaking of protection - just general laws protecting us from violence. Trans women of color, especially sex workers, experience violence at an incredibly high rate in comparison to the rest of the population, and often even if they try to press charges, it will not go anywhere. Laws clearly defining that violence against trans people is a hate crime that WILL be punished, need put in place. Additional laws are needed to protect trans children and teenagers from violence and discrimination from their family members - something put in place so these young people don't have to choose between living in abusive households or being homeless.

Another big issue is medical discrimination. Not only to obtain HRT, surgeries, etc, which have their own difficult hoops to jump through, but many doctors and nurses are biased and will not treat trans patients as nicely as they do cis patients, even ignoring legitimate concerns. This is also especially prevalent in mental health fields.

Speaking of which, if a trans person were to go inpatient, many facilities would place them in a room with their assigned gender at birth. It's already distressing to be in that situation, that can make things worse.

Also, trans people are often turned away from homeless shelters (cough Salvation Army cough) due to their being a trans person. This should be illegal. Additionally, trans people are often turned away from "x gender only" domestic violence shelters, as they are seen as their assigned gender at birth.

And the biggest one for me tbh, also has to do with this. Trans people are often sent to prisons of their assigned gender at birth. This often means situations where trans women are sent to male prisons, where they are extremely vulnerable to violence and sexual assault.

There are many other things I could think of, like trans people being able to play sports with their gender, that sort of thing.

Trans people just want to be treated like humans. We don't want to be discriminated against. We don't want to be victims of violence and abuse. We want to be able to have access to services that fit our gender. Etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 08:41:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not doorbells, but knocking. I constantly hear knocking, on the walls (the only one possibly real, I have noisy apt neighbors), on my door, but especially from above me (I live on the top floor). It's one of my most anxiety-inducing symptoms, as I am extremely paranoid about people coming to visit me for any reason. It's real rough, I've even been woken from sleep by these fake knocks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 08:25:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I lucked out (knock on wood) on not experiencing the nausea! But I start Lexapro (again) this week (for OCD) and boy oh boy I am NOT looking forward to that brand of constant nausea and vertigo for 2-3 weeks as I taper back on 😬 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 08:22:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same tbh, my biggest support was my friend I only talked to over Discord, every day, and not being able to have my phone was what made me wait so long. It was incredibly boring the first days I was in there, I spent most of my time sleeping or drawing, until I got a roommate who was going through opiate withdrawals and had Chrons, and then it was like I had a purpose: taking care of her. I made a few friends, including her, but man, those days were long, I missed my best friend so much, sometimes I just wanted to sit and play a game of sudoku or solitaire on my phone, ya know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 07:16:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Witholding necessary medical attention is abuse, full stop. Tell one of your teachers (a trusted one) what is going on, or if you can get in contact with your doctor, tell them what is going on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 05:27:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "ALL YOUR BASE ARE BELONG TO US" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 05:11:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Glanced at your post history, went real far back. Getting sectioned may be the best thing for you to be honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 04:44:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some of you need your medical licenses taken away lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 04:40:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, that thread sucked. Luckily most of the posts turned into "Doctors and Nurses thought I was faking and it nearly killed me," but yeah, I saw several posts about DID on there and a bunch of Singlets who weren't even doctors going on and on about how they can alllllways tell when someone is faking. I'd take it with a grain of salt, they're the type of people that hang out on the Farms and illness fakers, a bunch of incel troll assholes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> sometimes the shadows look strange to me </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 03:30:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wilson & Willow clothing swap! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 03:11:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 23:01:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was put on Cymbalta for a while, but was not a fan at all, it helped None with my OCD. I know some people like it tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 20:05:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One thing I've found that helps when I can't close my eyes, is putting icy hot or Vicks Vapor Rub or other strong smelling things over my eyebrows and on my cheekbones. It causes my eyes to sting and water, forcing them closed and to remain closed. Sometimes this even helps me to sleep, esp the icy hot stuff for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 19:57:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [This article](https://www.zdnet.com/article/facebook-sues-two-chrome-extension-makers-for-scraping-user-data/) lists out some additional info about the situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 19:50:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine only started when I went on Lexapro for my OCD, it is known to cause insomnia. Even when I went off it though, the insomnia never stopped. Now my insomnia is fueled by OCD and psychosis (mainly hallucinations, auditory and sensory), and also probably chronic pain (lupus and fibromyalgia). Irony is I also have chronic fatigue syndrome as well, so even though I feel constantly tired, sleep never comes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 18:35:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Luckily its mostly filled with people sharing their stories about how doctors/nurses thought they were faking and they nearly died. The few doctors/nurses that did post had people telling them they should have their medical licenses taken away, so thats good at least... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 16:53:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some of the doctors and nurses in this thread need to lose their medical licenses 😬 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 16:44:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I broke my pelvis, I wasn't prescribed pain medication of any kind - only muscle relaxers. All because the doctor I saw, saw on my chart that I have chronic pain, and she was worried if she prescribed opiates I'd get addicted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 08:53:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not a doctor, but have dealt with plenty since around age 12, when my endometriosis started to develop. I've had doctors and nurses, both good and bad...the ones I'd categorize as bad were the ones more interested in seeing if I was "faking" rather than believing me and actually running tests. From age 12-19, I was experiencing endometriosis, which progressively got worse to the point I was passing out, having violent period blood nosebleeds, throwing up constantly, in absolute agony, etc. It was literally only when I broke down absolutely sobbing, begging for my doctor to believe me, that she called for bloodwork, pelvic, an ultrasound, etc. i was completely unable to do a pelvic as my endo was so bad, and big shocker, when I got an ultrasound it lit up like the fourth of July. I needlessly suffered for YEARS because this bitch ass nurse thought I was exaggerating.

Another incident. I had pneumonia in fall of 2016, went on antibiotics, felt a bit better but not completely, tried to ignore it and push through the pain. My body is very resistant to antibiotics, so what happened was this pneumonia laid dormant in my lungs for about a month, before resurfacing worse than ever. I went to see a new doctor, told him straight up, "This is what pneumonia felt like a month ago," but he was determined I "just had bronchitis". I told him "no, I've had bronchitis before, its not like this". But he just kept refusing to listen, but I kept fighting. He eventually got super angry at me and was like "fine! I'll order some xrays if it will get you out of my office!" And big shocker, I had a case of pneumonia so bad I had to be hospitalized.

I could go on and on, especially dealing with rheumatologists, getting my diagnoses for Fibromyalgia and Lupus was like pulling fucking teeth.

Anyway tldr: Doctors and Nurses who are more interested in trying to figure out if a patient is "faking" or not, above actually fucking listening to them and doing the proper tests and treating them are only in this profession to have a sadistic sense of power over sick, chronically ill, and disabled people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 08:40:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chronic pain sufferer here. Every time I go to a new doctor and explain my medical history (endo since 12, fibromyalgia since 18, Lupus hereditary) they feel the IMMEDIATE need to inform me "We don't prescribe opiates" like??? I was just telling you my medical history? In fact, if a doctor decided to prescribe me anything of that nature, I'd tell them no, because I have a family history of addiction, and I know with my pain, I'd definitely become addicted. Like jesus, I wish they'd stop assuming everyone is just chasing a high. I just want to make sure my diseases aren't causing any more damage then they've already done prior to diagnosis/treatment jeash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 08:24:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Id say the only time I have ever experienced a true ten was when I picked up a metal cup that I had no clue had just been removed from over a fire. My hand literally sizzled and when i dropped the cup my skin just came off with it. Keep in mind, I have endometriosis, fibromyalgia, and Lupus, I've been in a car crash where my car rolled three times, I got sun poisoning over my entire face and hands which caused a fever of 103, I've had pneumonia 5 times in the last 4 years, and I have broken my pelvis. None of those were a ten but holy HELL that burn was a 10.

Also yes, I am an exceptionally unlucky person, I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> an endless cycle at this point (vent) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 07:00:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you just lay there, your eyes closed, for hours, aware of time passing slowly. hours and hours of just laying there, mind empty but aware enough of the passage of time. then 10 minutes before your alarm goes off, suddenly you doze. have some some sort of really weird vivid detailed dream. then the alarm for work.

i dont remember the last time i actually had a deep sleep beyond just that...stagnant resting period, of being awake but my mind being empty like i was sleeping, followed by a few minutes of dozing before my alarm. im exhausted. took two dramamine, a shot of whiskey, downed some NyQuil, rubbed some icy hot on my pain points (I have fibro & lupus) and yet here we are still. Biggest, heaviest sigh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 15:58:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For real, noticed this too. Also posts should not allowed to be posted without flairs, especially extremely triggering stuff. I get when someone's in a crisis its hard to remember this but jesus i don't want to get halfway through reading a post with a vague title with no flair only to see someone graphically describing their self harm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 23:40:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me, kinda. I mean I'm on Lexapro but thats for my OCD, psychosis is still untreated/unmedicated but I'm in the process of figuring out what to do there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 14:26:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me, I've noticed its mostly the taste/consistency that has a psychological response for me. I would say maybe try tapering off, slowly, so as not to shock your brain too much, and instead try drinking a little bit of juice that is similar in flavor to the zzzquil, right before bed. If you still have some issues, I'd try melatonin again with that. I also have found that CBD with melatonin is a bit more effective than just normal melatonin. A brand that works really well for me is Zilis, their "Ultra Dream" variety, but its on the expensive side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 03:06:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i feel like this is from the point of view of a hostage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 08:45:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i was curious and scrolled all the way back to check. so big thank you to u/lickybear ur the best for recommending Meridian to me ahh thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thank you (a follow up) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 08:40:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I posted a while back, asking for recommendations on mental health services in Louisville, and someone recommended Meridian Behavioral Health. It's a bit far back in my post history as I've been quite a bit more active on Reddit recently, but I just want to say a huge huge huge thank you to whoever recommended them. I have never EVER had a doctor before that is just so kind, so empathetic, so willing to actually help me, as the psychiatrist I'm currently seeing through Meridian. Just...thank you. I've been going through some extremely rough times mentally lately (my post history shows this for sure, but do not look if triggered by self harm/psychosis mentions), having a doctor like this is literally a lifesaver. Anyway, sorry for rambling. Just...thank you whoever recommended them. You've quite literally saved my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 05:51:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Shelter by Porter Robinson](https://youtu.be/fzQ6gRAEoy0) I love this song and music video, I relate to it a lot, some of you might as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I feel so conflicted now - Vent Post - Self Harm trigger warning </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 06:43:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I want to give a little backstory before I get into the thick of it. I was diagnosed with DID in Spring of 2019 when I was 21. I had not even considered the possibility before then. I have since had 4 alters make themselves known, who have been very vocal since the diagnosis. However, I also have been suffering from severe psychosis, between hallucinations and delusions, other such things, that make me feel I may have been misdiagnosed with DID? But also I can't say for sure, I'm seeing a new Psych on Tuesday to talk through all this.

BUT ANYWAY, I felt this belonged here because this almost makes me doubt my doubts. I was trying to charge my dead phone, which had died in the middle of me talking to my best friend. None of the three chargers I had decided to work. I felt supreme anger and frustration, then nothing. I blacked out it felt like. About a half hour laterh I came to, with deep bleeding scratches all over my arms, my face, my legs. I was in shock - even in all my times of experiencing what I felt was switches, I never felt I was truly gone. However this time I completely went somewhere else in my mind as someone else controlled my body, making it do these things.

I feel so shooken up tbh. I was so sure for a while I had DID after my diagnosis, then I began doubting things in spite of the diagnosis and evidence...idk. I just feel weird rn. Because I never would half self harmed, esp over something so insignificant like this. Even the alters I know of wouldn't do this I think? Maybe? Idk...I'm sorry, I'm so shaken up, I just passed over a year being self harm free (and mind you, when I self harmed before, it was using an exacto knife and was very precise, so this animalistic clawing crazy patterns all over my body is not at all like me).

Im not exactly asking for advice just...idk. i needed to vent all this to the void because I'm just in such shock over all this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm so angry at myself </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 04:08:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It had been over a year since I self-harmed, I have actually been feeling okay lately (aside from having strep throat and psychosis that is getting worse). Today, all three of the phone chargers I had decided to not work after my phone died, and for some reason, of all things, this made me freak out. I blacked out for about a half hour, came back to myself having clawed at both of my wrists as well as other places on my body, multiple bleeding wounds. I went to the CVS to get a new phone charger as well as some bandages, but I'm just so mad. It has been over a year since I self harmed, and my phone dying and me not having a charger cord that worked triggered me of all things. Ugh. I'm honestly just so annoyed at myself, I hope no one at work tomorrow asks why I have like 15 bandages all over my face and arms... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 03:37:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I totally understand that! And I really think that's great that it has helped you, don't get me wrong! And hearing you explain it more definitely makes it feel a bit nicer! It is just one of those things that many of us who are unable to really function with our disabilities have been told, and it can be triggering (For context, I have a handful of physical disabilities including Lupus, as well as mental disabilities, basically all of which combined makes functioning hard - and I have been told numerous times, even by doctors to "not let my disabilities limit me" etc, when realistically, they DO limit me). Just to clarify, no hate whatsoever towards you! Just adding an additional perspective! I'm glad this has helped you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 03:11:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If it helps you, then nice! I personally despise such quotes, because it makes it sound like "If x person works hard enough, they won't be disabled anymore" which is...rather problematic. Disability is not a choice. Saying that people "let" ourselves be disabled by our condition is really really gross and ableist. It's the type of stuff Facebook moms say to people who have illnesses, before telling the person in question to "just try yoga" or to "drink more water", or to try their "MLM essential oils in a diffuser" that will definitely cure all their problems.

If the quote helps you, then great. But it's not something that is helpful to most people in mental health, chronic illness, and disability communities, and people will likely be very upset at quotes like this being brought up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 05:53:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For real. I have been on birth control since I was 12, when my endo symptoms first started manifesting. I remember my mom telling me to never bring it up at school because she thought everyone would think I was a "slut". I ended up calling it my "period medication" for years, even in college, which got me weird looks lol. But like for real, Norethindrone has saved my entire life, whenever I see people be anti birth control I just want to scream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 05:46:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's so horrible :( Trolls are getting more and more vile by the day. Stay safe and take care of your mental health -A Jeffersonville ally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Do non-overtly-harmful obsessions exist for you? (Hyperfixations anyone)? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 05:39:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am very much involved with the mental health community on Twitter, and I often see Autistic people and people with ADHD posting about their obsessions, often with a form of media - "hyperfixations". I have always deeply related to these posts, as at certain times in my life, I have become absolutely obsessed with a certain form of media, unable to think about anything BUT that media. In my mind, I kind of always connected it back to my OCD, but I am honestly not sure if it is? Because I don't really see other people with OCD talk about that sort of thing.

I know OCD is considered a neurodivergency and there are many similarities between it and Autism and ADHD, but I don't often see people discussing hyperfixations! Hyperfixations to me, can be harmful in some ways (socially, for example) but are also comforting and happy in many other ways.

I was just kind of wondering if anyone else has experienced obsessions in the form of hyperfixating on a sort of media, in a way that wasn't overtly harmful to you, and maybe even brought you some sort of comfort or happiness? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 01:43:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doctors/Nurses can be such sensitive assholes sometimes. I swear some (if not 50% to most) of them go into this profession just to have some sick kind of sadistic control over disabled/chronically ill people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 08:17:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I definitely know the pain of having parents that are anti-anything-related-to-psychiatry/disorders, and I was in your position for a long time.

I'm not a professional by any means, but I also have OCD (have had it since I was a toddler) and have been experiencing Psychosis for the last few years. Many people that I know with OCD do experience a certain level of paranoia in regards to the things you mentioned, myself included (the reason I mention this is your family history of OCD). It definitely sounds, however, like you are also experiencing some level of delusions and hallucinations, which definitely lean you a bit more in the direction of having some level of psychosis.

Most towns/cities, even small ones, often offer psychiatric services at a reduced rate, or at least on a sliding scale/pay what you can scale (towns with colleges in them especially offer this sort of thing). I saw you say you don't have any sort of counselor at your school...if you have a teacher you can trust, I would bring up your desire to seek out therapy/psychiatric services with them (without revealing too many details, as teachers are required by law to contact parents/law enforcement if they believe you may be a potential harm to yourself or others, and they may interpret some details as such). Just bring up your desire to seek out affordable mental health services, and they may be able to connect you to resources.

Another helpful resource, believe it or not, is your local library. Most libraries have an information desk, and those librarians are often very knowledgable about local resources. They may be able to connect you to mental health resources that even aren't readily listed online.

I want to quickly add to NOT do what I did, which was seek help from online "therapists" through things like Betterhelp. I know how desperate your situation may feel, I was in your shoes, but they are expensive and not worth it.

 I definitely feel for your situation, I truly wish you the best. If there is anything else I can do to help you locate resources and whatnot, let me know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 07:44:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Big agree. I reported their posts but I'd definitely message some of the mods about this if you haven't already, because that person is awful and is targeting vulnerable people in our community which is gross. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 07:39:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I went and checked as well. Got to love the bigoted systems that like to fakeclaim others just because they have different experiences than them /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For those of us that struggle with cleaning 🙃 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 07:34:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 03:37:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not big on religion myself, but having watched the interview with the...pastor/preacher/minister lady on the livestream last night, they earned every bit of my respect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 02:17:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks so pretty! But definitely share to r/ForbiddenSnacks haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 01:05:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *wash her car with paint thinner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 01:04:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She has a lot to say for someone whose own eyebrows are trying to escape her bullshit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 19:58:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I relate to every word you said...I'm sorry you've gone through all this too ;;; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 07:35:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ooh yes! Those little rubber pom pom balls work wonders. I rotated between those and one of those scrub brushes with the stretchy rubber bristle things to satisfy my hair pulling compulsions when I had them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 07:31:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to have this bad with my OCD. I had hair pulling for a while in high school, but mainly skin picking and nail picking prior to that. For the latter two, the major way I coped was completing that same action, but in a way that did not harm my body! For instance, I'd get one of those big erasers and pick at it, pulling off tiny pieces. Or I'd cover my hand in glue, let it dry, and pull it off.

For hair pulling, I actually got a rubber scrub brush that had kind of little rubber "strands" that stuck up like [this](https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/61xq1RUTgnL._SL1001_.jpg) and I would kind of pull at those rubber strands. It wasn't exactly the same, but it helped to satisfy that compulsion for me! The big first step to take is to find some non-harmful method to satisfy your compulsion, THEN work on treatment and stopping completely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 19:41:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are being a massive and ignorant dick, you are making fun of OP in other forums. Feck off if you are not going to bring anything helpful to the conversation. Jesus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 02:03:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Binders are a lot for me as well (nonbinary transmasc person here). Even putting them on is an exhausting struggle. I have somewhat found that compression sports bras put less strain on me, both to put on and to wear for extended periods of times. You're a bit less flat in them, but it helps alleviate some of the dysphoria without making the CFS worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i wish i could sleep </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 05:15:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> small rant/vent. but im so tired. i can't sleep anymore, without alcohol or weed, or chugging nighttime cough syrup. like even when im at the point im hallucinating (worse than usual), not having slept for days in a row and I feel absolutely warn down...my body STILL refuses to sleep. i just want to sleep without having to use substances. i just want to sleep. I want to lay down and not be consumed by hallucinations or delusions or intrusive thoughts or obsessive compulsive thoughts, I JUST WANT TO SLEEP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 04:32:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bro my hometown ballet studio had this poster, and I lived up near Fort Wayne, Indiana, this was iconic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 04:04:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wiping habits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 04:32:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Brain balloon, very Mood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 04:31:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Both with my OCD and Psychosis. It's awful. I feel for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 01:03:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She did not end her career due to past problematic content, both herself and Julien have made this abundantly clear. Jenna is a self-proclaimed introvert. She is a very private person. Youtube/Twitch/being on the internet in general was taking a toll on her. Having watched the several videos before her quitting youtube, it was clear she did not want to be doing this anymore (her videos being much shorter less energetic, etc). She quit for her mental health reasons. I mean she's been doing this for over 10 years, and with her being an introvert and very private person, I imagine that has taken a lot out of her. Trying to frame the narrative around her being "cancelled" and that being the reason for her leaving...is simply wrong. She was simply tired and wanted a long break, maybe even a permanent one. And I mean, she probably has enough money to last her a lifetime, she has her dream house, her dogs, Julien...what more could she want? Whats the point in continuing if she no longer found passion around making content.

TLDR: Jenna didn't quit because she was "cancelled". Things just happened to line up that it seemed like that was the case. But both she and Julien have confirmed that that wasn't why she quit, so please stop framing it this way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 20:33:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was just venting, hence why I tagged this as "venting". People found it helpful because they experience the same things I do. Yes, it is important for people outside out community to realize that OCD is more than what it is portrayed like in media...but also, it is important for people in THIS community to not feel alone. I have never once seen a post about hoarding or wiping or having having issues with cleaning their homes or themselves, even though all those things are very common in OCD. Yeah, so anyway, maybe let people vent in the OCD forum about their OCD, don't be an ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 20:23:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Back when I lived with my parents, they constantly complained about the amount of toilet paper I go through, so I feel that pain...I'm so sorry you're having to go through that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 20:21:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To give you some advice, which applies to me and idk anyone else, the NORMAL (influence on normal and not sheer moisture, which is very greasy as well as eucerin) it has helped me so so much in regards to my issues with OCD. I have struggled with issues relating to OCD, both hand washing and face-washing. The normal Aveeno has helped so much in keeping my face/hands clean without the greasy feeling. Idk honestly what to present in forms related to wiping because even then the typical forms of wiping I have are because Down There is "too wet" so bidets/wet wipes are kinda useless...but anyway, I hope the first part helped you. The normal Aveeeno is the only thing i've found that moisturizes me without being super greasy. Less rashes on my hands and the like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 17:17:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lexapro was a life saver for me, I was so stupid to go off of it ;;; I'm going back on it at the end of the month because gosh, nothing else helped and I refuse to do exposure therapy ;;; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 17:15:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never watched it! But thank you for the rec! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i feel like this is the story of my life. cannot have one good day where i am able to walk around, without consequences, heh </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 13:45:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Let's stop sugarcoating the "gross" side of OCD </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 07:53:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This isn't a callout to the forum whatsoever, moreso a callout to media that represents OCD. People with OCD are always portrayed as "neat freaks" who are constantly cleaning. I want to give a brief shout out to Big Bang Theory, which I generally disliked, but it showed the character of Sheldon, who obviously had OCD, to be a secret hoarder. Hoarding is such a common occurrence in OCD yet no one talks about it!

Can we also talk about how wiping habits are such a common occurrence? But never talked about because it's considered "gross"? Like a lot of people with OCD have to wipe themselves a lot of times when they go to the toilet. This is a very common thing. Lets talk about it more so people like me don't feel gross and isolated, esp after being made fun of both my family and by people at school, and now work, for how long it takes me to take a piss.

Also - people with OCD can actually STRUGGLE to clean, shock horror. Because you know, touching gross shit like dirty dishes makes some of us us feel like shriveling up into a tiny wrinkled leaf. Some people with OCD, believe it or not, struggle to clean shit.

Sigh. Sorry for the rant, I'm just so tired of the portrayal of people with OCD being like "uwu clean freak" when many of the aspects of people with actual OCD are not at all like this. People with OCD can be hoarders. They can struggle with cleaning their living space. They can struggle with personal hygiene. That's not even to mention the internal aspects, like intrusive thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Memory Loss </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 07:37:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I also have some pretty severe psychosis in addition to my OCD, which causes loss of time and memory. This makes my OCD even MORE difficult to deal with than before I began experiencing psychosis, as now I completely forget if I have done certain rituals and whatnot! Making me having to repeat them probably even more times than what is already a lot! I was wondering if anybody else was experiencing this because my psychosis only has started to get bad within the past year, super bad only within the past couple of weeks...and it has caused a lot of issues in regards to my OCD rituals, in particular, remembering if I have done them or not. I just...idk. I feel so alone tbh, I'm waiting on my psych apt on the 29th but some of my habits are harmful to the body as it is, and having to repeat them due to memory loss is hell. How do those of you that have OCD and memory loss deal with this??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 05:43:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh most definitely! I have a plan for this, as well as much more, this was just a synopsis in the form of an unedited pitch letter! After such a positive response from this community, I definitely plan to flesh this idea out even more, I am filled with determination for this story idea to come to life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 05:01:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed tbh. Again, not to be tmi, but I also have OCD in addition to CFS, which results in "wiping rituals" which exhausts me even further. I have to psych myself up to go to the bathroom in any capacity, knowing even simply PEEING will take 15 minutes to complete, between wiping rituals and hand-washing rituals. Those things combined with my CFS causes 'using the restroom' in any capacity to be an experience I dread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TW: Suicide / Medical neglect / Medical Abuse - Last night at around 4am, I came up with the plot of a horror movie/novella, revolving around Fibromyalgia. I'm an English major who has had this illness for nearly 4 years now, and is struggling to express myself, so here's this I guess. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 02:55:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 00:28:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm in a better place now, insurance-wise, thankfully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A bout of pneumonia did this to me </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 18:47:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm bitter at the mere concept of pneumonia, as well as myself. Basically, in fall of 2016 I got sick with pneumonia, after ignoring symptoms of bronchitis for over a weak. Then, I remained semi-ill-but-not-super-ill through December and January, eventually becoming sick again in February. I was sick then with the SAME bout of pneumonia that had resurfaced because it had not been properly treated. This time I was sick for 2 months. This is what caused me to not only develop chronic sinusitis and adult asthma, but fibromyalgia and cfs/me. If only healthcare wasn't so expensive, I wouldn't have EVER waited at ANY point to go see a doctor. Now I'm stuck with lifelong debilitating conditions. So I guess I'm not as bitter at myself as I am the US healthcare system that made me to afraid to go to the doctor because I was afraid of what it would cost. Ugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 16:54:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm comorbid so it's hard for me to speak on that. I /will/ say I think there are heavy correlations between some of my OCD intrusive thoughts and my non-OCD delusions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 04:46:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg I'm cracking up at your husband cursing out a cricket, what a mood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I am struggling with my job [vent] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 21:29:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I currently work a full time job at a call center. I field anywhere between 80-100 calls a day, many of which take 10 minutes + each, often dealing with people who are super frustrated/angry. I started this job at the end of July, and ever since then, I have had increased episodes of psychosis, often taking the form of the regulars that call in to scream at me. It has gotten to the point that I'm losing sleep because any time I try to go to sleep I am being screamed at by voices of the regulars about all sorts of shit. I've lost so much sleep that I have to call in at least once a week sick, because I have migraines from lack of sleep/I know I'll fall asleep at my desk because I literally cannot control when I fall asleep or not. I have an apt for the end of the month to see if I can be put on something, anything, that can help me, but I just am struggling so much. I'm exhausted. I'm so stressed. How on earth does anyone with psychosis like this maintain a job?? Its literally killing me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 17:32:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep, Dan confirmed it in a comment on his youtube post on Crusader Kings 3 about a week ago, saying that he was "chasing his girlfriend around with his fake horse" or something like that :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 03:10:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually fell asleep to the lego harry potter streams with him and Jesse last night! Bless them tbh ;;; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Quiet Thank You </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 02:31:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have been suffering from psychosis for the past 4 years and severe OCD for much much longer, am on the way of being diagnosed with something on the schizophrenia spectrum. Every night, I would struggle to sleep, because voices, distressing voices, would fill my mind to the point I could not sleep at all.

Queue Daniel, of all people lol. His voice was calming, and after watching his videos, he became familiar to me, like a friend. Around November of 2019, I began turning on certain videos of his, to fall asleep to - funnily enough, the streams of his Minecraft Story Mode, and occasionally just his Minecraft build streams or his City Skylines streams. Hearing his voice, as I tried to go to sleep, quieted the voices inside my head. Thanks to him, I have been able to sleep once more, and thanks to him, I have a grounding force when I am experiencing an extreme bout of psychosis, esp as I am trying to go to sleep.

I have now been falling asleep to his videos/streams for nearly a year, since November of 2019, and I just really want to thank RT, Daniel, for helping me when I have felt at my lowest, for helping me to sleep after a few years of sleeping maybe 1 hour a night. I also want to say the last video Daniel posted on youtube had me in stitches, I have not laughed for months until now. Just...thank you Daniel. You are truly a gem and a lifesaver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 20:21:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a bit of advice that has been helpful to me as an artist! It's a bit time consuming, but it is the best way I've found to grow your audience organically! You just need to find a few bigger artists that have a similar style/focus/color aesthetic to yourself, go into their followers, and go down the list, liking a few posts from each of them. It helps to make people curious about your account and come to check it out! You just have to be careful, don't go too fast or Instagram will lock you out. It is also a good way to find other artists you might be interested in as well! Also, generally interacting with and commenting on other accounts art will help them to notice you as well! Lots of people have given me shoutouts, because of this! Basically, just be genuine, be kind, and have a niche! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 16:52:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/assistance might be able to help with costs/resources! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 16:45:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I honestly think everyone saying their pronouns should be normalized, even cis people. I mean some cis people I know also use alternative pronouns because pronouns don't equal gender (ie i know a few he/him cis lesbians, a few she/her cis gays) I personally never would have felt safe saying my pronouns if it wasn't for my college dorm normalizing it. So I definitely think it's a good thing, esp like having it in email signatures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 16:42:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are gorgeous!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 16:41:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Disney fanfics I wrote back in 2014 😅 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 00:08:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> THE TRUE DREAM YES </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 23:38:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I honestly hate the popularization of the word simp...it seems like any time a man defends a woman, esp on social media, they are instantly labelled a simp. Even if they are defending that woman from horrible things, like being harassed for their appearance or you know, "unproblematic" things. I def feel like the type of man that immediately label anyone who is nice to women in any capacity "a simp" are actually incels, who don't realize women or non-men are actual human beings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 23:35:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my GOSH that is so beautiful!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 20:04:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ENDO FRIENDO I LOVE THAT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 17:52:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't hate fish, in fact I respect them very highly! I just have medical needs and certain deficiencies that require me to eat things high in protein and iron :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 16:43:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember hearing about this on either Nexpo or Reignbot. So, so horrifying and so so sad... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 16:41:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By far, the story of Carl Tanzler, for me. A real life "A Rose for Emily" situation.

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Carl_Tanzler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 16:39:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From the book, Sharp Objects: "A child weaned on poison considers harm a comfort." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 16:36:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To be a veterinarian. Then I passed out while simply HEARING my vet explain to me and my parents the process of neutering my dog so...those dreams were crushed lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 16:33:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a pescatarian 99% of the time so close enough haha :)

Edit: idk why people are downvoting this haha, I don't have anything against people that eat meat or vegetarians or vegans, I respect all lifestyles! I would like to be vegetarian but my doctors advised me against doing so due to my illnesses (mainly Lupus)/vitamin deficiencies! The only meat I eat is canned tuna! Idk why this turned to a weird vegan debate when I simply posted about wanting to live in a cottage in the woods with a pet cow? But anyway please chill out EVERYONE and respect others lifestyles thanks! ✌️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 16:32:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Blair Witch Project mainly. I grew up in the middle of the woods and in said woods, a cult of witches would gather and sacrifice animals they had stolen from nearby farms, so yeah needless to say this movie hit a bit close to home when I watched it at around 7 years old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 16:29:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Moving to a cottage in the woods and having a cow as a pet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 07:54:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A big mood tbh, I am kind of a confused mix of traits that have been dxed as a wide variety of things, but is probably just flat out schizophrenia, but this community is so kind and accepting, it definitely helps me as well, it's so lovely. Thank you for posting ❤️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 07:49:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love the hair color! I've never been able to get my hair that neon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 07:48:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your hair color is gorgeous ahh!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 07:48:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> QT!!! And an excellent choice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 07:47:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cremation. Idk if this counts as "harmless" but I didn't know what cremation was until Avatar (you know, the blue people movie) came out. I was told at age 6 that my grandpa had been cremated and he was in a box in my aunt's living room. For some reason, I jumped to the conclusion that all of the bones and blood and organs had been removed from his body and he was now just an empty skin sack, folded up in a box. For at LEAST 7/8 years, that is what I thought cremation was. And it horrified me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 07:42:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my god, I'm so sorry you had to go through that!!! It was...definitely a process for me to get diagnosed. 8 years in fact :( I ended up having to sob and beg for help, for them to take me seriously. Then, In addition to Endo, I have extremely severe vaginismus, so pelvic exams were impossible. It ended up coming down to process of elimination/if a certain medication worked. Our current doctor is very nice though, not forcing paps and being very conscious of our gender/pronouns/name. I'm really sorry your friend and you have to go through that, it is awful...I hope you someday find a good doctor who will listen to you and take you seriously </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 06:23:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This honestly means so much to me, thank you tbh 💛 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 05:15:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Purple hair crew! Yay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 05:07:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so sorry to hear that, but I also 110% understand. I wish both him and you the best, I'm so glad you have each other as a support system! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 04:39:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hard agree on the gendered languages/resources (a recent post was actually what inspired me to make this post, as saying that "women are the only ones that suffer from this disease" felt very isolating to me). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 04:37:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I honestly suggest you check our r/egg_irl - it is a very loving and accepting community, but also a fun community, filled with people who are in a very similar position to you with very similar feelings! I wish you the very best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Any fellow non-women? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 04:32:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just curious, any fellow non-women (nonbinary, trans masc, trans men, etc) here that suffer from endo? I know from personal experience that suffering from endo made my gender dysphoria worse by tenfold. I was curious if there were others here and what your experiences were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 17:41:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First of all, please do not feel bad about struggling to do these things. It is very common for people with mental health issues to struggle with this - I most certainly do. I would suggest taking it one step at a time. Showers are probably the hardest - get some baby wipes to clean yourself up occasionally if need be. Dry shampoo is also a miracle. Changing clothes I also know can be very difficult. I would say the important thing is to at least change your underwear once a day, this will definitely help you to at least feel a little better. The only thing I will say, is that it is probably best to at least brush your teeth once a day - it will not only help them to not hurt, but it will improve your mental health a bit. Just be patient with yourself, work yourself up to bigger tasks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 16:05:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah sorry ;;; I got diagnosed a few years back and am not as familiar with terminology as I should be...he probably said the right thing I wasn't paying the best of attention. But thank you for the resources! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 13:48:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a mood ;;; I used to have two heating pads that I'd plug in and sandwich myself in between, as I had both stomach cramps and horrific back pain (at one point I even got some burns/discoloration in my skin because I had the heat way too high). Much love to you, hope you feel a bit better soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nosebleeds? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 13:46:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't had a period since July of 2017 (thanks to Norethindrone), but I'm honestly a bit curious about this! Whenever I had a period, I would get a series of severe nosebleeds, all of which were most certainly not normal nosebleeds (as the blood acted exactly the same as period blood). My doctor made the assumption that my endo has actually travelled so far to end up in my sinuses (which at the time I believed was also a major cause for my having chronic sinusitis, though my having Lupus and Fibro could have also played into this). I'm just very curious if anyone else had/has period nosebleeds with their periods due to their endo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 04:56:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like diet can somewhat help with inflammation, if there are other issues at play (ie chronic pain conditions like Lupis or things like Chrons/IBS) but I never really noticed any diet to help my Endo back before I was put on Norethindrone. Best advice is to take vitamins, drink water/things like gatorade(to replenish electrolytes), and to eat things you know will be easy on you ESP during your period (soups I have found are a rather safe bet, same with crackers and oddly hummus). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 02:01:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I still had periods, I had to use the extra thick extra long ones with wings. I have vaginismus so tampons were a no go for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 01:56:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww!!! A very sweet pic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 01:56:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm nonbinary as well :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 22:19:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have psychosis with delusions, so too many to count lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 18:53:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Paprika </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 18:44:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A rice cooker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 18:43:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aloe vera! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 18:42:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aloe vera! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 18:34:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love your hair!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 17:57:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm glad you are alive :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 17:39:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Glad you're having a better day today! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 17:39:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very! Tbh I was not a fan of the idea of birth control at first, but Norethindrone absolutely has saved my life. Haven't had a period since July of 2017! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 17:16:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love the piercings!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 17:15:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My thoughts exactly, this is definitely helping me to get through the day! <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 17:11:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! The call center life is a glamorous one haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 17:05:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you haha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 17:04:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so happy for you!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 16:48:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably Danny Phantom, Kim Possible as a close second. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Decided to join in on the fun, hello! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 16:45:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dear road construction workers, 6am is not a great time to start air-hammering the road outside my apartment </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 16:34:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have such bad noise sensitivity, and for the past 2 days, some road construction dudes have started tearing up the road outside my apartment at about 6am, it is so loud, impossible to tune out, it especially sucks because I can't even take a nap today because I'm at work all day today, I'm just...so tired ugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 04:49:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you ;;; I have been looking at them, the few I called though that supposedly took my insurance apparently lied on that website, talking on the phone is a lot for me so I am just trying to narrow things down a bit, so I don't have to call 100 different places to find a good one, ya feel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 04:45:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah its just a normal rectangular, built into the wall tub. It's just so weird, I've used this same brand for years, never an issue...I think the tub just may not be magnetic at all. When I get paid next I will definitely be looking into some sort of solution to this, I feel so silly having a breakdown over a shower curtain lol ;;; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 02:44:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> #1 don't call me dear. #2 how cis people/the general public views trans people is on them, not on people that don't conform to binary standards. Saying "Well cis people are being transphobic towards us because someone is using neopronouns or identifies with a different gender other than girl or boy," is stupid, and is misplacing the blame. Place the blame of people being transphobic/not "taking trans people seriously" on those people, not trans people. The whole "needing to be diagnosed as trans to be trans" is a whole nother issue, I won't go into it here. But maybe read some studies on trans stuff that is actually modern and wasn't written prior to the 1990s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 02:10:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hard agree. What a person majors in, especially in undergrad, tells you literally nothing about said person, it's so annoying when people automatically place stereotypes on you when they find out what you majored in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 02:06:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If other peoples' identities are effecting you, by them simply existing, that is a YOU problem, not a problem for anyone else, least of all the people that are simply trying to exist - signed someone who is also trans who also has diagnosed gender dysphoria ✌️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 00:12:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See mine has magnets! So I thought this wouldn't be an issue! But I don't think this tub is made out of a material they can stick to unfortunately, might buy some velcro strips to stick to the sides instead, see if that will help a bit at least lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Good psychiatrist in the Kentuckiana area? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 00:11:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live just over the bridge in Jeffersonville. I'm wondering if anyone knows of a good psychiatrist in the Kentuckiana area that takes anthem blue cross/blue shield, and preferably that specializes in things such as OCD and psychosis (including medication management)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My shower curtain is triggering me. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 23:58:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Need to vent - I believe my previous Psychiatrist diagnosed me incorrectly </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 04:39:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Need to vent - I believe my previous psychiatrist diagnosed me incorrectly

Just to make sure my post doesn't get removed, I'm not asking for anyone to diagnose me or anything like that, I just desperately needed a place to vent about what I'm currently going through, while I am in a moment of clarity. Also, this will probably be long, I'm a former English major and terribly long-winded.

In May of 2019 I was dxed with dissociative identity disorder. Previous to that, I was dxed with OCD and a mood disorder (unspecified) all by the same psychiatrist at my school. It was easy to accept OCD - it has been something I have suffered with as far back as I can remember. The mood disorder kinda made sense, I was just like "ok" because yeah I do boomerang around from mania and depression. The DID however, threw me for a loop. My doc said he "first suspected things when you [myself] began using "we" to describe yourself". I never noticed such things. I also mentioned dissociating and memory loss, which also apparently spurred on this diagnosis. After being diagnosed, it was like my alters came out of the woodworks, voices I thought were my own had tangible personalities, they have been very Present since that diagnosis.

But now...about a year and a half later, I have began to wonder, if perhaps I was misdiagnosed. Because...I have started to notice other things: My inability to focus on anything; my struggles with keeping my apt clean/personal hygiene; the voices I always "considered" my alters just always being present, as well as other sounds that I'm sure aren't really there; paranoia; specifically, my wake up call has been the job I was recently hired at, a call center. At this call center, every call is recorded, I occasionally listen back to my own calls to see how they went...and I began noticing, how...all over the place my speech is. Between run on sentences, repeating the same thing over and over again several times, even full on "word salad", as I re-listened to my recordings, I suddenly began to become concerned. To analyze things. This past week, I suddenly realized...I also have some pretty major delusions. I won't go into them too in depth as I don't want to trigger anyone, but it has to do with ghosts/demons/superpowers.

I have also been having increasingly vivid episodes of psychosis, typically tied to my OCD, but I've had OCD since I was a toddler, it has never been this bad. It also suddenly occurred to me, that all of this has been getting worse in the past few years, basically since I turned 19. Before then, I had OCD and depression yes, memory loss and some delusions yes, but nothing at all to this extreme.

I just feel like my whole world is confused rn. I still have these voices which seem like real, formed people. I am officially dxed with DID. But this past week especially, with everything getting dramatically worse, and that triggering a moment of clarity...I just suddenly am feeling so topsy turvy.

As a quick disclaimer, as soon as I had this kind of realization, I made an appt to see a local psychiatrist, which will indeed be taking place this week. I made notes so if I fall back into delusions and stuff, I will at least have that. I just...really needed to vent, because these past few years have been a lot, and possibly being dxed wrong and that having worsened things really freaks me out...Nobody has to answer but...was anyone dxed wrong at first? Or it took them a while to get dxed with something on the schizophrenia spectrum? Or does anyone with schizophrenia have a dissociative disorder as well? I'm sorry for venting again I just...feel lost and scared rn. Trying desperately to maintain this clarity until I can talk to a psychiatrist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 04:32:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get the fuck off this subreddit you gross fucking troll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 13:31:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If we're talking literally, back when I was 17, my car's steering malfunctioned when I was driving down a country road, it ended up rolling three times into a corn field, about 50-100 yards from the road. A farmer from a nearby house saw what happened and ran out to me. My car was on its passenger side, there was no way for me to climb out except through the drivers side window that my elbow (now with huge lacerations on it) had bust through. He actually climbed up onto the car, reached in and helped to pull me out, before calling an ambulance for me. I never learned his name, but without him, who knows how long it would have taken for help to arrive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 13:27:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Be firm with your doctors about your endometriosis and chronic pain symptoms otherwise it will take you a decade to get any diagnoses." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 13:21:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would honestly say any mental disorder that isn't simply anxiety and depression. So many are deeply stigmatized, with people not truly understanding how severe and debilitating they can be, how much they can truly effect someone's life. OCD, DID, Bipolar disorders, personality disorders (in particular cluster B), Schizophrenia, other forms of psychosis, and especially addiction, everyone has such preconceived notions about all of these things, most of which are not even close to accurate, which further stigmatizes these disorders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 13:14:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Mindhunter" on Netflix for sure, interesting take on the genre, amazing acting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 05:27:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been in a downward spiral for especially these last 3 years, it was only recently at my job (I work in a call center), listening back on recordings of my calls, that my speech often descends into run-on sentences, repeating the same thing several times, and just full on words salad, that it suddenly struck me that maybe hearing voices and believing I have the powers to speak to ghosts and that I have inter-dimensional demons following me maaay not be normal, heh. But at least yeah, i realize it now, hopefully I can get it under control quickly. *fingers crossed* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 05:17:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This was me until I started experiencing hallucinations and delusions this past year, recently experiencing "disorganized thoughts and speech", came to the realization this past week that my fears may be coming true... (Made an apt as soon as I came to this realization, we'll see). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I think my former psychiatrist might have gotten my diagnoses wrong... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 13:26:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was diagnosed in 2017 (aged 19) with OCD and a mood disorder unspecified (psychiatrist believed it to be a bipolar disorder, but could not determine which as my experiences were very varied over the years). Then, in 2019 (aged 21) I was diagnosed with DID. It's been a long journey to try and accept that diagnosis - while I feel like it fit in many aspects, I was still a bit unsure. But I trusted my doctor.

Now I'm not so sure. While I do feel like my diagnosis of OCD is correct...I am starting to believe that my dxes of bipolar disorder and DID may not be accurate...

To explain, I have been having increasingly bad issues since my diagnosis of DID with the "hearing voices" aspects of my "DID" in addition to having worse and worse issues with my memory. My ability to focus has completely evaporated, my ability to complete any normal tasks has degraded, I've become increasingly paranoid and my OCD has gotten worse as a result of this, and I've also noticed that at work (I work in a call center) my speech is...very quick and disjointed (like something happens between my brain and my mouth, like my mouth is being possessed). Additionally, I have had so so so many issues sleeping in the past few years that have gotten increasingly worse; and when I can sleep its just...extremely vivid dreams that I sometimes struggle to separate from reality.

Basically, I'm pretty sure I'm developing schizophrenia or at least something on that spectrum. (To clarify so this post doesn't get removed, I'm not asking for a diagnosis, what I need advice on is down below)

I've been trying to ignore all of this but it's getting increasingly worse. After having a horrible nightmare this morning, I finally searched up a mental health facility in my area to see if I can begin treatment/therapy again...but how on EARTH do I broach the subject of my former psychiatrist's diagnosis being wrong? I know psychiatrists can get super defensive about this sort of thing and like I don't want to act like I know better than them and am "self diagnosing" stuff, but like I just had a moment of clarity/realization this morning about all this and...yeah. Any advice on what to do in this situation would be very very helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 05:03:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you have an aneurism buddy? He wasn't even talking about that he was being sexist and homophobic, stfu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 22:30:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much!!! I transported him to the bushes outside on my break! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This leggy boi was hanging out on my desk today, super chill dude, but what is he? (Located in Southern Indiana) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 22:21:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-22 05:46:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is "Chacarron" by El Chombo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 23:29:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For ideas on who to add to Miitopia/tomodachi life, since Kevin was wanting some: Vin Diesel and Tommy Wiseau </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 15:43:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. If he tries, I know I and many others will make sure he fails. He should get used to his fake persona of being poor because he's never making another cent again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 15:36:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why is he even still trying to have a career? He should get off the internet entirely, never get back on here again, never show his face again, let alone try to have a career. He should crawl back to the sewers he came from and disappear forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 19:07:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that reddit is full of such snowflakes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-05 06:03:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I found that out, but they posted it today on their Twitter, they knew the statement they were making by doing that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-05 05:54:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Imagine simping for a bar, pretty pathetic m8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 23:58:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He should delete his channel, all his social medias, leave the internet, pay reparations to the people he has hurt, and check himself into an inpatient mental health facility and get some fucking help because he can fucking afford it. That is what would be best for everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A couple clown doll commissions I completed this past week! They’re girlfriends 🌈 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 15:16:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A couple clown doll commissions I completed this past week! They’re girlfriends 🌈 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 16:12:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 02:30:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All cryptids are gay, so you aren’t allowed in this community anymore. Bye! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 15:59:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Signal boosted on Facebook! Let’s get this sweet baby a home by tonight ❤️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rainbow worms for Pride 🌈 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 15:03:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> rainbow worms 🌈 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 01:02:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 10 baby rainbow worms for Pride Month </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 01:01:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 02:50:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Get Your Own Rainbow Worm](etsy.com/listing/809694978)
: etsy.com/listing/809694978 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 01:59:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [There is a full on wikipedia about him ](http://www.bloomingpedia.org/wiki/Uriah_Clouse) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I’m a queer toymaker doing a giveaway for this rainbow worm friend in honor of Pride Month on my instagram, the @ is rainbow_critter </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 00:20:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 01:52:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just heard that too... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 22:07:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are correct, the cops have been disrupting many peaceful protests, making them violent by shooting peaceful protesters with rubber bullets and spraying tear gas. Its the cops fault (as well as undercover neo nazis) that any violence has happened, thank you for pointing that out so eloquently </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 21:10:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ??? I am not sharing any rumors, I’m sharing the fear-mongering lies a local politician posted, so protesters are aware and can be safe. Read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 20:06:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Arming yourself against a unarmed people participating in a peaceful protest against racism, IS a violent threat you absolute troglodyte, don’t pull that “MAH SECOND AMENDMENT” bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 18:37:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wasn’t really sure who to report this to. I was hoping people here would know what to do, and to also get the word out to the brave protesters protesting today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-04 07:30:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much 🌈 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i made 3 striped friends with funky arms </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-04 05:46:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 22:04:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t want to seem super tinfoil hat, but at the exact same time At&t and Verizon were having problems, you look at the outage map, and its all the major cities protests have been taking place in. I’m not normally a conspiracy theorist, but it all feels suspicious as hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 07:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> rude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 00:03:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> instagram.com/rainbow_critter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I’m a queer toymaker currently doing a giveaway in honor of pride, for this rainbow worm friend I made, if you want to check it out! Link in comments 🌈 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 00:02:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hello! I am a queer toymaker and I am currently doing a giveaway on my instagram to win this rainbow worm friend, in celebration of Pride. My @ is rainbow_critter ! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-02 04:58:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I’m doing a giveaway for this rainbow worm friend on my instagram, if anyone is interested! The @ is rainbow_critter ! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-02 04:44:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 01:34:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes you do, esp if they are going to monetize their video, which is what they did (and why Trevor was upset). They were profiting off of something they did not own, while also violating Trevor’s VERY WELL KNOWN wishes to not make Sirenhead into another lame scp/give it an unapproved backstory. Which is obviously wrong. You wouldn’t do that to a random artist’s human original character, its not right to do it with Siren head. Want to do something without the artist’s permission? Fine, but you get what you get. This person is playing the victim and acting pathetic and entitled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 01:24:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Siren head is Trevor’s creation and so many people have been making videos/games/etc about Siren head without Trevor’s permission/without even naming him. Even this reddit doesn’t give any credits to him whatsoever, which is gross btw. While I do think he should have reached out to your first before issuing the copystrike, he created Siren head and he its his right to moderate what Siren head content exists 🤷 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 03:04:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you!!! And I actually have an etsy shop with all 10 of these friends posted on it! It is [Rainbow Critter](etsy.com/shop/RainbowCritter) on Etsy 🌈🌈🌈 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 03:03:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you 🌈🌈🌈 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> my little collection of hand made, ooak clown dolls (all crocheted by me) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 19:33:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 19:30:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As an additional little note - I am aware that the stitches appear “loose” - I purposefully made them that way, as I liked how the loose stitches looked much better than tighter stitches ✌️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 10 finished clown doll friends 🌈 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 19:28:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> canon facts about siren head from the creator himself </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 21:51:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i crocheted a little friend (character design credits to the original creator of siren head @/slimyswampghost on Twitter) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 21:49:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 21:22:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wanted to add on here - that there is no official siren head game, according to @/slimyswampghost - all games involving siren head have actually stolen the character of siren head from @/slimyswampghost for their own profits. I just wanted to let people know so they do not support thieves, and so they CAN support the actual, original creator of siren head, who is an amazing artist and a very cool person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i crocheted siren head ( credits to @/slimyswampghost on Twitter, aka the original creator of siren head) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 21:19:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 06:56:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Funny, already got a lot of presales so...also maybe learn when and when not to give constructive criticism (ie, maybe not when somebody posts several completed projects that took them weeks to make and they say they are very proud of them). Bye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> After lots and lots of hard work, my toy shop will be opening on Etsy on Sunday! I’m so proud of the 10 one of a kind clown dolls I made for the launch 🌈 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-22 19:03:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> a birthday present for my dad (this little guy is from his work’s logo) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 06:42:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 19:57:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Birdman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-12 23:34:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love this! Such a funky pattern! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-29 14:26:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im PRETTY sure it was hannah montana, but maybe it was another one of those live action kids shows that was around that time instead? not 100% sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-29 14:06:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my friends dad dressed up as the hair drier monster from this one episode of wizards of waverly place to prank us, so we pranked him back by trashing his bathroom, and long story short, i ended up slipping on the soapy floor and slamming my face into the door frame which resulted in my lip getting stuck in my braces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-29 14:05:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sharp objects. a show that was half-triggering and half-healing for me. watched it about 8 times from start to finish last summer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-29 14:03:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a raccoon. spayed/neutered, with rabies shots of course, so it wouldnt be angry, horny, and diseased. raccoons are some of the sweetest little critters ive ever handled...they’re like a mixture of a dog and a ferret with major gremlin energy. so fucking soft, so curious, and so chattery...and their LITTLE HANDS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-29 13:58:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “Demand your gynecologist tests you for endometriosis NOW. Not when you’re 19. NOW. You do not want to suffer pointlessly for the next 6 years you little bitch. Also you’re trans, so thats part of the reason you hate your body.” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 14:42:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the upside down girl threatened to kill herself before doing so quite violently in front of me. keep in mind i was very young at this point, had no clue what i was doing, and was also sick/feverish to top it off. ive seen her a few times since but noped out immediately. i think at one point she said her name was emily, or something else very common. she was young, around my age the first time i saw her but she hasn’t aged since. idk what she is exactly. doesn’t feel like a human or ghost but doesn’t feel particularly malicious. just generally frightening.

the shadow man has never done anything, but hes always there (basically why i havent projected for years now). hes very intimidating, ominous, definitely not human/ghost. i used to say he was a demon, but again, as scary as he was, i felt absolutely no evilness radiating off of him. i describe him more like an entity now, definitely something supernatural, but...idk what. dont really know his purpose either, but he followed me to college and the last time i saw him i felt oddly protective auras radiating off of him? he still freaked me out tho so ive stayed away from it for about 3 years now, since i can control when i project or not now (wasnt able to when i was young, because i didnt know what i was doing). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 13:41:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> astral projection is kind of scary because of the shadow man and the upside down girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 13:40:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no bra, no binder, no pants - its a t shirt and boxer briefs kinda life im living right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 13:39:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the basilisk in harry potter and the chamber of secrets movie is not a snake, but a sheltopusik (a legless lizard) because it is animated to have the same type of scales on its stomach as are on its back (snakes have different scales on their bellies than their backs) and it was animated to have eyelids (snakes do not have eyelids). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 13:28:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so i was kayaking with my friend in florida and this mama manatee and her calf swam up to my kayak. i put my hand in the water, and the mama manatee sniffed it, before nuzzling my hand, so i gave her a nice little pat on the head. she and her calf then swam on their merry way. after we finished kayaking i returned with my friend to the cottage her family were renting and i told them the story. i was then informed that touching wild manatees is illegal. which is a darn shame, because they’re just happy little sea cows that want nice pats sometimes!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 13:21:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dont refer to women or girls as “females”. ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 13:20:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> covering your hand in glue, letting it dry, then pealing it off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 13:14:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> become a mushroom farmer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 13:13:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i threw out my back picking up a newborn kitten. i was 12. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 13:11:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mom does a couple things. 1, she stalks me on the “find my friend” iphone app, and any time i try to turn it off she gets pissed at me and harasses me until i turn it back on. 2, she expects me to text her back immediately, no matter the day or time - I suffer from both insomnia and narcolepsy, so I tend to fall asleep at weird times, and every time i wake up, I always wake up to a flurry of angry/panicked texts which...makes it even more difficult to get real rest when i DO sleep because im paranoid about her texting me.

for context - im 22, i live on my own, i go to college...etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 13:05:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [https://www.volunteermatch.org](https://www.volunteermatch.org)

a lovely website where you can find opportunities to volunteer both in your community and remotely! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 13:01:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Snapchat and Whatsapp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 12:59:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> any time my friends hand me their phones to show me something i am HORRIFIED by the fact they are covered in greasy fingerprints...whats even worse is you KNOW they are on their phones when they go to the toilet like PLZ. CLEAN YOUR PHONE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 12:57:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> probably “call me kevin” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 12:55:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> midwest emo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 12:54:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “grandpa was cremated” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 12:50:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> about 5-6 years ago, i started following this artist because they were one of the big steven universe artists at the time and drew my favorite character a lot. they reblogged lots of peoples art all the time, but i usually didnt pay it any mind. one day they reblogged a drawing of a sword that i thought was pretty cool, so i checked out the artist. turns out she was working on a webcomic with her longtime partner - i fell in love with the webcomic, and on a whim, messaged them both to tell them how much i loved the comic. they both messaged me back, and were so sweet, but the partner and i just...casually kept talking. and talking. and talking. All these years later, the two of them are married, im best friends with the both of them, and the partner and i talk on a daily basis :) My life would be so so different if I hadn’t followed that random Steven Universe artist haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 12:43:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the fact that some people don’t clean their phones regularly really really really bugs me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 12:34:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i was at a sleepover with a group of friends and we were watching this hannah montana halloween special and we all legitimately got terrified of the villain who was basically a short person with a hairdryer? anyway, the dad of the girl whose house we were staying at pranked us by walking around outside at night with a hairdryer and a cloak, scaring the living hell out of us, so we decided to prank him back. we went to his bathroom and basically trashed it, shaving cream on the toilet seat, makeup on the mirror, and then fucking CARLIE thought it was a good idea to coat the floor in liquid soap which, you know, is slippery. one of my friends started to fall and pushed me, which caused my face to slam into the doorframe, which caused my upper lip to get stuck in my braces. all my friends started screaming and crying as i just laid there in a puddle of blood and soap, confused about what was going on. the dad ended up waking up and had to come pry my lip from my braces, and i was stuck with a bump in the middle of my lip the size and color of a grape for a month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 12:23:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> took the words right out of my mouth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 12:19:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a hot and friendly elf npc whose sexuality is ambiguous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 12:16:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dark Shows:
* Sharp Objects
* Mindhunter
* Castle Rock

Funny Shows:
* Broad City
* Letterkenny
* Parks and Rec

Food Shows:
* Great British Bake Off
* Chopped
* Hells Kitchen/Kitchen Nightmares </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 12:12:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> take your pick:
* 3 pet cockroaches
* a framed picture of a Sim
* a crocheted elephant
* a vibrator shaped like a rubber duck
* a collection of sticks i thought were cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 11:55:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sym Bionic Titan - it never should have ended in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> WIP crocheted elephant (no pattern!) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 06:17:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 13:52:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> id recommend hopping on popular, active ARGs to start! off the top of my head, iamsophie and Dad (both mainly on youtube) are very active right now with huge communities (Dad in particular has been doing dj livestreams nearly everyday (lol) and has a discord that is very active). them being popular = big communities to help solve puzzles, and big youtubers (nexpo, reignbot, etc) that do deep plot analysises. that way, you are able to interact with others and begin to develop puzzle-solving/plot-solving skills.

one thing i definitely had lots of struggles with in the beginning was deciphering codes, because its a lot of guesswork, can be frustrating. ive been kind of practicing with this app called PlayTheX, where you solve codes and stuff every week, and it has definitely helped to improve my skills, so i highly recommend it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 13:40:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really REALLY think about whether you really want/need to go to college or not, especially right out of high school. There is no shame in starting a job right away, taking a year to travel, going to a trade school, going to community college, etc. Take time to decide where you want to go in life, what your goals are, what in life you enjoy. you don’t need to rush into college right out of high school! people that tend to do that often change their majors several times, many drop out due to burnout, and they are left with major debt and nothing to show for it. be patient - life is not a race. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 13:35:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Patience! Avoid physical punishments - operate more on a positive reinforcement system. I know its hard right now, but when you’re able, make sure to get him used to other dogs, people, and especially children.
Honestly, I recommend you look up tutorials on youtube about self-training  a service/therapy dog - golden retrievers respond really well to that sort of training! It will help him to be calm in public, listen to you, and to create a very strong bond between you and him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 13:23:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a 5 way tie:
* interstellar (very smart, makes me cry, amazing visuals)
* mother! (unique concept, amazing acting, amazing visuals)
* arrival (very smart, that plot twist, amy adams)
* hereditary (toni fucking collette, the visuals, the soundtrack)
* the prince of egypt (the visuals, the voice acting, the soundtrack...everything)

all that being said, my favorite movie ever is Hanna - because of Saoirse Ronan, the visuals, the soundtrack, the unique concept...i think if they had a bigger budget/better pacing towards the end, it easily could have been number one here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 13:13:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the best “classics” are classic short stories in my opinion. “a good man is hard to find,” by flannery o’connor, “where are you going, where have you been” by joyce carol oates, and “the yellow wallpaper” by charlotte perkins gilman are all excellent, if you are into rather dark stories. additionally, take your choice of poe’s short stories. as for books, ones i am partial to are a clockwork orange, fahrenheit 451, and 1984. don’t waste your time reading anything by virginia woolf, thats my best advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 13:05:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i had these recurring dreams from my childhood (around 3rd-5th grade) where these aliens with paper thin, white, flaky skin; detachable jaws; and long sharp teeth, would break into my house to kidnap me and take me to their planet. i also vividly remember that they could steal the skin of humans and walk around in them, and that they all had biblical names (Josef, David, Eve, etc). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 12:59:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it certainly can be. i personally love writing and editing (granted im a writing major in college) and actually feel really relaxed doing both things! i just was chucking out a simplified version of the “publishing process lesson” my writing professor gave all of us in his class </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 12:56:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> actually pretty good. i no longer drink alcohol (i found out i was allergic and it was literally killing me, so that was pretty good motivation), i’ve been working on crocheting a lap blanket for this rad nonprofit, and i should be starting a new job in a new city in the next month! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 12:52:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> different highs by different means.

vaping a kingpen on a vape pen, its a very mild high. basically makes me less anxious and calms my chronic pain...but i am still fully functional, able to drive, etc. a nice easy come down

smoking from a bowl/bong/joint...depends. usually i feel really high right away, but not for long. i get extra hungry, and usually i get pretty horny when im coming down. when i come down too much though, it feels rough, so i usually try to fall asleep before i fully do.

edibles...only when i want to get really fucked up and be out of commission for hours on end. swallowing feels weird, time feels weird, i always focus too much on my breathing...best thing to get high with to just like zone out and marathon a tv show like broad city or play minecraft for hours on end. absolutely have to go to sleep before i start coming down though, otherwise i WILL panic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 12:38:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Read a lot. Gain inspiration. Start writing. Don’t stop writing. Have an interesting plot, interesting characters, etc. MAKE SURE, you can write a summary of your story using this format:

“When [inciting incident] happens to [character/s] at [a location], [character/s] must go on [journey] to complete [quest].”

Finish writing. Edit it. Edit it again. Edit it again. If possible, get a second (or third or fourth) pair of eyes on it. Find an agent that represents books in your genre. Write a pitch letter. Be rejected a lot. Don’t give up. Eventually be accepted. Work with agent to find editor/publishing company. Rewrite. Edit. Edit again. Edit again. Go through lots of legal hoops. 3-5 years after you’ve began this process, you will be published.

Or you can self publish and hope for the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 12:27:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i think you mean Kate Marsh* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 12:26:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ive bonded really well with both my cat and my cockroaches, neither hiss at me anymore even when they’re pissed off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 12:24:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you believe you are an entity that isn’t exactly human, isn’t exactly an animal...simply a Critter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 12:21:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> meet the robinsons for the ps2, no joke. i was really into movie videogames when i was young, but this one was something else - lots of unique game mechanics, additional lore that wasn’t in the movie, and actually incredibly difficult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 12:14:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pretty corny, but my group of friends and i had “choreographed” a dance to “come on eileen” in like 7th grade and danced it at every single school dance. by the time of our last school dance of our senior year, literally every single person in our grade (that was there) knew it and we all danced it together. it was such a cool moment, to see so many people from different cliques just letting loose and all vibing together for once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 12:08:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my grandpa died when i was 5, and my family told me he got cremated and was in a shoebox in my aunt’s living room. i did not know what cremation was, so naturally, my 5 year old mind assumed all his bones and organs and fluids had been taken out of his body to be repurposed and his skin sack had been folded up and put in the shoe box. I believed this until i was 11, when avatar (the blue people movie) came out and it showed a character being cremated in the beginning. so...i guess you could say my “moment” lasted about 6 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 12:05:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cilantro. just take a bundle of it and eat it like a rabbit. best snack ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 11:59:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dont starve </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 11:57:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> will definitely pick up some seeds from the grocery store the next time i have to go out on a toilet paper/cereal run! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 11:56:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a zombie apocalypse scenario was happening, but instead of turning into a zombie if you got bit, you would slowly turn into a velociraptor, and the only thing to break this “curse” was true loves kiss. i got bit and was laying in a coffin, slowly turning into a velociraptor, as friends lined up to kiss me to see if we were secretly soulmates. suddenly, saoirse ronan was there and she kissed me and cured me. this all took place in a snow globe that was on the back of a moose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 11:50:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hetalia; bad memories, having had written lots of bad fanfiction on an account i now have no access to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 11:49:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i adopted three little polish girls and we lived in a cottage in the mountains picking berries, reading books, and making flower crowns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 11:48:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> downloaded kik. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 11:45:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> go to lowes and buy some plants, im behind on my spring-plant-hoarding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 11:39:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> less is more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 11:38:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i procrastinate too much and my mouth goes crooked when i speak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 11:37:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> going to move my plant into a new pot, going to spruce up my cockroaches’ home, going to do the dishes, going to roleplay a mad max scenario with my friend, going to play minecraft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 11:34:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “how to grow psychedelic mushrooms”
“where to watch moominvalley for free”
“how to make cookies without vanilla extract, brown sugar, eggs, and butter” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 12:24:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the thing is, none of us know who you are, and at least i, personally, am here with non-judgmental ears. we don’t want to “ruin” you, ESP if this illegal thing you did didn’t cause harm to other people. if you don’t want to talk details publicly, thats fine, we just won’t be able to help you to accept/overcome your emotions surrounding what you did. tbh, if you want to chat privately about it, i could do that (again, nonjudgmental ears). but again, that would just be my advice rather than getting many opinions on the matter. i’ll leave this alone for now, and if you want to chat, let me know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 12:16:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if no one was harmed by your actions aside from the one person being upset, then i honestly think you would be alright speaking a few more details here tbh. we might be able to help you more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 12:05:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i saw you mentioned in another comment that what you did was illegal. i won’t ask specifics as you don’t want to talk about specifics publicly, but i do have to ask: was anyone harmed by your actions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 11:49:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i basically agree with what the others have said - confront the issue head on, talk about it with someone you trust. i think i saw you said you were a kid, so talking about what has been on your mind with a trusted adult is advisable, rather than talking about this with one of your peers, especially if whatever this is, is as serious as you are making it out to be on here. if something happened that perhaps caused harm to you, id even recommend contacting authorities or someone in a position of power like a teacher.

trying to simply forget things, to suppress things, especially things that are bothering you or were even possibly traumatic, will only hurt you in the long run. its better to deal with things sooner rather than trying to confront them later, or to not deal with them at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 11:42:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i have been. i have lupus and asthma, general kidney and liver issues, and have had pneumonia 5 times in the last 4 years (two of those times coming after i got my first pneumonia prevention shot). i may be 22, but stepping outside for me right now is basically a death sentence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 11:33:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> im allergic to alcohol and banana boat sunscreen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 11:32:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i crocheted an elephant, might tattoo my leg tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 11:31:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 11:29:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> very slobbery and his lip briefly got stuck on my braces :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 11:27:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Paprika </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 11:27:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i have been able to accomplish tasks i have been putting off for months. also a i crocheted an elephant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 11:26:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> doing alright, im usually quite isolated and lonely, so this hasn’t changed much. would definitely be in better spirits with some weed and a computer that doesn’t feel like its going to catch fire every time i run minecraft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 11:24:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> PS2. the only console i think i have ever got 100% completion on a game (granted it was Pixar’s Cars, but it took me months). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 11:23:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i would love to see a Wes Anderson cover of Midsommar. The Shining. basically a Wes Anderson cover of any and every horror film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 11:20:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> jewelry from claires, cilantro as a snack, the youtube channel “Dad” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 11:18:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my response: the water is worthless when both itself and the creatures it contains want to kill you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 11:15:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sleep paralysis/maybe astral projecting(?) when i was around 7 and had a really high fever. first time i saw both the shadow man and the upside down girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 07:52:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I LOVE HIM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 21:49:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> kind of defeats the purpose of an ARG to blatantly be like “THIS IS AN ARG FOLLOW ME”. Like unless this is a Seventybroad situation, doing this sort of thing is pretty cheap. I recommend you watch [this video](https://youtu.be/ipbyb6WftC4). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 21:02:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> probably a trap. in my experience, you will likely find yourself falling down an unending vertical hallway that is lit up so bright that you cannot see what it actually looks like. falling and falling and falling until you manage to reach out and catch yourself on another window, which will likely be the same window you climbed out of in the first place. not worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 11:49:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i feel my own story of coming out to myself is rather odd. when i was 13ish, i got involved in a massive harry potter roleplay group through a link i got sent on omegle. this girl and i’s characters became a couple in this roleplay, which continued on for YEARS, with all of us getting to know each other rather well. eventually this girl confessed that she liked ME as a real human person, around when i was 15. and i was basically like...i dont hate that idea. so thats how wee lil me realized Oh im Bi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 11:46:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i crocheted an elephant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 11:44:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> janice from friends, because you’d want to hide inside your house away from that voice too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 11:42:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> certainly feels like it sometimes ahah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 11:41:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bill-wi-the-science-fi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 11:37:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when i was 5 i was told my grandpa had been cremated, but i did not know what cremation was...all i knew was that grandpa was in a shoebox in my aunt’s living room. so i naturally thought they had sucked all the bones and organs and stuff out of him and folded his skin up like it was laundry and put it in said shoe box. when i eventually found out what cremation actually was about 6 years later, i was understandably shocked, but also relieved that reality was a lot less horrifying than my kindergarten brain had imagined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 11:34:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i have learned how to:
* give amazing puppet shows
* make oatmeal boxes into robots & superheroes
* wear mascot-esque costumes without dying of heat stroke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 11:31:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> anything and everything if you do not fear death </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 11:30:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a nice pair of boots and weed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 11:27:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i have really weird insomnia, struggle to sleep when its dark out for some reason. the second it starts to begin to get light out, though, i conk out as though i have narcolepsy. can hardly stay awake during the day either - i fall asleep in the middle of doing coursework, chatting with friends, watching shows, etc. tldr: i dont have any choice in the matter, my body has all the control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 10:15:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take your pick from the “Magic World of Ania” Polish (?) ARG, tbh. Yeah, its an ARG, but holy shit, the music, the visuals, its creepy as hell. [Here’s the first vid in the series](https://youtu.be/eQNY--Yx-Ac) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 07:16:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this feels very midwestern somehow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
