<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject20</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 21:48:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Los mejores churros son los que venden en carritos en las paradas de metro cuando vuelves a casa tardecillo: churro cubierto de chocolate, relleno de chocolate y te mueres del empalago, 10/10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 21:44:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Carrefour has some good plushies from time to time. I got a 1,2 m? black bear for 12€ a few years back and I saw they had some big plushies but I was in a hurry.
For smaller/locals shops I really can't help ya, sorry. But I'm interested too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 11:51:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo personalmente no las soporto y no entiendo cómo le pueden gustar a nadie, pero tengo amigos que las ven (no se cual es cual). Y sí he intentado verlas, como El Hormiguero, que tampoco le entiendo la gracia :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 11:20:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Copio y pego mi comentario de otro hilo sobre el mismo tema:
Si alguien quiere y puede hay un par de santuarios/protectoras que han intentado llevarse todos los que han podido (algunas vienen mencionadas en el artículo). Que yo sepa especialmente [Asociación Alba](https://albaonline.org/), [El Campito - Salvando Peludos](https://www.facebook.com/elcampitosalvandopeludos/) y también se que desde [Fundación Santuario Gaia](https://www.facebook.com/FundacionSantuarioGaia) se llevaron unos 300. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 12:30:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Si alguien quiere y puede hay un par de santuarios/protectoras que han intentado llevarse todos los que han podido (algunas vienen mencionadas en el artículo). Que yo sepa especialmente [Asociación Alba](https://albaonline.org), [El Campito - Salvando Peludos](https://www.facebook.com/elcampitosalvandopeludos/) y también se que desde [Fundación Santuario Gaia](https://www.facebook.com/FundacionSantuarioGaia) se llevaron unos 300. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 17:32:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo con que encienda me vale.

Fuente: el ordenador que me monté en 2013 por 300€ y del que he estado tirando hasta este año. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 17:08:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ¿Has mirado la opción de [Citipaq](https://www.correos.es/ss/Satellite/site/producto-correospaq_online-productos_az/detalle_de_producto-sidioma=es_ES#) de Correos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 10:41:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are you doing, step-bro?
Ese es el chiste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 09:12:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ¿UTBH? No, gracias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 13:53:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tío... ¿Necesitas que te lo explique o algo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 10:27:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 10:27:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much!

That has been very helpful. I wish I could hug you.

Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 09:59:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, tbh I didn't even know about my university before I got in there. You register for whatever degree you want in a specific comunidad autónoma, and then choose between the different comunidades you were accepted in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Econometrics - Simultaneous equations </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 10:24:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 22:17:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, I'm qualified to answer this! I've been vegetarian for the last 10 years.
It's getting easier, en mis tiempos...

Milk: easy, but I think only Mercadona sells unsweetened soy milk, in case you need it for cooking. There are some brands that have more sugar than whatever nut/cereal they use for the milk. You can also get plant-based cream.

Pizza: Papa Jhon's introduced a vegan pizza at the begining of this year, and some smaller places do have a vegan option but it's not common.

This year I started buying vegan cheese in supermarkets, and I love it, I did not had that option (I could only find it in specialized shops or Hipercor, none of those options work living in a small city, as I do).

Meat alternatives aint that good, tbh. The good ones are expensive, but we are getting a little more variety this year for some reason. Nestle has a line, Garden Gourmet, that is pretty good, but I personally avoid that brand.

Mind you, for meat/animal products alternatives, they tend to have egg and/or milk. Until like 3 years ago I couldn't find margerine that had no milk in it, kind of weird.

Don't buy Mercadona's sausages, those taste very bad.

Vegan restaurants: Madrid, Barcelona, Sevilla... you can find them in big cities, but small towns and traditional restaurants (even in Madrid, unless you are in Lavapies or something) here do not have vegetarian option, so you need to specifically ask for it. That's the reason I'm tired of eating tortilla and patatas bravas, that's the only thing they usually have. You can always eat at a kebab anyway, you have plenty of those around.

Traditional spanish food does have lot's of animal products, be aware. Some has lard, so read the labels.

Perceptions...everybody gonna ask you why are you vegan; I'm not, so they usually tell me that they understand, but they do not understand veganism, as it is kind of extreme. But you weont get bullied, if you live in a big city I don't think most people would care tbh, specially the younger ones. Plant-based diets are kind of in the middle of a boom rn in Spain.

Overall, eating vegetarian is archivable. Eating vegan can be done, but unless you live in a big city you are gonna have a hard time eating out (I hope you like salads, remember to always ask if it has tuna or bacon and pray that you don't only get iceberg lettuce and tomato)

Fell free to ask, I may have missed something and I was all over the place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 17:14:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> La cosa es que en España no hay trabajos. Yo he estado buscando cualquier trabajo que me permitiese ir a la universidad a las horas a las que tenía que ir (durante la carrera y a principios de este año) y creo que por no recibir no recibí ni llamadas para decirme que gracias por aplicar pero que no les interesaba.

Es duro trabajar en España cuando tienes pocas horas libres y no tienes experiencia laboral ni contactos, salvo que quieras dedicarte a Deliveroo o alguna cosa de esas, o aceptes trabajos que no te darán ni para pagar el alquiler de una habitación.

Igual espero que si OP decide venir que tenga más suerte, pero mi experiencia en el mercado laboral español ha sido, cuanto menos, frustrante. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Econometrics - Simultaneous equations </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 17:06:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi there.

I'm having trouble with econometrics and I'm looking to see if you guys can help me. I found a problem very similar to the one I have to do, but I cannot understand what's going on. If someone could help me or share any kind of resource to help me out it would be great. Also I'm not 100% sure that this is the right place for this, so please let me know if it isn't!

The problem is available [here](http://www.ugr.es/~jchica/Pagina2/GUIME/Otros%20ejercicios/Simultaneas1.pdf), but I'll paste the info in English here:

Given this model

https://preview.redd.it/jsb8845blio51.png?width=223&format=png&auto=webp&s=c22d7157e71c32b4a15d9f1b06e4432213240711

And this information on the sums of the crossed products

https://preview.redd.it/tsq3ataklio51.png?width=268&format=png&auto=webp&s=0ce9cb7073b17ffd313062bf098c307850b599c3

A) Identify each of the equations in the model

They give this answer:

To identify the model we will create the array (do you guys also call it matrix?) A formed by the parameters structural model

https://preview.redd.it/qqnmqoevlio51.png?width=121&format=png&auto=webp&s=4bc77d6d3594459ec4387f61ac1a9af03a1dc228

First equation:

[\(Range method: p\(A1\)=... identified equation \/\/ order method: e=... overidentified equationequation\)](https://preview.redd.it/r2l966hjmio51.png?width=456&format=png&auto=webp&s=129604d0243a563b551970487ac70cecdb6885c8)

Second equation:

[\(Range method: p\(A2\)=...identified equation\/\/ order method: e2=... exactly identified equation\)](https://preview.redd.it/ff8ar3k5nio51.png?width=470&format=png&auto=webp&s=e37701e4a05e3ac93f3b62bf1a07564b0f2724f7)

I watched a couple videos but I'm bad at math, I haven't actually done math for the last 8 years and I think I did not learn arrays? but mostly I'm having trouble understanding from where the numbers come from. I've done multivariate statistics analysis using SPSS but having to deal with equations is something else.
Sorry for the bad english, my head hurts and I cannot think properly but I'm sure I mess up directly translating some stuff.

And thank you so much for any information on this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 22:34:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Te recomiendo que contactes directamente con los docentes de las asignaturas, ellos te podrán informar mejor. En principio no deberían tener ningún problema, pero cada profesor es un mundo.
Sobre el voluntariado, en el caso concreto que comentas tampoco sabría decirte, así que un poco de lo mismo: contacta con los departamentos de biología/medicina de las universidades a ver qué te cuentan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 22:28:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> El [Goody Cao](https://www.google.com/search?q=goody+cao&client=opera-gx&hs=Dz3&source=lnms&tbm=isch&sa=X&ved=2ahUKEwiIgtTNg_HrAhVFUMAKHaERArQQ_AUoAXoECAwQAw&biw=1325&bih=627#imgrc=Ie9qz8harY0v9M) es el mejor.

Fuente: soy panchita. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 10:43:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, for that price, depending on where you move you can get a 2/3 bedroom apartment for 800€.

I gave a quick look around Idealista and I'll say that a 40-50m2 study can go around  500€ (studies in the center are like 25m2 for that same price). A 2-bedroom, 60m2 apartment can be 650-800€. A room in a shared apartment starts at 250€ (for that price you can get one tiny one without windows in the center), but an okay-is one can be around 500€.

And yes, you can ask for an empty apartment, but that depends on the person renting you the place, I'll say it's a 50/50 chance they can give you an empty one. You are looking for one "sin amueblar", which can be cheaper.

Good luck with the spanish! we know it's hard, so don't be shy and use it as much as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 10:50:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay, first: you need to learn to learn Spanish. That's a pretty basic thing to do, most people over, idk, 40? can't speak English and even if they can speak some English they are not used to it.

You can easily find something like that with your budget. Mind you, most studios are very shitty and small, you can rent a whole aparment for 800€ and live more confortable.
Most (all?) places do have washing machine, as for the elevator that is not always the case, same with AC.


* Will I find it difficult to communicate with landlords if I don't speak Spanish?

 Yes. We only use Spanish to comunicate, or regional languages.

&#x200B;

* Would it be better if I went through a realtor?

That's more expensive but can be an option, I guess.

&#x200B;

* What area would you recommend I look into?

IE University seems to be very much in the city center, so you can move around there. If you are looking for cheaper prices, Properidad is quite close, or around Ventas or Cuatro Caminos. TBH, with your budget (as a single person) you can move wherever you like.



* Are kitchen appliances (fridge, stove, microwave) usually furnished by the landlord in a rental?

Usually.

&#x200B;

* On idealista a lot of posting seem to be furnished. Is this common?

Yes.

&#x200B;

* A lot of postings on idealista seem to also mention multiple bedrooms like [this one](https://www.idealista.com/en/inmueble/90563452/). Is this a roommate situation even though it doesn't say so?

No, that's the whole place. Your link is for a rental in Castello de la Plana, Madrid is a little more expensive than that.

&#x200B;

* What utilities should I expect to pay other than electricity and internet ? How much should I budget? € 100?

Living alone? Maybe, including gas for heating and Internet + phone, around 100-200€, depending on your plan and how much you use them.

&#x200B;

* How long does it usually take to secure a place? Is 10 days enough?

That depends. I was able to rent a room in 2 days but last time it took me 2 months to find a place xd If you want to visit the places I'd recommend for you to think of the worst situation possible, so you can come prepared. Depending on when in January you are coming you can get lucky, as university students (mainly Erasmus) leave to their country, but I don't think we will be having many of those during a pandemic.

&#x200B;

* Is it common to have a washing machine in the apartment?

Yes, each house usually have one.


Excuse my English, but I honestly don't give a fuck if it is badly written. Let me know if you don't understand something, tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 10:30:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Walls are thin.
Source: Live in an adosado, noise from outside is okay but I can hear my neighbor using the stairs as if it was inside my own house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 20:28:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He sacado mi agenda y he añadido los gastos que tenía del mes de febrero, que son el último mes normalillo, de cuando vivía en Madrid con un solo compañero (me costó mucho encontrar habitación). Anyway:
Alquiler: 350€
Gastos (el agua estaba incluida en el alquiler, creo que es solo luz, con Internet serían como 15€ más): 25€

Gas\*: 100€
Abono (tengo menos de 26 años así que pago una tarifa fija): 20€
Papa John's: 11.95€
Mercadona: 29.86€

Lidl: 8.21€ + 4.70€

Churros (?): 3€

Taxi: 9.05

Cervezas: 10€

Normalmente me gasto unos 30€ en comer (vegetariano, todo lo cocino yo, poco o nada procesado); unos 10€ en la frutería del barrio y lo demás en compras de supermercado y algún antojo (y ojo, que yo como mucho), así que de verdad no sé cómo la gente siempre dice que 100€-200€ en comida xd
Sobre los trabajos pues mirate [Infojobs](https://www.infojobs.net/) a ver si encuentras algo para ti. Puedes buscar por data scientist, biólogo, investigador o lo que sea que sepas hacer. Yo creo que lo mejor que puedes hacer es ofrecer clases de inglés o sesiones de conversación.

&#x200B;

\*El recibo llega cada dos meses. Al mes siguiente llegó incluso más alto, así que es cosa de la compañía de gas que nos cobró demás. De normal yo diría que he pagado unos 60€ de gastos de luz, agua, Internet y gas viviendo con otras dos personas, en invierno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 23:58:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Las de Dialnet suelen estar disponible en abierto, creo que ni hace falta registrarte. Lo que pasa es que a veces te redirige a alguna universidad. De todos modos pertenecer a una universidad te suele dar acceso a los contenidos de otras universidades.
Siempre puedes usar [sci-hub.tw/](https://sci-hub.tw/), que es lo que uso yo siempre, la verdad; es más rápido que acceder a través de la universidad. Para libros [http://gen.lib.rus.ec](http://gen.lib.rus.ec) pero está un poco escaso en español. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-05 00:39:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tener pareja no te va a arreglar mágicamente la vida.

Sobre la baja autoestima, eso es cuestión de un profesional cualificado, como un psicólogo, aquí no te vamos a poder ayudar mucho.

La chica no quiere salir contigo, no pasa nada. A otra cosa.

Deberías buscar un grupo de amigos con el que te sientas apoyado y cómodo, quizá a través de un hobby en común o alguna actividad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 13:04:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can buy 2 okay houses/apartments with that amount of money.
I'd advice to get yourself tested on what you are allergic too and then choose a place to live based on that, because Spain is hell for asthma/allergies. Healthcare is free and it [seems](https://www.mscbs.gob.es/pnc/faq/home.htm) it's free to for europeans, but I would advice you to contact your embassy.

Spain is not USA, it's not frowned upon to be single or have no kids; for people your age is not the most common thing but the preassure to be married in Spain is very low compared to USA.
I spent aprox. 650€ living in (a shared flat in) Madrid per month (that includes rent, utilities, food...). It seems Malaga rent is similar to Madrid, so yes, you can live okay-ish with 1000€/month; in fact, [the most common salary in 2017 was 17.482 €/year](https://elpais.com/economia/2019/06/21/actualidad/1561105583_765818.html#:~:text=En%20España%2C%20el%20sueldo%20más,ascendió%20a%2023.646%2C50%20euros). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 12:38:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will talk about that with my doctor, thank you!
I think we are talking about different types of shot! The ones I meant are like a vaccine, you get the alergens inyected so your inmune system stops trying to kill you everytime you are near them (the same happens with the sublingual), and after 4-5 years you shouldn't have a strong allergic reaction; while the shot you say seems more like medication.
I still would advice you to go to the allergologist, at least they will tell you what you are allergic to \^\^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 12:33:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A ver si no me repito.
Durante un tiempo me dio muy fuerte por la música ¿indie? española; no son necesariamente similares a Joe, que me encanta y ya te han hablado de todos los que se me ocurren (hidrogenesse, Ojete Calor, Las bistec, Putochinomaricón, Los punsetes...), pero igual te van. Grupos de esa época son [Manos de topo](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ikc3Mvg5N6Y), [Depedro](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WWvAIz1tTQE), [Papá Topo](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1xtfCZENOhw) (y, en general, cualquier cosa de [Elephant Records](https://www.youtube.com/user/ElefantRecords/videos)), [Xoel López](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YPqnjxf_YG8), [León Benavente](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mAoyUHxpZ8w), [Niños Mutantes](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WykjF-rR29w), [Iván Ferreriro](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dHjw88P2hXw), [Julio de la Rosa](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HauMRzZX3NU), [The New Raemon](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PK16TIWY8Ls) (este me encanta, hacía años que no lo escuchaba!), [Pumuky](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2Cp0RZSRcPs), [Pauline en la playa](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G12JoQpeCvY) y [La habitación roja](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WpG8JVvC0sw). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 23:35:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Allergies themselves or Polaramine.

I'm a student, and did not had bad allergies when I did work. As I said, allergies are getting worse for me, I was okay during highschool, had allergies but manageable. While I was studying in Madrid it wasn't that bad either, perks of the concrete jungle.I', only knocked when I take Polaramine, the rest of the allergy pills are fine, and they usually help a lot, but I had to take Polaramine for a couple of weeks.And you do have the option to get the shot instead of the drops, but you need to go once a month to get the shot. I did not take that option because I travel between Madrid, my parent's city and my SO city, but I'd say the shot doesn't look that bad, my mom is getting hers (I think this is her second year).
And thank you, good thing I don't like going out so it's not that bad and most of the time it's okay \^\^. I hope you also get the treatment you need!

Btw, the treatment (shots or sublingual) takes 4-5 years to be completed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 14:00:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo he estudiado la carrera en la Autónoma y el máster lo hago en la Complu. Al menos en mi experiencia la Complu le da mil vueltas a la Autónoma. De las demás, mis compañeras de la Carlos III me parece que han salido muy bien formadas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 13:10:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. You take 4 drops when you take the whole treatmen (you need to spent like a week taking the 1st day (of the week) only one, the 2nd day you take two and the 3rd day you take the whole 4 drops; after thjat initial one you take 4 drops 3 times a week).
I was told that I should see changes after 3 years. The thing is, after my first year I did not recieve the  medical appointment  to get the prescription so I lost that year (so I'm on the 2nd year). I don't know if I will be taking it again, I will discuss it with my doctor this autumm. But so far I had a really rought spring. No side effects, besides a little tickle/tingle under the tonge right after (it feels like an itchiness), but it's gone after a few minutes.
I sneeze a lot, then I spent the rest of the day either sleeping or feeling very tired. I can take an allergy pill + nasal spray + eye drops (+ not going out at all and every window and door closed) for those symptons, but sometimes even all of that is not enough. Polaramine (allergy pill) is the one that works best for me, but it knocks me out. I feel like lately my allergies are getting worse, not better, last year was a little better than the current one.
Right now I can open windows and go outside during the middle of the day (there is more pollen during the sunrise/sunset), but I do have allergies all the year long. I'm allergic to the pollen from  herbaceous plants, olive-tree and grasses (Gramineae). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 19:38:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm using the sublingua too, but I have to pay like 140€? for it each time (once a year, take the drops 3 times a week until it's done, around 3 months before allergy season). Not much difference for me after 2-3 years.
Anyway, you need to be evaluated by an allergist, as the drops are made using some kind of biological profile (I mean, they are custom made) and only made to those specific allergens that trigger your inmune system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 19:16:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I studied in a concertada. It was free, but I had to buy the uniform and books. As far as I know, it should be free too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 12:58:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Around 200000 years. Humans have been pretty much the same since the begining, that why we classify Homo Sapiens as Homo Sapiens, it's literally the same thing. There would be some minor differences, but maybe not even noticiable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 15:41:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Idelista, Badi, MilAnuncios (esa regular). A mí en grupos de FB nunca he tenido suerte, pero los hay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 09:14:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. 4 different items :')

Edit: 5... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 23:59:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congrats! I've lost every single item I tried to get, so I'm a little jealous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 10:23:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hard pass for me. Chinese cosmetics are tested on animals (tho it seem it [should be changing this year](https://www.vogue.co.uk/article/china-lifting-animal-testing-laws#:~:text=China%20Will%20No%20Longer%20Require%20Animal%20Testing%20On%20Cosmetic%20Products,-By%20Daniela%20Morosini&text=The%20Chinese%20government%20has%20announced,of%20animal%20welfare%20activists%20everywhere)) and they usually contain formaldehyde, that not only causes irritation (at least for me, it makes my eyes red and I tear a lot) and smells awful but also [it could cause cancer](https://www.cancer.org/cancer/cancer-causes/formaldehyde.html).

&#x200B;

Edit: Born Pretty Store may be a safe place to buy tho. I have two stamping polishes + matte topcoat from there and I can't smell the fomaldehyde, but they have no labes/ingredients listed anywhere ¯\\\_(ツ)\_/¯Ialso  have a shimery Lulaa one too, I forgot about it. The ingredients listed are: butyl acetate, ethyl acetate, nitrocellulose, acrylic polymer, acetyl tributyl citrate, isopropyl alcohol and steralkonium hectorite. It does have a strong smell, that's why I don't use it.

All are regular polish\* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 08:04:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yesterday I was changing currencies on the phone app and got a popup saying that everything is actually paid in US dollars. Perhaps they got it with discounts/promo/coupons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 16:25:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cool! Here is mine, if anyone can help (updated).

Energy lab: [https://a.aliexpress.com/ BSUpGY](https://a.aliexpress.com/_B1TEKs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 17:26:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everything, if possible \^\^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [No due date] Final project fragment on ambiguous sex </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 16:23:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [https://docs.google.com/document/d/1udb4p7CVGs\_PBKoAuX7BKb1c4nFoSbepx2HFg2idzR8/edit?usp=sharing](https://docs.google.com/document/d/1udb4p7CVGs_PBKoAuX7BKb1c4nFoSbepx2HFg2idzR8/edit?usp=sharing)

This is a short part of my final project for my degree (already evaluated in 2018) that I decided to translate to English. It's a translation from my paper that was written in Spanish. I think it's pretty okay but I would love to hear something back.

I highlighted in red a phrases that I feel is weird sounding and the ones in black are originally wrtiten in Spanish (the translation is in the brakets).

Let me know if something is not clear, I would like my text to be readable but I've spent so many hours working on the original one that the words no longer make sense.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 10:42:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, being chill helps you focus and keep going. It also helps your team.

You can win more games just by not tipying (how many times have you died because you were writing??), and focusing on yourself and your own actions. There are bad games, there are good games, just have fun and maybe learn something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 10:36:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are allowed to have feelings but being toxic wont help you manage your anger. Been angry is not good or bad (as an emotion) but as a teen/adult in a social setting you should be able to behave.

Plus, being angry and blaming others 100% wont let you win games or have fun playing the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 10:28:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then they changed it ¯\\\_(ツ)\_/¯ a few months ago you coulnd't refund any **used** content without using a token. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 10:19:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 7 days is the limit, but I said UNUSED content. Playing any champ in either bots or training tools counts them as used, sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 09:43:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. You can only refund unused content within the last 7 days.
Edit: It has been like that since they introduced the refund tokens.

Source: [https://support-leagueoflegends.riotgames.com/hc/en-us/articles/201751864-Content-Refund-FAQ#h2](https://support-leagueoflegends.riotgames.com/hc/en-us/articles/201751864-Content-Refund-FAQ#h2) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 21:24:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love playing saturday at 2 am for that same reason. I'm not drunk or stoned, but I have so much fun watching people do the dumbest shit, I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 20:01:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Flex. Players there are more chill and sometimes drunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 19:55:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same answer.

Edit: both your support and jungle should know where the enemy jungler is, where it could be warded, etc. Not that ADC shouldn't pay attention to that, but the support is not farming and that kind of their job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 19:53:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To your team, it's a team game. But supports, as junglers, should had better macro and so and so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 19:50:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go fill, everyday is a surprise. That's what I used to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 15:46:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The minimap exist and it's free to use.

Wards are free too, and pinkys are worth the 75g. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 15:42:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You get skins you don't have. The chance is very very low for that skin line (around .4%), but it goes up the more skins you have. You can get her from hextech chest too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 21:45:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I can play her ADC.
Btw, I think Naut's/Mumu's crit animation are the funniest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 21:24:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Focus on macro. Ping for every objetive, be available to go there if your team needs you, etc. You can't win every game , but you can win half the games; losing is fine, learn from your mistakes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 17:59:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You've got some tips, let me give you a few more:

You'll fed sometimes, that's okay. KDA doesn't win games.

You'll get people complaining that you are feeding, no matter what you do. You can be 20/1/10 and someone will call you out for giving a shut down; don't worry about that.

Learn some macro, focus on yourself and have fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 17:47:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a nice person that has fun talking to their team and the enemy team. I've met some very good friends, told very good jokes and won so many game comunicating.

I only have negative interactions like once every 10 games, if I didn't want to have chat I would just /muteall or something like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 13:03:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I learned by playing the game and nothing else. Like, I just decided to download the most played game, then play the tutorial and play bot games.

I recommend you to do that first, so you can learn at your own pace. It took me a long time to notice that you had a chat option and things like that, but I'm glad I did it like that, maybe that works for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 12:33:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are 3 options you should try in the training tool and see what works for you. Settings → Hotkeys → Player movement and there you have player move click, player attack move click, player attack only click and player attack move. I personally use player attack move click so when I press space it AA's whatever is closer to the pointer (and I think it also give priority to champions, but I'm not 100% sure if that is an option somewhere else). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 12:23:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You win the game by taking objetives. KDA is useless, specially in lower elo. Focus on taking decisions that can lead you to take turrents. Forget about your team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 12:10:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a fucking game. Are you having fun? If so, then keep playing (winning is not the same as having fun). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-20 13:56:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Indeed. For that price you can get a 15m2 place badly distributed.

Plus, it will be hard to find a place for such a short time. I don't think any owner would prefer a short-term rent, but who knows how the world would go after Corona. Just look around in Idealista/Badi and see if you get lucky.

I lived in Toledo for a while and had to go to Madrid every single day and it wasn't that bad. I only had to pay the under-26 public transport fee (20€), but it took me 4h everyday. That's why I said it will depend on what you are planning to do; it's only an hour (in bus) from Toledo to Plaza Eliptica, so it may be worth it, and you can also take the Avant (30 min Toledo - Atocha), but the cheapest you can get a ticket is 10€.

So maybe think about living in Toledo, Segovia, Pinto or somewhere like that.

P.S.: When I first moved to Madrid I could affort to live in Lavapies. 5 years later I can only do that if I want to share a bed with a stranger :-), so who knows what the fuck would be going on next year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 23:06:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm currently not in Madrid but you can:

Sleep in the airport (I have a friend who likes to do that because it's free??).

You'll probably have more luck using Twitter or Facebook, maybe try and see if you can find a couchsurfing oportunity.

Good luck, I'm sorry you are having this problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 20:11:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 600€ for a whole aparment or just a room?
Idealista is the best website, you can also try Badi. The farther away from the center of the city the cheaper, but that would also depend on what you gonna do in Madrid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 12:50:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pesonalmente, te recomiendo que trates de buscar hablantes nativos en aficiones que ya te gustan. Por ejemplo, buscar un grupo para jugar a un videojuego o ver una serie juntos.
Empezar a hablar así de la nada con gente es un poco extraño y requiere un gran esfuerzo inicial, especialmente cuando se hace por mensaje instantáneo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 19:02:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha, I'm so sorry! In short, Spaniards do not like being called latinos because it usually used as a shortened version of latinamerican. So people living in Spain are spaniards/spanish, and almost any other spanish-speaker is latinamerican.

Edit: Spanish is spoken in Equatorial Guinea, Sahrawi Arab Democratic Republic (Africa) and it was an official language in Philippines (Asia) until the 80's. I wouldn't call anyone from those countries latino, but you can impress your friends with this info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 18:57:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. It's also worth mentioning that both words are probably related to the race concepts held in USA, which do not make much sense but are somehow very popular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 18:02:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spanish ARE latinos, but it's not commonly used to talk about them.

You see, people tend to use "latino" to talk about people from Latin America, but (at least in Spanish) it can also refers to places with languagues derived from latin (it's part of the RAE definition: [https://dle.rae.es/latino](https://dle.rae.es/latino) )

So, my point is that [latino](https://dictionary.cambridge.org/dictionary/english-spanish/latin) is not the same as Latin American, but commonly both words refer to latin americans, so be aware. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 17:49:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You may be able to help for projects like Proyecto CoViDa: [https://ayudacoronavirus.blogspot.com/2020/03/proyecto-covida-ayudanos-ayudar.html#comment-form](https://ayudacoronavirus.blogspot.com/2020/03/proyecto-covida-ayudanos-ayudar.html#comment-form) or A.I.R.E.: [https://foro.coronavirusmakers.org](https://foro.coronavirusmakers.org)
I'm unsure if there are more projects like this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-17 18:48:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo he estado pagando este año:

\- Alquiler más gastos: Unos 400€. De gastos siempre he pagado unos 25€ de luz y gas, algo más en invierno, aunque también depende de con cuántos compartas; puedes encontrar alquileres con gastos incluidos también. Luego el Internet son otros 20€ o así.

\- Comida: soy una rácana. He llegado a comer por menos de 30€/al mes, pero últimamente estaba por los 50€/mes.

\- Transporte: 20€/al mes si tienes menos de 26 años. Si no, abono zona A:  54,60€/mes.

Con carnet de estudiante casi todos los museos y actividades culturales son gratis o tienen descuento.

A partir de ahí ya depende de cómo vivas. Yo no salgo mucho, ni suelo comer fuera, pero si te buscas la vida comes y bebes de puta madre por nada (por ejemplo, la opción de comer todo lo que quieras del Domino's por menos de 8€). Yo diría que me gasto unos 20€ en comer fuera y tomar algo cada dos o tres meses, pero fácilmente te puedes gastar eso en dos bebidas en cualquier discoteca. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 17:12:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's totally fine! We all make mistakes, even in our native languague. The most important thing about a languague is practice: see, I do speak English but I haven't been able to use it in so many years that I speak like a child, I can understand it very well tho, and it is because, well, I live in Spain, I don't use English.
So please, talk as often as you can and do worry about mistakes, **the important part of a languague is to be able to comunicate!**

P.S.: I do mainly use the same spanish for everyone. I'm latina, when I moved here I had my friend's grandma tell me to never use "usted" with older people. I stopped doing it and no one has ever said a thing ¯\\\_(ツ)\_/¯ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 05:04:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just a thing: licenciatura AND grado, you should use both. We younger people, at least in spain, have grados. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 04:52:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No.

Source: have family there, can't understand when they talk gallego.


I mean, I probably could understand some things but it will require an effort from both me and the other person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 04:38:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude, romanians can pick the languague very (VERY) easy, don't worry! Most people are very patient when it comes to non-native speakers; I'll personally advice you to try and have as many interactions as you can (with spanish speakers) and you'll be fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-11 02:38:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, I see, since 2019 prices has been up :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 20:45:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When did you manage to find that? I rent a room there for 350€ and that was the best I could find in all Madrid after looking up for 2 months (I've been living in Madrid a long time). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 00:19:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Puede ser. La cosa es que asocie emociones positivas a hacer lo que le pides, y eso lleva tiempo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 00:09:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Carmina o revienta y Carmina y Amén me parece que son muy españolas, aunque te va a costar entender el acento \^\^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 00:07:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cambia progresivamente comida por achuchones hasta que se acostumbre </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 00:00:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ya acabó el plazo, pero igualmente muchas gracias! <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-29 15:06:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm in a long distance relationship, so not much difference (besides not going to visit them this Semana Santa). But feel free to ask if that is something you find interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 16:02:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Before the numbers went up? Nothing, it was only a flu... shit hit the fan and now we are in quarantine unless you have to work some shitty job that requires you to go out or need food/medicine.
Things are pretty bad. Stay at home if you can and avoid other people, make sure to wash your groceries and be nice to other people. Try to wear a mask (even a handmade one is better than nothing) if you have to go out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 15:14:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gracias! Te escribo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 19:57:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ¿Me lo puedes enviar tú? Parece que he llegado al límite de privados por día :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 17:53:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No puedo, porque tengo que dar un código único para cada perfil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 17:43:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me mandas un mensaje? Reddit no me deja :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 16:47:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ¿Me escribes tú? No se qué pasa, estoy llegando a pensar que he superado el límite de chats que puedes empezar al día, si es algo que existe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 16:09:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can also search for local Facebook groups, people are offering their resources there and even if she cannot find a mask there are plenty of volunteers that can help her with her shooping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 16:06:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me sigue dando problemas para enviar mensajes, incluso desde la app y usando los datos :\_) ¿me escribes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 15:33:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Por alguna razón no me deja mandarte privado, se queda la pantalla del chat cargando indefinidamente ¿me escribes tú? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 15:22:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gracias!! Ahora te escribo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 15:10:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gracias! Muy amable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 14:57:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Estupendo, te escribo \^\^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 13:10:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Genial, gracias! <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 12:52:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Va por perfiles, por eso no puedo añadir link al post. Si te interesa dime y te escribo a privado, porque además te tengo que dar un código según el perfil que cumplas.
Se que es un poco coñazo, pero es un proyecto grupal de máster y algunos de grado y somos muchos, así que cada uno tiene que controlar cumplir sus perfiles con los códigos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Encuesta sobre bicis en Madrid </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 12:42:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hola!Hago un máster en la UCM y con esto de la cuarentena y demás me está costando conseguir gente. Tengo que hacer una encuesta online para una asignatura (aka no se va a publicar nada y es todo anónimo) sobre el uso de la bicicleta en la Comunidad de Madrid. Va por perfiles, así que si a alguien le interesa participar que diga. Se tarda cinco minutos en completarla \^\^Un saludo y cuidaos mucho!

&#x200B;

Edit: La encuesta ya ha acabado. Muchísima gracias a todos, ¡habéis sido un encanto!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
