<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject72</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 16:28:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for making my day better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 00:15:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I quite like the nexplanon. It's no thinking involved birth control. Made my periods really irregular, barely have one. That was the only side effect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 13:47:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I've had no problems thus far. The differin didn't cause the dryness I expected in general </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 23:18:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's been a few years since I was in first year but I'll explain what we were told. The only actual psychology degree in UCD isn't through arts. That's for its accreditation. You can however if you're doing arts usually do some psychology modules in first year. When I was in first year, four years ago now, a lot of people tried to take the core psychology modules through the arts course in first year and then transfer into the psychology course for second year.... However this is quite difficult as it's limited places in the psychology course for the accreditation. Meaning that it would take someone dropping out of the psychology course for their to be an open place. I'm not sure however of the current guidelines. But that at least used to be the advice given. It's also possible to do structured electives based on psychology throughout your degree irrespective of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 20:38:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't receive a diagnosis as nothing turned up on the bloods, presuming that it was hormone levels that were checked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> PCOS or something else & diagnosis </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 19:48:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a 22(F) year old who only gets periods around every three months ish. This hasn't always been the case. But for the last few years has been.

I have always had acne. It's just been increasingly getting more "hormonal" looking with cysts along the jawline.

I'm overweight. I have lost weight before with what I perceive as a normal rate. I have always been overweight though since puberty. I've never managed to break through a certain weight.

My hair is thinning over the years to the point others have commented. I used to have really thick hair as a child.

I am lucky enough to have blond hair, but I do have quite a lot of facial hair etc. Not majorly noticeable.

When my periods initially started to get irregular I went to my GP after having no period for three months. She ran bloods but couldn't find anything. It was put down to stress. It's now two years later and in that time I have not had more than five periods a year.

Is it possible to have pcos without it showing up on the bloods?

Is there something else I should be getting checked out? Something else that could cause the irregular periods? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Diagnosis- nothing on bloods </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 19:44:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a 22 year old who only gets periods around every three months ish. This hasn't always been the case. But for the last few years has been.

I have always had acne. It's just been increasingly getting more "hormonal" looking with cysts along the jawline.

I'm overweight. I have lost weight before with what I perceive as a normal rate. I have always been overweight though since puberty. I've never managed to break through a certain weight.

My hair is thinning over the years to the point others have commented. I used to have really thick hair as a child.

I am lucky enough to have blond hair, but I do have quite a lot of facial hair etc. Not majorly noticeable.

When my periods initially started to get irregular I went to my GP after having no period for three months. She ran bloods but couldn't find anything. It was put down to stress. It's now two years later and in that time I have not had more than five periods a year.

I'm wondering could it be PCOS without anything coming up on the bloods? Anyone encounter this?

Just after having it all put down to stress before has made me... Not exactly enthusiastic to go back to the GP. Although at this point I really don't think it could be stress, these past years have also been the healthiest and happiest of my life if it is "stress".  Or nothing wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 13:02:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I honestly couldn't imagine the stress of dealing with that, but sounds very similar to my best friend's situation. PM me if you need to talk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 22:16:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most of the contents I was already aware of. Bar reddit which I don't really consider social media, I've already deleted all social media. It's interesting to see others realise how pervasive social media is as the dangers are now becoming more mainstream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 23:24:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never thought of some of this. But very valid points. The implications of class are very wide ranged. Thank you for sharing that. It makes me feel ... I guess seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 23:22:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. I will try some of the tips </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 23:21:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope you are doing your best to take care of it now. It's just strange reconciling the accomplished part of yourself, hard work and then a crippling mental illness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 23:18:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you both so much. It's nice to know other people get it. I've just retreated to my bedroom following a conversation about a three hundred quid yoga mat. *Sigh*

Same person offered to get an air bnb in a city miles away for my birthday for everyone. They've a lot of money but I just don't feel comfortable with that. I just feel like I'd owe it back as such even though technically I wouldn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Impact of growing up poor on anxiety </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 17:08:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I was growing up, my mother never owned a home. More often than not didn't even really rent. For the first ten years of my life, we shared a room. I'm not from a developing country, I'm from one of the richest countries in the world so that's not the norm. When I went to college I worked really hard to never have to go through that again. To be precise I worked overnights as a mcdonald's manager during college. When I was a kid if I got sick and needed the Dr... My mother often couldn't afford it- there was never any spare money.

I took an opportunity to live in a different country for six months and do something that makes me happy, but pays terribly. It is enough, but doesn't give much wiggle room. I am living with other people my age, essentially volunteering and being given a stipend. This is the first time in my life that it's not as simple as work more hours etc. And it's the first time since I was a child that an unexpected cost would not be able to be covered.

I'm really struggling with this. I'm really struggling with people who want to do communal dinners etc but then work out to be a lot of my weekly budget. It's making my anxiety go crazy. I don't feel in control of my finances. I can't not do it because then it's only me not. And i want to. I don't want to seem cheap either and it's a word that has been mentioned.  It's just I want to have financial control. I don't feel anyone understands me. Even those previously working minimum wage... They like to say they understand and say this whilst always then saying that they can just go home and wait for the next opportunity, that they won't degrade themselves for minimum wage. Meanwhile... I don't even have a home, not even a family one to go back to. My mam is still renting a room. Henceforth any savings I have are really important to get me back on my feet after this. I can't afford to dip into my bank account, I really rely on the stipend. A lot of the others have parents covering a phone bill or just straight up depositing money.

I'm feeling like by my age, mid 20s, this stuff shouldn't matter... Like I thought class wouldn't be so prevalent. I'm feeling really uncomfortable. Really anxious about this. Worse thing is when I do find someone with a similar background to me I get on better with them... but I'm still an outsider because my mother worked really hard to make sure I was educated and I just graduated from a good college etc.

Just wondering if anyone else felt the same. Like class never goes away. Like the poverty you experience growing up has such a profound impact on mental health? Like no one understands.

Tldr, I feel like the poverty I experienced growing up is having a huge effect on how I handle finances now and my anxiety. Anxious about seeming cheap when in reality I just come from a poor background and don't have family to rely on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 15:55:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's an AIB on campus. They seem to be the easiest bank to set up an account with for an international student. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 00:50:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Proud of you. Irrespective of the outcome it's a huge step!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 22:36:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go to a Dr. It could be an allergic reaction. Or it might not even be acne but rather folliculitis which depending on the cause of the folliculitis may require antibiotics and can actually lead to blood poisoning.  Not trying to scare you. But if you're having trouble, easiest thing is to go to the GP. Even if it is just acne they can help give you directions as to how to clear it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 23:00:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First of all, make sure you are taking care of yourself. Secondly, a somewhat neutral response. You don't want to inadvertently guilt her for having those feelings, but want to take what she said seriously. Ultimately, know that no matter what you do, her choices are hers. Just remind her you're there for her. Acknowledge her feelings, remind her of how far she's already come. Feelings of relapse are normal in recovery,  but she can recover from her ED.

Ultimately though, please recognize that whilst you can support, there's a limit to what you can do and ultimately it takes a myriad of support, not only friends but also therapists, psychiatrists etc to get through an ED. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 22:45:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would be interested! I think you should go for it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 05:37:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep, I am pretty much the same. Guess I'll see if it stayed between me and my boss tomorrow and if/who thinks I'm nuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 05:36:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was in this position today. I've seen a lot of people in my job get slack for mh problems, but today I had to leave work because of a panic attack. It didn't go as bad as I was expecting in disclosing.  I only told who I absolutely had to and then asked them to keep it to themselves why I had to leave as I don't want my health politicised, or subject or t workplace gossip. I have to go back to work tomorrow which is the hard bit and I feel like there might be some snide comments by coworkwers but even if the worst happens tomorrow, I do feel like my boss has empathy towards the situation.

Hopefully if you do need to disclose it will be okay- and if you do I recommend starting with the bare minimum of who you need to tell until you kinda get the general vibe of your workplace.

Wishing you the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 00:47:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends. School to school exchanges will have their own process. University wide ones is gpa only. My school was a letter outlining why you want to go on erasmus and gpa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 15:25:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As an Irish person I will say I don't find racism any worse than the UK or US and have lived in both. As other people have pointed out there's a lot of ignorance. Having lived elsewhere Ireland truly is ethnically homogeneous. Even nowadays, the diversity is still tiny in comparison to most countries. I think due to immigration being a newer thing there's a lot of ignorance and less integration. For example, my education was majority white Irish. Even my university was white European/American.

Immigration is perceived as an issue here, but most people target their anger at the big US tech corporations that kinda cause as some have mentioned the issues with rent etc.

The Irish have a history of emigrating and thus don't routinely take issue with immigrants. Unlike most western countries we haven't had a political resurgence of far right nationalism. Surveys routinely place Ireland highest for positive sentiment towards refugees in the EU.

In saying that rascism is everywhere. Ireland is no exception. In my experience, eastern Europeans have it worst, largely because of that being the largest pool of immigrants.

Some people have mentioned English people. I would encourage people not to conflate an anti English sentiment (as in the country and a rivalry with sports etc) with racism. Being English would not be a disadvantage in Ireland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 22:20:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's hard today for me too. Can't talk to my SO often because if time difference, both of us working full time and college full time. Finally finished college this year and planned to close the distance and live together for the second time, and hopefully permanently this time. But then trump stopped all visa processing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-07 00:42:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. Was going to comment this if no one else did. A lot of the way Japan views itself is because of the way America set it up after WW2. For example, they thought keeping the emperor would provide stability and so didn't try him with any war crimes and also tried to shield him from as much association as possible.

Equally as much on the flip side, most Americans don't know very much about the devastation of the atomic bombs on Japan. Or the internment camps people of Japanese heritage were kept in the US during the war. Nor do they know a survey in 1944 found that 13% of Americans wanted all Japanese exterminated (Feraru, 1950). Not to dismiss what the Japanese did. They too were horrible, but so was everyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 17:13:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep. It's like every long distance couples nightmare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 03:36:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so sorry OP. My partner is American too and I was supposed to be immigrating this year. Not going to happen now. I feel like all my options are slowly being taken away. I'm hoping Biden wins in November. I think that would ease my anxiety. Feels like with Trump you're always anxiously expecting some extreme immigration measures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 03:29:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A pen pal website called interpals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 03:26:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My partner encouraged me to go further away when the opportunity presented itself. I was worried about the relationship. Don't think I would have gone without his support, but it was the best thing that has ever happened to me (aside from maybe meeting him), and I am a better person and partner for it. And he also gained from it in a lot of ways too when he came to visit (seeing new culture, travelling more since it was cheaper to travel etc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 03:20:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's beautiful OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 03:19:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I'm actually so grateful to have people who can relate. Everyone is driving me nuts with struggling not being able to see their partner who livss in the same town. But they have the option to in the near future and can do what they want. I'm in Ireland, he's USA. We managed to close the distance four years ago and actually lived together but he had to move back to years ago and is now in college over there.it's been really difficult second tine around. I'm finished college this year no longer tied to Ireland and Ireland does a graduate visa with the US that i was planning to do... But then that got cancelled. Only other option would have been k1, and now that's gone too. It's just hard not even having the option. Feeling like unless Biden wins against Trump in November the chances of a K1 are limited 🙄 i really hope I'm wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 03:12:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Long distance can be rough. Talking needs to be prioritised and planned more in LDR than regular ones. Just because of busyness and schedules and not like you can kinda at least go to sleep in the same bed, or whatever like in regular relationships.

In terms of kinda cute ideas... I like falling asleep on the phone to my partner. Emails. Letters take too long. But you can schedule a surprise email for when the other person wakes up if you have their email address. Then there's letters and care packages. I think anything with symbolic meaning that can be done from afar. Cheesy but the biggest one for us was a childhood teddy bear exchange. He had to root his teddy out of a closet somewhere but my childhood teddy had stayed in my room since I was born. When my family heard the Teddy had gone home with my bf they all knew it was serious lol. Just use what you know from your relationship and get creative I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 02:56:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I second that. It could be a lot of things. But you will need to have a conversation with her. If she says she can't video chat or call, or keeps putting it off, I would suggest an email. It allows you to voice your concerns without interruptions and can give space for a logical answer as the instantaneous nature is less so than messaging. However with anything in text, reread it imagining the worst possible uptake on her end. Tone is everything and unfortunately missing from messaging.

I would imagine whatever it is, it's likely amplified by quarantine though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 02:49:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My first suggestion would be to try and ride it out regardless until post-COVID lockdowns. Household tensions are hard to handle rn without the ability to get out of the house easily.

Covid aside though... A relationship is give and take, and two people need to be willing to work on the issues. If you have brought up these issues before with no results.... Well its either accept the situation or then divorce. However, maybe bringing up little things might help, especially rn. Like saying hey hunny can you take care of the kids for an hour whilst I take a nap? Or whatever the request. Maybe add in how you feel. As in 'I'm feeling really drained from taking care of the kids 24/7 in this current situation and I really need some sleep/space for a bit. Same goes for the increasing intimacy. Maybe try a suggestion? It could be blatant ignorance on his behalf, some people , my partner included, need literal directions sometimes. It's frustrating. But then after that there's either effort or not. But also it is worth considering that perhaps your husband is also struggling in new ways now being out of a routine due to Covid and/or the lockdown is amplifying problems. I hope this helps, just some thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 02:31:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been there, but worse, different countries. He initially asked me to be his gf. For the first while we were talking he was with someone else though. I originally said no for the same reason. But then I realised there was no way I would be able to be with anyone else, I was in love with him. It was either change my mind and say yes or I think I would have had to cut contact. I agreed to the relationship though because as far as it could be at the time, it was a relationship (without the title). We loved each other, talked all the time etc. That was over five years ago and was worth it for us. Not easy and I think because of the dedication needed, very real costs of visiting each other and also the fact we're from different countries, life would have been very different without the relationship for both of us. It literally changed the direction of our lives. That's something to think about when deciding what to do as well. But it was worth it especially because we were practically in a relationship before having the official talk about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 02:18:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm the same way. I just had that conversation with my SO and we were fine . He respected that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 01:53:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm my experience, my twenties so far are much better than teen years!! Not perfect by any means but better. But when you think about it... I always thought it was kinda sad when people said that. When older people say that it's like well... Do they not like their lives now? When other teens do i think its naive. Maybe for some people teen years are the best. But for others life gets better over time. Or at least fluctuates. But yeah... Was always told teen years would be the best by my dad especially. Made me feel like shit and guilty. But I am in my twenties now. Old enough to be able to enforce boundaries and get away from shitty people and situations. And life is much better. Keep hoping and working OP, I think you're right when you say when you get away and can control your own life it'll get better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-15 00:54:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello again. Formal requirements,

http://www.inis.gov.ie/en/INIS/Pages/Employment%20(Permits%20etc.), there's a section about finances at the bottom. Once you know that you've enough, I guarantee what INIS estimate is enough is lower. Although you are required to show health insurance, which would be no worse than what you are already used to. And you will need am address to register at.

As for costs getting settled here, if you're renting, again it's one of the most expensive places in Europe to rent. Expect a month's rent as a deposit. If you're buying, housing costs more and a mortgage deposit is significantly higher than the US here. Depending on how banks classify you here expect a mortgage no more than 3x your earnings and at least a 10% deposit.

As for your friend, they'd need a work visa. However you don't need a visa to visit and scope things out.

As for your degree, you likely have business experience. It's not useless. (also happens to be my degree) There's a lot of political science graduates who go into business or the civil service. And you'd likely be able to enter Ireland and work on your husbands visa anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 23:22:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ultimately it depends on the company, but generally yes, all over Europe there's a much less of a work until you collapse kind of culture of the US. As mentioned, you are legally entitled to four weeks. Most professionals get weekends, bank Holidays off. A lot of companies are more forgiving here in general when it comes to children, eg in most cases let's say a child gets sick and you've to miss a day of work that's okay.

Irish people value their weekends and as a kind of remnant of the past influence of Catholicism, you usually get paid more for working a Sunday or other benefits.

Long story short in a professional setting, you probably wouldn't be expected to work after normal business hours or weekends.

In more low skilled work, retail etc unlike the UK we actually have longer retail opening times (lived in the UK too and found that one a big adjustment as I like to shop in the evening- on a Sunday shops of a certain size are only allowed open for six hours). So that kind of work, you work awkward times.

One thing to keep in mind with work life balance here is commuting times. Dublin is one of the most congested cities in Europe. Most people i know live in the suburbs, and it can be an hour and a half each way very easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 23:08:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Blephagel/blephaclean for the wipes. They're with the eye stuff in the pharmacy section of boots. Might need a bigger boots to find them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 01:56:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Husband should get a job easily enough in Ireland, and as you're a spouse as far as I know you would be able to join him without a work visa (I still think you could work even as an applicant on husbands visa). If either of you happen to have Irish ancestry, citizenship is an option. Irish immigration is quite relaxed in all honesty, especially for Americans(partner is American). I presume you've checked out inis, that would be our immigration service. Their website and citizens information (https://www.citizensinformation.ie/en/moving_country/moving_to_ireland/working_in_ireland/coming_to_work_in_ireland.html) are good places to check out. Both Ireland and the Netherlands are expensive. Salaries in legal professions are usually lower here, although I'd assume you'd have decent experience etc which would help you out.

If you do move to Ireland I'd recommend choosing to register with INIS outside of Dublin. You're supposed to register in the nearest office, except if you live in Dublin. If you live outside of Dublin county (a lot of people in the greater Dublin area do live outside the county), I'd steer clear of the Dublin office. Much quicker appointment wise, much more relaxed.

Aside from that there are the practicalities of housing being more expensive and hard to find. Public transport... Not great. So cars are necessary. And then depending on the age of your children, schooling will be a difficult transition. The younger, the better with that one.

First and foremost, a visit here is a good idea. Check job listings, get an idea for the jobs on offer. Check websites like daft.ie for house prices etc. If you like it then the rest is logistics. Your husband will definitely get a job. I have no doubt in that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-13 17:53:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Proud of you OP. Besides anything else, you're doing right by your son. He doesn't need seeing parents argue or his dad like that as he grows up. Your ex is a grown man, responsible for himself and if he wants to he can get himself help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-12 03:11:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Make sure that you keep the area clean.even with that my eyes were sore af and needed more, needed to be hydrated but not made any worse through a greasy moisturiser. I got sterile wipes made for around the eyes, and a sterile moisturiser/ointment? Both were made for dermatitis/blepharitis etc and for eyes. And both were OTC. But depends on the country. If you happen to be in the UK you can get in them in boots. But elsewhere idk. They were the only things that worked for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-11 03:07:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Over 3700 miles. Different countries. Five years. We closed the distance after a year, but then three years in he had to move back to his country and I stayed to finish university. On the relationship front, it takes communication as others have mentioned. It takes a lot of planning and foresight to permanently close the distance. There's someone giving up their lifestyle, or in my case legal issues. Plan ahead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-04 01:55:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can relate to this so much. Taking a coding class, now online, and had similar issues with packages not working etc. Also suffer from GAD. Wish I could offer a helpful tip or something but I don't think I have found anything that works. Well, I have found that not fighting panic attacks shortens them, but nothing that will stop them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-04 01:51:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Walmart one. Equate flat top blending brush with the white handle. Not even American, bought on a holiday, have real techniques, japonesque, morphe etc brushes, prefer this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-04 01:46:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry OP. First things first, you have to take care of yourself as best as you can, mentally and physically. I imagine the anxiety makes the covid symptoms even worse. Do whatever you can, whatever you need, to help yourself on the anxiety front. What I can say is that you should be okay. If you're 23 and in reasonably good health otherwise it is just temporary. Even if at the moment every morning it's worse, you will get through it. Your family will have to help your mom, and you will need someone to get you food etc. But try and stay in your room. I know in my country the advice is if you are positive for covid 19 use seperate kitchen utensils, seperate bathrooms as the rest of the household if possible, stay inside, in your room and wash any laundry above 60°C. Ask someone else to wash your bedding. After this is over you can further the progress on your mh. Although it sucks, life is up and downs. I don't want to dismiss what you are going through. It's tough. But I'm sure you've been through stuff in the past, you'll get through this. Get better soon!! Your kitties need you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 20:05:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you live with your landlord it's technically speaking not a tenancy, it's a licensee agreement. So unfortunately you are at her mercy. She can go into your room, through your stuff, give you no notice and kick you out. It's very hard to get any sort of legal supports in that situation because regular tenancy stuff doesn't apply. My suggestion would be talk to your student advisor and try and get on campus accommodation. Hopefully they can sort something out. I live in fear of this happening to me but so far my landlady is okay. Good luck OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-29 03:06:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ireland is expensive. As we speak English, we have plenty of tefl teachers here for forgeign students learning English in Ireland. Bar that there's no jobs for tefl teachers here. And tefl teachers here tend to either go abroad or the ones who do get a job here do english teaching part time on top of usually have full accreditation as a teacher for regular schools here. I wouldnt recommend Ireland. As others have mentioned places like Germany are cheaper. Both for further education and living costs. Dublin is one of the most expensive cities to rent in the world. The public transport infrastructure is terrible. And most people end up living a good hour or so outside the city centre. It also is one of the most congested cities in Europe for traffic. And as we are a small country, we have small cities and not a lot of them. So Dublin would be your best bet if you did move. Finding a job here is also not as easy as in the USA. Generally there is a lot of experience requirements. My partner is from the USA, and struggled. Also in terms of looking into moving to Ireland, we have quite a big financial services hub, tech companies and pharmaceuticals. They'd be the best option to get a work visa in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 23:18:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If we include universities in this, my school is struggling. Always requesting more government money. Taking eight weeks to get an essay back because class sizes are so big. Spending 22m on a new, flashier entrance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-14 22:03:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree. Cut contact with him OP. Don't try to empathise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How to support Bf- found out his grandfather sexually abused his mother </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 19:28:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-04 17:50:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pyrithione zinc is the active ingredient in all head and shoulders products. Look for a replacement in head and shoulders range with similar strength? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-22 05:42:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to love baths as a child. To get me to get out my mam would pull the plug, and you know the gurgling of the drain? She told me that was the drain monster and if i was still in the bath when i heard that he'd come. Anyways, that noise is still kinda creepy to me today, even though I'm aware there are no drain monsters 😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 00:56:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have to use two shampoos. Only thing that works on my seborrheic dermatitis. Haven't noticed any negative side effects or anything. And I was my hair quite often because of itchiness etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 19:09:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look up blepharitis and see if it sounds like it. I had a similar rash and thats what it turned out to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 19:07:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is incredibly sweet. However in practice you can't fix each other. Only yourself. And hopefully you both can. I hope it works out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 19:02:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel this. I feel like most of last year though, i worked hard, saw progress in every aspect of my life... And then things changed and I feel like I have gone back to the beginning and maybe this is what I'm actually like etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 04:47:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Day normally. I get ny worst anxiety in the morning normally. I have also heard that it can cause insomnia. I have barely even taken it late at night so I honestly can't comment on that with me. But just something to think about. It will probably be trial and error. Within the parameters as set out by your dr of course </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 04:12:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's because it is intended for use for blood pressure patients. And if you stop taking it in that case, and your blood pressure stays high, then your risk of heart attack, stroke etc goes up. My current GP recommends that for anxiety I only take as needed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 03:47:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use it as needed. There have been times where that's everyday for a week or two, and then I can go ages without. I was the same but this is literally the only thing that I have tried medication wise that has worked without side effects. I think the placebo effect of knowing its there when/if you need it helps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 02:42:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use it and find it better than anything else I have tried Without any side effects. Like any other medication though it really will be trial and error. I know others who've tried and didnt find it useful. I have never gotten low blood pressure from it. Obviously have my blood pressure taken a lot. Its always okay. If not a little bit high because I'm anxious. And I've never found whilst taking it that I've gotten weak or dizzy etc from low blood pressure. If anxiety increases adrenaline, and then propranolol inhibits adrenaline then with the correct dosage it should bring you back to baseline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-30 01:14:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know it's not what you want to hear but if pre breakup she was planning on cheating then it's probably best for you that you broke up. I think it helps to kwn what you did right and what you could have done better, and it sounds like you are. Besides that just keep working on yourself, and any goals you have. In terms of mh, whilst incredibly difficult, try to follow the basics, decent sleep, exercise. Journaling is good. And keep trying with the NHS. I know again it's difficult, but sometimes perseverance pays off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-23 13:44:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. Deleting fb was the biggest relief. I debated it for ages and stayed on it for people I shouldn't have. But I finally did it December 2018 and haven't looked back since. I have since deleted all social media. It's gotten to the point where i also have to tell people idc about fb drama though. Plenty of people rant to me and I'm just like nope, not dealing, this is why i deleted it. So that's been the only lasting remnant of it affecting my mh. But I'm so much less anxious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-02 16:34:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have seen an orthodontist and GP who have referred me between them to a consultant whose title I believe was an orofacial pain specialist and maxofacial surgeon I think it was. Either orthodontist or GP could refer you. The specialist's background is dentistry and if you're being referred depends on who is referring you as to whether it will be private or public. In my country most dentistry is private so I paid a lot when referred to a private specialist, however I am sure there is public consultants too. A dentist can fit a bite guard which helps. But I've had most luck from what I believe were steriod injections into the jaw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-02 16:21:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you took very brave steps. You don't deserve that. I'm proud of you and wish you every success in 2020 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 19:41:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was just about to say that. I do have anxiety and tmj problems but irrespective of that I have become aware of myself clenching my teeth during the day when doing something difficult... Could be psychological based like taking am exam, could be lifting a box. Also, benzos are muscle relaxants and if you are taking.5mg at night it's probably worn off by daytime and you're clenching throughout the day would be my thinking if the pain gets worse throughout the day... Or some form of overuse? Just something to think about in terms of looking for a solution. Also, something to look into if you haven't already... I got steroid injections into my jaw joints by a specialist as well as the bite guard and found the injections to be the most useful in treatment. I would imagine that would be a much cheaper alternative to try first. But I think you would probably need to see a specialist for that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 19:31:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really can't comment on your particular relationship but being in a relationship with both people having mental illness is tough. Both me and my partner suffer from the same mental illnesses and there are times when we can both be incredibly understanding. But I'm still human. Even though i have the same issues i get pissef off at them for things every now and then and vice versa. As someone else said here as well it manifests differently sometimes too but more so we both have very different ways of dealing with it or needs from people. I need stability and I am relatively open with how I'm doing so i don't like a lot of questions. I like to be distracted etc. They find communicating difficult and need to be reassured by me asking a lot of questions. So ultimately it depends on the couple and the issues. There's a saying in relationships that no two people grow at the same pace and naturally people change over time. This is heightened with mental illness. One person might be doing better at some points, the other not. There can be frustration at a lack of progress. And then it is of course possible for the illness to feed off each other. One person relapses and it triggers the other etc. My advice would be to make sure you both individually take responsibility for your health and recovery. Don't do it for your partner. Don't wait to be convinced to book that Dr's appointment etc if you need it. Be proactive. Find meaning and ways to shore up your recovery outside of your partner. If you do that then you will be better off regardless if you guys stay together or break up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 19:22:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've dealt with this before. Not Dutch. Also as someone else said especially with psychiatrists there is a lack of them knowing how to properly handle the issues in a humanistic way, just a medicinal way. Unfortunately that doesn't stop them from giving their opinion on personal stuff which should be left to a counsellor. Also if the psychologist isn't right, change psychologists. I have had this experience and I persevered with a psychiatrist who at one point told me to self harm that it was better than jumping off a bridge and at that point I wasn't suicidal. But he did make things worse and I stayed seeing him because he was the professional. Since then I've talked about that experience and other mental health professionals have even encouraged me to report him, but i don't want the hassle. But my point is switch psychologists and explain you've had a bad experience in the past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Long distance Bf(23) decided to surprise me... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-27 03:09:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So me(22F) and my bf have been going on for nearly five years. In that time we lived together for two years but last year he had to move back where he is originally from so now until we're finished college at least we're doing long distance. When i say long distance, 8hr flight. So this year has been shit for us and we were actually engaged and called it off. And we were arguing and he is eluding to that he has a surprise for me for xmas. This is the longest we've gone without seeing each other. I genuinely hate surprises, i have generalised anxiety disorder and a fear of the unknown. And he tells me my mother knows what it is and that i will love it. And then to calm my anxiety more, or at least i thought, when in actual fact it was distracting from the real thing, he said that it was happening on x date and in the city etc. This caused an argument in the first place because it meant that i had to be back to the city from my hometown straight after xmas. So when that started he finally tells me that actually it's not anything hes said but that he was going to surprise me by coming early... The only thing is i work, and have booked time off for the days he originally told me. And now I am going to have to work when he gets over, because i know its too late to book more days off. I am actually incredibly angry at this. Because we've both had to work a couple of days on past visits and hated it and now I know i have to again. And I'm so angry at him and my mother for thinking that I'd be okay with this. Am i overreacting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-15 01:29:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree. I went to the Dr after a particularly bad bout of anxiety and having been prescribed different meds before. I was desperate and willing to try anything but the Dr listened to how I felt previous medications hadn't worked and put me on propranolol. It has made a huge difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-15 01:22:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Propranolol is the first thing that's ever worked to manage my anxiety. I don't need it all the time either. But if I'm going through a rough patch I'll take some daily. It is great for those days where there's the physical symptoms without the mental ones and allows me to get on with my day. When I have  strong mental anxiety if that makes sense it also eases things enough to where its more manageable. Best medication I've tried. Never found lexapro helped anxiety in my case. Also I use it in public speaking settings or anything where I know those fight or flight scenarios will be heightened. In college in small group seminars so I can actually focus on the subject matter not focusing on feeling every physical sensation of anxiety etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-15 01:15:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. But it's perceived as being kinda pissed off to outsiders. I work in customer service. I will need to go to the bathroom to cry after dealing with an irritated customer. Today I had a particularly bad one. And even when I got my break an hour later I bawled through it. But before going on my break my manager said that when I got my break I could take a break etc. But it was said more so that he thought I was pissed off. I wish I could say how I get through it. Walking away. Did that today. Don't feel like that's really supported though. And as I said seems like I'm perceived as being pissed off. So idk. I also grew up in a household with a lot of yelling. Once or twice hitting and definitely throwing and slamming doors. So I guess that's where my anxiety of angry people come from. Thing is in my job I can and do sometimes get threats of violence because I work in a bad area. That's definitely not helping </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 00:42:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mother always did the check ups etc with the dentist. And my teeth needed more work when I was a kid and getting regular check ups and having my oral hygiene monitored by a parent than now. I have been to the dentist this year and I'm in my 20s and there were no decay issues and it was the first time in about five years. As a child (baby teeth until about 10) every time I went I needed something done. There has to be more factors involved than just oral hygiene.

Also at 15... Should you really have to watch a teenager brush their teeth?! They should know better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 00:29:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy birthday!!! Hoping this year will be one of the best of your life 🎉 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 20:20:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just find getting out the house quickly helps. That's the only thing that's worked for me. I am in same position a lot of the time though with work or school </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 20:17:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For some reason I still feel like titanic would be bad even though it's a ship... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 20:14:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like you had a good day 😊 self care at it's finest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 20:13:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Milk is bad but I work in McDonald's. Within the first month of working there I lifted up a tray to discover someone had vomited on it. And yes it spilled a bit. Then the week prior a teen came in asking did anyone find a retainer. She had got it that week. Left it in a napkin on the table. I knew I had cleaned the table. Knew it was in the bin. I ended up having to go through the bin TWICE to find it. So I had all manner of things on me. And milk is bad but imagine milkshakes and other drinks as well and then trawling through blood stained napkins to find the one with the spit covered retainer in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-26 16:25:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't help answer the question, but same has happened to me. Teeth moving. If you do go see another orthodontist and find the cause please update the post. I never considered wisdom teeth. Haven't gone back to get braces on again however as I can't afford it right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 11:56:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same. But if I get up any earlier I lose sleep I desperately need. And due to work schedules I can't go asleep earlier either. Any hacks for mornings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 12:31:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly, scrap the friend. That's my advice. In my younger years and when i first started receiving treatment for my mh I had friends who were so misguided. I think their hearts might have been in the right place but even when I tried to establish boundaries as in my treatment is my own and requesting not to comment, they were still incredibly headstrong about it. At the end of the day a professional of some sort is the way to go. Start with any one. I mean ideally you would see a psychiatrist and a therapist but sometimes people when not in the situation do fail to see the barriers to getting help. But once you are trying to, and if that means seeing a psychiatrist that is a great step, then no one has the right to question things. You are trying to get healthy. And just be honest with yourself. I think it's normal to doubt our experiences but just be honest with yourself and whatever professional you turn to for help and it should be okay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 12:25:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An extradition bill. Allows HK citizens to be extradited to China. Although as far as I am aware they have scrapped the bill now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 02:50:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Heard. And can relate. Feel very much like the stuff I need to do for survival are preventing me from living a happier life but not in a position to be able to change much significantly rn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 02:45:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm going to presume there's a reason you're with your bf but this is a standard men should get to do what they want and women are supposed to be willing and nice about. I think you acted exactly how I would in the situation. And I think your bf is hopefully clueless about the amount of these types of interactions females face and nope, you didn't act like a pscyho, and you certainly didn't have to be nice to that guy at all and even flatly answering the questions was nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 02:40:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No one would care if you didn't turn up to school. Said when I was going through a depressive episode at 18. I argued back with the person, who I considered my best friend. She was arguing no one cared about me basically. I argued back because a few people had reached out guessing something was up. Actually stayed friends for a few years after that because I was an idiot with low self esteem. Out of my life now though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 02:36:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it whatever way is easiest for you to tell him, tell him, whether text or person. Just make sure to explain how autism affects you in case he is not familiar with it. With adequate explanation I feel even over text if he is interested in the relationship it will be okay. Hope it all goes well 🙂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 02:32:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand the other comments on here but at the same time in a lot of relationships it takes a long time to get the way you are. And I don't think you being straight forward is a bad thing. In my opinion it simplifies things. And if a relationship is to be sustained then it will come to needing to be diplomatically honest at some point. Perhaps you're just weeding out people you are unsuited to early. On the other hand I do understand how that might come across stronger if you're let's say only in the early stages of dating. Regardless I would ignore the particular slant the roommate has taken of "playing the game". If you play the game you will only end up with people who like to play the game back. Not ideal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 02:22:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As lame as it sounds because everyone else was. And I was easily swayed even when i tried not to. I guess it was insecurity and wanting to fit in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bppv symptoms or not </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 02:20:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I came very close to fainting in a train station this week. My vision went, I could only see bright light, I felt nauseous and lightheaded. I clearly looked ill as a man stopped to help me before I had to sit down on the platform. Following this I went to the Dr and was diagnosed with bppv. The Dr asked did I ever have balance problems or disorientation before but I think he misinterpreted my response. I've always had bad balance since I was a kid. And for the past few years I've been getting feelings of disorientation on and off. But it lasts hours. The above incident was intense and lasted for a few minutes but for the rest of the day I just felt disorientated again. It's my understanding bppv lasts minutes and causes dizziness and room spinning. When I get disoriented it is like my perception is off. Kinda like when you get a new glasses prescription and the floor feels at a different distance if that makes sense? I also get a feeling of pressure and sometimes headaches but do have a history of tmj so tend to lay the blame for this to my jaw. I'm just wondering what others might think? As I said it isn't a minutes thing, it's hours and not really what I'd describe as dizziness. Is this still symptoms associated with bppv? Thank you
21F, 190lbs, 5'9", no medications </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Beta blockers for anxiety </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 12:58:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 10:42:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I tried everything too and found that using a combination of salicylic acid shampoo and something with selenium sulfide works. I personally like vichys decros shampoo the best. But you have to leave them on for a few minutes to allow it to work and I massage it in with a scalp brush too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 10:39:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you can't find vitamin é oil, coconut oil and rosehip oil have some in them as far as I know and with patience and consistency do help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-26 10:34:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look up blepharitis too and see do you think it's that. I got it and it caused peeling on my eyelids and undereyes too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-13 17:56:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try washing with an antibacterial soap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scalp scabs </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-11 01:44:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Since I was a kid I've had dry scalp, which I scratch at and subsequently get scabs. I've tried multiple things. Natural remedies, shampoos like nizoral, prescription stuff. I wouldnt say I have dandruff. If I scratch it looks like I do but it takes that to get the flakes or pieces of dry skin/scabs. Can anyone even tell me what I might have and any suggestions to get rid of this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is the cause of my tooth pain? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-09 06:30:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In April I went to the dentist about what I thought was a typical toothache and would probably be a filling. I described to the dentist the pain and tried to locate the exact tooth. Dentist took xrays but couldn't see anything. Eventually she found a minor crack and presumed that to be the cause. Following filling of this the pain hasnt gone away. I clench my teeth so upon a future visit thought it might be tenderness from that. However I know that feeling, doesn't feel like it, wear a bite guard, and in general it hurts when I bite sometimes and aches on and off during the day.

Anyone know what could be the cause? Should I get a second opinion? Regardless cant keep going on ignoring the pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Long distance depressed bf </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-29 12:25:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me and my bf are doing long distance for a second time after living together for two years. It's been difficult but before he moved we discussed how we wanted things to be. But whenever we discuss things he can agree to something with me but his actions dont follow his words. He moved last summer and we nearly ended things over the summer because he didnt meet any of the requirements to try and make this work. He said he was depressed having to move, which is understandable because he left me his friends and his college behind pretty much. It really upset me however that he couldn't even be honest and say he'd given up. He was supposed to be figuring out if he could come back to my country too and always maintained he was trying thus keeping me on the hook, but he didn't actually take any steps to try. By xmas we had gotten to a better place and I found out he bought an engagement ring. We spent a lot of time at xmas again planning how we wanted this relationship to be , that we wanted to be a team, and that there was concrete steps to take in both our personal lives to secure our future, eg paying down debt. But within weeks he had gone back on what he also agreed to. Got more debt. Told me he'd come visit me in a few months. He was certain. And then went back on it within a week. He keeps getting defensive anytime any issue is brought up. I am finding it really hard to trust him. We were on and off constantly since xmas. The concept of a last chance seems lost on him. But now after I feel a lot of what has been said has completely destroyed our relationship, he has admitted he's been really depressed since xmas. I dont know what to do. This cycle is really damaging my own mental health. And it has eroded the trust between us. I don't know what to do. I can respect the mental illness but he never told me up until yesterday. And he never helped himself. I feel really guilty for leaving him. And I want to make this work. But I also am not naive enough to think it will. He's been inconsiderate of my feelings for months and pushes responsibility for his actions to anyone or anything else but himself. He will escalate arguments and be relentless going non stop for hours only in the end to admit that he does it and is wrong. But it still doesn't stop the cycle of this behavior. I don't know what to do. I cant do much from a distance. And rn for various reasons it's going to be three years more of long distance. If communication is all we have with the distance I cant handle it being bad. I cant handle the resolution even. The aha moment where he goes he was wrong. Because I know it won't change anything. And I dont want to be in a relationship that continues like this. He keeps saying hes changed and doing the same behavior that broke us up before. And the worst part is when we were living together it was nothing like this. We've even done long distance before in the past and it was amazing. Well as amazing as long distance can be. But now... just from the beginning it hasn't been good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 01:22:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's not abusive. He just struggles with communication. It's just, I don't know what to do, I don't envision this being fixed anytime soon without his 100% effort. We don't argue often luckily, but when we do it always ends up in me questioning the relationship. The mean comments in a general context aren't terrible But they're quite triggering for me and I honestly don't think he comprehends that or that this cycle is making me anxious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A vicious cycle </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 00:21:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My bf admits he escalates fights. For me the mean unnecessary comments during arguments and the fact he brings up stuff I supposedly done in the past (usually a year in the past) plus adding more irrelevant issues to the original is getting to me, and I'm struggling with my mental health because of it. Usually a day later bf will come say he's sorry, that he realises he was wrong etc. This year alone though we've already broken up because of it, got back together, then it happens again. He says he's changed. I wanted to break up with him again in march, he was adamant things were going to change, it happened again. Thing is he's my best friend, and I really do love him and I know he loves me,but I just don't know what to do anymore. I can't trust him to work on communication and I've a history of mental health problems and this cycle is really aggravating them. Any advice? He's saying that we'll work it out etc, and if I actually believed he'd work on things I'd stay with him no doubt. Just can't trust him rn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-01 01:35:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People inherently seem to think they know everything. Even when they're not professionals nor have any experience to back up what they say. File a complaint for sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-01 01:32:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whilst I agree with this, in terms of the running away from yourself, I moved country. Better job, better people, easier way of life, went from suicidal to struggling but doing significantly better. And I left all the bs in my home country.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lying in a job interview </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-01 01:24:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-30 00:16:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never had my b12/folate checked however I do take b12. I think I probably have a coirdination/balance issue. So probably just clumsy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Something or nothing? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-29 23:54:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a 21 year old female and for as long as I can remember I've had bad balance. I find it  anxiety provoking to walk down stairs and occasionally find myself veering into walls, curbs etc unintentionally. I also have bad circulation I'm pretty sure. Again for as long as I can remember I've had prominent leg veins and spider veins. I even got teased about them as a kid. But now I think I'm developing varicose veins. And to add to that I find my legs and feet tingling and going numb quite easily. Recently the same has begun with my arms. Especially for some reason my ring and pinky fingers. Can any Dr's help with some advice? Are these two possibly linked? Is this something to be concerned about?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Causes of CPTSD </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-21 02:30:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I may experience symptoms related to CPTSD, but I'm unsure if the cause is traumatic enough for me to mention it to a Dr if that makes any sense. Can anyone share their causes of cptsd so I can get a sense of the variety of reasons it occurs? Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-12 04:41:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My FMIL won't allow me or her son to use the words dead in relation to her husband even after five years. Apparently it's disrespectful. We don't have to point it out. Literally her words. From someone who similarly says my bf left her... after two years though. And she has two other sons living with her. None doing anything with their lives. None of them can interact with each other without screaming at each other. But can't point out her husband is dead. And maybe she should start moving on. After five years she still hasn't cleaned out his closet. She won't stay in the bedroom. She won't get help either. Everything else is somehow everyone else's fault.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 02:26:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay. I have been there with the missing school. If you feel so much guilt and everything, it is better to try and go in. In my life I have missed school because of severe lack of motivation, and in the hope of working on my mental health. When I chose not to go to school, to take a break and reevaluate things,  it was the best decision of my life. However, i wont sugarcoat it, i was told by virtually everybody that i was wasting my life wouldnt graduate etc. Instead what happened was i took a break, about a month and came back stronger and ready for the last few months of school. However when i missed school because of low motivation the opposite happened. I became more isolated, felt worse and my grades disappeared. Dont push yourself to do much, but try to make it into school. Just make it past these twenty days. If you try and you cant, that is okay too. But do get help. Tell your family how you feel. Heck, if you cant do it show them this. Or other websites. Helpguide.org i think is a good one.  Even get them to pm me. They probably just dont understand because they havent been educated on what it is like. Of course they should encourage you, but they shouldnt berate you. If the guidance counsellor is nice, maybe try to alter his perception of you. Tell him the truth about how you feel. He probably just sees you as a lazy kid unfortunately. But remember he doesnt know what is going on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 01:57:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First of all, you are strong for trying to talk to your parents. Second, nope, didnt make my day worse. Parents often link stuff like this to teen angst, etc. I know when i told my dad in particular about my struggles he thought it was just teenage bs. But although he doesnt hava great understanding of it, i think he now believes me because of a professional has confirmed it was mental illness. Is there anyone in school who could help you? A guidance counsellor you trust who can talk to your parents? If you feel you are in immediate danger try telling your parents about your suicidal thoughts. Even write them a letter. If you cant do that call a suicide hotline.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 01:38:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow. You seem to be doing better already. Proud of you. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 23:35:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its okay. You feel how you feel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 22:06:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You might always be overwhelmed ,but sometimes you manage, sometimes you dont. The point is getting away from the people and situations that have you feeling this way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 21:53:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If it is worth it, then try to get a job. Even a part time one if you feel overwhelmed. Keep trying. If you leave it again, it is okay. But at least you tried </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 21:34:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you are in danger, yes. But they will make you speak to a psychologist or psychiatrist, who may try to hospitalize you. But if you need it, please, just do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 21:28:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont know your therapist, so you will have to judge yourself. But if you be honest with them maybe things wont turn out as bad as expected. Explain the long term risks that being hospitalised causes. Or even kinda feel things out first. Say you arent coping well, and are worried about that affecting your work life. Then say you couldnt cope with losing your job and why etc. Other than that just continue to reach out for support in groups like this and even call a hotline if neccessary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 21:24:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know but it is difficult to change a mindset. Focus on creating a bit of distance between your family and you. I know that has helped me greatly. Is there a way you can save to move out or anything?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 21:18:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could you try and explain that to your therapist? Maybe they would understand. They are a professional and can help evaluate the risk in doing so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 21:17:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just keep trying. I have had thoughts in the past about things i also felt that shouldnt still be bothering me. But therapy mainly helped me get over it. There might be somewhere that does free or affordable therapy. Check to see is there anything in your area. It helps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 21:07:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Keep up the therapy regardless of whether you tell them how bad you are. Is there anyone on a personal level you could tell how you are feeling? If you get bad though, is your job worth your life? I know though the prospect of being homeless is horrible. Just take every day as it comes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 21:04:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand. Can you move away from your family? I understand feeling like everyone is against you. At least you are catching that it is distorted thinking, that it is subconscious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 20:58:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont give up on yourself too soon. If you feel fucked up , there is still time to try and change. It is difficult, but not impossible. I guarantee there is someone out there more fucked up too. And would you tell them to give up? I am not trying to guilt you or anything. Just trying to see where youre at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 20:55:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also could you try talking to a therapist? If you are honest and not actively planning , a therapist may help you. I have told a therapist in the past about being suicidal and increased my sessions. I also told someone close to me how I was feeling,so she knew someone else knew. But we talked about hospitalization and decided against it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 20:52:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Perhaps the upsides might outweigh the downsides?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 20:45:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try to seek the right support you need. Talk to a friend, family member or a professional about how you feel. It is hard, but getting help is worth it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 20:42:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are not useless. You bring great joy to your fiance, friends and family i am sure  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 20:41:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think that is not that strange. Just try to lean on him but use other sources of support as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 20:40:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Give yourself the two years. See how you feel then. But in the meantime you can try and live life to thw fullest you can imagine. Move to a different country....play video games all day... Whatever it is you want. See can you make it a reality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 20:36:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just do what makes you happy. You like to draw? Spend as much time as possible drawing. Just do what makes you happy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 20:35:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unless you are a psychic then you dont know what you will be doing. You could be doing exactly what you want to be doing in 50+ years time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 20:29:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do not listen to people. And avoid people like that. Your mom probably cares more than you think. When i try to talk about issues with my mam quite often she doesnt really reply. It is usually because she doesnt know how to. Its horrible but understandable. Perhaps there is something similar wrong with your mother. Call the emergency number of your country. I knoe it is difficult, and i know you are scared but you need immediate help if you have a knife  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 20:26:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Failing your gcses is not the end of the world. I know it is shitty but you still have options. Try talking to your mom about how you feel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 20:25:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is nothing that is 100℅ effective. Try calling a suicide hotline.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 20:22:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay first of all what does kind of mean? If the medication isnt working talk to your dr and see what they can do. I am glad you told her how you feel. Incredibly brave. Try your best to avoid alcohol. I know from experience it makes things worse. As for your best friend... Most people feel shame they place on themselves more than other peoples feelings about them, if that makes sense. If you talk to your best friend he may be angry but it will probably be from a place of love and care. But in my experience I feel more shame for myself than ny friends every did for me in a similar situation. Have you tried counselling? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 20:17:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go for the coffee, and tell someone you are having the urge to use. You are strong enough. I am sure you have managed urges before, just gotta try and get through these ones. It might feel like these feelings will last forever right now, but they wont </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 20:14:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ahh. I get you now. If you feel that way it is horrible. Try to confide in someone you trust about this feeling? A friend or therapist? I have never personally felt that waking up was a nightmare. There has been times where I dont think I would have cared if I did not wake up the next day, but the right people helped me past it. Just try and take every day as it comes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 20:11:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are not wasting your life. You have been through a lot, and everything you have achieved up until now is just that, YOUR ACHIEVMENTS. Did you try to seek help for the overanalyzing? Therapy? I know it is hard but ignore your parents. Or at least just try your best to explain that them saying things like that is not helping. That is if you can.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 19:57:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you try and talk to your doctors about it? Tell them your pain is causing you to be suicidal. See do they have any ideas to reduce the pain? You could even say the pain is so unbearable I wish I was dead etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 19:54:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not sure what you mean .. Elaborate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 19:53:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Getting thoughts written down helps me. I hope it helped you. Would you consider opening up to her how you feel? Or getting medical help if you need it. Give yourself a break. What you have gone through is tough. But time makes things easier in my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 19:49:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing in life is certain. If you feel you are weak, I disagree. But that is just my opinion. There is strength in posting on this subreddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 19:47:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have come so far. Just take every day as it comes. Or if that is too much, every hour. If you do it, then you will also have no chance to prove your innocence. You know the truth, and that is the most important thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 19:43:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are not standing in anyone's way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 05:52:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is harder in your head than actually saying it though. You have to remember that these people are professionals. They have dealt with it before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 05:43:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You need to be honest with them in order to get the care you need and deserve. I know it will be hard, but it easier to inform them this way, rather than them finding out at a later date.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 05:37:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hold out. Til your birthday. Have you told anyone you feel this way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 05:34:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I read the first two. Good movie though. A good escape movie. Any other movies you like? My favourite is Moulin Rouge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 05:29:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is your favourite movie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 05:21:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are no answers in life. It is especially not my place to give you answers. Truth is I don't know. You need to find the answers for yourself. I can suggest things. I can tell you the answers I have found. But your life is very different than mine. Best you can do is decide what you want to do with this reply. And that is your right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 05:18:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will answer. And you do not deserve to feel like this. No one does. Life is not linear. Things might be bad for a while, good for a while. Perhaps your time is coming. Maybe life wont get better. But maybe it will. Maybe you will get the right advice or help, and things will get better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 05:13:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are so strong for reaching out. You have managed to fight these thoughts so much up until now, you can do it again. If you need to call a hotline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 05:04:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This life might not be for you, but life in six months could be different. Your presence on earth is enough. You dont have to have money or an education. You are enough. And if you are strong enough to battle this, you can truly do anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 04:14:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i sent you a pm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 04:01:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait a while. Give yourself even another hour to see how you feel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 03:48:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Things do get better. As you get older everyone finds their tribe so to speak. Just hang on in there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 03:27:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's tough. You are doing the right thing, trying to find a will to live. A suggestion, your will could be the unknown. We could end up being friends, and you'll never know if you do it. You could win the lotto tomorrow. You never know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 03:13:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not inevitable. I understand where you're at, but it's a much better idea before you've tried. Most people regret it as they jump, pull the trigger etc. Keep holding on. Pm me if you want to talk more. Xx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-07 02:59:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Advice needed- Psychiatrist </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-01 05:40:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have been seeing the psychiatrist at my college once every two months or so since September. He's very egotistical, and often says things which are somewhat unprofessional and very judgemental. In February I mentioned my fear of relapsing with self harm after two years clean. He told me if I self harmed but managed to go to class, it'd be okay, and he'd forgive me. Along with advocating it was better than let's say jumping off a bridge. For the record I had never mentioned feeling suicidal. Since that appointment however I have relapsed sh, worse than ever. I've also gotten to the point of being actively suicidal. I did go back to him for a check up, but the only question he seemed interested in was was I going to class. When I answered yes he said he'd like to take my off my antidepressants in the near future. It seems as though he's considering functional a synonym of cured. Admittedly considering everything else in the past I told him nothing else. If he didn't ask, I didn't bring it up. However now I need medical certs for school. But don't want to go back to him. I can't afford a psychiatrist elsewhere. I fear another appointment with him will do more damage than good. Any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
