<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject11</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 11:12:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mum (single mum, working 2 jobs) didn't want me going to the same school she did as she had bad memories from there, so she sent me to a "better school" on the more affluent side of town.

From day 1 the kids bullied me because they saw her drop me off in a Q plate (stolen and recovered) Ford Fiesta, and their parents all had more money and nicer cars.

A few months into the school year and I had been bullied everyday, but nothing serious. Then one day while waiting for the bus I got beat up and my bag stolen. So I missed the bus and my homeroom teacher had to take me home and wait with me until my mum finished work and got home, as my keys were in my bag. While waiting she begged me not to change schools, worried about the schools reputation, and then when I went back in a couple of days later she took me to one side and begged me again and I said I'd think about it.

In those days I was off my mum had already contacted the other school, and had only sent me back in to the school that day to make sure I was certain about transferring, and that teacher being more interested in saving face than my wellbeing sealed the deal. I started at my new school the following Monday and made friends straight away :)


And that's how I got bullied so bad I switched schools. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 21:49:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shake the can well before opening and it'll be perfectly mixed and have a normal cream consistency, or if you need a thicker "heavy" cream drain some of the coconut water off the top of the can when you open it, and then stir well before you add to the recipe. By doing that you may need more cans than the recipe suggests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 08:46:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was the same! I just had my first shift back at my old bar and loved it! It had only been 2 years but it was so great to see my old regulars and only a couple prices had changed so I just sailed through and it felt like I never left! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 10:49:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Told my husband he knows where they are when he needs them so he should know where they go back. He hasn't said that one again since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 23:05:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ask my mum about the rest of my family she kept me from </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 16:58:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm glad you can see through it too. It's hard when you've had a close relationship in the past, but looking back I now see the signs that it wasn't healthy.

We can stay strong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 16:45:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, I appreciate the offer. Same to you ❤

Now go get some cake 🎂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 16:36:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This should be higher up. "Smile love, it's not that bad" GRRRR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 16:29:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You gonna die </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 16:06:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> General advice where I live is to nudge the leader so they go in a circle then cover them in hairspray and burn them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 14:59:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do not smash. Their hairs will float and do some nasty shit to you or other people/animals nearby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 14:57:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We do here too. I know some dogs that have lost their tongues, and even died from them. Nasty little fuckers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 14:51:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy Birthday!!

I'm going through a similar thing with "friends" right now, so I know how much it stings.

My plan of action is:

Make new friends, be honest about my mental health and when I feel like I have the energy to be sociable make spontaneous plans.

Anyway, I hope you have a good birthday new internet friend 💗 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 14:36:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My bald spots are filling in now, and not just with grey hairs! My baby hairs at my neckline are growing in very VERY curly. I literally have 1 thick ringlet that will not be tamed and still isn't long enough to go up in my mum-bun 🙃 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 12:30:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. I don't trust her at all.

For more context. In the past my mum has been my confidante. I would tell her about things that were going on in my life, issues I had with my now husband (housework and stuff, nothing major) and one very specific complaint about our accountant messing up a grant and costing us money. I didn't realise what I mistake I was making.

Everything I spoke to her about ended up being gossip between her and her friends. When her friends got sick of her (as they all do) they told my husbands parents everything she had said to them and how she hates him for being lazy, unmotivated, wasteful and arrogant. And said that she had been trying to break us up from the beginning.

So since then she has been on an information diet.

We stopped speaking completely in June this year after a big argument where she went to hit me. We only spoke when she was picking up or dropping off our son (we didnt want to disrupt his routine) but ended up speaking again 2 days before we got married as she apologised and said she would be better. But I don't trust her yet.

She knows we are short of money because Covid took my job and she knows my husband plays golf some weeks. Last week when she came to see our son she said him playing golf was causing us to be poor, and that he is neglecting his family. I set her straight, said he's paying all our bills and rent and is entitled to a hobby (he already had clubs from before he met me) and to keep out of it.

Then she sent me this last night after seeing me for an hour yesterday.

ETA: we aren't poor. We rent a 3 bed house in a beautiful part of the world, all of our bills are paid and we have food on the table. It's tight but it could be a lot worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My mum sent me this last night. I have typed up a response but not sent it yet. Please have a read and tell me if its OK. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 11:54:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 09:51:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg yes! Well done OP 👏 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 09:49:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can tell he put a lot of thought into that ring. It suits your tattoo perfectly 👌 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 09:47:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We all know that if the tables were turned and she was sat in the ice cream place while a kid was tantruming, and the manager did nothing to find the mum she would kick off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 09:39:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I go for playdates at my friends they always apologise for "the mess". I'm like comeon, don't apologise, we're all just surviving right now lol.

As long as its a safe place to play I dont care what you're house looks like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 11:58:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didnt dare speak to my mum about anything like sex and birth control until I was much older, but was lucky enough to have a family friend to talk to instead. So I give you all of my respect for raising your daughter to feel comfortable enough to come to you with this. Have my poor man's gold🏅 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 13:41:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi! I remember this feeling well. The isolation, constant fear and sheer exhaustion of having a newborn is so hard, even without the added stress of covid.

Mine is 2 now, so believe me when I tell you it does get better. In the meantime here's some advice:

Make a point of leaving the house, even just for a walk. I did this today and it improved both of our moods.

Invite a friend or family member round once a week to provide adult conversation and an extra pair of hands so you can have a shower or cook a decent meal or whatever you need to do. My in-laws have come round every Thursday evening since our son was born, and it was a lifesaver when he was younger!

Don't worry too much about keeping the house clean, if everyone is alive and happy at the end of the day then it's been a good day.

I'm working from home so I'm always near my phone, if you need to talk or vent or anything please send me a message ❤ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 14:10:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tramadol is very addictive and should not be used to treat anxiety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 22:15:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been on it for nearly 2 years, at a dose of 10mg now 15mg.

I dont get stomach ache any longer but I do still get loose bowels most days within a few hours of taking the tablet. Sorry for the TMI.

I still have the fatigue, I'm fine if I'm busy but if I'm at home with my son and not leaving the house I'm exhausted by 2pm and need an afternoon nap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 10:47:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Car. ftfy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 21:22:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was about 7 and was running through the inside of the A frames that hold the carpets up in showrooms. I ducked under the horizontal bars all the way down the row, but somehow forgot to duck under the last one and caught it with my eyebrow. I woke up being prodded by a poor confused old couple and they found my mum for me. I should have had stitches but the shop staff just put a plaster on it. The scar isn't very big but reminds me daily how stupid kids can be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 19:11:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://youtu.be/oQbei5JGiT8

I'm just gonna leave this here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 14:03:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I gained weight, my moods were awful, my skin was a hormonal spotty mess and I had random dry patches of skin on my arms.

But I didn't get pregnant, and didn't have a single period (except when I had it replaced too late)

And I also ended up with less cysts on my ovaries, they were bursting but not being replaced so that was a huge plus for me.

Personally I would have it again now we've had a baby (he was planned, we are one and done) but my moods were so bad I wont put my husband through that, he suffers enough with my rocky mental health as it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 23:14:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was exactly the same, I felt like a cow being milked 24/7, and being attached to the wall by the plug was such a pain that I couldnt help with our boy much without risking not pumping enough for the next feed.

Formula was an absolute life and sanity saver for me, and baby was so much happier with it too. He slept for longer and put weight on quicker.

If she won't suggest the switch to formula herself I would mention it gently.

Maybe get some cartons of premade formula ready for if she decides spur of the moment she's done like I did.

Congrats and Good luck. It does get easier 💙 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 18:45:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No im talking about citalopram AKA celexa. But I am in Spain so it might be different to where you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 10:37:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You've just made me realise I do that too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 15:03:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How are you feeling now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 15:03:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been on them a long time, I dont know how quick she'll taper them, but tbh I worry about coming off them too quickly so I don't mind taking it slow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 15:00:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dr allows an increase after 2 months to give it chance to work, but to decrease I have to wait 6 months. Im in Spain so it might be a bit different for others.

ETA sorry that wasn't clear on my initial response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 20:49:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I personally went from 10mg to 15mg about6 weeks ago and feel much better for it. My doctor has said that any increase needs to be for at least 6 months, so if I feel better by Jan I can reduce it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 12:03:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It took me 3 months to have a period after having mine removed, and another couple for them to become regular again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 11:52:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I read a case file of someone who went to ER with a toilet brush up their butt, bristle end first. The only thing I could think was WHHYYYYYY???

Ninja edit: spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 23:50:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine too. Always grabs the same sauce and wanders around with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 14:27:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's all I did when I woke up from my appendectomy, I just kept asking "did you take it out, did you get it?" Then fall asleep, wake up and ask the same question again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 21:59:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beautiful cake! We're going to have similar style and colours for our reception next year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 00:05:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My heartrate  has just gone back to normal thanks to these photos. Thank you.

This needs more upvotes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 00:00:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've always had bad cystic acne, keto makes my skin so much better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 18:03:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Proud of you for asking for support. You are braver and stronger than you realise.

You matter ♥ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 09:45:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My friends put the pants on under the nappy when night time training. They said it works within a couple of nights as their boys didn't like being wet (and as a bonus the parents didn't have to change the sheets in the middle of the night)

The other idea I've heard is leaving the nappy and pants off, and having the bed layered: mattress protector, sheet, mattress protector, sheet. So when they do have an accident in the middle of the night its just a quick job taking the top 2 layers off and back to bed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 15:44:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 5) They are also printing labels with photos of dogs that need adopting in the hopes of helping the overflowing animal shelters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 09:27:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In 2014 the pope said dogs "and all gods creatures" can go to heaven.

I'm not religious, just happy dogs can go to the good place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 00:18:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plan B should be a last resort, it's not meant to be used as a form of regular/frequent birth control.

I'm not surprised you're getting side effects like sore nipples and nausea, you've overdosed on hormones and your body has no idea what's going on right now.

If you don't want to use condoms there are a lot of other forms of contraception out there that will be less drastic on your body. Eg:

Implant
IUD
Depo (injection)
Various types of pill
Coil
Patch

Please look into these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 22:36:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My ankles and knees have always done this. Mr doctor put it down to a calcium deficiency while I was growing up.

I'm lactose intolerant but that wasn't a thing in the 90's so I used to get force fed milk and then throw it all back up again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 22:26:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to do this as a kid, and now my 2 year old does it.

Same thing with running too, hurts my heels and knees, so I don't run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 11:13:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahaha my mum gave me my first car so I could drive myself to college and work, but the first time I worked on the closing shift and stayed later than she deemed necessary she took the car off me and said she would pick me up when I finished.

I purposely didnt call her for a lift until nearly 1am and stayed for a drink with my coworkers instead, knowing she had work at 5am.

I got my car back 😁 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 08:53:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If she is related to you I wonder if she has any abilities of her own? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 18:05:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NHS Direct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 12:06:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The first few weeks won't feel any better but you will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 21:17:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Insane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 17:37:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a shame, but you're totally right. And yes thankfully you're working from home, so you can still practice some selfcare.

I wish you luck fellow redditor. If you need advice or a pep talk any time feel free to shoot me a DM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 17:23:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I remember those days, its so frustrating. But it should pass soon. It may be an idea to mention to your bosses that you have started medication that's causing some short term side effects, so they will hopefully give you a little slack for a few weeks. In my experience it's better to be upfront about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 17:13:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> About 3-4 weeks is normal until you start to feel better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 22:56:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It absolutely is ok to tell them no. It's also ok to hide in the car to eat your snack because it gives you the time and peace to properly enjoy it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 08:57:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love that film </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 23:31:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you tried turning it off and on again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 22:01:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi there! I'm on a lower dose (being increased in 5mg increments) but in my experience it can take up to 4 weeks for the effects to be recognised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 21:41:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought that. All 3 of my implants (both implanon and nexplanon) travelled and embedded into my arm muscle. Despite the fact that the Dr told me Nexplanon was brought out to replace implanon because of the travelling it was the nexplanon that was the worst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 19:17:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spore. Sailed through the early evolutionary stages then you were in space being attacked from all angles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 12:19:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We had the same rule and called it "you wake him you bought him." After we enforced it the first time someone actually woke him up it didn't happen again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 22:47:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The issue with taking both MDMA and an SSRI antidepressant is that they both increase your serotonin uptake. Antidepressants do it in a controlled way and MDMA just makes your brain take it all at once and leaves none.

To put it in a crude metaphor, SSRI's are like having a glass of wine a night and leaving the rest of the bottle for the next day. MDMA is like finishing the bottle, and drinking whatever else is in your house until there is not a drop of anything left and you wake up with a stinking hangover.

So mixing them is a bad idea, because the MDMA will empty your brains store of your serotonin but the SSRI will still try to access that store and take what isn't there.

I hope that makes sense. Good luck with it all man. Stick with the antidepressants, dont miss doses and dont come off them without dropping the dose gradually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 16:22:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never heard of it, thanks friend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 14:42:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> IKR! You come on HMB to see guys doing daft stuff and cringe at them getting hurt. Its awesome, but too pure for this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 14:32:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 100% number one! Its romantic, sits well on your body and is perfect for an outdoorsy wedding.

It could be the fit of them but 2 and 3 don't look great in the cleavage area, they do your boobs no justice at all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 11:11:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooof she would need the burn ward after that! Love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 11:05:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Set yourself a reminder on your phone "coffee and pills" so you dont forget.

Also try an app to help you relax in the 5 mins you manage to get to yourself, something like mindful or smilin.

I hope your little bubba is gonna be OK, she sounds like a real trooper. Just like her momma ❤ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 21:41:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could be an ectopic pregnancy. Get it checked out ASAP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 12:55:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love seeing awkward pictures of people trying to sell mirrors, especially when there's a doggo involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My Nmom has refused all invitations to our wedding, told her this morning that we are eloping this week and she was fine with me then posted on Facebook how she "wasn't welcome" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 23:30:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On mobile, sorry for f'd up formatting. Also LONG.

So my fiancé  and I got engaged last October and he told his parents by WhatsApp but I waited to tell my Nmom in person as I'm more sentimental. She was furious that we told his parents (a whole 30 minutes) before her and held it against my fiancé, along with a multitude of other things (stories for another time) She announced our engagement on facebook before we even had as we were enjoying our little post engagement bubble for a couple of days. I told her off and she took it down after arguing that she was so excited and its her news too.

So since then her and my fiancé's relationship has completely broken down, and is now irreparable, and she has also put a massive dent in my relationship with her also (again, another story) so we have not been speaking for about a month apart from to arrange her seeing our 2 year old boy.

Now we have just today decided to bring our wedding forward from October to next Monday, 7 days from now! I got everything booked and messaged her that we are busy on her usual day to see our son, so she could have him tomorrow instead, which she agreed, and I said I'd call her when he finally decided to nap to explain why (I know I didnt need to explain myself to a narcissist, but I thought I owed her the decency to know before she found out from someone else)

When I called I explained why we would be busy Thursday she seemed excited for us, and apologised that she wouldn't go as it didn't feel right to be there at this time, but hopefully things would be smoothed over enough to celebrate when we can hold a reception next year.

A few hours later she posts on Facebook that we are going to Gibraltar to get married and have told her she is not welcome! My fiancé, his mum, and several friends screenshotted the post and let me know what was said, so I replied in the comments:

To everyone reading this and judging me:

A) she was invited both times we have tried to organise our wedding and both times she rejected our invitation. Once immediately and the 2nd time after an argument.
B) she hates my fiancé and has told us both that she would rather do anything or be anywhere else than at our wedding. We have proof of this

After the comments that followed got pretty heated with people arguing for both sides she deleted the post and started messaging me that she wants to come and to let her know the details, she wouldn't miss it for the world, move heaven and earth to be there blah blah blah.

My response: you made me look like the worst daughter ever so I might as well say it now, you are not welcome.

Now she has people messaging me asking me to let her go and she's threatening to turn up anyway even though she doesn't know where or what time the wedding is (I will be calling the registry office to make sure they don't disclose this information to anyone, dont worry).

And I'm not replying to any of them.

Goodbye mum 👋 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 18:54:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I struggle on Citalopram, and its rare for me to cum with a partner but I manage it almost consistently with my satisfier clit stimulator.

I'm also over sensitive, but this works wonders, and isn't as loud as a normal vibrator.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-26 23:30:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I've just had my dose increased and I'm suffering all of the above. Give it another week or so and it should calm down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 19:35:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's beautiful, and will suit a wedding in Spain perfectly! ¡Felicidades! ❤ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 18:45:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats what I thought too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 11:06:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a trainer at work who wore his sunglasses the whole week I was taking his classes and whenever we asked why he just shook his head. On the last day he asked us why we thought he was wearing them and we gave him lots of daft reasons. Turns out he was acting out the power of the unique selling point, and said we will never forget him. He was right, this was over 10 years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 12:09:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That hit me right in my core. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 20:54:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The sound of my baby's heartbeat was so relaxing, I always used to fall asleep attached to the foetal monitor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 12:51:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Came here to say this 👍 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 09:39:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well that sounds like it could be it.

I hope as you settle back into work your anxiety calms down. If not have you got the option of getting signed off by your doctor for mental health? That way you'll still have a job when you're ready to go back x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 00:36:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're under more stress now than when you started taking it that could happen. Or if you've had a few drinks it can make you feel more anxious for a few days.

I've had to increase my dosage and decrease my alcohol intake to manage my anxiety recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 01:49:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 01:28:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They are the best of doggos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 00:15:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It wasn't just white chocolate, it was just a part of the story. There were about 6 selection boxes (wispa, crunchie, dairy milk and the rest of the classics) also demolished </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 23:59:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well that sounds like fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 23:48:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He didnt even have a problem with all the chocolate, not even the runs. My mum was furious! It was the year white chocolate after eight leaves came out so she was so excited to try them and he ate them all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 23:46:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All I remember being left was the carcass. There was another dog there, the one who opened the fridge door, so between them they demolished this turkey. I also remember being kind of happy about it because it meant beef for Christmas instead of turkey 😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 23:35:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I was about 7 my dog ate a whole Christmas turkey, meant for 8 people and a curry, his partner in crime had opened the fridge door.

Another Christmas he ate a Christmas pudding, excluding the plastic tub, in our bed.

Another year we thought we had learnt our lesson and he had the kitchen and lounge only to roam in while we were out, he ate all the selection boxes from under the tree.

He was an Airedale Terrier and actually lived until he was nearly 15, despite his christmas treats. And he was the best boy ever 💖 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 13:08:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok this might be a long one.

I have been on citalopram (celexa) 10mg daily for nearly 2 years. Mostly I have been able to drink any amount and had no adverse reactions besides the usual hangover.

However, recently I have been under ALOT more stress (Covid, family issues, wedding planning, money...) and every time I have more than a couple of drinks my personality changes. I become nasty, hurtful and sometimes suicidal. All of this happens without me knowing, I totally blackout and remember nothing the next day.  This has now happened for 4 weekends in a row.

At first I didnt put the 2 together, just thought it was my stress coming out with being drunk, and I went to see my Dr who has increased the dose to 15mg daily. But last Sunday after another bad Saturday night I researched SSRI's and alcohol and discovered a lot of people have this reaction.

It is not recommended to drink on SSRI's, for 2 reasons.

1. These types of antidepressants can trigger a craving for alcohol, and cause people to become alcoholics.

2. People have reported the same as i have experienced. Manic episodes, blackouts, suicidal thoughts, feeling of invincibility (leading to jumping out of windows and other things you wouldn't normally do)

My advice:
If you do drink on this medication keep it sensible, and if you are under additional stress avoid it all together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 21:37:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg he is BEAUTIFUL 😍 Makes me miss my bubba being this small and cute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 10:35:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your hand goo is escaping </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-10 10:52:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw man this update has made me cry. I'm so sorry your beautiful boy had to go through that, but I am also so pleased he has such a wonderful grandma and dad, and that you were able to get him out of that situation.

Sending some super huge internet hugs your way 💙 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 20:19:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're very welcome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 20:07:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And I was exactly the same, feeling the need to lie about why I didn't jump to attention the second she wanted me to.

You don't need an excuse or a reason, sometimes you just need a break. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 20:05:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being honest I am VLC right now, I'm only responding to messages regarding her seeing my son, anything else is either ignored or responded to with greyrocking.

Before I went VLC I would I ignore the messages where she said those sorts of things, and then when she was being normal I'd start to reply again. This worked for a while, but during lockdown she was quite needy and with her being alone the whole time I gave in and responded to every message, but that has led to the situation I'm in now with her as she felt like she was back in control and could treat me like crap with no reason.

Seriously good luck with it. My DM's are open if you need some support or to rant xx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 19:40:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get the exact same messages off my mum. Its a sign of a personality disorder, either NPD or BPD. My advice would be not to rise to it, and don't apologise for not replying quick enough (which I assume you've done 1000 times explaining you aren't awake at that time) She has chosen not to listen to you so don't waste your energy saying it again.
Dont Justify Argue Defend or Explain (JADE) any longer.

If you want to continue a relationship with her make sure you're happy with the terms. You are not her emotional punchbag or crutch.

Stay Strong Friend xx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 00:24:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 00:01:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A note I wish I could publish on my Facebook or Instagram without repercussions. No advice needed, just needed to get it off my chest. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 23:34:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anyone who knows me knows that my Mother and I haven't always had the best relationship. Right now it is bad, really really bad. And I am standing my ground, because now I am a mum and I have created a family, a family I chose and will choose EVERY SINGLE DAY. So thank you to everyone who is standing by me through this, I know it's not easy to see me implode, explode and every other kind of 'plode but it means a lot to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-06 23:19:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for paying the dog tax </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-27 00:03:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's been said already but dropping off meals for them will be such a help, as well as some cleaning and laundry (although I was too proud to let anyone help me and would clean before anyone came round, I now look back and realise I was daft)

Let them nap while you watch the baby. Babies have this amazing thing where they wake up every hour, and it is torture! My boy was such a bad sleeper so we took it in turns to sleep so we would each get a solid 5 hours a night, this lasted about 4 months and naps were very important for our sanity.

If you make plans and they cancel, be understanding. Especially if those plans involve them leaving the house. Seriously, taking a baby out takes more planning and preparation than a 2 week holiday!

If they have any pets you could offer to take them for a while, to take some of the pressure off.

Learn to change a nappy/diaper and offer when you are there.

If mum is breastfeeding make sure she has water, and take snacks just for her when you visit. (I mean take snacks anyway but making milk is hungry work so momma needs her yummies)

Check in often. It sounds like you're a great friend and would do this anyway, but it's worth saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 14:24:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally having this issue with my mum right now after I didnt invite her to sit with my friends and I because we were at our covid19 10 people group limit.

A few days later she screamed and pointed in my face about lack of respect and how dare I treat her like that.

I also saw that the day before "invitationgate" occured she put a meme on facebook about me not speaking to her enough, even though we spoke every day.

I'm not backing down this time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 09:31:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Baby and Dog Tax](http://Baby and Dog Tax https://imgur.com/gallery/ByZmWcK)

My tax is paid. Doggy cuddle here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 09:16:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He wants to cuddle her but she runs away, unless he has food haha! We also have an older dog and they do cuddle 😊 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> It's my cake day and its Thursday so here's a 2 year throwback photo of my baby girl resting her head on my baby bump 🥰 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 07:39:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 00:14:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Headaches, cant focus, stress, shakes, racing heart, you name it and it happens. And my poor fiance has to deal with me when I get home xx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-02 00:07:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm using a micellar water cleanser and kiko's shine refine tonic. These are helping. I have also started taking vitamins B and D and turmuric and these have made a clear difference too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 18:55:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I make jamaican jerk wings and also a use a diet doctor recipe with orange zest and ginger. We're having wings tonight, yum! Xx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 18:45:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No advice needed, its stunning! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-22 22:06:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup I'm living that same life right now 😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-21 14:50:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beautiful rings! My HTB has the same style as yours! X </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 08:53:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This. 100% all of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 00:33:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> GINA NO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 10:21:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yay that's such an exciting milestone!! Our little boy started walking on his 1st birthday and hasnt stopped for a second since.

We got him a shopping trolley off amazon about 3 months ago (he's 20 months now) and although he definitely doesn't need it to walk he loves pushing it round and going shopping in the kitchen 😊 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-02 21:02:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy cake day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-26 02:47:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha it confused me because I'm from England and know them as bullrushes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-26 02:39:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mum used to use these as decoration in the house. She would spray them with hairspray to stop them from bursting, but it would only last a few months before they got too hot or dry or whatever and just spew seeds all over the living room. It seriously caught her off guard every single time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-02 16:06:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like she's in the UK where abortions are free on the NHS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 00:10:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's entirely possible. However pcos can make periods irregular so best to take a test to be sure.

Also, stress can make periods late aswell so it might just be all this craziness from Coronavirus.

I'd recommend a pink dye or clear blue test as they are the most accurate if it's still really early in the pregnancy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-22 11:12:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy cake day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-21 20:36:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy cake day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Another Coronavirus meme. Day 7 here. Stay safe people! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-20 21:41:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-19 21:16:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This recipe is identical to the one on dietdoctor.com, except they specify that it should be a green pepper used instead of red as the carbs are lower.

It's a really tasty recipe, will be making it again soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-19 19:09:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Minecraft, little big planet, fortnite, overcooked, wizards journey, sims.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 11:03:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy cake day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-16 21:53:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A very happy unbirthdayyyyy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-16 13:21:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mum went to her local supermarket today on a large expat urbanisation, she said the shelves were all restocked but she had to queue for an hour to get inside. They would only let 40 people in at once and you are restricted to 6 max per item.

She then offered to bring us some supplies and borrow some gravy granules, haha not after standing next to all those people!

Are they clapping on roofs and balconies at 8pm there? Its gaining momentum here, there were even fireworks last night so we will have to put little one to bed a little later and let him join in I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-16 10:12:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy cake day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-15 23:29:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How are the supermarkets there looking? Mercadona and Consum here have been absolutely ransacked. We are lucky to have Tesco, it's the only shop with anything in because it gets deliveries so frequently and stocks a lot more frozen produce than most shops here.

Good luck in the lockdown! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-15 23:12:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha oops, it was meant to say pepperami and nuts. That will be the rum typing 😂 Got all our snacks and frozen food from "The Food Co." AKA Tesco in Puerto de Mazarrón. They will be opening more stores around Spain too.

Where in Spain are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-15 21:04:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And ALOT of rum

Edit: emphasis on amount of rum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-15 20:32:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Freezer filled with meat and veggies, 4 packs of bacon in the fridge, a ton of UHT milk for our little boy, and pepperami nuts for snacks. Couldn't get any eggs, will try again in a couple of days. We are in lockdown here (Murcia, Spain) but can still go shopping/pharmacy/medical centre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-14 11:11:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congratulations!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-13 22:56:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks delicious! Upvote from Puerto de Mazarrón, Murcia, also in lockdown. Stay safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 22:29:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I snack on a chunk of mature cheddar. Being quite strong I can't eat too much of it so it stops me from overeating, and it's a good source of fat and protein to help satiate me until my next meal.

For me it's not about stopping snacking it's about what you snack.

You can also try having some cooked chicken in the fridge ready to eat, again it's more filling than nuts and not as easy to overeat.

And weigh everything onto a separate plate/bowl before you eat it so you dont have any more accidents with eating too much while zoned out.

Good luck OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 10:10:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you want to ask me anything I'll be more than happy to help. I don't have all the answers but don't have an agenda either lol. Dm me if you want x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 00:10:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know it, I feel it already too. I think it's a natural feeling as so many brides seem to get it. Just know that you totally rock this dress! Your tribe knows you well 😊 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-06 22:34:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg this dress is stunning! I bet it is a perfect reflection of your personality too, which is what you want from your wedding dress! Mine is not traditional in the slightest, and is nothing like the dress I thought I'd get, but it is more me than any of the thousand dresses I saw online.

Honestly its gorgeous, looks incredible on you and will make jaws drop 💖 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-06 22:30:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Babycenter and the bump apps were both so helpful to me while pregnant and when LO was born. Honestly I would have been so lost without them. My Nmum tried to give me advice but it was actually wrong a lot of the time and made me wonder how I survived my childhood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 22:19:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry for the essay lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 22:19:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She's just a typical narcissist and is trying to make it about her. She is trying to get an apology from my fiancees parents for something they havent done (not intentionally anyway) and is using the wedding as leverage over them, and us. She was hoping I would get upset and end up begging them to make it right and she would win. She keeps posting about "I hope they make it right before I miss my daughter getting married". Problem is as an only child of a single mother I had my eyes closed to her behaviour for my whole life, and now I'm not accepting it any longer. She almost ruined our engagement,  she did ruin the birth of our son, she's not ruining our wedding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 22:03:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can I ask, what gives you that impression? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-25 16:02:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yeah, they lay it on thick that you should breastfeed. My boy wouldn't latch properly so I expressed and then fed it him in a bottle, but I always got grief from his paediatrician, and Spanish people who passed us bottle feeding him out of the house would judge us. When we switched to formula due to my production dropping to 3oz a day (yep, total) that was a whole new issue 🙄 Also I wouldnt have been paid anything the extra month if I had taken it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-25 15:37:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spain is 16 weeks (20 if you're breastfeeding) paid by the government, but they take their time about it. My son was 14 weeks old when I finally got any maternity pay, so luckily we had saved enough to pay our rent and bills in that time, and have amazing family and friends who would pop in with food and nappies and other things to help us out. Life with a newborn is hard enough, without all the added crap from employers and the government.

Good luck OP xx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 19:52:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You got this!!!  💪💪

Dont think too far ahead, just take it day by day and it'll become second nature again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 19:14:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Former retail banker here. Worked my way up through the branch roles from cashier/teller to branch manager.

She was in the wrong for saying it the way she did, and I would hope the head cashier/controls manager/branch manager picked her up on it. She did need to say something, but not like that. A gentle referral to a personal banker would have been an ideal way for her to handle it.

I'm sorry she was so rude to you, and I'm especially sorry you had to deal with that on top of your husband just passing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 19:03:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a very good idea. My friend has my toddler when I need her to, and I'm having her 3 boys for 2 hours a week so she can go back to work (filling the gap between her leaving for work and their dad getting home) Mum friends are so important as they understand the struggle and will (hopefully) help when they can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-20 21:29:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I made these this week from the diet doctor website. They were amazing! I added a sprinkling of cayenne on top for a little kick and it was just what it needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-20 17:36:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The picture didnt make me wince but that comment did 😖 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 13:57:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congratulations!!

Be prepared for your wife to be cranky and hormonal both during pregnancy and after birth. Silly things like dropping something can evoke every reaction from tears and anger to hysterical laughter. You have been warned!!

If momma is breastfeeding or pumping she will be super hungry and thirsty all the time, but wont even notice. Provide her with cushions, a drink and snacks.

Once baby is here and you know what size nappies you need stock up. There is nothing more frustrating than having to rummage through drawers and changing bag to find a couple of nappies on a sunday night to last till the morning.

Buy jumperoos/walkers 2nd hand, after spending €80 on a vibrating rocker chair he used twice then decided he hated I've bought everything else off facebook.

Don't buy too much clothing too soon, I know its tempting but you will end up with so many unworn clothes after everyone gives you "teeny tiny adorable outfits they just couldn't resist."

Don't pressure her to breastfeed. Sometimes it doesn't work, and that's ok. I managed 3 weeks pumping to give my boy breastmilk as he wouldn't latch, which meant I was plugged into the wall for roughly 18/24 hours a day! At my best I produced max 8 oz a day and was utterly miserable. Switching to formula gave me my freedom back to enjoy being a mum instead of a dairy cow.

And be prepared for when you're at work and she's at home for her to feel slightly jealous that you get to leave the house without a baby. If she says you need milk and wants to go alone, let her, she probably needs that 20 minute break and will almost definitely scoff some chocolate in the carpark before coming home.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 18:37:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so sorry. It's not nice at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-11 21:52:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg I could eat a slice of oreo cheesecake and be within my macros! I'm so excited! 😊😊 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 09:51:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know how you feel, I had people ready to rugby tackle mine if needed 😂

Seriously, just do what you need to do to enjoy your day, even if it means nipping any bad behaviour in the bud like you would with a toddler, and when she throws a tantrum remind her where the door is (or send her to the naughty seat 😂) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 23:21:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I swear my heart just skipped a beat - over 500! What is your ideal attendance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 23:17:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so sorry, that really sucks :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 23:09:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ugh that would really annoy me. I bet she had a face on for your whole wedding day too!

I'm hoping my mum doesn't change her tune like that. She didnt get the reaction she wanted either, and still has the invitation on the fridge. Gonna send her some information on cruises next week I think 😊 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 22:23:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha you're totally right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 21:43:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah :/ Not ready to go into the whole thing yet, but long story short she doesn't like my fiance or my in-laws, or their friends, or my friends, or her own sister who I've invited.. so she'd rather go on a cruise than put herself through that.

It will actually be a more relaxed experience for everyone, so although I'm upset I'm also a little relieved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 21:14:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mum was pushing for courtesy invites too. She has now decided she isn't going herself. She was the first to get an invitation when they arrived and so as soon as she told me she wasnt coming I went home and crossed all her guests off the list!

Nope
Nope
Nope

If she gets questioned why they haven't received their invites yet she will have to explain that she's not going either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 22:45:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yum! Gonna need the recipe please! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-31 20:47:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would say ESH. Only because everyone should have had a person with a healthy weight and a "Patty" to work with to make it fair. I get that you would need to be able to take a BP and BPM reading on all shapes and sizes, but for the teacher to fail someone based on a test that is harder for them than others is unfair. However you should  have phrased it differently instead of coming across rude about Patty's size. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-31 16:27:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >It's super comfortable and it has pockets!

Everytime someone compliments a dress 😊 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-30 16:19:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is hard to keep up, without this it would take a lot more mental effort to work out your exact carb intake. Be aware that some food has been input slightly incorrectly by other users, so check the packet against the app. And remember to drink lots of water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-30 16:02:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We're using myfitnesspal, you can change the macros in it. it's not precise unless you pay for pro but it gives you a really good guide as to how your doing daily hitting those macros. You can also put in your weight and measurements so you can see the changes on a graph and it helps you appreciate even the small wins. You can scan the barcode on the food packet and input the amount you are having, so dont freak out when it comes up with 9gs carbs for 100g parmasan for example, just change the portion to what you're actually having and it'll be much less. Good luck! We are 2 weeks in and lost around 2 kilos each already. X </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-28 22:17:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I seem to remember this being on here a few weeks ago from the other POV. Or have I been dreaming about AITA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-28 22:13:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >rather than little girls in adult bodies

I read that as little girls in adult boobies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-28 22:10:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw man that is a cute baby! 🥰 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-26 17:06:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Parenting advice is typically to give a baby a relaxing bath before bed to aid sleep and we just ended up sticking to the same routine. Except now it's not a relaxing bath, it's more of an opportunity for him to burn off any remaining energy before bed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 22:10:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ours has the same, reply by Jan 31st or bring a chair and a sandwich. Still only 15 people confirmed so far. Lots of people will be eating stale sandwiches at our wedding haha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-23 14:51:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck Colgate - the 10th dentist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-21 15:26:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel the belt is drawing attention to your waist and making your torso look shorter. But it does add a bit of bling.. perhaps a sash with some jewels on.

The dress is gorgeous btw, and suits you perfectly. 💖 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-21 15:02:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congrats on your upcoming wedding! We are on day 5 of Keto and getting Married in October, and I would hate to miss our reception with a carb hangover! 😣

You've done so well already, well done! And thanks for the helpful tips 😊 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-18 17:15:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously impressive! Well done 😊 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-17 20:38:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> POUR THE CHAMPAAGGGNNNEE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 23:51:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Day 1 of keto.

No breakfast as such, just coffee.

Made keto creamy carrot soup for lunch. Approx 150 cals and 3g carbs.

Burnt off 150 cals on exercise bike

Made pork stroganoff with cauliflower rice for dinner.

Actually really impressed with myself, and even at nearly midnight I'm not hungry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 22:42:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pork/beef stroganoff is keto friendly, at least the recipe I use is. I used cauliflower rice as replacement rice and it was delicious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 21:25:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah.. dont get him wet or feed him after midnight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 17:42:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Be their safe place. Encourage open conversation, establish trust and dont make promises you dont intent to keep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-11 10:14:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-10 22:16:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg sounds like a really tough time. I'm sorry you went through all that and hope you are feeling better now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-09 23:42:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wedding date buddies! In the process of doing ours now, my choice hotel wants actual names and dates and even passport numbers to block any rooms out though, and it's a bit frustrating people arnt getting back to me very quickly!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-09 10:29:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Remind me! 18 hours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-09 00:04:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish I could upvote this every time it makes me laugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-02 01:08:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really proud of you for sharing this with us.

I'm going to say it sounds like post natal depression/anxiety. I felt exactly the same when my boy was crying as a baby. Not always, but if he had a bad day with teething or colic and I'd not slept well it got BAD.

Ask your midwife/health visitor/doctor for support and medication.

And know that with time your baby will get better at communicating their needs and you will be able to know without even thinking about it what the problem could be.

Good Luck OP. 💙 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-01 11:27:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too! 297 days to go! 🥰 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-31 22:54:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just because it isnt fair to get mad doesn't mean you wont. When you're up for the 5th time that night, he's snoring and rolled onto your side of the bed and you've given up even trying to sleep you'll be ready to smother him with a pillow.

Dont. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-31 05:46:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My boyfriend joked that if he wanted to hide something from me at 8 months pregnant he only had to put it on the floor 😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-31 05:37:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like your wife needs a satisfier or womanizer type toy instead. Less harsh than a vibrator.

Don't expect to see her for a while after she opens it though Haha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-28 23:19:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends where in Europe you are. In England it can be anywhere from a couple of pounds to 10% of the meal depending on the service. In Spain tipping by the locals isnt normal but by tourists is expected, again just a couple of Euros is plenty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-26 10:21:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YoU'rE NuTS 😂

Have a great Boxing day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-26 10:09:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doesn't matter whether it was assumed, the fact is OP knew and wasnt told not to say anything. I've been pregnant and didnt want everyone to know before 12 weeks had passed, told our parents only because of the number of doctors and bathroom visits they would have worried, and told them not to tell anyone.

My mum told people in the estate agents next to my work (so she could be nearer to us) and naturally everyone in our town knew within a few days.

That's a fuck up, because I said not to tell people.

But if someone told me someone was pregnant and didnt say it was a secret I would assume (rightly or wrongly) that it was public knowledge because otherwise why tell me?!

I mean that's just my opinion.

And yes, BFF rolling their eyes and then not denying it when OP guesses correctly counts as telling OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-26 10:01:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No his sister did, OP's BFF, I know that. She should have said "my family doesn't know so keep it to yourself" or just not told OP at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-26 09:38:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> However if she was less than 12 weeks pregnant OP shouldn't have been told, or should have been told not to tell anyone as it's too early in the pregnancy for everyone to know in case something goes wrong. So my point still stands . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 08:44:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To be fair most expecting parents tell people at around 12 weeks so how were you to know they hadn't yet (as with 5 months left I'm guessing shes somewhere between 16-18 weeks). Your friend should have said it was a secret to avoid you accidentally spilling it, or just not told you in the first place.

You didn't fuck up as such, you were put in a tricky situation without warning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-18 21:52:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I'm gonna agree with the others and say you can't leak it all out once and it's gone. I struggled to breastfeed, I ended up taking my boy to hospital thinking something was wrong and it turned out he was under fed and almost jaundiced because he wasnt getting enough milk from me even with pumping almost continuously and trying to breastfeed, so I switched to formula. My milk took about 5 days to dry up, and even a hot shower made me leak all over the place! And to avoid mastitis I had to keep "taking the edge off" by pumping a few ounces, because SERIOUSLY swollen and sore boobs are not fun.

Sorry you have an Nmum. Being aware of it now is a good step towards protecting yourself and your baby in the future.

Good luck OP, need any advice or an ear to listen please dm me xx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-18 21:02:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would get counselling for this. Its not lame, its self care. You will likely keep replaying the scene over and over in your mind, which isn't good for you. And your kids need their mum at her best. Do what you feel is right for you all, counselling and limited in-laws access included.

And congratulations on your wedding! Xx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-18 11:59:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are seriously rocking this dress! Perfect figure for it! 💗

I agree with above comments, see if you can get some extra fabric added to the cleavage area if you are feeling a bit self conscious or over exposed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-18 10:35:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA

They couldn't afford to home themselves and their newborn and you stepped up, and provided food nappies and the rest, and helped them care for the newborn, and then at the last minute offered to have their baby for a few days, and instead of showing gratitude she decides to tear down your ability to care for a child because you dont have one?

Sounds to me like you already looked after more than 1 baby for 6 months.

And assuming someone else will take care of their kid so they can go away, I mean that's just pure entitled.

Me and my fiance have a toddler and have been away without him for the weekend, but we have always asked our parents first if they can have him. That's just common sense!

Sorry but I would let them cancel their weekend away, if you have the baby now they will continue to treat you like this because you'll be telling them it's ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 09:13:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. I really hope she doesn't do that to you.

Be strong, you and baby don't need the stress. This is the time to be putting up your poor swollen feet and resting ready for your LO's arrival.

You're always welcome to DM me if you need some support, with Nmum or baby stuff 💗 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-09 22:12:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >Massive pressure to come with myself and DH to appointments, and to be there when I give birth. In the end she backed off about my scans, but only after I made it clear I didn't want her there and still with much guilt tripping. In an argument today she essentially said that she should be in the delivery room because she's my mother and she was here first (vs DH who you know, is only my husband).

This is ringing some SERIOUS alarm bells. I mean don't get me wrong it all is. But this is exactly the same as my Nmum.

Mine ended up camped out in the waiting room during my labour (after being told not to come until I had given birth as she wouldn't be allowed into the delivery room anyway and would have to wait at least an hour to see us, so she should get a good nights rest and then use that time to make the 30 min journey to the hospital), she repeatedly pressed the bell for a nurse to ask if she could come in, and was told no every time, and was also messaging me to ask me to let her in (I ignored the messages). About 30 mins after I had given birth my OH messaged her to let her know, and she rang the bell again and demanded the nurse make me let her in! At this point I was still being stitched up and my placenta was being examined by the student nurse, no way I was letting her in!

So she left. No goodbye message, no apology, nothing. My OH went out to say we were being taken up to the maternity ward and she could come see us and she just wasn't there.

And that is how my Nmum made what should have been one of the best days of our lives all about her.

Moral of the story: Dont tell her you're in labour. Maybe even give yourself some time to bond and be a family before you tell her you've given birth.

And buy your own cute things. You want to remember your LO dressed in love, not spite.

Good luck OP. ♡♡ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-06 10:27:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't watched the news in almost a decade, but hadn't been able to put my finger on the reason why, I just knew it made me feel "off" for the rest of the day.

Thank you for helping me figure out what was wrong.

Self care is more important than watching the news just to be in the loop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-27 07:47:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you I'll take a read through it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-26 22:51:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hope you have an amazing Christmas just you SO and puppy.

Finally getting our 1st Christmas in our own home without my Nmom this year and we are so excited! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-26 22:30:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My SO wont even be in the same room as her now. He tried for my sake, as did his parents  but they are sick of her games and lies.

Our problem is I didnt realise she was a Narcissist until I met them and I realised what a family is supposed to look like, so I haven't been protecting myself or my SO from her for very long and that means I opened us up to her schemes unwittingly. Thankfully she hasn't got between us, but I'm sure she has managed to sabotage my relationships and friendships in the past.

Low contact is the best route I would say. Protect yourselves and be happy. 💕 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-26 22:00:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In a similar situation. My Nmum has never liked any of my boyfriends. I'm now engaged to the love of my life and she doesn't like him (or his family) I've come to realise it's because she feels like she's going to be replaced as the most important person in my life and she doesn't like that.

She has even tried to break us up, constantly talks shit about them all and tells her friends she's worried I'm changing because of them.

Be prepared for all of this behaviour as your relationship becomes more serious. And don't fall into the same trap I did where she acted all lovely and pally when I needed to rant about about living together (housework and money generally) and now holds those things I said against him.

Good luck with it all. As long as you are happy her opinion isn't important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-24 19:38:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha mine tried to do the same thing. I told her it's useless as she always leaves her phone at home anyway 😂😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 22:44:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are not dumb. The receptionist not having the paperwork ready is not your fault and your dads reaction to you telling him is not your fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 22:00:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >“you’re being brainwashed” (“OH NO! My Offspring Unit™ has gained sentience! We must regain control!”)

Are you sure you didn't receive an email from my mum?! Since I met my very understanding fiance I've heard this so many times "I'm worried your company is changing you/people I've talked to thing he's a bad influence" that sort of thing. What she really means is "I'm worried that he has made you see what a controlling asshat I really am and want you to hate him as much as I do, and the people who are worried are people I'm slagging him off to" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-05 20:43:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well done little guy! I hope you're prepared to never get a minutes peace again 😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-27 22:51:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didnt know I could! I was honestly so dehydrated after 😂 The cuddles and love after was so important, we're both excited to continue with this, but only because we know how much we love each other, if he had even the slightest bit if doubt it wouldn't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-26 23:52:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you 😘 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 18:07:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mum has always done this, from copying my clothes to getting the same theme of tattoo as me. I got butterflies on my leg 8 years ago, so she got a butterfly on her back, I wanted a rose tattoo on my back so she got a rose tattoo. I then didnt get the rose because I saw what was happening and she blew up! "How could I let her down like that, now she has a rose for no reason, she's stuck with it, without me it means nothing.."

She also likes to give me clothes in her style to try to mould me into a mini her, they go straight in the charity bag 😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 11:48:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My Nmum put a sliding lock on the bathroom door higher than I could reach so only she could lock the door. Our upstairs phone was in the bathroom so I would be having a bath and she would "need to use the phone" most nights. I also couldn't lock the door even when her boyfriends would stay over and one would frequently walk in on me, making me not want to have a bath, I would then get blasted out for being disgusting and called a tramp. I still feel weird locking the bathroom door, and do not like showering with anyone other than my fiance in the house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 11:33:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love this idea! Keeping it in my memory bank for if I decide to go NC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 08:12:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have your fingertips facing up, slide them in and as you're able to curve your fingers you'll feel a ridge in the "roof" or "top" of the vagina. That's where you want to be tapping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 00:25:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My pleasure 😉 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 00:06:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the follow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Losing my V(ixen) card ;) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 23:33:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Losing my (F31) V(ixen) card. True Story </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 23:04:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a long post, and I'm not the best at story writing, but it is the true story of my first time being a vixen/hotwife. Please enjoy :)

So I’m on Tinder, haven’t been very successful but that is the struggle of many hotwives. I swiped right on a guy who is hot and looked interesting, and we swapped numbers. Within a few minutes I got a couple of dick pics and a video, I honestly thought “oh great here we go..” and almost blocked him, but he seemed kind of sweet with it, so I gave him a shot.

By Thursday night just gone, we had been talking for a couple of weeks, not making plans just getting to know each other a bit more. He said how hard he had been working (as a personal trainer) So I joked that if he was free the next evening I could help him relax, and he was into it.

The next morning (Friday) cucky asked what we would be doing with our free evening. I mentioned I may have a date lined up. We had our usual discussion about how it would work because he doesn’t want anyone here or me to go to a strangers house, and I don’t want to have sex in a car, so we agreed if it actually happens it’s best in a hotel. I Messaged OG (Other Guy) about it and he agreed a hotel was a good idea, so cucky looked online and booked it for us.

When we got home from work I started getting ready, I made cucky paint my toenails to get him nice and submissive (he likes feet), and then put on his cage. I showered, chose a dress and got made up ready to go. We didnt have time for a warm up, so my good little cucky suggested I take my clitoral stimulator to warm up in the car.

Warming up in the car was so hot, with my dress pulled up and my pants pulled to the side my toy was really doing the job. I had to stop when we got in traffic, and I almost got too close to cumming before we even got there!

I checked into the hotel and cucky dropped me to the bar to meet OG, following a few minutes behind so OG wouldn’t know it was him. We sat and got to know each other over a drink, and got a bit flirty. I was the one to suggest going to the hotel, happy that he wasn’t a catfish or a weirdo.

As soon as we got in the lift at the hotel he started kissing me. Deep, passionate kisses that made my body tingle with anticipation. We got out the lift all giddy but behaving, and walked into the hotel room as calm as we could. The door had barely clicked closed when he started kissing me again, more desperate than before. He kissed my neck and bit my lip. He turned the lock, and I knew we were definitely going to have sex.

He resumed kissing me, and pushed me backwards onto the bed. He covered my neck and chest in kisses, then stood me up and took off my dress. He looked me up and down and bit his bottom lip, which made me feel like the sexiest woman alive. I took off his shirt and Jeans and he was rock hard in his tight red boxers.

He pushed me back onto the bed and we started kissing again, he pinned down my shoulders and started kissing his way down my body until he got to my pants. He pulled them to one side, and started gently licking my clit, his tongue felt amazing! After a few minutes of licking, he slid his fingers into my already dripping pussy and started rubbing my G-spot, first gently, then with a look to check I was ok with it, he started pounding me with his fingers, so hard and fast that I didn’t even have chance to feel the build up and I squirted for possibly the first time ever!

I needed a minute to compose myself, and let what had just happened sink in, so I pulled off his boxers, got on my hands and knees and started licking and sucking his 8 inch cock. It was longer than cucky’s, so when I took it all in I could feel it hit the back of my throat, which made me want to deep throat it. I started deepthroating him, loving the moans he was making in response, and getting wetter myself with his pleasure. He took my hair and started fucking my face until I was gagging. We recorded all of this and sent the video to cucky, who was sat in the car outside the hotel, knowing it would drive him wild.

He put a condom on (safety first!) And pushed me onto my back and guided his cock deep into my wet pussy, recording it for cuck. He  pulled in and out a couple of times to get comfortable, then he started fucking me rough and fast, and so hard the bed was thumping against the wall! It didn’t take long for me to squirt again, and again. He stopped after 3, letting us rest for a bit.

I took the opportunity while he was lay on his back to start sucking him again, he told me that he doesn’t normally cum without finishing himself off so that made me determined I was going to make him cum! I made it a really sloppy blowjob, and was sucking and stroking at the same when he said he was close and wanted to cum in my mouth, so I got on my knees and kept sucking until he grabbed his pulsating cock. I stuck my tongue out and caught his load in my mouth, swallowed it, and licked his cock clean, savouring all of his delicious cum.

After he came he forced me back onto my back and finger fucked me again, making me squirt again and again and again, until we were both tired and sweaty.

I took a shower, dried off and walked back into the bedroom naked, and we lay on the bed and talked for a bit, about our past relationships and work and other random things. He was about to go in the shower and as he got up he kissed me again. That kissing led to his fingers finding my pussy, another squirt, and then fucking again, and another squirt.

He went to get up and shower again, almost got off the bed, and somehow his fingers found my pussy again, squirt, squirt.. omg I was empty!!

He finally went in the shower and I got dressed, we might not have left the room otherwise. He came out the bathroom and got dressed himself, we had another long, sexually charged kiss, this one  recorded to show cucky how good our kiss was, and he left the room.

I stood at the bathroom door, looked in the mirror and just grinned at myself, not able to truly believe what had just happened. I waited 2 minutes and went down to the car where cuck was still waiting for me, eager to know what had happened.

He drove me home, listening intently to all of the details I could give him in my post sex haze. He was looking forward to reclaiming me when we got home.

When we got home he made me a drink, and sat on the floor to rub my feet while I told him more, and I read out the texts me and OG were sending each other, planning to meet again soon. I told him to lie on the floor so I could rest my feet on him, and I settled with one foot on his mouth and one on his neck, with him holding my glass. He was still locked up and getting really sore balls.

We went up to bed, where he licked my pussy until I was satisfied I was clean, and I finally let him out of his cage, but with his hands tied to the headboard so he couldn’t get tempted to touch what was no longer his. I sucked and licked his cock, telling him how much bigger OG's was and how I wish it was his cock in my mouth, and when he was about to cum told him he wasn’t allowed to cum in my mouth, and while I stroked him I teased him with the idea of OG hiding in our honeymoon suite so he could use me on our wedding night and then he would be the ultimate cuckold. This idea pushed him over the edge and he cum so hard it hit his pillow next to his head.

As it was my first time with another guy, I expected the comedown to start with the refractory period, so we had lots of cuddles and love you’s, before falling asleep at about 4am.

I'm getting wet again just writing this down and reliving it in my mind. I can’t wait for next time.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 20:03:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
>I would still show up to celebrate with you, and probably would refrain from eating if I couldn’t handle something.

With you there, I suffered too. Even went out to a restaurant for my birthday when I was unable to eat anything so at least my family could have a nice meal. Gonna have to say she sounds really selfish, and I wouldn't change my venue for one person. NTA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 19:13:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You might think that its weird and awkward to say that but it does work! Add it into your dating profile, regular no strings attached fun wanted, or something along those lines. The right person will come along, however, you may have to sleep with a few guys to find the right one. Dont overthink it just have fun! Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 00:03:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >4. You don't get to wake the baby up. If you wake up the baby, you will not be allowed back. Ever.

You wake it you bought it was our rule 😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 00:00:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like my mum all over tbh. I completely sympathise with you, and 100% agree that you are NTA and are doing the right thing putting your foot down. Babies need a schedule, if he is sleeping dont even open the door as you know you're just gonna get moaned at and then have to make drinks and food. I actually locked my gate on a couple of occasions so they would have to call me instead of banging on the door and waking us. Anyone of your family who tells you you're being selfish should expect a phone call every time your baby wakes in the night, because then they MIGHT understand just how tired you are. Take the time to bond, cry, sleep, eat and do what you need to do to be happy because that's what your baby needs. Being a mum is one of the hardest jobs in the world, and you're doing great Xx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 23:36:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No we havent, that's not something my cuck wants unless he becomes a regular bull/boyfriend. It was someone I met on tinder, I've been flaked on so many times that we had almost given up hope. So dont give up yet, your couple will be out there wishing they could meet someone who won't let them down. 😊🤞 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 23:09:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trust me I was a very lucky girl 😉 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 23:07:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 🙈😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 22:37:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I'm a vixen, potato/potahto 😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 22:35:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not this time. If we meet again maybe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> From last night, that's not my Fiance. Now officially a hotwife 😊 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 22:06:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 17:53:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She deserves better. Get your tongue in there to warm her up for bigger men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 1st time post here. Worst thing my Nmom has ever done. Very long. TLDR at bottom. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 21:19:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So at the time I let it wash over me, but what happened has never and will never be forgiven by me or my fiance.

Last september I gave birth to a beautiful, perfectly healthy baby boy. Labour started in the afternoon on my due date, and we didnt tell our parents until I was admitted onto the labour ward so as not to get them excited if it was another false alarm (we had a few).

So when I rang my mum at about 9pm while my fiance was getting some drinks and calling his parents. I told her the situation as it was, I had been admitted at 3cm dialated, was having an epidural so couldn't move and would be checked again at 1am. She said she wanted to come to the hospital now, but I told her not to because it was still early, and she wouldn't be allowed in the room so would be stuck waiting in the waiting area for a very long time. I said I would call again at 1am with an update. My OH's parents said they would go to bed and wait until our son was born to come down as they would take 30 mins to get there anyway. (My mum lives 2 streets away so would take the same time for her)

At 12.30 my Nmom starts calling me. She's waiting outside and wants to come in. When I tell her no she cant come in she starts ringing the bell to get a nurses attention to be allowed in. The nurse comes and tells us she's being a pest, can we tell her she's not allowed in. We're actually trying to get some sleep. (The epidural meant I could get cat naps in between checks) so I call her and tell her to stop ringing the bell, it's not my rules it's the hospital, she can't come in because my fiance was my birthing partner, and I could only have 1. She has a whinge but leaves us alone for a bit, and I text her with the update at just past 1am that I was more dialated but still not enough.

Now apparently between then and the call she got to say he was born she was out in the waiting room (a horrible room with big windows and about 6 seats, all occupied by another waiting family) sitting on the floor with her boyfriend at the time doing meditation to keep calm. Just waiting and getting more and more annoyed at the other family and at me and my fiance for not letting them in. (Apparently he should have left the room so she could be in there with me)

Our boy was born at 5.55am, and by 6.10 she was pestering the nurses to be allowed in, I was still being stitched up! We told them under no circumstances were they to let her in the delivery room, she had wait until I was up on the ward. So they told her no she couldn't go in, it would be another 30 mins.

She left.

No message, no call, nothing.

My fiance went out to get her while me and our boy were being moved upstairs, and she had gone. I messaged her after he told me, and she took hours to reply that she had to leave because the dogs were at home alone, and she was upset.

She didnt visit until the next day. Claimed to be too upset to visit the first day, and too tired from sitting in the waiting room all night "for no reason"

I haven't actually had it out with her over it, we have talked about it but she can't see past her feelings,basically butthurt because we should have let her swap with my fiance, we should have let her in while I was being stitched up, and she was not the first to hold him. But because she gets so annoyed at us for being selfish, despite me telling her not to come that early and warning her they would be waiting hours and wouldn't be allowed in, I just close off.

I know that if I let out my true feelings, or even a small portion of how me and my fiance feel, we would never speak again. There are only so many times I can say that she was warned without just telling her to stop being a dick and leave us alone if we hurt her that much.

Fiance hates her. He doesn't like many people and certainly doesn't suffer fools, but he has never hated someone like this. He sees how she treats me and it makes his blood boil so much, he despises her. Makes things a bit awkward for me, I still want her to be part of our life, but I can see why he feels like that.

The worst part is that I feel guilty for making her feel bad. That's what her narcissistic behaviour has taught me to feel, guilty, for wanting a private, peaceful birth for our son.

I dont need advice, because I know what you're all going to say. I just wanted to get it off my chest as I still can't actually believe it happened.

TLDR: Nmom came to hospital while i was in labour after being told not to as would be a long wait. Left after son was born, but before meeting him as they had been there so long (6 hours) they were tired and the dogs were alone. Didnt visit our son until the next day and blames my fiance for not allowing her in. Makes me feel guilty for the whole thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 12:33:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cant see the comment where someone asked what being English speaking has to do with it.. in case you didn't know, Murcia is in Spain 😏 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 08:49:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Me (F31) and cucky (M27) are going to be in Murcia City this weekend (6th-8th September) Message me if you want to play! (English speaking please) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 19:15:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 23:17:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty sure that would come out my mouth while I ride you, but it would be worth it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 11:15:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To the people saying why didnt she get the card in her own name by lying about her income.

You can lie about your income on your application but they dont look at income they look at credit score, maybe she's had shitty financial past and cant get a card in her own name.

Not justifying anything here just explaining as a personal banker how the application for a credit card works. I've had people with no income get accepted, and people with high income get declined. If she got declined and appealed the decision she would then have to prove her income, which obviously she couldn't do as she hasn't got one, and the application would actually damage her credit score further.

It was a shitty thing to do, and I hope if they ever end up in that kind of financial situation again they can tackle it together.

He needs to get his head out of the sand and take some responsibility, she needs to learn to talk to him before things get that bad. Easier said than done but no relationship can survive without communication. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-07 22:30:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chilli Doritos out the fridge. Mmm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 21:30:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My cuck and I have that sort of agreement. We actually have a contract, which is quite restrictive to be honest,  but it covers the vanilla stuff quite well. He isn't allowed sex with me, cant see me naked, can't cum without my permission, must offer to eat me out every day, cant refuse my advances, must clean up my bull and I if we ask him to, must help with preparation for a date, warm me up for a date and must fund the date (hotel, meal anything like that) we are new at it too and it's not all happened yet but it's fun to be in the right mindset even outside of your playtime with your bull. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 17:19:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me I enjoy being a sub/slave non sexually for the fact I can turn my mind off and just be focused on my bliss, even though I'm doing things to make you happy. I am dominant in all aspects of my vanilla life so to not be in control of a situation and being given instructions means I can switch off, and being used sexually puts me in subspace for the same reason, it's all about not having to think and just being in the moment and able to have fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-28 20:45:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-28 20:45:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Murcia Spain. Not the actual city but I'm not getting specific here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> (F)lashing in our local bar </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-28 20:39:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Looking for Bull with dominant tendencies. F31 Murcia </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-28 20:37:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-20 22:48:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being honest this is exactly how my boyfriend (now cuck) started off with the kink. I would wait for him to approach the subject, because if you start the conversation it could make him think you want to cheat or have cheated, which isn't the fantasy of cuckolding. Maybe when you are out together just a lingering look at a guy you would take a fancy to, or a passing comment on someone will entice him to talk about it. Just my opinion, because I know how that gets my cuck excited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-19 13:33:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 22:56:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 😂 I've done that too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hotwife/cuckoldress (F31) in need of a hung bull in Murcia region of Spain </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 21:54:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> F31. Hung Bull wanted in Murcia region of Spain for newbie Cuckoldress. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-18 21:43:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 1st time being spanked in public. Such a turn on! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-08 22:54:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> F31 sucking not my boyfriends cock and swallowed his cum </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-07 14:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-06 11:50:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spain, Costa Calida Region </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 18:17:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem. It's not something to rush into but I think in your situation could be worth a try. I'm on fetlife.com, it's been very helpful getting all the information and support to start the lifestyle change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 14:36:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you thought about cuckolding him? That way he gets to be sub to you and you can be sub to someone else. That's what me and my bf are doing now and we're both very happy with the situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-03 21:50:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi Cutie! 💖 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-02 20:47:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm on fetlife.com and tinder, so far I have met two good matches that way, so excited to play with them! It can be hard going and repetitive thinking you have someone you could meet and then they get cold feet or say something that turns you off, but I'm sure you'll find the right bull in the end. Good luck and happy hunting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-01 20:17:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 100% yes yes YES! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My cuck was disappointed it's not a cock in my mouth so I'm going to have to go back for seconds to get him better pictures. 1st time hotwifing. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-01 20:11:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-01 19:19:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm on fetlife.com, that's how I found my first bull. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The only photo evidence of my first time as a hotwife. Cuck is disappointed it's not a cock in my mouth, but I promised more photos next time 😈 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-01 19:08:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-01 18:15:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not for you my little cuck 😈 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 21:42:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> En Mazarrón. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-27 23:38:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would love nothing more than to meet up with you in Valencia, love that city! But my work is seasonal and taking time off now is not possible. Hope you have a great time though x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-27 08:23:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will you be going through Murcia/Cartegena? I'm a first time hotwife looking to find an experienced bull for my debut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
