<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject31</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 22:28:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 22:15:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love this outlook it has helped me think a bit differently about things especially with where I am at mentally at the moment. Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 22:12:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel alive when my mental health is good. I can do anything and be anything I want to be therefore anything will make me feel alive because life will feel amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 01:12:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand this feeling. Tell the doctor exactly what you have written. I hope the doctor you see understands mental health enough to help you, or even to refer you to a psychiatrist. They might ask you if anything happened 3 years ago whether it is big or small that may have caused you to start feeling this way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 01:03:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like this when I am depressed. Once the depression is gone or somewhat better I don't feel stupid or tired anymore. From my experiences with mental health I can answer with a yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 20:19:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think its from pushups. I have had mine for 7 years now from the pressure i put on my wrist. I haven't seen a doctor about it though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 01:43:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you know how it formed? I have one aswell about 2cms below yours on my wrist too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 20:45:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is the opposite for me. I feel more depressed during the day and for some reason at night time I feel a bit better. However it can hit me really bad at night time aswell and the thoughts racing through my mind are very destructive.
I hope things get better for you, no one deserves to feel this way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 17:38:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> London </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 03:29:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes I do, all the time its a terrible joy stealer and time waster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 20:40:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People can be so terrible :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 20:31:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 20:15:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah it is quite dead, I checked it out. I wanted to post something there but it looks very inactive. It seems like one of the least spoken about subjects it would be nice to have a community for it.
I hope so too thanks for commenting :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 20:13:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That actually makes sense. I will research more into adhd. I have been asked a few times if I have adhd because I have alot of energy and maybe other things they noticed about me but I knew nothing about adhd so I just denied it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 17:21:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have missed so many things because of depression and social anxiety too. Then I feel bad for not going,which makes it worse. I remember years ago my friend had a birthday outing with her friends. I went to her house to get ready we got to the train station tapped in with our oystercard  and I told her I couldn't go anymore. That was so bad of me, but I felt sick inside and I didn't even know that it was social anxiety. I was feeling depressed at the time and I didn't know what anxiety was or that I had that. My friend had to go without me. I probably ruined her birthday. I have let so many people down.Work is also a horrible experience for me.... I want to run away whilst I am there and I dread going. I would enjoy work if my mental health was good because it isn't a job that i dread when my mental health is good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 16:32:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does any one ever pretend to search for something in their bag to pass time in a social setting. I know there is nothing in my bag that I need. Sometimes I pull out a bottle of water to drink it and take my time. I always feel like I have to keep searching in my m bag to look busy when I know I feel uncomfortable where I am at. I don't know if anyone has ever noticed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 16:23:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do this all the time and sometimes the cars decide to slow down and stop for me and I just wished they didn't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 16:22:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 16:21:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Accurate + more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 16:17:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy birthday!!! I am happy hearing that you are happy. Thanks for the encouraging words. I wish you more joy and fulfilment. Good health,success and more. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 15:44:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I could type a whole book but I will start small.  Cluttering for me is very frustrating
In so many situations. I can't say all the things that I wish to say. My words come out sometimes sounding like a jumbled mess. I struggle to explain things to people. Sometimes I am fine with how fast I speak but I am not fine with when I have no control over it. It gives me so much anxiety. It is definitely affecting my career and any social encounter I have. There is so much I have to say about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can we discuss Cluttering speech </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 15:28:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can we share our experiences on cluttering speech please. I would like to be in a community that openly discusses this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 15:22:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes I have done this many times it irritates me. Also some people that I ask to order for me think they are doing me a favour by saying no. My friend said he likes to help people so making me order will help me.i get what he means but it leaves me feeling terrible after or I just want to run away. I get some people do not understand so I can't even be mad at them for not wanting to speak for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 02:43:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have experienced what you have described and i have the speech disorder 'cluttering'.
I also purposely avoid certains words aswell as it is a struggle and I do not want to be embarrassed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 02:26:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This makes sense to me. I can't always write out my thoughts and I have never really thought of it to do with my cluttering speech. What I have found from research is that it is part of dyslexia but I am not too sure. It does make sense to me that cluttering speech and dyslexia coexist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
