<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject25</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 13:22:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Atlantis (trident) design + kraken (probably octopus) figurehead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 11:57:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I found some very very similar rocks in my area that turned out to be calcite. At first glance it could also be quartz. If you have taken a fragment you can take the [acid test](https://geology.com/minerals/acid-test.shtml). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 10:59:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Surely someone with more knowledge answers. I have noticed that the piece has some bubble holes that could indicate that it is slag, it also has a less dense appearance than the obsidian that I have been able to see.

But I'm far from an expert and maybe it was formed naturally. In any case, it's a pretty cool piece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 10:53:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Obsidian comes to mind, but it may be some kind of slag that happens to be black. Do you know the procedence? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 10:30:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amazing. It has a *Moria* feel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 10:25:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tras leer todas las preguntas se me hace extraño que no preguntéis la edad, cuando parece que buena parte de esas respuestas se podrían explicar por el envejecimiento natural. En cualquier caso espero que os sirvan los datos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 14:46:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agree. Manganese/iron [dendrite](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dendrite_(crystal)) for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 13:18:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Microcrystalline quartz. Chert probably. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 12:18:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As spaniard can confirm the fart part. Similar to the Argentina form, we say "Estoy pedo" o "Estás pedo" for the vulgar "I'm drunk/You're drunk". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 14:39:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/FossilPorn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 14:04:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It doesn't look like any meteorite I've ever seen. On the other hand, if a meteorite (let's say the size of a golf ball) passed through your window, it would do a major damage. It may even retain enough heat to cause a small fire, depending on many conditions.

Most likely, if it came through the window, someone has thrown it.

In any case it is difficult to give a solid answer. Perhaps with more detailed photos.

As for a meteorite average appearance, [check here](https://meteorites.asu.edu/meteorites/meteorite-appearance). In my experience smooth surface and thumbprint-like features are usually a *must*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 19:40:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought that amber could form a botryoidal habit but not, you are right. When thinking about how amber forms it doesn't make sense that it has any habit of crystallization. Only could be amorphous.
As for the photo, Google tricked me. My bad!
Thank you very much for the correction! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 14:57:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A fragment of [botryoidal amber](https://www.washingtonminerals.com/sales/carnelian-693-17-1-t.jpg) maybe?
Edit: Sorry OP, this is not an option, my bad. See below. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 14:09:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Icaros in a cage? NEVER </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 10:03:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi! Need some help. This chunk is probably a gypsum form but I was told that could be teruelite (CaMg(CO3)2). I think teruelite has a different crystal habit and chemically it should have reacted to the acid, but I'm not sure.

\- Foliated, platy or rosette habit (not sure).

\- Vitreous, black/traslucent.

\- Mohs 3-5 (hard to check, very tiny crystals).

\- No reaction to HCL.

Any insight will be apreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ID help, info in comment. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 10:02:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 10:00:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The furry one in *goodboyerite*, the other one maybe lepidolite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 00:06:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 12:05:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, hard to guess further by the pic but you can say that is something high-carbon-based for sure.

Perhaps someone with more knowledge knows of a test to determine the composition more accurately. Now I'm curious too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 10:41:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it sticky? Then almost sure asphalt. If not it could be lignite or anthracite, some carbon mineral forms can have a glassy look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 10:04:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a liutenant! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 10:03:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The brain has its tricks! For me is at 20:46, probably because it was a special number between me and an old love, due to a movie of the same title (2046, Kar-Wai Wong). My brain "clicks" when I see that number, and I'm probably looking for it subconsciously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 09:42:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Related question to anyone reading. I have an identical couple of chunks. When I'm in doubt I make acid testing (I use diluted HCL). In my experience well formed quartz crystals are not affected by the solution.

Is it possible that other varieties of quartz crystallization are affected by the acid? Or what I have in my hands has a better chance of being a carbonate compound like calcite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Finished my first (but not last) walkthrough + achievements! Here some pics of my odyssey. I have tried to select the ones that do little to no spoiler. Such a beautiful game! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 09:07:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 08:35:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Balrog scene. Damn, I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 08:08:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right now I'm really into Assasin's Creed Odyssey so those 24h for exploring the beautiful Atlantis City sounds exciting! If I finish soon I would spend the rest of the time walking around Elysium. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 09:03:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very few but damn beautiful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 09:01:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Santiago de Compostela is in Galicia, northwestern Spain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 14:53:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The [Greenland shark](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Greenland_shark) has the longest known lifespan of all vertebrate species, one of them estimated to be somewhere between 272 and 512 years old (experts used its length and radiocarbon dating).

The shark would have been alive during major world events such as the founding of the US (1776), the arrival of the First Fleet at Botany Bay, NSW (1788), both World Wars (1914-1918 and 1939-1945) and the sinking of the Titanic (1912). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 15:03:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Origins](https://www.reddit.com/r/comics/comments/d1sm26/behold_the_ultimate_life_form/) (can't find the original from Shen subreddit, sorry)
From the great [u/shenanigansen](https://www.reddit.com/user/shenanigansen/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 12:35:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like quartz but if you have already given it a good cleaning with water, try adding a few drops of vinegar on the rock. If it bubbles, it could be a carbonate compound like calcite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 17:57:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for asking, I've been wanting to talk a bit about this topic in general terms for a long time.

First of all, a sincere apology to the OP if he/she has been offended, it is not our intention at all and of course that dish has nothing to envy to a paella.

First, it must be said that paella is not synonymous with seafood. Of course there are variants that carry it but it is not the original recipe nor the most popular among the Spanish people. For example, in my experience the [Valencian paella](https://www.recetasgratis.net/receta-de-paella-valenciana-autentica-11730.html) (chicken and certain vegetables and legumes) is the most popular. I am particularly a fan of "[paella de la huerta](https://cookpad.com/cl/recetas/902933-paella-de-la-huerta)" (from the garden? or something like... all vegetables).

Second, to be or not to be a paella has to do purely with the ingredients and the way to prepare them (particularly using a paella pan, which gives it its name). The end result may be more or less to your liking, it may not be better than the OP's rice with lobster).

Speaking from my experience, with family and friends, I think we have never seen a paella with lobster (although there is a similar dish called "[arroz con bogavante](https://unareceta.com/arroz-con-bogavante-y-almejas/)", more mellow in texture). I also don't know of any acquaintances who have used chorizo ​​in paella, I didn't know this was a real thing until I started on reddit. Another unusual thing is the mixed paella (chicken + seafood). It is not something that we like very much here, the common thing is chicken and/or rabbit or entirely seafood (which usually has [langostinos and or cigalas (prawns or very similar, not sure), squid and mejollón (a kind of mussel)](https://unareceta.com/paella-de-marisco-con-sepia/), and without going overkill because the protagonist must be the rice.

Another thing that people here like is "[arroz negro](https://www.pinterest.es/pin/654640495812414778/)" (black rice), which although it is cooked in a paella pan is not considered a paella (this is also a mystery to me, it could be called an "ink paella" for example).

I sincerely believe that the fault of the misunderstandings in the recipes lies with the Spanish restaurants, particularly those in tourist areas and the coast. They know that "paella" is a world famous word and that they can call a dish "arroz de x" and charge X amount for it or call it "paella de x" and charge 2X or 3X for it. It is business.

Hence, atrocities like [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tvedDQjDwX0) have been appearing online for years.

To anyone who bothers to read my long rant, I leave some tips to improve their paella, whatever the variant:

\- Use dry "[ñora](https://es.wikipedia.org/wiki/%C3%91ora)" pepper, it enhances the flavor and color.

\- If possible, use a [paella pan](https://encrypted-tbn0.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn%3AANd9GcSFlBzZnTYQnRNGw_lmYi9RrIb4qpFvRIHQVg&usqp=CAU) or the widest and shallowest pan you have. That's the key!

\- If possible, use homemade chicken broth instead of water (or lobster broth if you are making the seafood version).

\- Before adding the broth, fry the dry rice directly in the fried tomato (homemade fried tomato if possible). The rice will absorb the oil along with the taste. This also prevents pimples from sticking.


Edit: he -> he/she </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 14:33:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It baffles me how people downvote this type of comment in every free-style "paella". You said the truth in the most respectful way. As a valencian I die a bit every time this kind of rice is called paella but long ago I learned not to take part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 14:56:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree but since the video does not show that scratching and I do not know minerals that match that appearance and that have a hardness of 7 mohs or more, I have only been able to base my guess on the look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 13:41:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You won't find satisfying answers on this subreddit. Although [Kirlian Photography](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kirlian_photography) is certainly a purely mechanical-electrical technique, the subject of ["auras"](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aura_(paranormal)) as far as I know it is considered nowadays pseudoscience and/or fraud.

If you are only interested in building the device, surely the [photography subreddit](https://www.reddit.com/r/photography/) can help you (be careful, High voltage device, no joke).

As for the subject of aura... I couldn't tell you, but surely a quick search in the reddit bar for "aura" will lead you to some other specific subreddit.

I have put some links in the comment, I would recommend that you review them thoroughly before embarking on a construction job that will surely end in disappointment. Sorry if this is not the kind of answer you were looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 13:15:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It has a complicated answer. I would surely say The Witcher, Skyrim, WoW or any game with epic music, but when I played Subnautica (which has a very techno music and is very far from my usual style) I realized that I really enjoyed playing it.

I think that if the music matches the theme of the game, it immerses you in the atmosphere and has been carefully elaborated, it is the best music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 12:45:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like [galena](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Galena) to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 12:33:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Correct. They are the main or ["Galilean" moons](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Galilean_moons), the only ones that you could capture with your telephoto lens or telescope due to their size.
Edit: typo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 13:56:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're wellcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 12:39:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not fossil, just eroded gastropod conch (Not 100% sure but almost). It is nothing other than the operculum of the marine [gastropod Astraea/Bolma Rugosa](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bolma_rugosa), here in spain it's collected on the beaches and people call it "[piedra de jaqueca\*](https://1.bp.blogspot.com/-FVn2a1sh03U/Tmeh9nf558I/AAAAAAAAEhY/tm14QnDgZTQ/s1600/DSCF2745.JPG)". The operculum is a plate that develops on the dorsal and posterior part of the foot of the conch and that serves to close the opening when the animal retracts inside, constituting a true “door” that prevents access through the most vulnerable area.

\*Jaqueca means headache. Here is a myth, especially among older people, that these stones cure headaches. 🤷‍♂️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 11:49:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This.


The [wikipedia article](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Island) is very good.

Extract:

*"An* ***island*** *or* ***isle*** *is any piece of* [*sub-continental*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Continent) *land that is surrounded by* [*water*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Water)*."*

*"Differentiation from continents*

[*Greenland*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Greenland) *is the world's largest island, with an area of over 2.1 million km2, while* [*Australia*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Australia_(continent))*, the world's smallest continent, has an area of 7.6 million km2, but there is no standard of size that distinguishes islands from* [*continents*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Continent)*,*[*\[6\]*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Island#cite_note-google1-6) *or from* [*islets*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Islets)*.*[*\[7\]*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Island#cite_note-google7-7)

*There is a difference between islands and* [*continents*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Continent) *in terms of* [*geology*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Geology)*.*[*\[8\]*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Island#cite_note-8) *Continents are the largest* [*landmass*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Landmass) *of a particular* [*continental plate*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Continental_plate)*; this holds true for* [*Australia*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Australia_(continent))*, which sits on its own continental lithosphere and tectonic plate (the* [*Australian plate*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Australian_plate)*). By contrast, islands are either extensions of the* [*oceanic crust*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oceanic_crust) *(e.g. volcanic islands), or belong to a continental plate containing a larger landmass; the latter is the case of* [*Greenland*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Greenland)*, which sits on the* [*North American plate*](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/North_American_plate)*."* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 13:15:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does the last name *shark* exist in English-speaking countries? Because that would be a thing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm glad I signed up for the multi-adventure pack! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 14:28:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Some close encounters [legendary beasts spoiler] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 14:56:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 12:28:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a Valencian I have to admit that it is the closest thing to a real paella that I have seen on reddit in a long time. The quantity and arrangement of the seafood is a bit crazy but it gives the look. I am also glad to see a paella made in a paella pan (paellera, I don't know if it has an english name).

I take this opportunity to encourage people to try other paellas, the seafood one is neither the most popular (in here) nor the tastiest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 14:33:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you are trying to identify something in particular you can go to r/fossilid including photos and a description. If you know where was found much better.

If you are not sure if it is a fossil or a rock, go here r/whatsthisrock.

If you are looking for general advice to identify fossils in the field, it can be quite complicated or extremely simple, depending on what you find and its state of conservation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 13:26:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Perfection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 11:50:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds very good, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 11:33:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is green sauce made of? Garlic, parsley and olive oil? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 10:21:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Quartz.

Here in Spain we call this variants "[Jacinto de Compostela](https://es.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jacinto_de_Compostela)", not sure in english. They are usually double-terminated and varies in color depending on impurities.

Edit: Adding a bit more:
*Variety with a bipyramidal or only bipyramidal prismatic habit with an intense red color. Common in Triassic marls and gypsum (Keuper facies). In a broad sense, the rest of the quartz that appear with these are also called this way, although their color is different (colorless, white, pink, greenish, smoked, black ...).*
Translated from [here](https://www.regmurcia.com/servlet/s.Sl?sit=c,365,m,108&r=ReP-26901-DETALLE_REPORTAJESABUELO). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 10:12:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *This is fine* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "Hey, you!" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 10:11:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The water and lights in this game are mesmerizing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 10:08:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 13:45:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pintaza 👌 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 13:21:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The WHAT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 14:36:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm 36 and I love the three of them, specially Adventure Time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 13:51:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mmmm torreznos... yummy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 12:49:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a child I ran to the bed but jumped too hard and nailed the wall headfirst (like in cartoons). I was so small that my skull was still in the process of solidification and an internal cyst formed.

As the skull grew over the cyst the doctors had to remove part of my skull and now I am wearing a screw-down plaque to commemorate my magnificent jump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 12:21:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >Since I started working from home, I basically do take a siesta. I block off an hour on my calendar for lunch, but I'm rarely hungry so I just take a nap.

If you take a nap before lunch it is often called "siesta del borrego" (sheep's siesta or something like). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 12:04:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A very nice piece anyway. Keep it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 11:54:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But the most beautiful province, along with Galicia :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 11:51:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We all know how to dance sevillanas and make paellas. Of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 11:12:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hard to say. By appearance it could be hematite or galena. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 09:44:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A *FUS* can be a mistake. A *FUS RO DAH* is a premeditated attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 09:48:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *I... am an enchanter.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 15:01:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Habrá que probar! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 14:11:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm from Alicante and thought the same, but made a google search and appears to be a Puerto Rican recipe (but not found another Mallorca in Puerto Rico). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 09:38:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To be sure the fluorescence comes from the rock you need to break it a bit and check that it is not a surface layer. Some fungi/lichen can be fluorescent under UV light. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 10:26:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would be delighted as long as the flower is in a pot. No dying flowers please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 17:18:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't be sure of course. I have seen some fossil corals and some modern corals and to me looks like modern. I can be wrong, in that case you have an extremely well preserved one.
Wait a few hours, maybe someone with more experience reply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 14:07:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some recipes use cream with milk and sometimes the dough has egg and/or milk. I suppose they used substitutes like oat milk or soy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 09:02:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not a fossil, modern coral... Or maybe lettuce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 14:42:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The second most popular variant of our "Tortilla de patata" is the one with onion (my favourite one, here in Spain there is a big fight about how is better, with or without onion. All of them are a blessing!), then the onion and zucchini one, and from here you can escalate to the "[Tortilla de la huerta](https://4.bp.blogspot.com/-vdhyZ68LwT8/W5eD3gK-o6I/AAAAAAAAIZM/6CAqJpWLuRAecyjepMomPCLSCCrWxdd-QCLcBGAs/s1600/Tortilla%2Bde%2Bla%2Bhuerta.png)" (any vegetable you can think of can fit, just why not?). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 14:58:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mmmm this could work nice with rum, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 08:35:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Before you get to the builds the initial playstyles are:

&#x200B;

Crusader: Protection-style-crusher

Barbarian: Berserker-style-crusher

Monk: Speedy-puncher

DHunter: Speedy-thing-thrower

Necro/WDoctor: thing-summoner

Mage: Elemental-melter

&#x200B;

Of course this is just an initial brushstroke. When you reach level 70 and start to get sets you will have more concrete options.

The best advice I can give you is to try each class little by little, they all have their charm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 09:48:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Last Waterbender </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 13:19:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Found these tiny iron-ish crystals. Could it be hematite? Goethite? Maybe oxidized pyrite?

The zone is mostly made of clays and gypsum and it's easy to find tiny red quartzs.

Thank you all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ID help, ironish crystals. More info in comment. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 13:19:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 16:57:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I'm not sure what is ethical in some cases. Where I live is forbidden to take any rock because it is "geological heritage", but I saw those same GH been destroyed with the city expansion... Maybe you just saved it.
To polish or not? I like to keep the original aspect, raw. I like rocks/fossils not jewerly, but it's up to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 09:11:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To me looks like coral, genus *Hexagonaria* maybe*.*

Yours looks like [petoskey stone](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Petoskey_stone) but with a different kind of erosion, less smooth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 08:41:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To me looks more like calcite but I'm not sure. Is that pyrite? Very nice piece!
Edit: Spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 08:32:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To me looks like quartz too.
*Mohs Hardness of Common Objects*
*Fingernail	2 to 2.5*
*Copper sheet	3*
*Nail	3 to 6.5*
*Glass	4 to 7*
*Knife blade	5 to 6.5*
*Steel file	5 to 6.5*
*Streak plate	6.5 to 7*
*Quartz	7* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 18:42:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi, I have been fossil hunting in an area that is kind of famous for early whale bones.
The geological map mark the area as mostly pliocene. Besides, the area is rich in bivalves, gasteropods and corals.

Are any of these bones? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 14:57:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awesome reading! Thank you very much.
Indeed we have very interesting places like Cerro de la Cruz (http://www.senderosdealicante.com/geologicos/lugares/cruz.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 14:30:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Campello, Alicante (Spain) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 13:46:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi! Are those fossils or semi-modern? Gasteropods imprints maybe? Looks like stone formed around them but I'm not sure. Found in a beach in the east coast of spain. This part of the coast is famous for pliocene specimens.
Thank you in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Are those fossils? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 13:45:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 09:31:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was looking for some quartzs yesterday and found this. To me looks like flint, but I have never found flint before so... It has a matte-glassy look, a white patina and the crystalline part is dark-gray/smoky. I couldn't find any more of that.

About the terrain: It is a hill with a high content of clays and ocher. It is easy to find gypsum and small quartz pieces (red, black, milky, smoky).

Thank you all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ID Help </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 09:31:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What mineral makes the glitter effect? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-05 12:33:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 14:47:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I Agree. But to be fair, life is sex driven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-25 19:27:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Closer look: http://imgur.com/gallery/kbIIv4W </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-25 16:43:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It could be, I have searched for photos and looks almost the same. Nice add to my starting collection! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 18:39:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They would probably focus more on the poor whales. But I love sharks and megalodon was awesome so take my upvote! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 18:33:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Black N°1 - Type O Negative </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 16:52:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are right, it reacts. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 15:04:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just tried, no scratches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Marble maybe? Looks like milk </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 14:46:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 10:21:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spain here. Cachopo!  Is a dish characteristic of Asturian cuisine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 10:05:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 09:56:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Skyrim and Subnautica </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 09:45:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Seek fluid intake." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 08:06:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've felt the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 13:18:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mostly Subnautica and a bit of Diablo III season 20 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-12 10:02:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm really concerned because here things are going a bit crazy because misinformation. Every one in tv or media is an "expert" and -especially- old people can't really see the difference with a real expert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-12 09:40:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sadly it is not a matter of my interpretation (copy/paste fragment below, spanish original) but thanks to your explanation I understand what they were trying to say. It seems that now everything fits.

This fragment is going viral\* via whatsapp/telegram and lots of people really think they can avoid the virus just consuming hot drinks.

*"El virus no resiste el calor y muere si está expuesto a temperaturas mayores a 26-27 grados, por lo tanto debe consumirse abundantemente durante el día bebidas calientes como infusiones , caldos o simplemente agua caliente, estos líquidos calientes neutralizan el virus y son fáciles de ingerir."* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-12 08:51:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. It sounded like media nonsense to me but it seemed better to ask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-12 08:38:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> **Question: So I'm hearing/reading a lot about the Covid-19 dying above 26-27ºC (78-80ºF) but as far as I know human body averages 36–37°C (97–99°F). In my understanding the virus can't "live" in such a warm body. What am I missing?** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-28 18:13:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! Beautiful game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-28 12:07:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By a Reaper Leviathan, sorrounded by darkness... Nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-28 11:49:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ytUygPqjXEc](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ytUygPqjXEc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-27 12:48:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The trick is to have no choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-19 11:17:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >aggressively human

Agree. X-files has a very funny chapter about. *S10 E03 · Mulder and Scully Meet the Were-Monster* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-19 09:23:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agree. I use to recommend this one along with [The Thirteenth Floor](https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0139809/) & [Nirvana](https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0119794/). Three of them underrated.
Edit: spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-11 09:07:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I prefer not to advertise products but if someone wants the link let me know!

Edit: Since links seem to fail in chat here is the item. I found it on AliExpress and recognized it in the wallpaper. It will be perfect for cosplay but be careful, it is very sharp.

If link doesn't show search in AliExpress, look for "item 32884833016 mini knife"
https://es.aliexpress.com/item/32884833016.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Details </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-11 09:06:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-20 14:18:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Calm down Maurice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-17 12:25:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And I suppose your own radiations will keep bouncing inside your body, about 0.05 μSv. Sounds nice to me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-17 12:12:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here! To the point that I feel more comfortable with english than Valencian. I can no longer speak fluent Valencian but I still understand it. To be fair never spoke perfect Valencian since I grew up (and I'm still in) in Alicante and Castellano was my first one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-05 12:11:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As others have commented, they are indeed fish.

To elaborate a little more on the subject, do you ask because its shape resembles that of cetaceans (dolphins, whales)?

Well, about this it must be said that it is the cetaceans that resemble sharks (fish in general), since they are much older. Why they shape is similar to fish? Convergent Evolution. Although their origin is different they have evolved into a common shape because they have the same needs (swim as well as possible, catch prey). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-04 14:53:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hudson Hawk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-04 11:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take your upvote. Hail Hydra! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 08:45:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Be careful when choosing server. There are some Roleplay PVP servers.
Usually in server list, in the column type they appear:
\- RP -> Green text
\- RP-PVP -> Yellow text
Found [this](https://static.invenglobal.com/upload/image/2019/08/19/i1566246023508908.jpeg) screenshot for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 13:42:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ulver - Perdition City </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 09:56:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happened to me. I feel your pain.
Think of it as you are helping another one with the mount :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 08:32:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *I'm doing my part!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 15:55:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course, half a century goes a long way. It just seemed like a very stimulating read to me.

Could you recommend something more current? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 09:15:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Miss* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 08:28:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Carl Sagan wrote a book talking a lot about the brain and has some sections dedicated to sleep/dream.
I found it very interesting.

[The Dragons of Eden](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Dragons_of_Eden) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 13:38:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mars One

or

Mars Prime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 09:03:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! I'll try RareAware this weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 09:02:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-25 14:52:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What u/misc_fame said plus:


The smaller the child, the more need he has to sleep. It is the need for bone and muscle growth plus the energy consumption that entails. On the other hand children have to assimilate more information (I do not mean studies, the brain collects information that assimilates or processes during sleep). It is a necessity for a growing brain.

Those are the reasons why babies sleep so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 15:13:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To be fair the meaning is not bad at all. From the latin "Lux fer". It means "the light bringer", sometimes called "the morning star".

Tell the kid he has a cool name! Surely he needs a bit of support dealing with his name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 13:32:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't do that please. It's rude and disrespectful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 13:23:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think is nonsense.

Other animals from very different species had homosexual/bisexual behaviors. Some even can change sex in certain conditions (hermaphroditism if I'm not mistaken).

I remember reading about, many years ago, something in the line of:

*When studying homosexuality in groups of animals that have a very social way of life, we realized that the population did not decrease, but rather increased. Why? It seems that a high percentage of these animals tend to take care of others wounded / elderly / disabled to a greater or lesser extent, even more than females. This translates into greater biological success in the groups that contain these genes.*

**I can't remember source, only that the article was talking about research in animals (no humans involved or compared), so take this with a bit of salt.**

So maybe, in the end, homosexual related genes keep population high. It is something very interesting to think about.
Edit: typo, bad english </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 07:49:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry, just a bad joke about *Stranger Things - The Upside Down*  :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 14:42:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hawkins, Indiana? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 13:54:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the level of pollution remains more or less constant.

If your sky is level 7 or below of [this infographic](https://goldpaintphotography.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/light-pollution-levels_small.jpg), perhaps your only solution is to get good binoculars. They do not simply increase the apparent distance, but the amount of light that incides on them. You can see many more stars with them.

If you are really interested I recommend to you that ask in r/astronomy for a more proffesional response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 13:43:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The question is not when but WHERE. Check out this [light pollution map](https://www.lightpollutionmap.info/) and find places near you with the lowest polution rating.

The darker the sky, the more the stars will shine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 12:49:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry but you are both right. Before, religion and science intermingled.

Everyone had religious beliefs to a greater or lesser extent. The point is that some were blinded by religion and others accepted what was later science as part of religious mysticism.

I often remember the internal debates Darwin noted when working on the Origin of Species. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 14:33:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Firefly. *You can't take the sky from me* [🎶](https://emojipedia.org/multiple-musical-notes/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 13:32:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Pepito"

Simple and delicious. It is a beef and butter sandwich (Spain). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-29 13:43:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *The best is yet to come* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-23 08:09:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The point is that germanic cultures developed their own mythology (not based on greek/roman). Their gods are not their greek/roman counterparts, but a very (VERY) far "cousins".

They seem to have a common ancient ancestor, the Proto-Indo-European cultures.

For example the greek Zeus has the traits of Odin/Woden (father of All) and Thor/Thunaer (god of thunder). Or maybe it's the other way around. It is hard to know because their common ancestors are too far away and there is little or no information.

Found a very good explanation in r/askhistorians by u/Alkibiades415, if you are interested.

[https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/aej1i0/why\_is\_norse\_mythology\_so\_similar\_to\_greek/](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/aej1i0/why_is_norse_mythology_so_similar_to_greek/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 14:56:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Leveling! Especially with friends.
When I look back and everything I've played the best memories are not end-game, they are those first little steps and see your character grow in a certain way (I think especially in my WoW years). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 14:37:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It depends on the language. Here in spain it is true for (for example) *Miércoles* (Wednesday), because derivates from latin word *Mercurii* for Mercury planet, or *Jueves* (Thursday), *Jovis* latin word for Jupiter.

English case is different: (copy/pasta) *Old English Wōdnesdæg ‘day of Odin’, named after the Germanic god Odin or Woden; translation of late Latin Mercurii dies, Odin being equated with the Roman god Mercury. Compare with Dutch woensdag.*

Same for Thursday, for example (copy/pasta): *Old English Thu(n)resdæg ‘day of thunder’, named after Thunor or Thor, the Germanic god of thunder; translation of late Latin Jovis dies ‘day of Jupiter’, Thor being equated with the Roman god Jupiter. Compare with Dutch donderdag and German Donnerstag .*

Edit: just examples, there are more, like friday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 09:36:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It reminded me of a programmer job offer (*Swift/Apple* if I remember correctly) asking for 10 years of experience. At that time that particular language had at most two or three years of existence ...

The world of work is fantasy, so give some to your resume too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 13:03:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ["Nirvana"](https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0119794/), it's a very interesting thriller about AI and existential issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 13:49:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you have a dog it is a pretty regular feeling! And of course it is reciprocal :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 13:35:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, if you have survived everything that happens in the books you can survive to the end ... I don't know if I hate it or I love it but I think it is a suitable end.

Of course there were books that fascinated me and others were little more than a link to the next (but all of them enjoyable), but I strongly believe that the whole is what counts.

In short, I also wanted more, in fact right now I am sailing among other Stephen King books looking for flashes of The Tower and its characters. There are days when I want to read again the entire saga but I don't have the strength to go through all that again (emotionally speaking). I will let it rest a little more.

Whenever I see a comment about The Tower, that feeling wakes up again, like feeling "the beam" in the books ... In fact my only gilded comment was something about this!

You are not alone, my friend. Commala! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 13:12:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have always thought that The Dark Tower is a very complete reading that tests one's mental strength.

I recommend the saga to everyone, although I believe that nobody has listened to me yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 13:01:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn, we are old... I remember doing silly things like changing my avatar to get someone's attention.What times, when still give a shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 12:56:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why does my dad only talk about his adventures in Skyrim? Was it a  war or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 12:03:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agree. The best thing to do is to assume that someone around you can understand the conversation and take precautions to talk privately as if you were with your countrymen.

Spanish has also become a fairly common language, I was surprised by the number of people with whom I could have a basic conversation when I traveled through Scotland and Norway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 11:52:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Checked wikipedia and this is totally true. And, by far, bones are an animal product.

"Gelatin is a mixture of [peptides](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peptide) and [proteins](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Protein) produced by partial [hydrolysis](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hydrolysis) of collagen extracted from the skin, bones, and [connective tissues](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Connective_tissue) of animals such as domesticated [cattle](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cattle), [chicken](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chicken), [pigs](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pig), and [fish](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fish). "

[Source](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gelatin#Composition_and_properties) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 11:38:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or Koalas, specifically swimming koalas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 11:34:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I prefer the Credence Clearwater Revival "I Put a Spell On You" cover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 11:25:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A close friend and her family. They are americans but living in spain since 1980 plus minus. When they need to speak in private they change to english... Well, when we were kids that worked, but not anymore!

Anyway I have warned them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 11:08:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I don't believe in science"


Edit:Science is not a belief. It is a method to unveil the world around us and ourselves, and the conclusions drawn from that study you may like more or less, but they do not depend on your belief in it.

In addition, scientific thinking requires that you to be prepared for new proofs at any time and to not hold on to a point of view without evidence to support it.  - Sorry for the bad english </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 10:28:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In many places cheese + some sweet (like honey, marmalade) is a dessert.

The stronger the cheese, the better the combined flavor. For example cured spanish cheese with tomato jam is a delight, if you have the opportunity do not hesitate to try it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-13 13:14:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course you will get better and deeper answers in r/askscience, but I will try to advance more or less what they will answer:

>"was once super densly packed"

Pretty sure we do not know (for sure) this one, but we know universe is currently expanding, and any expansion needs a starting point. Thats why we think it started from a infinite density point.

>"why didn't it all collapse into a black hole"

On this one you can only speculate, since there is no way of knowing what happened before the Big Bang (there was even a "before"?). The concept of time is closely linked to space and at that supposed point of infinite density perhaps there was not even space/time ... but as I was saying we can only speculate :)

By the way make sure you check the topics in r/askscience, pretty sure the answer you are looking for is a hot topic occasionally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-13 08:55:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because they are! Check out [this image](https://www.universetoday.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/galilean_moons__earth_compared_1024.jpg) for a size comparison.Edit:  Found another of [Jupiter vs largest moons](https://farm9.staticflickr.com/8605/16644423011_dfba6b9eb7_b.jpg). More or less the proportion we see in your photo, saving the extra size generated by the brightness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-09 11:08:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then it will be next on my list. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-09 11:00:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just started it. I really liked the saga of the Dark Tower and it seemed to me that I should give a chance to other works of Mr. King. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-09 10:29:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Stand, Stephen King </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-09 09:45:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like to follow a theme, pharmaceutic for example.

*"Flutox the Dark"*

*"Propalgina of Rivia"*

You know...

Beer can be a good theme too, like *"Grimbergen the Wise"*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-08 14:50:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Hold my beer"
[Ponytail song](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BDg6-v9V8lo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-08 12:59:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Regular donor here. It'doesnt hurt as other redditors said. I think it's something rather psychological. Fear or apprehension of the needle or the sight of the blood (or the bag of blood) maybe.

I think it is a very rewarding experience because it costs very little effort in relation to the good it does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-08 12:46:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As other redditors said, it is not possible to happen, but the truth is that it is a very funny mental image! It's a matter of density. We could fatten (even with matter out of earth) each one to cover the entire surface of the planet and you would not get a black hole, just a rather weird and unpleasant image xD

Neutron stars have such a high gravity because all matter is compressed (there are no atoms or the internal space between atoms and their subparticles, only tight neutrons). At this point the gravity is so strong that eventually collapses on itself and, among other things, forms a black hole. Not the only way a black hole can form but the most well known.

A black hole is not such an object, but rather a place or location in space with particular conditions of extreme gravity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-07 13:58:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chicken unborns 12/pack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-07 11:54:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As another redditor has pointed, manufacturer requirements. Not only the lenses, the diaphragm mechanism needs to have the widest possible open / close range in a least bulky mechanism possible, and that can only be achieved with retractable moving parts with curvature.

Look at this picture:

[https://farm8.staticflickr.com/7222/7228218072\_042541190a.jpg](https://farm8.staticflickr.com/7222/7228218072_042541190a.jpg)

With a rectangular mechanism it is not possible (or at least it would not be easy at all) the turn, and therefore would need a much wider structure.

As for the image, the opening of the diaphragm projects a circular image on the sensor, with the entire sensor remaining within that circular point. Check out this image: [https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/8/82/Image\_circle.jpg/220px-Image\_circle.jpg](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/8/82/Image_circle.jpg/220px-Image_circle.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-06 14:53:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Awarded as best product of the year"
Yeah, sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-06 14:35:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Idiocy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-06 14:32:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Check out the [Darwin Awards](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Darwin_Awards)
"The Darwin Awards salute the improvement of the human genome by honoring those who accidentally remove themselves from it in a spectacular manner!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-06 08:42:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Source? Can't find googlin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-05 15:01:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eggs -> Unborn chickens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-05 13:25:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my experience (playing since 2016) 95% players I met are in the 20-50 age range and usually playing in groups.

A predator probably have more possibilities at the local pool.


Edit: Only kids I have seen were with their parents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-02 15:00:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Glühwein (spiced wine) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-02 14:47:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >chances are we wouldn’t recognise it


Not sure about that. Shared needs often ends in shared traits. We know this as "convergent evolution". For example fish and cetaceans share body shape besides different origins because some traits are best-performing on water environments.

So I could imagine a lot of kinda-animals with certain similarities with the earth ones if they share the type of environment.

If you are asking about intelligent ones, if they are in an evolutive stage not extremely far from us, I bet they'll have some kind of limbs with some kind of fingers (or maybe tentacles?) because technology needs manipulation. For the same reason I suppose it is easier (but not exclusive) to find a civilization that has evolved in a dry environment since fire and metal work in one way or another are necessary for mechanical and technological advancement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-02 14:19:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You will enjoy r/askscience too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-02 10:28:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spanish. I love the strength that insults have. The way each syllable is pronounced by saying "gilipollas" or "hijodeputa". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-02 10:21:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Entropy concept. Myself included. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 13:24:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *If we were randomly released within the Cosmos the probability that we were on a planet or near it, it would be less than one part in a billion billion billion (one followed by 33 zeros). In everyday life such a probability is considered void. The worlds are a precious thing.  - Carl Sagan*
\[poorly translated by me from the spanish edition\] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 12:29:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some months ago I asnswered something about astronomy, don't remember exactly what but the OP started with "I asked this in another forums and I didn't like the answers. I refuse to believe that".

As you can guess trying to answer the question was frustrating and a waste of time.

There are people who really want to know and others who just want someone to support their ideas, no matter what. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 11:05:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take more weight than you can safely lift. First day of training injured. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 10:29:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plankton represents about 98% of all ocean biomass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 10:23:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Canaries Islands owe their name not for the canaries (bird) but to the dogs (the Romans called them "Islands of the dogs" and dogs are "can/canes", spanish derivation from latin "canem/canibus"). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 09:46:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Adventure Time is awesome for kids and even more for adults. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-31 14:22:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agree. But give a chance this episode of season 10 "Mulder and Scully Meet the Were-Monster" ep3, I'ts special. Not related to other episodes so there's no spoiler danger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-31 14:14:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow! That's almost 70! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 15:01:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Playing a game is NOT (allways) wasted lifetime. As another redditor commented ( u/MarcusChapmanHere )  there are gorgeous stories (like Braid), wonderful landscapes (like Skyrim/Witcher) and much more.
At 34, I haven't stopped playing, and I hope I don't have to do it because of bigger obligations. As someone who has traveled and in general has done things in the real world, I can tell you that the memories you have about a game are different but not worse.

To those who have not given the games a chance, I can only say that they are missing something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 14:26:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is nothing better than not going where you have not been invited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 14:09:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In fact it's something like. The Earth attracts us and we attract the Earth. What happens is that the gravity of our mass is a negligible amount.

For an external observer it is relative. When you jump, is it the Earth that attracts you? You to Earth? The truth is that both are true.
Edits: bad english </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 12:44:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2001: A Space Odyssey or Blade Runner.
I'm not sure which one I love more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 12:37:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will try, but I promise nothing. This time I will leave the bed unmade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 12:29:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry, it was me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 12:05:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to enjoy watching the show "Forged in Fire", but every single time they get to the cutting test with animal corpses it makes me feel a bit more unconfortable.

It already hurts the way we treat animals in general but in that case it is even worse. Besides unpleasant it is a waste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-29 08:28:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >"Care knee asada"

Gorgeous. Made my day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-26 14:52:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! Totally intended :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-26 14:46:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, Earth would be better without us, so I guess some kind of genocide :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-26 14:05:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spanish here. The art loss has been worth it for the meme gain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-26 11:56:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Large Hadron Collider (LHC) discoveries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-26 10:27:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This question leads us to another interesting one: At what point does a puree become soup? Where is the line? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 13:21:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel your pain. *"Could you put a typography more ... striking?"* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 12:58:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How have you solved the problem of traveling long distances in space? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 12:53:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Since you are half father genes and half mother genes NOPE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 12:50:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spine. I'm a simple man, just want to get rid of hernias and pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 12:37:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oceans acidification (related to global warming).

Our seas could face a severe population decline due to the rise in acidity (tropical oceans not able to sustain coral reefs, polar oceans becoming corrosive to calcareous marine organisms and so on). By the way the calcareous marine corrosion lead to more carbon released to the atmosphere, wich lead to rising CO2 levels again.

Apart from ecological issues, the decline in quality and quantity of several species indeed affects the economies that rely heavily on the fisheries sector, thereby incurring heavy losses. Also regions with seafood as staple will hit numerous bottlenecks like food shortage, health issues etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 12:06:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I'm from Spain, not traveled a lot but noticed general behavior.  People get 'nicer' as you move away from ecuator. We have received a friendlier treatment in places with generally cold weather like Norway or northern Scotland.

Another thing I noticed is the "regular delinquency level" appears to be much lower. For example here in spain (specialy in major cityes) you can't left your bicycle in a shop entrance without surveillance or al least a chain. It disappears as soon as you turn.

When I was in Oslo I noticed a lot of behaviors that show confidence like openend windows without people in the house or unchained bicycles everywhere.

Allways thought (hot) climate affect a lot people behavior. The more I travel, the more convinced I am of it. Of course as I said I traveled very little and all that could have been just coincidences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 11:36:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you took out all the empty space in our atoms, the human race could fit in the volume of a sugar cube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 21:05:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To listen, my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 14:42:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Build my own computer.

I was scared as fuck but then I realized everything has their socket type and you only can plug it in there. Motheboard has instructions for the complicated ones. Success. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 14:01:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have read the saga and seen the movie and all I can say is that those in charge of the movie have forgotten their father's face.

Edit: First gold! Commala kind stranger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 12:59:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's it. You need to "fill" the sensor/celluloid with an amount of light, but since it is dim it needs more time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 12:56:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Practice. First you need to control euphory/happiness (make it only happen inside, not outside visible... after time even not important anymore). When you manage to control your positive states you are ready to practice on the negative ones.

Very effective but as you can guess you "lose sensitivity" in both ways. It's the price.

*The Hagakure* (book) talks a lot about this type of self control practices if you are interested. Half philosophical/psychological reading but is a good one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 12:44:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> \[Photography\] Well everytime I have to explain the relationship between shutter/diaphragm I like to use tap/water glass analogy.

If you open a bit the tap, the waterjet is very thin (diaphragm precision) but it takes longer to fill the glass (shutter timing).

The opposite fills fast but has a thick jet, less precise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 12:23:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “All things serve the Beam.” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 12:11:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I vote this one for r/stupidquestions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-24 11:46:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can have a web that actually works!

&#x200B;

Seriously speaking, I suppose you mean "hiring VS getting some prebuilt template". Templates are ok if you can adapt your needs to the template.

If you are looking for the opposite (personalized design, something adapted to your needs) then hire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 14:26:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well arachnids are not insect in the scientific way but...
[Maratus](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Maratus) spiders are so damn cute.
Pic for you: [https://i2.wp.com/entomologytoday.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/Maratus-volans-closeup-Jurgen-Otto.jpg?resize=878%2C584&ssl=1](https://i2.wp.com/entomologytoday.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/Maratus-volans-closeup-Jurgen-Otto.jpg?resize=878%2C584&ssl=1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 09:52:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not weird at all, it's beautifull. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 09:51:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A few years ago we traveled to Norway and spent a few days in Oslo. I remember having breakfast in a mountain shelter or something similar in Frognersetteren. There was fog but the views were spectacular and I was with the woman I love.

At that moment I felt at peace and it comes to my memory very often. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 09:43:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not exactly "based on" but if you ever played ["The Secret of Monkey Island" (1990 first one)](https://es.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Secret_of_Monkey_Island) you will have seen the similarities, much more than coincidences with *Pirates of the Caribbean*.

The plot has similarities and here some images:

[https://www.netambulo.com/wp-content/uploads/2007/05/turner\_guybrush.jpg](https://www.netambulo.com/wp-content/uploads/2007/05/turner_guybrush.jpg)

[https://i.ytimg.com/vi/8LmnedosUUY/maxresdefault.jpg](https://i.ytimg.com/vi/8LmnedosUUY/maxresdefault.jpg)

[http://cdn3.whatculture.com/images/2015/08/xlmPAdUf-600x338.jpg](http://cdn3.whatculture.com/images/2015/08/xlmPAdUf-600x338.jpg)

&#x200B;

It's a great game saga by the way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-21 18:39:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Dark Tower </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-19 14:15:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being attacked by a shark </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 14:38:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A bit early to be burned by the Inquisition but I would not take the risk. No thank you, I'll never tell anyone. I'll do my best to survive in the forest, far from city plagues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 14:32:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I must say that the movie reveals a bit, so try to forget as much as you can.

I've watched it mid saga and the Roland physical description got some merge in my imagination, I really liked Idris Elba as Roland.

You are with the first one so I have an advice for you. If you ever feel like "What the hell I'm reading?" just keep on. Sometimes it's like a roller coaster... The third volume really engaged me until the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 14:16:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's what I thought, but when someone says something like this and I respond with "but we are animals too... you know" starts an angry "I'm not an animal!"...

I'm tired of that, so I do not argue with them anymore.


Edit: "She" by the way, I'm the "he" in this case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 13:27:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Dark Tower.

The only good thing in this movie is the Roland characterization. Not the original, but very good.


Edit: Not only a 2h. film, but a saga. One for book at least! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 13:04:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I hate animals, they are only food". Was a first date so I'm happy I discovered this so fast. Payed for my coffee a left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 12:43:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To add a bit more: Looking back we will see that every time we have felt unique or special we have been wrong (when it was believed that the earth was the center of everything, for example). In this case, the same will probably happen.

In a couple of decades we will probably find microbial life in our own solar system and at some point in the future there will be a contact with another civilization. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 12:09:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Surely increase the entropy and end the universe as soon as possible. We are very efficient energy consumers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 12:03:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Coding. A Lot of people thinks it's something like "ey computer, do this thing \[ENTER\]". Same as photoshoping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 11:36:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Top Secret </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 11:29:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Silence, my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 12:28:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well maybe not "all star" but you can see a young George Clooney in [Return of the Killer Tomatoes! (1988) ](https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0095989/)
Edit: Another gold-one. Sean Connery in [Zardoz (1974)](https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0070948/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-16 09:59:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the correct answer.
Smell and taste a bit... if both are ok then eat. So simple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-12 14:56:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is also terribly irresponsible to make terraforming plans when a planet has not been explored in detail. If there is life, even if it is only bacterial, we have no right to colonize it. They must have their opportunity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-12 14:35:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For learning C/C++, easy but you need to know what are you doing to actually make things work.

If you only want a "first date" with programming maybe some mix of javascript/html/css can make the basic understandig plus some visual output. You only need a plain text editor and your browser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-12 13:25:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shark roar! Jaws: the Revenge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-12 13:12:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spanish here. Can confirm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-12 12:27:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Best way is just to say NO. Another approach is to say "Well maybe, but you have to \[insert equal or near cost/hours here\] for me. Free.". Then his/her face expression changes. Some understand it, others do not... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-12 09:39:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Waters in general. I remember snorkeling as a kid and there were a lot more wildlife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-09 10:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It fascinates me that all we can see and touch is basically empty space. At atomic sizes there are an electron-probability cloud and tiny nucleus. Between them there is a huge empty space. So we are made mostly of empty space and electromagnetic and nuclear forces keeping things together and/or keeping things separated.

In the same way, everything is made of the same components. The number of protons in an atom makes different elements. ¿2 protons? Helium. ¿79 protons? Gold. Thats crazy in a day-to-day way.

Those things amazes me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-08 13:33:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In the day before a paintball work-people game. A workmate and I were joking in the office about some mid-boss and A said "I want to hit with the butt of the gun, paint balls not enough" and the face of my mate... well... Mid-boss passing behind me.

I worked in there at least two or three years after the happening, so I suppose my work worth to keep me in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-05 14:44:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I'm just a bit overweight, but in my experience was an absolute win.

&#x200B;

Back in my teenager days I was in a very athlethic shape. For one reason or other girls never gave me a chance.

Then I had to stop doing sports due to an injury and ... When I got some weight they started to pay attention to me.

I will never know exactly why, maybe my physic spoke for me and told them I was brainless. Maybe I went on to look like a "real" person. I don't know.

I'm sure that my personality and my conversations did not change much from one phase to another. It was something physical.


Now I worry to only about to be in the healthy range, never again something like having a sixpack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-05 14:22:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spain here. Very touristic city (Alicante) and I want to share some experiences in my basic english:

&#x200B;

\- I met some Norwegian tourists extremely surprised that it was raining a lot when they arrived. It is true that it is not usual but **sometimes it rains**.

\- Some german friends having fun (I admit it's fun xD) when I heard that some miles away was snowing... This is an event here, never saw snow until I grew up and traveled a bit. Here winter is just a couple of weeks of insane cold and hummidity, then sun and heat again.

\- (Please) Do not tell to random people in the streets "dance a sevillana/flamenco"... well, most of us don't know about sevillanas/flamenco more than you (except in Sevilla maybe).

\- I don't know what is that wet-yellow-rice-thing that I see in some photos, but I assure you, that  **is not paella**.

Some tips for paella: Do not trust anything than contains seafod + vegetables + maybe other things. Mix-ones are bait for tourists.

&#x200B;

I know those things are films fault, not blaming anyone. It is fun as it's own way. And It has taught me to (try) not be "that" tourist when traveling.
By the way, thank you people from Scotland and Norway for being so hospitable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 18:44:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agree. Since I discovered r/askscience and r/sciences are a must-check every day. No matter the topic, allways learning something interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 14:58:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dogs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 14:56:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Science (amateur level, not a doctor!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 09:58:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When you ask yourself if it is you it becomes clear that you care about others, it is a point in favor and there are possibilities that you are not a toxic person. In my experience the toxic people I have met have in common a strong disregard for others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-03 14:39:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow missed the hidden comments. Sorry my bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-07 14:28:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because at the moment it is not essential to make babies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 13:06:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Usually it gets a state of "available to overwrite". It is hidden in a way.

The new data can occupy this space.

When you format a pendrive in a computer it ask you to choose between "fast" and "deep format". The first one does the "available to overwrite" while the second revoves the info. Thats why it takes long to format.

There are softwares to recover info in a disk if it was deleted by the fast method (and not overwritten).

Edit: bad english </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-05 12:18:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agree. Skyrim belongs to the Nords! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-05 10:19:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Experiments point to that hyperoxia (and specially aPO2 levels) modifies the size of an insect over some generations, so why treat it as a myth?

Of course further investigations will prove how much those circumstances are affecting the size, maybe a bit o maybe a lot, but it seems that it is a factor to be taken into account.

Sorry for my english, not first language.

Some sources

[https://royalsocietypublishing.org/doi/full/10.1098/rspb.2010.0001#d3e1504](https://royalsocietypublishing.org/doi/full/10.1098/rspb.2010.0001#d3e1504)

[https://www.quora.com/Could-giant-insects-be-grown-in-a-high-oxygen-atmosphere](https://www.quora.com/Could-giant-insects-be-grown-in-a-high-oxygen-atmosphere)

[https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2010/10/101029132924.htm](https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2010/10/101029132924.htm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 11:55:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I responded too some days ago similar question. I bring it to you:


>Just to add a very interesting example. **The Heikegani or "Samurai Crab"**.
>
>In short: They developed samurai faces in their shells because people in the area avoid to take the ones who has a face-like pattern. This human behavior leads to a high face-like poblation of crabs passing their genes.
>
>Long (and very interesting):
>
>[https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Heikegani](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Heikegani)
>
>And by Carl Sagan in Cosmos:
>
>[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dIeYPHCJ1B8](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dIeYPHCJ1B8)

Original post here: [https://www.reddit.com/r/askscience/comments/b25lvd/what\_effects\_are\_humans\_having\_on\_evolution\_of/](https://www.reddit.com/r/askscience/comments/b25lvd/what_effects_are_humans_having_on_evolution_of/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 09:48:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well not an expert, so take it with a bit of salt.

Just to clarify, we understand exoesqueleton creatures have not inner esqueleton, so we can avoid caparace creatures.

I have no knowledge of any exoesqueleton being out of the families of insects/mollusk/.. (invertebrated ones obviously).

During the Carboniferous period the oxigen levels reached 30%-35% and the size of insects (not sure if it affects all of the invertebrates) is directly related to the amount of oxigen available. In this perior there was insects up to 1m more or less.

About microscopic life nothing in my knowledge, I hope helped a bit with your question.

Edit: bad english sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-03 09:18:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The calf is impregnated with human smell and the mother can reject it (even with a very small contact, her sense of smell has evolved for that). In addition, you could be attacked by the mother if she sees you approaching her calf.

In short, it is not safe for both calf and human.  Edit: bad english </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-25 09:50:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In addition, many of these organisms have evolved bioluminescence systems: to predate (baiting the prey), for mating, camouflage, communication, etc.
These systems requires the eyes still existing and evolving. Some eyes have evolved to capture specific wavelengths, for example.


More info:

[https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bioluminescence](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bioluminescence)
[https://phys.org/news/2016-12-unique-visual-deep-sea-fish.html](https://phys.org/news/2016-12-unique-visual-deep-sea-fish.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-19 14:56:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> \+1 To all said by u/aClimateScientist


Just to clarify, I think you mentioned the "1-2 degrees" because is in the news, documentarys and so on. Titulars use to lack in details, and those "1-2 degrees" represents an average over the entire surface of the planet.

*"A one-degree global change is significant because it takes a vast amount of heat to warm all the oceans, atmosphere, and land by that much. In the past, a one- to two-degree drop was all it took to plunge the Earth into the Little Ice Age. A five-degree drop was enough to bury a large part of North America under a towering mass of ice 20,000 years ago."*

Source: [https://earthobservatory.nasa.gov/world-of-change/DecadalTemp](https://earthobservatory.nasa.gov/world-of-change/DecadalTemp)

As non-scientist I found this article very informative and word-easy to read, so If you are interested in further learning I recomend it to you.

Sorry for my english by the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-19 12:56:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> \[First, sorry for my english\]

Just to add a very interesting example. **The Heikegani or "Samurai Crab"**.

In short: They developed samurai faces in their shells because people in the area avoid to take the ones who has a face-like pattern. This human behavior leads to a high face-like poblation of crabs passing their genes.

&#x200B;

Long (and very interesting):

[https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Heikegani](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Heikegani)

&#x200B;

And by Carl Sagan in Cosmos:

[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dIeYPHCJ1B8](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dIeYPHCJ1B8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-07 13:14:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mmmm good point sir. I suppose the vegan path still requires not to eat any animal-being-or-something-like product, even if is a very old zombie-like creature.
Let's leave this question for the philosophers of the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-07 09:50:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can try to not smith/enchant anything, just use items you find/steal. Trust me, it is a big challenge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-07 09:13:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Be careful. Dragon souls count as animal product. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-18 11:43:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try [Glühwein](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mulled_wine) and Skyrim while winter time. You're welcome ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-31 08:38:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lot.

I suppose the "17 artifact boy" reached cheating 50k before joining. Since they use the first run jumps over MS to get cheaters... If he was already at the max it is hard to detect by this method.

Number of artifacts, time since install, time played, etc. Those things must be something mandatory to check.

In other hand. What's the point to start and end a game in a couple of days? Is there any goal? :| </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-31 08:30:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally agree. Even more than 3, for example in Victor Vran you can activate more than one at a time, with which each one can customize their own challenge based on their strength and self-confidence.

Of course we talk about general concepts. In the end, the type of challenge and the "numbers" behind (for example the negative-portar, 50 would be too much) would be balanced by the development team.

To me the idea sounds interesting, I hope that at least GH team get an echo of this post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-30 17:35:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It depends on the rewards but I understand your point. The challenge must be a bit pain but not too much. Game must be still enjoyable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-30 17:33:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love the ideas. Thank you for such a complete reply! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Challenge Mode </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-30 15:53:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How about a high-rewarding mechanich like "challenge modes". I saw in some RPG games things like "You activate a button for a given extra difficulty and if you succeed you get an extra reward"... I know this idea is widely open but has a lot of potential.

i quick thought, for example...

Challenge name: *Nega Portar*

Difficulty: *Your portars take you back instead of forward (pain, I kwow). You need to reach your MS to get rewards.*

Reward: *No idea. Shards? Titan Chests? Achievements? All?*

&#x200B;

You know, It's a mechanic that can fit with a lot of "challenge" ideas.

As button-activation is needed, there is no obligation to participate and it could stimulate bored players at the max. **Of course I think these "challenges" must be adaptative in order to every player to participate, despite MS.**

&#x200B;

**As an example, Victor's Vran Hexes:**

*Hex of Malice		Monsters hit for 50% more damage and cause Cripple for 2 sec. on crit*

*Hex of Pain		Victor Vran loses health periodically*

*Hex of Tenacity      Monsters gain 120 armor and Regeneration*

*Hex of Time		Monsters move and attack faster*

*Hex of Tyranny       Some monsters become Champions. Tyrant Champions are not counted towards challenges*


\##Summing up the idea: Pain in the ass but highly rewarding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-29 13:56:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why so angry? Is not this subreddit for this kind of discussions? Or just for tourney wins screenshots? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-29 13:24:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are right. After a couple of replies I feel dumb... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-29 13:16:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >None. I repeat this post was for the statement of "zero obligation", with which initially I disagreed and about which I wanted to open a friendly discussion.
>
>The reason for this post is not that I want to be informed of anything in particular, but to let GH know that I value communication (as it has been up to now) as part of the gaming experience and it is something that I would like you not to miss . Edit: I would not like to lose it? Sorry, my english again. I hope it is "understable".

Edit: Sorry for copy/paste, just answered in another comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-29 13:11:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> None. I repeat this post was for the statement of "zero obligation", with which initially I disagreed and about which I wanted to open a friendly discussion.

The reason for this post is not that I want to be informed of anything in particular, but to let GH know that I value communication (as it has been up to now) as part of the gaming experience and it is something ~~that I would like you not to miss~~ . Edit: I would not like to lose it? Sorry, my english again. I hope it is "understable". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-29 12:38:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe your are right. In "legal" terms there is no obligation of course.

Still think communication is a good "task" they can assume to benefit both player tranquility and incoming flow.

I suppose that I am not the only one who pause purchases after/until event/fix and (even if we are very few) it is a sad decrease of incoming just for a simple matter of communication. Maybe it's not that simple but you understand.

As you said. We can only suggest things and hope. So this is my suggestion and I hope they have it in mind. If not? I will not get mad or go crazy. It is a game after all.

I will continue playing while I still like the game, and I have no doubt that 3.0 will be great.
Edit: type error </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Complaint / Suggestion to GH and users </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-29 11:48:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TL/DR, and sorry for my english

First I want to say I have no hurry for 3.0 or any patch. I understand the workflow and things are not allways released in date. In other posts I was (and still I am) being a defender of that the development team has the time it needs to work.

That said, I want to refer this Chris statement [https://imgur.com/a/YvWBX4h](https://imgur.com/a/YvWBX4h)

*"There is 0 obligation for us to communicate"*

Mmmm I don't agree.  As a company GH has an (maybe tacit) obligation with the user group. No communication is no respect. Same in the reverse way with the user toxicity in reddit and discord. They are our entertaintment source and we are their incoming source.

So, my complaint to GH: Communication is needed. This doesn't means releases when the users want or this sort of demands, JUST communication. And yes, I see this as an obligation.

And my suggestion to the users... Of course being toxic is useless, if you have a complaint:

1. Use the reddit/discord being polite, specific and constructive. If you agree with other user complaint UPVOTE to GH to see. They will.
2. If it is a mayor pain and/or seems to being ignored by GH you need to be serious. Not crying anymore but using your wallet. Stop any purchase (including ads, specially for FTP) until you think the game "deserves" it.

Of course this is like politics or strikes, to be heard we need to be united. This only can work if a big amount of the user database is doing the previous 1 & 2 steps.

Personally, I don't care patch or release dates if the content is worth. For me it is important to GH take us seriously and respect us as their source of income.

&#x200B;

To finish I just want to emphasize in not to be toxic but constructive users. If we want to demand communication we must deserve it.


EDIT:

Since I saw for the replies that probably I did not explained myself very well, I want to clarify two points:

1. Not asking for GH to comunicate more. Asking GH to not to end comunication flow because I like it and (for me) is part of the game experience. I love the game and I love this community and I just was worried after reading Chris statement.

2. As well, in the replies users suggested that the statement probably was out of context and I have gone too deep into a phrase without relevance. I see it now and TOTALLY AGREE, but I prefer to not delete posts because there are other user points of view.

&#x200B; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-28 15:42:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, probably I'll be downvoted to the hell but... I can wait. It's not that hard. It is a good time to play relaxed or even take a break.

On the other hand I'm sure that the delay is not due to being lazy or relaxed. I think it's better that they take the time they need to have the patch ready. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-23 10:28:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats it. So you need mana balance to "stay" with the bonus. Plus, every skill tree has a skill that increase duration. There are artifacts too. If you din't get those yet just be patient :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-23 10:21:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. Flute affects active skills, so for get the bonus you need to unlock and activate the main screen circle buttons (Heavently Strike, Deadly Strike, Fire Sword, War Cry and Shadow Clone).

By the way the Flute description says you only need 4 of those for the bonus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-16 15:27:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats it. Portar isn't involved in damage calculation. Critical/Deadly Strike/All prob. count in the calculation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-16 11:43:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe you can switch permanently to a SC or HS build. If you prefer to stay in your clan the only way is to splash, splash and splash. If you choose SC make sure you have the Ruthless Necromancer mythic set in order to splash through bosses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-14 15:43:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. Your "Clan Damage Bonus %", wich is a All Damage bonus will drop down. No further problems like retire or stuff. Just your advanced start and your All Damage.

**Edit:** For future tournaments, the algorithm  takes your higest clan bonus, so if the new clan is far lower be prepared for harder tournaments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-09 16:00:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. The algorithm matches player "potential". The algorithm think you can do it better. Maybe your skill points are not optimized. There are a lot of factors like quality of the artifacts, equipment owned, set bonuses and so on.

2. It depends. Do you focus yor skill points and your equipment in Shadow Clone? In that cas YES.

3. Slash equipment. Can have as secondary bonus critical chance (rare quality or better). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-09 14:27:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hard to say, too much factors. You need to try spending some diamonds.

When you change your build your needs of relics spent in artifacs totally change, so keep in mind that probably your max stage right after this change is not accurate. You will need some prestiges to rebalance SC dependant artifacts and have a better comparision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In another vein... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-03 15:58:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I play with my friends and we have a whatsapp group for tt2 talking, tournament complain and crying, those things you know. We would love to GH release a **sticker pack for** whatsapp/android&ios, just like they did for [iOS](https://itunes.apple.com/bo/app/tap-titans-2-sticker-pack/id1197555216?mt=8) time ago.

The gaming experience could be extended to the social environment a bit more.
Do you like the idea? Please upvote to GH to see.

Thank you all and keep tapping!

&#x200B;

&#x200B; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-28 14:17:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A telescope is like a funnel that amplifies the light it is receiving. That light enters through the lens of your telescope that is practically at the same distance as your eyes from the observed object.
You should think of a telescope as a tool similar to your eyes but with better features in certain aspects.
In no case a telescope "brings you closer" to the observed object, and therefore the distance that light has to travel through space is the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-28 12:44:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is not an attack to you of course. Just trying to help.
You can believe scientific community or you can make your own experiments with light... I cannot even imagine what an experiment would be like to measure the speed of light but of course there will be many that you can consult in the scientific community, but need to trust on those experiments to replicate them...

In the other hand, if you "believe" that light has a speed limit and if you "believe" that there is a given distance between your eyes and any object in the sky... well it is all said. The difference with your naked eyes and a telescope is only the long of the telescope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-28 12:24:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It does not make sense for you to ask about something you do not know and not accept the answers just because they do not match what you thought you knew before. So you will not solve your doubts and these people are striving to give you an answer.

Light needs time to travel, no matter how distant it is. If that explosion of which you speak happened in our sun you would also perceive it with a delay of a few seconds.

On the other hand light is susceptible to gravity and if in its path were an object with a monstrous gravity could change direction or even be completely engulfed and never reach here.

You need to get rid of preconceived ideas and look for literature on scientific dissemination. Edit: Sorry for my english, not my first language </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-26 13:58:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really enjoy with the binoculars the Galilean moons. The Orion nebula is great too (M42 if I'm right).
When I started with binoculars I was surprised with how many stars can be seen because the bightness increment, not only the zoom. I'm sure she will love to "explore" the night sky.
Plus. With some apps she can check what object is she currently seeing, follow satelite paths and other things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-26 13:02:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So many questions haha!

Well, I'll try to answer some:

\- Seasonal character: This characters are separated from your other characters until the season end (if I'm not mistaken this season ends 5 Jan, next season starts 11 Jan). I am loosing muy seasonal character when the season ends? Not at all, it became a "regular" character and shares stash again with the others.

Consider the seasons as "fresh start" games. Each season has a bonus and some special rewards. Check [here](http://diablo.wikia.com/wiki/Season).

\- Why fast leveling 70? It is considered that the game begins at 70. You know the story already, now try "adventure mode". You have contracts, rifts and other things to do. By the way, rifts are a great way to improve your items and collect set items.

\- Monk? It is awesome. All chars are, I strongly reccomend you to test any other character and find wich one fits better with your play style. I love monk so go ahead!

\- Rift: Open game in adventure mode and you will find a "pylon" in the town. It is very intuitive, don't worry!

\- Your are currently level 12... Well, don't worry about gear until 70. Then try to complete the currently (if the character is seasonal) season journey. More info [here](https://us.diablo3.com/en/blog/22493264/season-15-boon-of-the-horadrim-begins-921-9-14-2018).

&#x200B;

Hope it helps!

&#x200B; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-26 11:39:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should probably expose your doubt in a thread of [ophthalmology](https://www.reddit.com/r/Ophthalmology/). It is a phenomenon that has nothing to do with the nature of our star, but with the way in which the optic nerve and the brain process the information they are receiving.

Since the radiation the eye is receiving is very high, it is probably due to a low damage to the eye cells, but it is best to ask an expert in the field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-20 13:33:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not sure if it is accurated but [here](https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/worldnews/australiaandthepacific/australia/1436902/More-stars-than-grains-of-sand.html) is a rounded calculation.
Extract: *"There are 10 times more* *stars* *in the night sky than* *grains* *of* *sand* *in the world's deserts* *and* *beaches, scientists say. Astronomers have worked out that there are 70 thousand million million million -* *or* *seven followed by 22 zeros -* *stars* ***visible*** *from the Earth through telescopes."* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-14 13:25:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those virtual-operating-system apps consume a lot of memory. Maybe you are running out [RAM](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Random-access_memory)?

I've never played TT2 on nox so I can't help further :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-14 10:23:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When the problem persist the official support is the better option. With your device model they can check compatibility and other stuff. Hope your problem will be fixed soon and stay tapping ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-14 10:17:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe a corrupted file. Did you tried to uninstall/reinstall the app?
If you did try to contact [GH support](https://www.gamehive.com/support)

Hope it helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-13 15:29:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Homing Pads](https://us.diablo3.com/en/item/homing-pads-Unique_Shoulder_001_x1), but the bubble is only active while channeling the TP.

In HC a good "lifeguard" is [this amulet](https://us.diablo3.com/en/item/ancestors-grace-Unique_Amulet_102_x1), only available in HC, but destroys itself on fatal damage so can't be used in Kanai cube.

[Ancestor's Grace](https://us.diablo3.com/en/item/ancestors-grace-Unique_Amulet_102_x1) *"When receiving fatal damage, you are instead restored to 100% of maximum Life and resources. This item is destroyed in the process."* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-13 15:27:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you mean this Homing Pads, but the bubble is only active while channeling the TP.
https://us.diablo3.com/en/item/homing-pads-Unique_Shoulder_001_x1

In HC a good "lifeguard" is this amulet, only available in HC, but destroys itself on fatal damage so can't be used in Kanai cube.
https://us.diablo3.com/en/item/ancestors-grace-Unique_Amulet_102_x1
Ancestor's Grace
"When receiving fatal damage, you are instead restored to 100% of maximum Life and resources. This item is destroyed in the process." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-13 12:45:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry for my english and...

*If i quit while im in hardcore and in a greater rift, lets say 2-3 seconds before i die - am i safe?* **NOPE, so be careful. There is no safety trick in harcore**

*2: im planning to play whirlwind or the charge, depends what i found first - does hardcore requires different variations of the builds? Like unity ring or something like that, that would help me to stay alive.* **Nothing special but there is a special amulet to fake death, like in the passive**

*3 - If my hero dies, and i decide to make a new hardcore hero, do we have a shared stash with the dead hero?* **YES, only stash, nothing equiped in the dead char**

*4 - barbarian is fine for hardcore yes? I have that passive skill that fakes death or something.* \\**Every class has kinda passive for this purpose, so if you are sure to play HC you can use the class of yor play style choice.**


**Extra: If you play HC, in any given moment (specially with you first HC char) you will die. Be mentaly prepared and have a deep breath when it happens. First die is hard...** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-12 13:59:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thinking about the monk can be a very powerful tank too, and of course has great attacks. For me is the most fun to leveling :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-12 13:32:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try barbarian and crusader, maybe one of them fits better to you... But hey, it is recomended to try every class in the game, you never know if you are missing your favourite class!

Plus, every class has many different builds in the end-game, so you have a lot of play-styles to choose. Have fun testing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Christmas straightforward wish list to GH :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-06 15:56:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> \- That sweet buy all button

\- Please stop extra long ads (+1min)

&#x200B;

Thats it! Guys share yours :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-04 14:35:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For a very new player my tips are (and sorry for my english):

\- Play some solo or at least with players of your same level. This allow you to test every new skill when you get it. There's no hurry! Relax and enjoy. Avoid speed runs or rushes at the begining to better "taste" the game.

\- Do not worry about enchant or keep items until you reach level 70 (unless you start playing in a really hard torment mode), probably every single item you have at this point goes directly to dismantle or to the cube. Maybe you can keep some legendaries in the stash to get the power when you get the cube, specially if they are specific for your class ().

\- When you are about to level 50+ maybe you want to make the quest of the Kanai Cube in adventure mode and some runs of city quest. At level 60 you can get Death's Breath from elite monsters, with the items of the quest rewards you can then extract some magic powers from legendaries to keep in the Kanai Cube (one for main/off hand, one for armor and one more for jewerly).

\- When hit level 70 do Greater Rifts to get special gems with powers. Those are powerful game-changing items!


Have fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-16 09:26:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Although it is essential to look at some build later on, at the level where you are now you will get more rewards (especially in tournaments) if you assign your SP in a way that enhances the best equipment you have at your disposal.

For example, if you have a mythical or legendary weapon that enhances a lot  shadow clone, perhaps using a focused build (at least in a tournament) would give more benefits.

In case that you do not want to change often or that you just like very much the build you are currently using, you have two options: boost speed (by splashing) or boost pushing power.

For speed Aerial Assault because splash power.

For pushing power a combination of Tactical Insight and Anchoring Shot works very well for me right now.

&#x200B;

I think having fun and feel comfortable with your play style is the most important, so I recommend you to do your own experiments regardless of the advice we give you  :) - Sorry for my english - :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-15 16:01:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Currently shards are the best (and expensive) resource, specially at advanced levels.It's hard to get full mythic sets, those chest help a lot.

If I were you, I would buy the shards chest.

Putting my case as an example:

MS 26K. SP 820 + -

If I buy an 8-SP chest the profit is very low, I could not spend it on any skill of interest and I would have to wait to gather more SP.

In the case of shards it may not be enough to buy an interesting single-item, but completing sets gives you very interesting passive skills and a significant relic increase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-07 15:23:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (Sorry for my english) I never doubt they can make (or al least supervise) very good mobile games. The problem is that if they focus on mobile PC titles can expect a decrease in quality and quantity (or even no more PC titles, who knows). They changed their target-customer for another. Maybe is a very good business change for the company, but not for the current customer. We have a "profile".

&#x200B;

I can't fully speak for other customers/users, but in my case a mobile device can never achieve the level of in-game experience:

\- I like to configure and buy a very powerfull machine to play, is part of the experience.

\- I like to play in a big screen, high level of inmersion when all you can see is in-game info. In mobile experience is mostly your fingers getting mad and the surroundings...

\- I really like to "mess" with keyboard/mouse bindings, play style personalization is a very important part of the experience.

\- I like to have peripherals and apps in background, a Twitch chat for example with overlay... I don't know how to a mobile device can hold this kind of situation with the SO and other processes running (and in-game chat is not solution, It wasn't in the past though).

&#x200B;

I can't imagine myself enjoying a situation similar to:

"Forcing sight to see a small screen, full of fingerprints and even sweat (do not forget that we get nervous in certain situations, especially in harcore-mode or raid-like situations). The smartphone is getting hotter and the battery goes down quickly, it becomes hard to play with the charging cable... Enters a call..."

&#x200B;

I tried lot of games for mobile. It's not the quality of the game, It's just I don't like mobile-phone play. I'm the opposite of this new business target. Of course we all continue with our lifes and we will find another game or franchise for us... But it's hard to say goodbye after so many years.


Sorry for the TL:DR! I feel better now xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-07 14:47:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So this is a farewell. It was nice while it lasted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
