<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject60</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 14:21:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Labels are hard, because you can think exactly the same and still end up calling yourself different things. I see myself as biromantic, demisexual and polyamorous, but my partner see himself as pansexual. Still we feel the same way, atraction to the person not the gender.

From what I’ve found on the internet and talking to people it seems that the label you chose depend on your age and in what society you grew up.

For 12yo me  back in 2004 my mind was blown when I learned that there was a name for liking both boys and girls - bisexual.

I’m not sure when my partner realised it, but lets say it was at the same age. For him that would be 2008, and the world he grew up in online was a completely different one from the one I had (I had an old modem, and he most likely had broadband). That’s probably why he got introduced to multi gender atraction (MGA) in the form of pansexuality.

Later generations had even more to choose from and I think that’s where omnisexuality shows up most.

As for the ace spectrum I’m not as sure. Asexuality is the umbrella, and gray is the part of the spectrum that sometimes feel atraction, and demi is a part of the gray part of the ace spectrum? At least that’s how I visualise it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 21:05:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You don’t have to be sexual to have a strong relationship.

I’m polyamorous and demisexual, as is my boyfriend, so we don’t really have sex. My husband on the other hand is allo, and both me and our boyfriend have sex with him. That doesn’t mean my bf is any less of a partner than my husband.

Let it take time, don’t be afraid to talk about things that worry you. Try not to force it. Asexuality is a spectrum and two demisexuals can have different preferences even though they use the same label. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 15:41:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you tried antidepressants? They both make you happier and lowers your sex drive 😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 10:01:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I fell in love with my husband’s boyfriend, but that don’t mean I need more than one partner, I just let myself feel what I do.

And how is it better with cheating and drama and love triangles and ”ownership”, than listening to and respecting your partners and your own feelings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 19:16:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a fellow demi I would say play the long game. Romantic relationships isn’t a must. Do you like him as a friend? Do you still want him in your life?
If the answers is yes I would say don’t fuck that up. My husband had 2-3 other partners from the first time he hit on me to when we became a couple. It just wasn’t our time yet.

As a polyamorous person living in a triad I would also want to remind you that there is the option for ethical non-monogamy, and as long as it’s agreed upon by everyone involved it can be great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 11:31:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If this is marketing research I would recommend you to limit yourself to your country (wich I assume is the US) since many countries don’t have commercials for medication </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 10:15:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s fun when you find your labels :)
I (F28) identify as a polyamorous biromantic demisexual, and as long as you are true to yourself and communicate with those around you, you will find your people.

Another thing to remember is that you don’t have to be in a romantic relationship to form that bond and cuddle. My best friend and I always end up cuddling when we watch movies, and it’s completely platonic. It’s also great that I can talk to her on a level I can’t with my husband and boyfriend~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 18:11:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True, and that’s hillarious since I’m literally asexual </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 17:50:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, as a biromantic demisexual woman in a polyamourous triad with two men I get the ”straight-passing” thing sometimes, and it’s one of the reasons I’m not active in the local LGBT comunity... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 14:32:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would say that’s some exclusionist BS. After all, the A in LGBTQAI+ is for us aces </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 08:36:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My husband had a couple of FWB’s between the first time he showed interest and the day I was ready for a relationship. If he had waited that year for me I don’t think I would have said yes since it would have led to a lot of ”naging” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 01:23:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What’s that guy’s name... Ryan Creamer! He has a bunch of videos on pornhub that’s just things like ”I deliver your pizza without putting my weiner in it” and ”I tuck you in at night”
I think it started as some college humor-sketches or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 10:40:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right! I don’t want to invalidate anyone or their relationships, but it makes me wonder. As a biromantic woman there’s the stereotype that we are easy and up for anything, and porn does not help us with that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 10:36:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So much this!
My triad started as a V, but then my meta and I fell in love too, and I think that’s how it has to be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 10:35:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m in a MMF triad and it’s great. I think the reason FFM is more common has to do with OPP and unicorn hunting. It’s the ”ultimate straight man’s fantasy” and as such I think we see it more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 07:41:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not the main storyline, but The Deathworlders has a triad as well as an open marriage. It takes a while for it to get to that point though, so you have to be a bit patient. It’s a really good HFY scifi though so I think you’ll enjoy the ride </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 15:11:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Biro ace, but crepes/Swedish pancakes with ice cream and queen-jam are the best 👌 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 10:29:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The moment I *knew*? That was when I fell in love with my fiancé’s boyfriend. At that point we had been in an open relationship for a couple of years though, so I knew I might be something other than mono ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-01 18:49:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I try to talk to them both, after I’ve checked my own mental and physical wellbeing (sleep/food/water/meds/hormones/stress). We’re a triad and we live together. My meds lower my drive, and I’m demi, so I’m not in the mood often, but I can still feel left out.

Our solution is mostly that I ask fore more intimacy in the form of cuddles and time spent together, and sometimes I join them when they play. It can be really fun even if I’m not in the mood myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 00:04:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Biromantic demi/ace here. You are valid however you identify, and no matter what, asexuality is 100 % real. We are not broken and, most importantly, we are not alone.

It can be worth looking into the different kinds of asexuality there is. After all it’s a spectrum. And just because you are ace you don’t have to use the lable if you don’t want to. I still go by bisexual most of the time, even though I have no problem adding I’m ace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 23:52:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For those who want to own these they are available as patches and pins!!
I bought the battleaxe pin and it’s beautiful

Check out Foxflightstudios on etsy

https://www.etsy.com/se-en/shop/Foxflightstudios </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 23:51:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They are available as patches! And pins!!

Check out Foxflightstudios on etsy

https://www.etsy.com/se-en/shop/Foxflightstudios </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 23:50:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They are available as patches! And pins!!

Check out Foxflightstudios on etsy

https://www.etsy.com/se-en/shop/Foxflightstudios </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 22:32:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s worth noting that some nonbinary people use ”hen” instead of changing between the gendered pronomen though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 22:25:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You don’t have to be sick or traumatized to be asexual ~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 22:22:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s really important that you don’t take it as rejection too. My fiancé and I had very missmatched drives the first years, and it can be hard when your partner doesn’t want to have sex with you, no matter how much you understand it.

For me it varies a lot. Some days I’m horny as hell, and others i could just as well be doing the dishes. I do however love to see my partners enjoy themselves, so sometimes I just watch as he and my fiancé play.

I don’t know how you see mastrubation in your relationship, but that can be something to encourage too. Half of my orgasms are to get rid of headaches, stress or to help me relax. As for you, if you get a no from him, just play by yourself and let him know it’s okay to join if he change his mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 18:23:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m a demisexual ace and for me the important part is that I’m seen in my relationship. I live for physical affection, but sex is not needed.

Talk to him about what he like and experiment with other kinds of intimacy. Try to make him feel like he has the choice to join, not that he has to.

Read up on different kinds of ace (there’s a lot of them!) and see if anything hits home. Once you know you’re not broken or alone it can get a lot easier. Maybe check out some poly ace groups on facebook? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 12:44:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If there had been any posts to read it would certainly be interesting... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 12:41:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m f. Does it matter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 12:35:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My fiancé, my boyfriend and I all sleep in the same bed, and it happens. Most of the time it’s in the middle of the night and I just want to sleep, so I just pet them and let them do their thing. Other times they play without me, and sometimes we play all together.

When it comes to the jealousy bit it depends on how I feel for the day. Sometimes it’s awesomely hot, sometimes it’s depressing and gives me anxiety, sometimes I care as mich as if they were playing cards. The important thing is to speak up when you need more attention, or if something makes you uncomfortable. You have to figure this out together </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 09:46:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My fiancé and I have been together for 5 years. During that time he realised he is polyam and we decided to start slow with just FWB’s. One of these FWB’s was a mutual aquaintance who started to hang out more and more with both of us. Fiancé realised he had feelings for him and we became a V, and as we spent more time together we realised the bf and I had feelings for each other too. 6 months later bf and I had our first kiss, and right now, about a year later I’m lying in bed listening to both of them snoring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 22:31:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Many European countries are as fluid in English as you are. Maybe look into Sweden (people have a hard time learning the language since we all speak English), Norway Denmark or some other country like the Netherlands. There are a lot of videos on youtube of exchange students talking about their time in the country if you search for it, might make it easier to choose :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 20:39:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The crew of BGEV-11 Misfit in [The Deathworlders](https://deathworlders.com/books/deathworlders/chapter-00-kevin-jenkins-experience/) (trying not to spoil too much, but if you know the Misfit, you know about the characters)

They are so sweet, but you have to get relatively far into the story to meet them (and for them to become a triad) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 09:29:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The thing to remember in a triad is that it’s not one relationship,  it’s four. You and F1, you and F2, F1 and F2, and the triad. Each one of them will be different.

That said, if you feel left out you should tell them.

I (F) am in a FMM triad and each of us have different needs and wants. It’s important to talk about things early so they don’t become big problems and seething resentment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-05 16:19:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vasa never sank, she flew </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 17:29:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! I didn’t get it to work, but now I at least know there will be problems linking to wikipedia haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 16:55:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Np

Here ->https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Helmet_(heraldry) you have some more info about the helmets role in heraldry

Edit: I’ve tried to fix the link, so now it at least go to the right page... better luck next time I guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 16:50:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You mean the black thing between the tree and the kneeling saint(?) ? That’s a black frogmouth helmet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 13:08:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was going to say it wasn’t true, then I realised one of my boyfriends is a teatcher, and that me and my other bf is educators/leaders at the local folk education center (folkbildning/studiefrämjandet) 😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-07 17:31:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As someone who have a lower libido than my partners I agree that the best thing to do is to talk about it. Sometimes it’s just one of those dry periods, but other times it can be insecurities, pain, depression, hormones, fear, bad experiences in the past, performance anxiety, body shame or a million other things. Or she might just be asexual. But even as an asexual there are a lot of variety (I’m ace/demi so I know).

If you want a ”natural” way to start the conversation without putting preassure on either of you, maybe watch the show Sex Education on Netflix. It’s really good and talks a lot about communication, and it’s really good with LGBTQIA+ representation (it even has an asexual character) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-03 07:58:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I (F28) am in a FMM triad. We usually cal ourselves a triad, but with others, especially those who don’t know, we call it ”the collective” (I guess it can be ”the commune” too in English). Other than that I usualy say ”me and my boys” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-29 18:53:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. Cis woman

2. I am in a triad and we’re all on the same level of seriousness since we’re moving in together later this year.

3. Two </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 15:19:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s been really nice, but the best thing is that I told my mother about our triad today and she had already figured it out, so she just smiled, hugged me and told me I am loved no matter what~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-04 14:07:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m demi and I realised that I was poly when I fell in love with my fiancé’s boyfriend, so you’re not alone :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-23 13:57:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought I was mono untill I fell in love with my meta.

Me and my partner had an open relationship for 3 years after we came to the realisation that he was poly. He called himself polysexual and got a bunch of FWB. One of them was a friend of both of us, and my fiancé realised he was polyamorous as well. For a while we were a V, but since I’m a firm believer in KTP we started to spend a lot of time together. After a couple of months hesitation and a lot of talking we realised we all had feelings for eachother (both me and our boyfriend thought we were mono before that) so we became a triad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-23 05:36:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have thought a lot about this too, and I’ve even started to look up laws and things that could be used for us. One thing I’ve thought about is that we could all get the same last name, and if/when children come into the picture the third will be a legal guardian with the same rights as the bio-parents. But it’s hard. I find some comfort in that the world is changing and Canada have given a cild the right to 3 parents, but things move so slow

What would make you feel like a real part of the triad and not just the gf? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-23 05:32:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Glad to hear it! We’re all new to poly, but it feels like we’re doing something right.

Oh, and we settled on that we can always get a divorce if it becomes a problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-23 01:29:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think so. I don’t want my triad to be a couple +1, but all three of us on the same level. Me amd my fiancé will get married this summer, and I’ve thought about calling it of so our boyfriend would be on the same level as us, but he wouldn’t hear it haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-22 23:33:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s not an excuse. Me and my fiancé had been together for 5 years when we got together with our boyfriend. We live together, and our bf is 1,5 hours away by car. We work, and own a house, our bf  is a student in a 1 room apartment. We make sure that we go to him since he can’t always come to us, and even though we don’t live together all three yet we make sure to talk on the phone at least 3 times a week, sometimes more.

You should probably call to a board meeting and simply ask what this means for your relationship. Why they didn’t tell you and why they don’t invite you. Worst case it’s a break up, but then you don’t have to settle for less than you want. Think of how much you want to see them. If they will leave you hanging for months at a time they have no right to ”force” you to just date them (as I understand your closed triad?). I can’t shake the feeling that you’re their unicorn and they are not ethical hunters.

I’ve seen others post this link often in situations like this on other forums, might be some interesting/relevant reading for you?
https://www.unicorns-r-us.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-22 23:11:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think everyone is jealous, the difference is what you do with it. It sounds like it’s rough on you. Are you sure they give you what you need? Have you discussed couples privelege? What future do you see together?

I’m in my first triad, and I’ve had to face the fact that I’m responsible for 50% of my relationships with others, so I can’t just wait for others to contact me in the right moment, I have to work to make it work. It feels like he hasn’t come to that realisation yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-22 22:43:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s okay to elope spontaneous, but they should have told you that day. It’s not that hard to send a picture to say they sealed the deal. What’s wrong is that you heard it from other people. That shows that they either don’t value you, or that they are afraid to talk about things that might cause drama. Either way it’s a huge red flag, and you deserve better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-22 22:38:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think MFF is most common since it’s The Ultimate Hetero Guy Fantasy. I have no stats on it but from what I’ve seen they often have an OPP too, so there is ”no way” to add another man since it would be gay(?)  🤷‍♀️

I (F) am personaly in a triad with my fiancé (M) and our boyfriend (FTM), and I think we are many that isn’t MFF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-22 22:28:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you’re in a relationship there should be discussions, or at least a check-in, about everything that could affect the dynamics, such as getting married. I’m engaged to my fiancé, and one of the first discussions I had with our boyfriend was if he was okay with it (and if he still wanted to be in my entourage).
That they forgot to tell you that they were going to elope AND that they had done it is just wrong, mo matter that you knew it would happen some day. They shoult tell you when that day comes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-21 21:03:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’sgreat to hear! I came out to my closest friend this weekend and she had already figured things out lol
till gathering courage to tell my parents though, even though I think it’ll be relatively okay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 20:48:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yes, it’s so nice when there’s some happy suprises for once ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-11 21:08:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Swedish 27 year old bi woman who thought I was mono untill last year when I fel in love with  my fiancé’s boyfriend. We had been in an open relationship since 2016, but this was the first time he got together with someone I knew. None of us saw it comming since both me and our boyfriend thought we were mono, and my fiancé thought he was only polysexual. Now we’re in a triad and talk about moving in together later this year and it feels amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-08 19:09:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right?! I’ve been trying to get over it by telling myself that I have the same chance of success as when I was mono, and I’ve made sure all three of us are on the same page when it comes to goals and dreams. I hope we’ll get to a point where we can be open and accepted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-08 16:41:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me and my bf are talking about this a lot since I already have one for my fiancé and it gets confusing to use the same for both (we’re in a triad)
I thing we agreed to let it be for now and see what  comes naturaly when he move in with us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-08 16:32:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m glad to hear there’s some who are willing to let others learn feom their mistakes. We have a closed triad with two previously mono and one who thought he was just polysexual, but we all love each other. So far we’ve figured out that we need to communicate, and that jealousy is frustrating lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-08 16:27:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. I’ll check it out

I’ve joined a couple different groups here and on facebook and such, and there’s a lot of varying tones in them all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-08 15:45:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The bitterness from those who had a bad experience with [whatever the topic] and just tell people that the way they do ENM is doomed to fail.

As someone new to ENM, in my first triad and who previously thought I was mono, many of the comments on things that is relevant for me just say that we’re going to crash and burn. It would be better if people said things like ”I’ve tried it and it failed because of X”. That way we could learn what be weary of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-05 22:23:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m so glad to hear that it works for you! I’ve tried to convince myself that anything’s possible if everyone’s on the same page and as long as we don’t force things. But yeah, all people come into your life for a reason. The only thing we can hope for no matter what is to part ways as friends if it comes to that ~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-05 19:11:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember the first time I saw a triad on TV. It was one of the million american crime shows, and one of them mirdered one of the other two out of jealousy... I remember thinking it was a bad way to represent LGBTQAI+ people (I had just come out as bi) and I probably commented on it since my mom said that ”those relationships never lasts”... I think she has changed her thinking now though as it’s been 10 years, but still (at least I hope she has as I haven’t told her about my triad yet)

Tbh I see a lot of negativity in the community too... sure, I’m just shy of a year in my first triad (with two others that’s new to poly) and almost everywhere I see people say that all triads are doomed to crash and burn...
As someone who want the ”forever after” it feels like I’m not really welcome many times, or that I’m to naive to know how the world works. But is there really worse statistics for us than for mono people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-03 00:33:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me and my fiancé opened up our relationship, but we didn’t do anything for about a year. Instead we made sure our relationship was strong and healthy, and that both he and I were in a good headspace.

Talk a lot, especially when you feel envy and insecurity. That way you can stop a lot of problems before they become  problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-31 15:08:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha most of my friends are Slytherins, so I’m not that concerned. Once you get past the ambition they are real sweethearts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-31 11:25:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m a Hufflepuff in a triad with two Slytherins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-31 10:11:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly. I was happy when it was just him and me, and since I knew about this being a possible problem we found ways around it, like me actually telling him when I really need a hug, or me getting that attention from my platonic friends. And I didn’t become poly to fill that need, I did it because I fell for my fiancé’s boyfriend, and I think that makes a huge difference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-30 22:31:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had been with my fiancé for 4 years before we met our boyfriend and started talking about a triad. We love each other and I would want to spend my life with him, even though we have to compromise and learn how to make both of us happy. As it is now, when the pressure of providing hugs and cuddles for me isn’t only on my fiancé, he’s become more relaxed about it and started to give more than when it was only us.

We’re all really new to all this (first polyam relationship for all, and both out boyfriend and I thought we were mono before this), so I have no idea if this will last, but it works for now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-30 21:31:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me it’s been pretty natural since my fiancé (first partner) is autistic and doesn’t like/need the same things as me. I have a pretty physical love language, and he doesn’t want that most of the time. It’s not something that would be a dealbreaker, but after we found our boyfriend things are more balanced and everyone’s more content since my fiancé isn’t the only one who have to fullfill my need for higs and cuddles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 19:40:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I feel like this I usually look to myself first. Has something happened that makes me more axious/insecure/jealous than usual? Am I feeling allright? Most of the time there’s something else going on with me, like a rough period at work or such.

When I’ve thought it over I usually set my fiancé down on the couch and then I say pretty much exactly what you wrote here, and that I need some more attention right now.

New relationship energy (NRE) is definately a thing too. It’s that honeymoon phase, and it’s really easy to forget about everyone other than the new one. Once you are aware of it though it’s easier to make sure everyone is feeling seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 21:56:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As someone who has been in the same situation I would say take a couple of deep breaths and try to figure out what it is that actually bothers you. Exactly what is is that makes it hard?
Once you know that talk to your girlfriend (or both of them if you want a kitchen table- relationship) about how it make you feel, and try to work out something that feels right and respect everyone’s feelings.

For me we started opening up our relationship about 4 years ago, but it was only my bf D who was interested in others. We took it slow, talked a lot about how we felt, and as soon as I started to get insecure or jealous I tried to say it. Last year D started dating our friend L (the first one I’ve known about and met), they liked each other a lot and we started to hang out together, and now we’re in a triad and are planning on moving in together next year. Neither I nor L thought we would ever be anything but mono, and here we are.

As mentioned above, the one penis policy is a sign of insecurities. Even if she doesn’t plan on finding another man I would say it’s a rule that could complicate things down the line. Right now I don’t think it’s the most pressing issue though.

Sit down with your GF and say that you are happy for her, but your anxiety and insecurities are acting up. Don’t be judgy to yourself or her, just try to be as matter-of-factly as you can. Talk about your goals with this new relationship, how much you want to be involved, how much you want to know, what you need to feel secure and seen.

The thing that got me through a lot of my own insecurities was [this site](https://www.morethantwo.com/poly-mono.html), it might help you too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 18:31:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Demi-bi polyam here in a triad with a demi-pan and an allo-bi. It can totally work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 00:39:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When me and my partners were at a hotel last week we got the room with the largest bed. It turned out to be 2 beds pushed together, so we flipped the matresses 90' and slept on it that way all 3 of us.

In your case I would talk to your partners. Not everyone has the same needs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-05 21:26:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Deathworlders (originally from r/hfy) have a triad that I just love (it takes a while to get to them though, as the characters meet around chapter 21) as well as other characters in open relationships who are more in the background </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-24 18:41:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As someone who was the "I can never do it because I'm jealous"-part of the relationship I have to say that it's all up to her. For us it worked because my partner never preassured me to be poly, but instead let me set the pace and feel like I was in control as I worked through my insecurities.


Me and my faincé talked a lot about everything concerning sex and relationships, both past and present, and while discussing him cheating in the past (before we met) he mentioned that he had realised he was polyam. We talked about it a lot and decided to try "freecards", ie he had permission to play with others X times a year, but only if he followed the rules we decided on together and that he made sure not to use them in a way that would hurt our relationship.

This worked nicely for a couple of years, and now and then we evaluated how both of us felt about it and renegotiated the rules.

About a year ago he started talking about wanting a relationship with one of our friends, and as we've all come to know eachother better we've decided to go all in, so now I have both a fiancé and a boyfriend.


Let it take time, don't be dissapointed if she never gets there. All three of us are new to this, so I don't know how it will turn out or if it's the right way to do it, but yeah...


[This page](https://www.morethantwo.com/poly-mono.html) helped me a lot when I still thought I was mono, might be worth a read </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-12 13:30:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also, I think Alex was filming for the Annabelle movie that came out recently, so he had a good reason for his absence ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-12 13:29:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Jason rolls for the guests that doesn’t know the system so they can avoid all questions about what dice to use when. The more times the guests join, the more they roll for themselves. Other guests that have played VtM before roll for themselves from the start </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-10 19:21:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's- That does have a ring to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-22 08:15:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was released on 2004 so I think it was for xp.

I have never worked with anything like DosBox but I guess it’s time to learn something new. RDP seems like it might defeat the purpose as the reason I want to play on the laptop is that my boyfriend are using the desktop, or is there a way to do both?

I’ll try some different resolutions and see if it’s that simple. Thank you for taking the time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-14 19:45:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Season 2 and all the epilouges can be found on twitch (as a subscriber you can see all the episodes). As I understand it they post the episodes on a regular interval on youtube, not sure if it’s once a week, but if you’re patient I think ep 8 will be uploaded on youtube in the next couple of days. If you’re not, give G&S a subscription (i think it’s like 5 or 6$/month) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Looking for a song </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-07 18:54:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just realised I lost a great song that I found on youtube a year or two back, and since it was about renn fairs(/sca/reenactment) I hope someone on here can help me.  I’ve tried google, but it seems like the lyrics isn’t posted anywhere

I think the title is something like medieval people, but I can’t remember.

The chorus (as I remember it):

I’ll fight for the honour
Of every young maid

I’ll stand and I’ll die
With the friends that I made

My boots may be tattered
My cloak may be frayed

As I go into battle I am not afraid
My wit is as sharp as the edge of my blade

TIA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-02 23:39:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just got a heads up on G&S twitter. There will be an update about LA by Night soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-02 20:15:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hear you! I’ve only subscribed to their twitch because of LA by Night... so I’m hoping that there’s some perk for subscribing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-02 16:34:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am wondering the same. In the last episode of season 2 Jason says that ”the show will be recorded and shared at a later time” (quoting from memory, so wording might be off) but I’ve not found any information about it either. I’ve tried messaging G&S on facebook about it too, but got no response.

I’m hoping that the plan is to show it after season two has been uploaded to youtube (e6 went up the other day, so that would be in 3-7 weeks, depending on if it comes before or after the epilogues) but I have no idea if that’s the case. The only thing I have to go on is that it’s what I would have done.

Please, do share if you get an answer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-27 05:54:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ofc! The good stuff needs to be shared :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-26 18:54:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I might have overdone it, but I got lost in the stories I have saved, and there are so many good ones!

For longer series my favourites right now are

The Deathworlders

[Transcripts](https://www.reddit.com/r/HFY/comments/5tcesp/oc_research_transcripts_of_dr_xant_translator/)

[Interactive education](https://www.reddit.com/r/HFY/comments/60fs0q/interactive_education/)

[The new students](https://www.reddit.com/r/HFY/comments/axtlcn/the_new_students_part_1_first_impressions/)

[They are smol](https://www.reddit.com/r/HFY/comments/9d7pk1/they_are_smol/) - it’s a shitpost dumpster fire, but a great story

[They are smol - the invasion of earth](https://www.reddit.com/r/HFY/comments/aerh85/they_are_smol_invasion_of_earth_chapter_1/) - and it gets (more) serious too

For one-shots and shorter stuff these are fun and/or interesting

[We knew them](https://www.reddit.com/r/HFY/comments/bdbi04/we_knew_them/)

[The other kind of human](https://www.reddit.com/r/HFY/comments/bcpfon/oc_the_other_kind_of_human_immigration/)

[The divine sound](https://www.reddit.com/r/HFY/comments/2csman/octhe_divine_sound_part_1/)

[Clipboard](https://www.reddit.com/r/HFY/comments/4mjmp9/clipboard/)

[Crisis simulation](https://www.reddit.com/r/HFY/comments/aw4qxb/oc_crisis_simulation/)

[Human magic](https://www.reddit.com/r/HFY/comments/7t9zjd/text_human_magic/)

[Do you hold our debt fulfilled](https://www.reddit.com/r/HFY/comments/8wvafy/do_you_hold_our_debt_fulfilled/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Windows 10, problem with screen size while running older games </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 09:45:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Less than a year ago I bought a Lenovo Ideapad 330 with Windows 10. My problem is that when I try to run older games, like Guild Wars 1 and Vampire the Masquerade Bloodlines, the game comes up in full screen mode, but the cruser won't move more than a third of the screen. Within that third of the total screen you can find the buttons and such you can see on the full screen, and klick them.

For GW I got around the problem by simply not running the game in full screen mode, but with VTM I haven't found that option.

I have tried restarting, reinstalling the games, every compability-setting, running as admin and I've googled a lot, but it doesn't help and I don't know what to search for any more.

I'm thinking it has something to do with the laptop since I have no problem playing the same games on my stationary computer.

TIA

(this is my first post ever, please tell me if I need to fix anything) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-14 20:48:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You got me thinking of Trojan Horse from a week back or something?

[Trojan Horse](https://www.reddit.com/r/HFY/comments/9ji09f/trojan_horse/?st=JN980HGI&sh=a017f16c)

(First time trying to link anything so not sure if I’m doing it right) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-14 20:37:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really liked this. The long-range doctor is a reality today as the hospital I work at already use radiologists in Australia during the night shift in Sweden. There’s also a lot of internet-based healthcare center visits available via smartphone.    With all the robot-assisted surgeries this might not be that far away either. It’s a fun time to be alive ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-07 18:25:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like when it’s about more than just humans, like the tumblr-thread where Earth is basicly space-australia. It would be fun to read about more animals in space, maybe some Steve Irving-type trying so save as many terran animals he/she can from private collections around the galaxy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
