<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject58</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Interests </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 05:20:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First I must provide that I am diagnosed with BPD and I find a lot of difficulty in making decisions for myself and therefore I just coast by most of the time.

Now onto the show haha,
I have thought a lot about myself and why it is so hard for me to connect with people or form basic friendships. I have come to the conclusion that this is because I have never done anything interesting, I have any hobbies or passions, I don’t go out of my way to try new things, I barely even do my school work, hell, I haven’t ever even asked a girl out.
Through these realizations I have decided that I need to find a hobby to hopefully discover myself again and hopefully discover other people as well.
Please help me think of hobbies or passions that I can look up and hopefully get into. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 04:52:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, I’m really sorry you guys have to deal with this. A very important thing that I like to tell myself is that it is that life will continue moving, bad things unfortunately happen to the greatest of people, it’s our decision whether we get up and keep going or we let it continue to eat away at us. We make that decision, not the bad thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 04:48:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like to consider myself high functioning and I’m currently trying to make a decision to get on meds (with my psychiatrist of course) and I am mostly normal but I do have certain days where thoughts or “false realities” become very strong and it is nearly impossible for me to get rid of them. A very common one is when I’m going to sleep by myself I feel a malicious presence of someone standing above me or just in the room with me. Despite many coping mechanisms such as deep breathing and counting, or trying to focus on music or watching a YouTube video to distract me. It doesn’t help until someone else (an actual physical real person) is also in the room.
To sum it up, I really don’t like medicine but I also really don’t like having these thoughts and feeling so I want to try medicine again but I’m terrible at making decisions :/. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 04:43:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is hilarious 😂😂
And it makes a lot of sense too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 05:59:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you homie :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Additional diagnoses </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 04:23:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had my first appt with a therapist through my school in about a year and she told me that my old psychiatrist had diagnosed me with “drug induced psychosis” as well as “BPD”. I knew about the BPD one but she never mentioned the other one. Which I felt kinda hurt by that she wouldn’t tell me about it. Like I know that they’re just professionals and it’s kinda reinforcing that they don’t actually care about me and they just write their little notes without a care in the world.
I also had my first meeting with a psychiatrist today (through my school and since the beginning of this year) and she kept comparing me to someone with Schizophrenia because I was talking about being confused about this reality (kinda complex). I just really can’t convince myself to trust the “mental health professionals”. I feel like I need to talk to other people that have personal experience with this stuff instead of just learning about it in a book. (Another reason why I want to become a therapist) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 08:11:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really appreciate that :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Avoidance Walks </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 07:12:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> CW: Suicidal thoughts and self harm
Anyone love going on late night walks? I am currently sitting outside my campus’s church so I don’t hurt myself and so I can focus on other things than suicide. I haven’t been able to sleep the past few days and I’ve just been hurting on the inside. I have my first therapy session (for about a year or so) in two days and I also have a chemistry test that I have no idea about, I also have a calculus test and I skipped my biology quiz last week. I’m literally falling apart, I have been trying to pull it together because my mom is getting married in less than a week and I want to be happy for her because she’s the only reason I’m still living today.
60% of my thoughts the past few days have been about dying or otherwise hurting myself because I need to release this pain that’s just been building inside me. This was supposed to be a nice post but at this point I just want to stop existing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I really want to </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 07:59:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven’t thought about hurting myself in such a long time. Then i broke about a week ago and now it doesn’t leave my mind. I am legit fantasizing about my body being covered in wounds and maybe finally all the pain will have bled from my body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 08:01:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If they feel the need to reinforce something they shouldn’t do in the first place then it is probably gonna happen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 07:39:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, I personally haven’t been through this but in my head, (based on my emotions), I personally would never be able to justify something that is hurting someone else simply by saying I have BPD. In other words I don’t think it is an acceptable reason to act the way you have described without some sort of trying to better yourself.

And a romantic relationship between two people with BPD is always very very difficult. (Atleast from what I’ve read about people and what I would assume from my life)

The only thing I can really advise is to follow your heart and you should always seek to increase your own happiness and allow yourself to blossom first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 07:34:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s true! We all deal with it in very different ways, and I’m very happy that you have such a good support system :)

And rough seems like an understatement haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 07:18:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats actually really noble, I personally would not want people’s first experience with BPD to be me because I can be quite a lot sometimes and even though I don’t want to admit it I can be very manipulative at times.

Also I’m not very versed in telling people in relationships about it because my only relationship was before I was diagnosed, and I don’t usually talk to anyone here on my campus so idk 🤷‍♂️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 07:08:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely 100%, sometimes I feel like I’m absolutely the worst person in the world, but then I get sometimes, can last from a few minutes to a few days, where I feel like I could jump off a 5 story building and the only thing hurt would be the concrete I land on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 07:06:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> **this prob isn’t healthy**
But I usually just don’t tell anyone that I have BPD, the only people that know are my parents and my sister. If I was going to tell someone I had BPD I would probably wait until you’ve known them for a while because there is such a stigma attached to it. So that way the person won’t associate the stigmas with you because they already know how you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 06:47:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I absolutely do this as well, I don’t think of it as a bad thing because the things I don’t tel her are things that I don’t want to burden her with? Even though I should absolutely be telling her about everything that is causing me trouble. I’m not sure if it’s a form of manipulation, I don’t like to consider myself manipulative but I do try to sway people’s opinions by acting certain ways and almost like telling them what they want to hear.

Something that I need to keep reminding myself of and I recommend you do the same is that your therapist is there to help you, they are in that profession to help you get through life, and they are unable to do this 100% if they don’t know what’s going on. It’s really rough for me to come to terms with this but I’m working on it and I hope you can do the same :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 06:43:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have BPD and it certainly is annoying hearing it be used as a descriptor for people’s negative actions. But BPD is a highly stigmatized disorder and the majority of people who don’t associate or talk with someone who has BPD and only hears about it online are most likely going to assume BPD is terrible.

The only advice that I have that I use is to just try to not let it define your life, you are a human who happens to have BPD, not a Borderline human, if that makes sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 06:17:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like this :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Idk what this would be called? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 11:54:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey guys I keep going back and forth between wanting to help people and then just feeling like my comments are worthless. Even on here I try giving advice to people with things I have personal experience with. But then I’ll write out a nice comment and then I’ll just say “what’s the point, they won’t care” and I’ll delete the comment. Does anyone else do this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 11:50:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ve kinda accepted the fact that I will eventually die at my own hands. I’m just trying to help as many people as I can before that happens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 11:49:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you send it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 11:38:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, I also go through this thought process very frequently except for me I just want to disappear into the woods and never talk to another human ever again and trying way too hard at school and trying to better myself and get my degree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 11:36:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, I am 19 diagnosed with BPD less than a year ago when I was 18 just starting college :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 11:22:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey OP, there is nothing more liberating than getting a diagnosis (in my opinion) and it certainly helped me in my journey of my mental health. I wish you well and I’m glad you feel like you belong here :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 11:17:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I needed this :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 11:17:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really don’t like when people without BPD try to explain what BPD is about. I think it is just annoying because there is so much stigma attached to the disorder that people who are uneducated about it are very easily deterred and it doesn’t help when those articles farther the negative stigmas that people already think about BPD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 11:14:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey OP I feel very similarly and oddly enough I am also in my dorm. When I hear other people having sex I feel grossed out and I don’t like it but at the same time I am reminiscent of the happier times when I was in a sexually active relationship. But it also makes me uncomfortable to think about having sex with anyone right now in my life, I really would like to because of the very good feeling associated with it but i for some reason don’t want to think about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 11:06:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, I know this might not matter, but there is always a reason to continue on. I have been in the lowest of low points in my life, completely out of my mind on drugs screaming at myself in the mirror with a knife to my throat, but something inside me stopped me from putting in that final cut to take me out of this world. I still to this day do not know what that special thing was but I am so ever grateful for it. I’m still not 100% better but I am so much better off than that point, my point is that it takes extreme lows or dips in our lives for us to truly bounce back. It’s like landing on a trampoline, the deeper you bounce the higher you go. I really hope that you can pull out of this and Just know that you are not alone and if you want to talk farther my DM’s are always open </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 10:52:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is certainly not an easy situation to be in. The only thing I can think of is to tell her that you want to help her and you only want the best for her and you will be there if she needs you but you cannot be in a romantic relationship with her if she continues to explode and then blame you for things she does.
It may not be good advice but It’s what I would want someone to do with me if I were doing that. (It might be really tough at first for her to accept and that’s the most crucial point to be supportive) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 10:41:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree with other commenters. As someone with BPD it is very difficult to have a relationship with someone who has BPD, but that person should not use that as an excuse to treat the other person poorly. If the person with BPD is not able to have healthy mechanisms to deal with their own issues, they shouldn’t be in a relationship. (Side note: This is why I am not in a relationship haha) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 10:38:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know this might not make much sense but, if you look at the a graph of the stock market over a year, you’ll see it is a positive and is getting better. However, if you just look at one day or even up to a month, it might not be an upward trend and even a loss on some occasions.
The point of this is that even if you have a bad moment, it is okay as long as you keep working towards your goal, in the long term it’ll always work out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 05:48:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey OP, I’m not sure what FP means, but I’m assuming it has to do with a relationship of some sort.
But you shouldn’t feel bad about talking people you don’t want to be associated with each other anymore, especially if you think that relationship is not healthy to your mental well being.
I hope this helps and I wish you the absolute best in your recovery and your life in general :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Friendships </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 05:44:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey guys, I keep telling myself that the next time I am in a social situation I will talk to people. But then when I am in those situations I kinda just shut down and try to be as inaccessible as possible. Mostly with class as I am a college student. I usually don’t go out to social situations because I get so much anxiety, even though I want desperately to have healthy meaningful relationships with people, I don’t know if I can physically bring myself to try.
Does anyone have any advice or any methods they use to talk to more people or when forming friendships? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Any advice please :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 05:39:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey guys, I am a 19 y/o sophomore in college and I have BPD (borderline personality disorder). My school offers free counseling and I did attend therapy pretty much all of my first year and that’s how I got diagnosed and they put me on an antipsychotic and this mood stabilizer that’s normally used to treat seizures. I have yet to go back this year 1. Because they are doing just online video sessions 2. Because I’ve had this switch within my thinking where I feel like they are trying to control my mind and they are just trying to hurt me or make me part of the system.

Explanation for #1, I have this irrational fear of phone calls and the video call seems like it is just a setup and isn’t real.

Explanation for #2, I’ve always felt like they were against me but I kept going to talk about my feelings. But over the summer I stopped talking my meds cold turkey and I felt absolutely the same about a month later, this furthered my idea that they weren’t trying to help me, because the medicine did absolutely nothing yet my psychiatrist kept telling me that she saw improvements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 05:05:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey OP, I was about 2 years clean as of a few days ago and I didn’t have quite an experience as you with blacking out and I just had overwhelming urges to cut myself. I acted upon those urges and I have only felt dread about my decision. I was very angry with myself and it made me want to do it even more. But I have found that it is very beneficial to realize that it is okay, it will be okay. One lapse is not terrible. Just realize that it’s not beneficial to yourself as you have seemingly already done. I hope this helps and my DM’s are always open if you start to freak out again or just need someone to talk to about anything :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 04:56:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hey, i’m here for you <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 04:36:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> unfortunately i do this thing where I act, like really bad and I have almost perfected it where normal people cannot sense that anything is wrong (that or they don’t say anything) and I refuse to talk about too much with therapists because I think they’ll send me away in a ward or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 04:34:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea, it would certainly be a very thin tightrope you’d have to walk every day, but it would just feel like you know what the other person is going through and how to help them right? and vice versa with them to you, they could relate and help you. I think i just imagine it like a symbiotic relationship where it’s all giving to each other </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 04:18:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s pretty similar and I do tend to reminisce on the visions that I see, just the good ones lol. Although one time I was sitting across from my psychiatrist and i started seeing the room from the upper corner like a camera and then i saw my psychiatrist morph into a monster and attack my body. I snapped out of it but it happened like 3-4 times back to back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Relationships? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 04:14:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 04:09:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s exactly what it feels like sometimes, like i’m able to detach from my body and be someone or something else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 04:07:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey OP, personally I never knew what BPD was until I was diagnosed and since then I have absolutely dreaded medication. Although i have found that the diagnosis has 100% helped me in finding my identity (albeit quite a scattered one) it has still helped nonetheless. I would recommend getting a diagnosis, however if you’re able to get that through counseling or psychiatrists then I would try that first instead of going to a psych ward, I hope this helps and I wish you well in your future endeavors:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 04:03:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey OP, this is so relatable i thought i posted this lol. I am also a sophomore in college with BPD. A lot of the time i also feel horrible about my classes and I feel like i’m doing something wrong just by being in college and not doing something else. I also feel absolutely horrible and like a complete waste of a soul whenever I miss a class or an assignment. Something that I have realized though is that everything is okay in moderation. A lot people use moderation as a mechanism for Alcohol or dieting but i have found that applying this ideology to normal life to be helpful. I tell myself that if i do 3/4 assignments then i am doing perfectly fine and it’s okay to miss some. same with classes, if I go to most of them then I am doing alright, thankfully my classes don’t count attendance. I hope this helps and I hope you feel better about school and you are not alone :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone else? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 03:55:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is anyone else able to like, pause their vision and then see things through someone else’s eyes or even like a camera up in the corner?
It’s a hard thing to explain and I hope I explained it so you guys can visualize. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I feel like i need someone to be complete </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 02:26:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have only ever had one girlfriend and that was truly the happiest i have ever been in my entire life so far. Ever since then i have just been soul searching and avoiding forming relationships with anyone. I still feel like even though i was with my ex for a year, i never really became attached to her, because i knew she would eventually leave. I think i just enjoyed having someone to be intimate with and that was all it was for me. I basically just played her “game” of the little relationship things that you do like ask about how their day was or go on little dates, etc. This was before i was diagnosed with BPD and i knew something was different about me but it seemed like all the disorders that i read about on the internet all applied to me, anxiety, depression, bipolar, and i also had auditory and visual hallucinations but i tried to not tell anyone about that because they weren’t frequent and i didn’t want to be labeled a crazy. Back to having someone in my life, i feel like i’m missing a puzzle piece and that piece is on the shape of another human being. The only issue is that i’ve developed a really unhealthy mechanism of not talking to anyone more that idle conversation and i’ve just come to the conclusion that i am better off alone because i don’t get along with anyone and nobody would be able to understand my problems. Part of me also doesn’t want anyone to have to deal with me and to save everyone else i have built up 30 ft wide concrete walls 12 miles underground with laser turrets on the surface so nobody even comes close </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> need of help </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 02:16:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *disclaimer: i’ve been self harm free for nearly 2 years
Hey guys so i usually do not self harm or anything of that nature as when i think about it, the other side of my head reminds me that it only leads to regret and always makes me feel worse than the moment i was in that made me self harm in the first place. But recently i was gonna go to a party (in a college student) and then i told the person i didn’t want to go anymore like 10 minutes before because i just had a really bad feeling about the whole situation. Then that thought began to grab ahold of me and i just couldn’t bring myself to go at all, so i didn’t go. But then after that he went and i felt this overwhelming sensation of dread, despair and guilt like i just killed someone’s cat. Then then out of nowhere the thought of cutting crept into my head. I told myself i wasn’t gonna do it because it just makes me feel bad about myself and this one time my mom almost noticed my scars and i never regretted something so much in my life before. I went for a walk around my campus and just tried to listen to music but the more i walked, the more powerful the  thought of me hurting myself became. Then i started to think about the positives of it, (i know they’re are virtually no positives but I thought of stuff like it releases pain from my body). I then went back to my dorm and i tried to watch a movie and stop thinking about hurting myself, but then it was almost like i wasn’t in control of myself and i started cutting. that was three days ago and i still feel horrible about it and i don’t know why that thought decided to come into my head. I would love to know anyone’s coping strategies or how they prevent themselves from self harming so i can hopefully prevent it in the future.
side note: **maybe triggering** i was taking a shower and i was feeling the cuts and i began to visualize/see myself completely covered in scars and actually happy for once </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 00:33:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s what my therapist would say about doing acid with bpd. Thank you for the help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 04:09:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m pretty sure she was trying to get it in 😂😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 03:59:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ay, sending good vibes! Have a good one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 03:58:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree, even though I had an ego death on Dec 15 last year I still look at it a learning experience, like not to take four white on white in a frat house with people I’ve never met before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 03:55:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bro I was tripping with my roommate one time and I looked at my hands and the only thing I can say to describe them is that they were baby hands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 00:34:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just printing out on clothing rn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 00:33:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 19:25:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you don’t want to do it atleast 90% I would not recommend it but if you still want the experience I would keep a safety net like maybe your favorite music in a playlist and easily accessible headphones so you can come back to a happy place if you feel yourself slipping away, I wish you good luck and sending good vibes for your time <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 08:02:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The patterns were really dope! And sometimes I got to see the ending of movies if they were empty and it’s really cool seeing large scale screens on cid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 05:23:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m fairly certain Greigers was just expressing his awe at what was said, it was very intense to think about those feelings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 05:20:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would love to see it haha, that’s a really good song :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 05:19:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey man, as long as you are with people you love I believe that it can be a pleasant experience if you don’t dwell on bad thoughts and you make sure to think about how much you are enjoying being where you are and who you are with <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 05:17:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha I just tend to ignore it and try not to touch it in any way shape or form because every time I pee It feels like it’s gonna shoot off too 😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 05:15:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I personally have BPD and I used tripping to escape reality and enjoy other worldly feelings because I absolute dreaded being in this world. I tripped maybe 50 or so times, sometimes up to 6 hits and I would always have a good experience until I went to my friends frat house and tripped with him and two people I didn’t know and I took 4 white on white tabs and I ended up having an ego death and I still deal with flashbacks or waking up and having my soul sucked back into my body and my body feeling like glass shards and portions that don’t have feeling. The point is it only takes one trip when you have a mental disorder (like mine, idk about others) and always make sure you are with people you know and people you trust especially when you are suffering from a mental disorder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 05:09:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sending good vibes <3 just know that it wasn’t real and it was just the drugs <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 05:08:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have a good time <3 sending good vibes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 05:07:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it’s for other people to gauge how it’s going to feel and how they’re going to be throughout. But as someone who’s bought white on white from cartel (pretty close to the source if not the source) the guy still didn’t even know how strong it was, he just gave me a range of 200-300, of which I took 4 and had an ego death so I could reasonably assume I was on 800 and I will not be taking that amount again XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 05:03:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey man I had a really insane ego death on December 15th, 2019 and I still regret that it’s my last experience with cid. I really want to try it again and get rid of that memory but I still have flashbacks to those feelings and that place and i think I just need more time to distance myself before I can dose again but idk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 05:00:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Grateful you had supportive friends so you didn’t spiral ❤️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 04:59:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never really listened to her until I watched every single video imaginable one night on a trip so it just felt like the acid brought us together and I’ve had a soft spot for her since :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 04:58:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bro we like good energy, sending good vibes homie ❤️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 04:54:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Enjoy homie, sending good vibes ❤️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 04:53:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember my ego death trip all I wanted to do was get my headphones and listen to Billie Eilish and I kept telling myself if I could just listen to her id be okay but I did not get to her sadly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 20:53:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/kdvDNQ this active for y’all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 14:52:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/dV3sHa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 14:51:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/dV3sHa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 14:51:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/dV3sHa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 14:51:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/dV3sHa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 14:51:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/dV3sHa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 14:46:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dm it please bros </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 03:41:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All got taken down :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:42:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/6TtBUrU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:41:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/6TtBUrU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:40:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/6TtBUrU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:40:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/6TtBUrU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:39:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/6TtBUrU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:38:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/6TtBUrU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:38:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/6TtBUrU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:38:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/6TtBUrU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:38:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/6TtBUrU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:37:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/6TtBUrU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:37:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/6TtBUrU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:37:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/6TtBUrU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:36:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/6TtBUrU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:36:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/6TtBUrU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:36:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/6TtBUrU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:34:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/MPyyKZ9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:34:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/MPyyKZ9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:33:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/MPyyKZ9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:33:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/MPyyKZ9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:32:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/MPyyKZ9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:32:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/MPyyKZ9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:31:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/MPyyKZ9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:29:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/MPyyKZ9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:29:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/MPyyKZ9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Join the OnlyFans For Free | NSFW Discord Server! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 04:13:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 02:51:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://discord.gg/wnTurvZ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
