<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject79</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 10:14:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Catfishing can only be a good if they’re the ones giving money, or the victim knows theyre a catfish but likes to roleplay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 19:36:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> kind of. I’ve told mine several times that I experience psychosis both when depressed and manic, but they insist I’m type 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 19:10:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah. I don’t think people are purposely trying to do any harm, but it always comes across like “when did you chose to be gay?” or “why are you gay”. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 18:50:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> and there goes my faith in humanity again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 18:49:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it makes every message seem passive aggressive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 14:47:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is wholesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 06:17:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Saw a GP for what I thought was a physical issue, I was manic and he noticed something was up and referred me to a psych who then diagnosed me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 21:31:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sorry I had to. this is a very real and important question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 21:31:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bird 🦜. depressed 😪. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 15:06:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is breathtaking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 04:38:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> makes sense! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 20:32:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sure it will turn out okay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 20:28:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> told my mum on the night of my 18th birthday. she disowned me then told everyone in my family, 2 weeks later I moved across the state alone and started college ✨

Took a few years but we're really close now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 20:18:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Delete photos off your phone that you don't want. Time consuming and productive! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 20:14:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm almost 21 and I still feel like an infant. Doing my own tax returns didn't change a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 20:11:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This might be better as a poll question :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 20:08:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anyone can reclaim language that has been used against them either personally or historically.

You get my gay stamp of approval. ✨^((not that you needed it)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 19:53:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for sharing some of your story. It takes a lot of courage to do so.

I'm not trying to shun people with mental illnesses into hiding. I was diagnosed with bulimia and bipolar disorder a little while ago, and hearing of others experiences or people sharing their stories to break the stigma is so uplifting.

I've always thought 'coming out' was a term exclusive to the LGBTQ+ community and I guess I've just been seeing it pop up more outside of the queer community which has confused me a little, the same as a lot of other queer terminology. But that's just my experience, and I can totally see why people would want to also disclose other parts of their identity using similar language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 05:41:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> found out I was gay at the same time I found out what lgbtq+ was </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone else weirded out by people ‘coming out’ as non-LGBTQ things? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 05:34:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ‘coming out as conservative’
‘coming out as a cancer patient’
‘coming out as having a mental illness’
a few examples I’ve seen.

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/j8y9hu) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 17:45:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We love an ally!

The term queer has been historically aligned with people that are not cis-gendered or heterosexual. If you identify with both of those then you wouldn't be considered queer.

This term has a lot of pain and liberation connected to it, and myself and many other lgbtq+ people have a strong reaction to it. If someone uses the term queer outside of this understanding, I would personally feel pretty silenced and ignored.

This is just my opinion, and I can't stress how thankful I am that you have resonated with and supported the queer community to the extent you have! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 04:18:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sorry you have to go through such quick swings. it must be pretty exhausting, you’re doing great!
This video might help;
 https://youtu.be/Bb2i35Y9J9k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 05:04:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 05:03:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I support you and you are justified. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 04:57:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> love the username, hate the attitude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 04:38:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> whats that I smell? oh, transphobia from someone who can’t imagine a world where people just live their life in ways that will never and have never effected them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 19:59:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> was dumb before, I haven’t noticed any difference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 19:53:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everyone’s preference is different. The lighter the tip the softer/ thinner the reed making it have less resistance when playing. This can also mean less air support, control, and timbral richness. I prefer a bit of a thicker reed but still thin enough that I can use great consistent air support without feeling out having an airy or thin sound.

All reeds will have a lighter tip and darker base. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 19:19:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're talking about the ombre effect on reeds being lighter at the tip and darker at the base, that's because of the way single reeds are carved. They are thinner at the tip and thicker at the base. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 18:32:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wanted to try bullet journaling.

Went to a few European countries, I'm from Australia. I'm also a broke ass college student. That was my entire savings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 16:48:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have no idea. The song resonated with my gay little heart tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 05:31:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> here we go again 😭 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 05:04:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> $3000 on travel.
$200 on stationary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 05:02:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Considering most of my music taste is depressing af, this is the best I can come up with:

Love me the same - Dan Caplen

Ride - Benji Lewis

Only Me - Tim Chadwick

Butterflies - Cub Sport </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 04:49:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me the biggest sign is my sleeping habits. If I’m sleeping less and not feeling tired at all then it’s likely I’m hypomanic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Crying Over Geese </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 19:14:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think i've hit a new low. I've been crying for the past 15 minutes watching videos of geese. Thats all, I'm still crying but I figure someone might get some joy out of how ridiculous this is.

They're just so cute and innocent and sometimes get a bad reputation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 18:37:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm questioning everything. People think tennis balls are green? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 18:24:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no it's really useful! I thought you were a bot account but you're not :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 12:15:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - it’s a really supportive thing to do. And your sister’s negative behaviour would be more disabling to her future prospects than getting professional support. Also I don’t know about your country but employers can’t ask for pre-existing medical information except maybe the military. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 12:07:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> kept putting something off because it’s a source of anxiety, but putting it off was giving me more anxiety. So I did the thing and now I feel less anxious about both.

I also deleted my calorie counting app that made me relapse on my old ED behaviour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 10:19:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is clearly an ad. but also ive been using this for a while and its gr8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 05:21:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my dog comes into my room after walking around or sleeping and whines until I play with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 05:07:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lamotrigine enhances the effect of alcohol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 04:36:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> liquorice flavoured lube </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 04:31:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is why it took me so long to get help and diagnosed.
When I was depressed I knew I had to seek help but I didn’t have the energy.
Then I’d get manic and think I’m cured. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 04:21:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right now I’m depressed so I feel like I’d notice not feeling this way. But also I have never realised in the past until afterwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 17:34:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for your reply. I'm definitely going to ask my psychiatrist for clarification at our next appointment. I tried to at my last but he just upped my medications and told me to see him in 2 months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 16:21:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Advice from a kid who grew up in a rural Australian town 10 hours away from the nearest city. For anyone who needs it.

It won't suck forever. You'll move away and realise you're not alone and there are people out there that will love and support you unconditionally. Until then; consume queer media, write shit down, explore your sexuality safely, come out to a friend or two, make use of lgbtq+ spaces online (the wholesome ones), and remember that you are so much more than the people around you and their opinions of you.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is This Psychosis? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 16:07:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was diagnosed with bipolar II earlier this year despite potential psychotic symptoms. My psych never explained my diagnosis even after telling him about this. I'm wondering if anyone with type 1 or type 2 can relate/ I'm curious of type 1 manic experiences.

Mania:

My most recent manic episode I thought I could see people's auras and predict the future. I spent over $3000 on an impulsive trip to several European countries. This left massive financial consequences for my broke college student ass. I frequently went days without sleeping, otherwise I sleeping <6 hours on average. I blew up at a few friends and strangers because of my irritability. I was still able to perform daily functioning and my delusions were largely kept to myself.

 I experienced one auditory hallucination about 5 years ago which was probably due to starvation (ED).

Depression:

I usually think people are conspiring against me. Believing spiritual or supernatural things are trying to harm me. Recently I  saw moving shadows around my room briefly for a few hours.

&#x200B;

I am mainly just confused when people say that type 2 is 'less severe' or hypomania is just feeling great when my experience doesn't feel like that. Hypomania has some great moments, but my episodes are very destructive leaving severe financial and personal consequences.

I'm interested to see what anyone else thinks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 04:51:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> koalas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 04:39:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> depends on the type of kangaroo. Red kangaroos will fuck you up, grey kangaroos will have a solid nap in the corner.
- sources; I’m Australian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 18:42:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bipolar is driving a car in the city.

You’ll get stuck in traffic,

Not moving and alone in your car.

You’ll get on the highway with cars rushing past,

Frantically changing lanes looking for an exit.

Eventually you’ll reach your destination,

Everything will be calm.

Until you have to return. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 18:25:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> silent practise can be just as useful as making sound!
- Try listening to your piece whilst playing you sax without a mouthpiece.
- Try just doing the fingerings of tricky passages until they feel fluent to build that muscle memory
- Going to your sheet music and write helpful markings you forget to write down when practising; rhythms, articulation, improv notes, breath marks, phrasing, dynamics, piano or accompaniment short scoring/ queues etc!
- Find new music to play.
- Taking time to rest away from your instrument is also important in not getting burnt out

These are just some things I like to do!
Good luck, I hope your recovery goes well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 19:34:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 17:34:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was just a comment on anther subreddit. It's not the psychiatrical explanation and hypermania isn't a word, but I find it helpful to think of it this way. It makes it seem like hypomania isn't just extended periods of feeling happy and optimistic when it's a lot more than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 03:10:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 18:00:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's exciting, I'll have to check it out then!  My opinion above is just what i've heard from others and the young audience it seems to have gathered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 15:26:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (20M gay) who gave you the right to take my fricking breath away on my feed unannounced. You're so gorgeous! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 15:18:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow I feel the exact same way! Hypomania is great for productivity until I have so many things going on at once I can't focus on any of them because my mind is constantly jumping. And I procrastinate so much to get the energy out I end up sewing a new bag and writing a 3 page poetry essay instead of finishing a work task by it's deadline.

gosh this subreddit is amazing for making me feel less alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I can't believe I have never thought about hypomania like this before! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 15:07:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just read something that described mania in terms of **hypermania meaning completely manic, and hypomania meaning slightly manic**. Both are still **mania** and manic episodes.

Until this point I've always felt weird about having BP2 because I felt like I was somehow less severe (therefore needing less help) than someone with BP1 because we don't experience 'mania'. But my hypomanic episodes have been the most destructive periods of my life (they've also had some joyous moments), and I have been able to relate to so many people with BP1, however I have never had to be hospitalised for my mania and even when experiencing delusions I have never felt completely disconnected with reality whilst manic.

I was diagnosed earlier this year and I have done so much research but never found something so impactful as this random comment I found on a subreddit. I hope this helps someone else as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 10:35:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I recognise you don’t have the capacity to be understanding of lgbtq+ because of how your religion has taught you to perceive us. And I also recognise you are a lovely and well meaning person who deserves no hate, however there is a deep historical pain that every lgbtq+ person carries associated with your beliefs surrounding sin and the responses to this post are because you are adding fuel to a fire, however as an individual, you are not the fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 10:26:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you’re can’t be sorry.
God intended us to live without sin and the aim of religion is to get back to that place. A place where lgbtq+ people wouldn’t exist if you believe we are committing sin through our uncontrollable existence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 10:05:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You say you don’t like how Christians have treated us, and then treat us like all the other Christians have throughout history believing our existence is a sin and therefore wrong.
Thank you for believing we should have some equal rights and using preferred language though.

But I’m done with this ‘I’m a good guy christian but I still think you shouldn’t exist’ bullshit. Downvote me to hell idc, the sooner I get there the better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 05:30:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My last episode:
didnt sleep for a few days, spent my entire savings on trip to 3 foreign countries, cut off my closest relationships because I was irritable, reorganised my house then my friends at 2am, thought I possess magical abilities. But hey, at least i managed to start and finish 2 major assignments in 3 days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 22:11:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> selmer or yamaha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 22:07:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here are just some I’ve noted along the way.

Please Like Me: Rose. The main character’s Mum really captured the pain, funny bits, and utter devastation of bipolar. I’ve also never seen a more accurate portrayal of MDD than in the character Hannah. TW.

Silver Linings Playbook: Pat. There we’re definitely bits that were over dramatised and unrealistic, but I saw myself in Pat so much it rendered me speechless and was the first time I considered I might have bp before I was diagnosed.

Euphoria: Rue Bennett. I haven’t seen it, and not sure I want to. It seems to glorify bipolar and mania. The fanbase seems to find bipolar trendy, but apparently it portrays it well.

Skam (norway): Evan. Watched this way before I was diagnosed. The manic scene might be a bit extreme but it showed the importance of support and understanding. It’s also very cute.

Infinitely Polar Bear: Cameron. I haven’t seen it and I’m just preparing myself before I do. It seems like it really captures bipolar parenting accurately. The happiness the pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 18:54:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Peter pan in the 2003 live action movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 08:03:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this gave me a good chuckle after scrolling though all the cats and dogs. he’s gorgeous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 17:19:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He justified a mass shooting on a minority group... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 16:09:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> happy birthday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 21:12:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not American. I wouldn’t say it makes a massive impression unlike other accents.
It’s not a bad thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 19:42:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is everything to do with him and nothing to do with you.
when I’m manic I have a short fuse and when I feel like people will try and slow me sown or stop me (because they are concerned) I push them away and get angry at them for trying to stop me whether this is reality or delusional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 18:55:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd consider him questioning or bisexual. If a gay man on occasion willingly sought out and enjoyed having sex with women, I would consider him bisexual.

Probably because I've never experienced it but I just can't get in the mind-frame of a straight guy seeking gay sex and considering him self straight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 18:40:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's possible, but pretty extreme. Personally as a gay man, there is no level of desperation I can imagine that would result in me having sex with a woman. Unless there was a significant monetary reward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 18:37:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA - I think you meant well! But also an 18 year old engaging in a private conversation with a 14 year old to the extent you were is creepy. That's just my opinion though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 18:33:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A straight man is not romantically or sexually attracted to another man.

But someone who is not romantically or sexually attracted to another man will not engage in homosexual behaviour such as going to a gay bathhouse or having gay sex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 18:23:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a person who engages in homosexual behaviour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 17:58:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> **Homosexuality** is [romantic](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Romance_(love)) attraction, [sexual attraction](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sexual_attraction), or [sexual behavior](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Human_sexual_activity) between members of the same [sex](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sex) or [gender](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gender).[\[1\]](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Homosexuality#cite_note-AmPsycholAssn-definitions-1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 15:17:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you for the reply </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 15:17:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ive only had short mixed episodes (a day or two) before an episode switch. they are the worst I cant imagine going through prolonged mixed episodes.
my hypomania is on the higher end of the scale, you’re right it is a gamble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 15:15:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t really know what this means </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 15:15:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> probably explains why I have such a shitty memory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 19:23:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes.

It is manageable until my brain convinces me to attempt suicide again. It is manageable until I speed down the freeway with my eyes closed at 5am seeing how long I can last before opening them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 19:42:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you for the tw. seems like a beautiful post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 18:49:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rather than getting caught up with self diagnosis, look up things that help people with bipolar; keeping a regular sleep and meal schedule, having a support group etc.

For reference though my episodes usually last 2-3 months and that’s on the shorter end. Bipolar is more than being moody during the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 18:36:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it’s called ultradian bipolar. it’s a bit controversial </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 20:09:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are some side effects you experience? I've just started my lamictal journey a month ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 19:56:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh my goodness. ignore the typos, I'm writing this with tears in my eyes. You madam are simply the best.

There are going to be things you don't know that she also doesn't know, but part of growing up is learning that stuff, and part of being a parent to an LGBTQ+ child is offering support and safety along the way. Coming out is the beginning of someone journey, not the end of it.

Sex:

You don't have to be the one to show her methods of safe sex or discuss sex in detail with her, no child enjoys that! But telling her that she should follow safe sex with a man or a woman, and that there are resources online available for that is an important conversation to have, since she probably won't learn about gay safe sex in school. Also talking to her about consent is important too.

Support:

I didn't have a supportive reaction from my mother when I came out. However she came around after a few years and now we are close again. The most impactful thing my mother has ever done for my little gay heart was asking "would you like to watch 'love simon' (a high school gay romance movie) with me". We watched it in silence, and didn't speak afterwards. But that is possibly the most impactful moment of my life. Initiating a desire to watch or listen to gay media will make your daughter feel so appreciated. Showing interest in general, "that girl is cute!" "did you know Drew Barrymore is bisexual too?" She might be embarrassed, but she will feel normal, and it will become less awkward and allow her to discuss it openly with you as well. Educate yourself as well on the LGBTQ+ issues, definitions, advice forums (you're doing great at this already <3) .

Concerns:

Unfortunately LGBTQ+ individuals are 2.5 more likely to suffer a mental health crisis compared to cisgendered heterosexuals. Bisexual and gay women are twice as likely to experience substance abuse issues in comparison to heterosexual women. This is something that is rampant within the community and it will be important to monitor this closely. Even in the most supportive home environment, it is difficult to feel supported in a world that wasn't designed for you.

She will still go through the normal stages of life, she will have other issues and concerns, and being bisexual is just a part of who she is it doesn't define her.

You:

Because of her coming out you are going to notice things in the world around you, you may notice more of the microagressions and homophobia in the world and it may be difficult knowing you can't protect her from everything. Just know that you don't have to be perfect, and it's okay if at times it is overwhelming for you. You are not being selfish for feeling the emotions you are feeling now and in the future, but you have a new responsibility to your daughter now and you will need to love her so deeply she will never forget how amazing and valued she is. I wish you the best of luck, and a part of me is jealous but so excited you and your daughter get to experience something the majority of LGBTQ+ people never have or will. You are amazing. Your daughter is amazing. <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 18:46:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It takes a while to taper up to a therapeutic dose of lamictal so it may be some time before we see results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 09:30:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If the issue is reaching the low C:

Keep your throat open (similar to your throat position in a yawn) and think about engaging the top like a bit more, if you throw in a lot of ab support you'll be able to hit the note without any drama!

Don't worry about the staccato or dynamics for now, get comfortable resonating the note at any dynamic and with a full sound. You can always go back and perfect the markings later!

Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 19:42:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> doritos!

and to tax the rich </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 19:09:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is not your fault. Whatever you're feeling right now is valid and justified, but just know that this was a reflection of everything good in you and everything bad in the other person. You shouldn't feel ashamed for being kind and trusting, these are good qualities they were just abused in this situation.

I was catfished and I didn't see red flags as red flags until a long time afterwards. It's easy for others to tell you things were red flags or you should have known when they didn't experience what you experienced in the environment you did.

This is a lesson. It will guide you though life and is so valuable yet not many learn it. There are genuine people out there, and your good qualities are still good. You are still an individual who is strong, amazing and is worthy of genuine connection.

My heart breaks for you but is excited that you get to move on to better things in your life. Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 17:05:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That must be pretty exhausting. I've never experienced that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 18:07:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much! I'll check this out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 18:04:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have such a bad memory, my friends say it's one of my biggest personality traits. I have 0 long term memory and I am constantly forgetting things. I'm 20 but have been scared of having dementia before.

This was true even before meds, I wonder if it may be a result of harmful behaviours earlier in my life.

Good luck, I find keeping a well structured schedule helps and setting lots of reminders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 17:58:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Be yourself, people who comment on a mans perceived femininity in a negative way have a very fragile and toxic perception of what masculinity is 💕 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I don't know what 'Baseline' is. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 17:54:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been tracking my moods for a few months now after my psych told me to, and I'm finding it difficult to track when I'm feeling baseline. I'm either manic or depressed with no in between according to my tracker.

Does anyone have any tips or advice about how to not subjectively track their moods? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 17:44:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So true. In a way I feel like it's been painting this picture that suicide isn't serious because the people posting aren't serious about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 17:41:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd see a GP (family doctor) for a physical check after telling them your mental health symptoms, if its all clear they'll refer you to a psychiatrist who will then evaluate you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 20:23:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can set multiple reminders via the settings and I make notes throughout the day whenever I’m free in the ‘daily notes section’.

Use whatever works for you, I used a physical mood tracker for a while before eMoods. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 20:19:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use eMoods and I love it so much more than Daylio which seems to be popular on here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 20:15:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m actually currently on lamotrigine! It’s too soon to notice any difference yet though. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 04:22:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe check out bullet journalling! It’s what I do and I’ve never been more organised. It does require some upkeep, you can be as organised or disorganised as you’d like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 21:00:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It suits you so well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Finished my first sheet of meds today, feeling proud :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 17:42:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 17:34:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Different practises have different policies. At my work I have a duty of care over a group of people who are a similar same age to me. If I engage in any romantic or sexual interactions with someone from that group, my contract will be terminated and I will be fired.

Think about how this may impact your teacher as well as your own engagement with your therapy programme. You can do better than some PE teacher :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 17:20:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We never know the whole story. Please don't come on here to blame victims. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 07:19:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry to hear you're going through a tough time. I'm also diagnosed with bipolar and was too a lonely gay teen once. Things will make sense in the future, I can't say when they just will. You will meet people that make you feel appreciated and heard, until then take this time to become your own best friend and perfect the craft of self validation before relying on others to do that for you, you'll be a much stronger person because of it.

Good luck, and remember there are always people on here and professionals that are interested in listening to you and your story <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 07:04:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> because we're conditioned to believe love is wrong, so when someone shows interest our response is skepticism, or purely sexually driven since that is the majority of the media that we have seen showing 2 gay men 💞 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 06:55:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think this is a wonderful mental note to remind yourself of your worth and boundaries. If I saw this on my facebook I probably would think this was a bit random and uncomfortable to engage with as it seems more like an inner monologue than something someone should post on social media.

If someone posted something like "after a lot of reflection I have realised some boundaries that I look forward to keeping in the future when it comes to whom I surround myself with" then I'd totally love and understand that.

I absolutely love what you've written though and I hope more people can set boundaries like this in their life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 21:41:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The deep sense of self-evaluation and reflection that we experience trying to come to terms with our identity, something that straights will probably never go through.

And penises. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 08:55:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A teacher can walk you through the basics, but it might be good to check out some 'saxophone fingering' videos on youtube just to remind you of how the instrument works!

In the beginning of learning, and picking an instrument up again, it will feel really slow and it might be overwhelming, but I promise after the first month things will really change and everything gets so much easier! You'll be performing in no time! You've just got to keep it up, and having a scheduled weekly or biweekly lesson with a teacher can help with that motivation :)

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 15:10:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you block them and then unblock them (remember their usernames), you both automatically unfollow each other. It's like it never happened </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 14:54:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> from what I've been told by my doctors and online, it isn't common that lamotrigine will increase depressive symptoms it's more likely going to help lift the depression a little bit but taking anti-depressants alongside it is very common. Doesn't mean that depressive side-effects aren't possible, and I would definitely talk to your doctor about it asap - this also might just be a depressive episode coming on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 14:49:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's so exciting!

There's lots of videos on youtube for remembering the fingering of the sax with some scales as well. There's some song tutorials for sax on there as well, otherwise check out muscore for lots of free sax music.

Alternatively see if there are any local sax teachers that might be able to help you out (I promise you we love teaching mature aged students as well, it's pretty common) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 14:40:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personally it would make more sense to write that in the question "Any reminder brought back feelings about Covid-19" which still doesn't make sense as question but is less vague. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 14:38:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> also for transparency it would look better to keep all mentions of covid-19 as either covid-19 or coronavirus not mixing between the two like in q. 7 of page 3 "coronavirus-19" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 14:34:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> page 2, q. 12 has a typo 'feelingsabout' -> feelings about

q. 14 and q. 19 have similar typos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 14:27:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the question "Any reminder brought back feelings about it" doesn't make sense by itself and also in relation to the question brief at the top of the page. If you're referring to stressful life events pre-covid, it would make more sense for the question to state that (during the last 7 days, and as a result of the covid-19 pandemic) "I spent a long time thinking about stressful past events"

And for the questions that follow after that, stating what "it" is would make it easier to answer. Both in the brief and in the question itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 14:25:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The possible answer selection for "How long has it been since the first COVID-19 cases reported in the area you reside in?" isn't coherent. "poor health - 1 2 3 4 5 -  good health" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 15:57:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel this way too, especially right after  I was diagnosed. It still comes in waves of thinking I'm fine until something happens and I realise I'm not.

Keep going, it's scary but it will all make sense eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 15:55:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would go to your GP and talk to them about this, otherwise if you have a psychiatrist or psychologist I'd bring this up in your next meeting :)

Good luck <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 15:44:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 22:40:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 100% agree. I hate questioners and end up answering everything with "sometimes". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 21:37:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just started lamotrigine too :) Well done for getting help and starting this new journey of stability, good luck <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 18:23:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 18:20:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It still says "you need permission" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 18:11:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "This form can only be viewed by users in the owner's organisation." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 09:36:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you so much. I'm glad you don't hate yourself <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 11:17:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like psychotic depression </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 11:08:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy birthday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 11:06:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldn't tell people I'm something that I'm not diagnosed with. It can be helpful to share and reach out when you're experiencing bipolar-like symptoms though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 10:57:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I couldn't agree more! I hate that bipolar is becoming romanticised </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 06:45:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> take this time to digest it for yourself. It will be good in the long run to tell the people lose to you, but also you need time to process before telling others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 06:29:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> clinginess and emotional availability. (I'm into guys that treat me like shit, I hate it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 06:20:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> voted no - but I think there might be some grey area when it comes to self-defence (not rape).

The sweetest  (and like 4ft 4) girl I knew in high school tried to defend herself against someone who had been abusing her and her mother for years, she hit him and he fell and died. She's in jail now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 06:14:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I totally agree with you. Thanks for having this conversation with me.

I feel weak as hell right now too, sometimes I try to say positive things hoping I might believe them. I've spent a few months coming to terms with my diagnosis as well, still go through periods of denying it completely. (insert optimistic statement neither of us believe)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 06:05:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry to hear you're going through a mixed/depressed episode. Must be pretty frustrating.

I'm glad I'm not alone in this, I don't feel like accepting the thoughts is a healthy thing to do - especially suicidal ones, but the fact that we're still here is pretty remarkable and maybe it's a sign of strength instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 06:00:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So proud of you for even considering it! Don't forget behind the ears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 05:57:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was raised in a small conservative town of about 12,000 people (Australia). Had people frequently say homophobic shit to me, and went to a religious school that made us declare why homosexuals should die multiple times in our compulsory religious classes.

I yeeted out of there as soon as I graduated and haven't looked back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 18:54:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks, you too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 18:41:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> tiger king </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 18:38:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> murdering baby tigers. lashing out at people around him. only caring about money and fame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 18:34:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Voted No.

I feel like he started out as a good guy who had to go through some difficult things, but he slowly became really volatile to both the animals and people around him. I think he needs some time away to reflect and hopefully when he gets out he'll lead a different life away from animals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 04:51:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so far im just on lamictal, I'll eventually add others, but its been 6 days since first starting meds after many months of my doctors persuading me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 19:07:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> penguin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 18:39:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you fucking did that! im so hyped for you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 18:32:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the progressive movements and conversations that are happening. But god, every day it amazes me that the country has lasted this long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 18:29:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> be the person you wish you had when you were going through a difficult time. <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 18:22:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> somewhere outdoors away from people. I go for a walk sometimes. Or I just drive aimlessly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 18:14:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yep on mood stabilisers. Will probably be on them for a long time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 18:07:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NAH

Wasn't just ethnicities that were targeted - other minorities were as well like homosexuals and 'gender deviant' people, but no one likes to talk about that. It was a horrible time for lots of people, and everyone is valid in feeling sad and angry for those that passed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 17:58:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get intrusive thoughts when depressed/ anxious but I've never had intrusive thoughts that felt external - that sounds more like hallucinations. It might be good to call your doc and see what they think just to be sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 14:32:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right! I think it also needs to show the negative sides to stop the romanticisation of bp though - but please no more serial killers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 14:30:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't seen it being romanticised as much as other mental illnesses (like eating disorders), but I think it probably still exists. The whole Kanye West situation didn't help.

I think there has to be a healthy balance between media portraying bipolar as a serious illness, ie: mania can be very destructive and isn't just a quirky creative phase, with  depression also being a serious part of the illness. Whilst also showing that people with bipolar are just like everyone else and can live healthy and stable lives too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 10:28:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry to hear you mixed episodes can last so long.

Yeah I get very irritable and often have a very short fuse so will likey lash out on people for the smallest thing (which I hate). For me when I say 'physical' it more feels like my skin itself stings and tingles - it's more of a psychological thing I think rather than an actual condition that occurs during a mixed episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 10:17:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope you can get some answers and the help you need. I'm sorry to hear you're going through a difficult time, it must feel pretty frustrating. Good luck <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 09:49:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We grow up in a society that tells us it's wrong on social, cultural, historic, and political levels.  Just because someone is surrounded by support doesn't mean they won't still carry a lot of shame and fear because of the pressures they know exist.

If you were in a room filled with safe object, but you knew outside it's burning and there are armed murderers waiting for you - you probably wouldn't feel very safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 09:38:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely talk to a doctor about this as soon as possible. Lots of things can cause mood swings - it's best to get a professionals advice and run some physical tests before researching too deep into bipolar which might make it difficult to get the correct diagnosis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 09:35:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't imagine what it's like to be in lockdown in an unsupportive environment! Good luck hon! Watching lgbtq choirs on youtube is an emotional and liberating rollercoaster if you're up for it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 09:29:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for posting!

Even the most progressive countries have people who have experienced horrific treatment for being lgbtq+. And attending pride for those people can be incredible healing. Even those who have grown up in a supportive environment will surely feel some sort of liberation attending pride.

But also we can't forget that Pride isn't just for that city or country. When I was younger I would look at photos and videos from Pride events around the USA (I'm not American) and it would make me feel less alone and as though one day I could be who I am authentically.

Just because you think it isn't necessary, doesn't mean that it isn't necessary for others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 09:21:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally. Even in progressive countries there is still a lot of homophobia and danger for lgbtq people. I grew up in a small town in Australia, I've received threats, my gay femme friend has been attacked and chased on foot and in vehicles (we are both 20-21). And the normal gay slurs and religious people trying to give us interventions. A girl at my religious high school was kicked out after the principal interrogated her about her sexuality (a year or two before my friend and I were there).

Yet somehow being gay is now 'becoming popular' as the straights like to say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 09:10:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your birthday is just a date, you don't have to celebrate it on the day! You can still do your plans just a little later, or do something with your partner as a celebration of being out of quarantine but also turning 21!

All of my close friends rarely had their 21st party on the day they turned 21 - they would save it for a weekend or an upcoming event.

When you can, I'd talk to your doc and see what they say about being off of meds right now since it sounds like it might be a bit of a difficult time ahead.


Good luck and happy birthday!!! <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 09:01:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Laura Marling - My Manic and I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 08:51:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mixed episodes can appear in lots of different ways.

For me they feel like I have a million things I want to do, but I physically don't even have the energy to get out of bed and shower. It feels like I'm going insane a little to the point it physically hurts when I'm like this. It can look like severe boredom as well, doing lots of things but nothing gives me any entertainment, or being so bored and yet I don't want to do anything. Sometimes I can have bursts of energy followed by severe lows all within about 10 minutes. When I'm like this it feels like my brain is about to split in two and I get really aggressive because I don't understand whats going on and I can't stop it.

My mixed episodes don't last for long, at most they're a week long, but usually it's a day or two before a major episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 08:36:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Been on lamotrigine for about a week - haven't noticed any difference, but haven't gotten the rash side effect either so it's going well.

I'm having a really bad day today, I'm considering going back to my doc and asking for my fluoxetine prescription. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 09:36:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> studies have shown a connection between genetics and bipolar.

If you note obvious periods of low and then elevated moods in your mum  (lasting from weeks or months, years), then I'd consider looking deeper into the diagnostic criteria of bipolar, or better yet asking her to see a GP for a psychical and mental health check and they might be able to refer your mum to a psychiatrist. That's if she's willing, which usually isn't the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 19:03:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> call my psychiatrist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 19:51:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I totally agree it's good to find a psychiatrist that you trust! I think part of my trust with my psychiatrist is built on the fact that he is a mood disorder, specifically bipolar specialist. But he lacks trust in other areas - it's really up to individual preference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 19:31:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> maybe try creating a poll for questions like this next time - but yeah it's annoying when people do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 19:23:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no way.

also people down voting you are probably treating this like a poll - so they're down voting to say "no" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 19:19:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're undiagnosed - talk to a GP first and they will assess your physical health (lots of things can cause mood abnormalities), then they will refer you or you can ask to be referred to a psychiatrist who specialises in mood disorders (usually). A psychiatrist can then recommend a psychologist - some doctors also do this.

If you're diagnosed looking for a second opinion/ additional help, talk to whatever professional you've been seeing (GP, psychiatrist or psychologist) and they'll be more than happy to help!

Also you definitely want someone who specialises in mood disorders if you can! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 18:47:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's 2020, if someone uses 'my camera doesn't work' as an excuse - they're almost definitely a catfish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 18:42:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I felt the same after I was diagnosed. But after really looking back, I realised I did have manic episodes I just didn't realise it at the time - which is pretty common with mania, and it can be even more tricky to pinpoint with hypomania. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 18:40:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> whats a pirate age? like dressing up as a pirate, but it's age appropriate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 18:35:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dating can be scary for anyone, but especially for gay and trans folk. Just remember that you can't force love, it'll come to you when you least expect it.

I'd try tinder, it's a great way to see who's out there and I've found it a less intimidating and sex-focused dating app compared to grindr. Maybe see if there are local groups or activities for trans and gay people in your area as well!

Good luck, I'm so happy you can now start living as the authentic you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 08:50:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd wait a little while hun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 08:49:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what does that even mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 08:47:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No - you don't need to come out. But if you know there's no reason to be worried about it, then I personally would. I think it would help avoid the awkward tip-toeing around the subject in the future and also the unnecessary anxiety/ uncertainty that you're holding onto (eg: posting on here). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 08:38:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was 17 when I first considered it - followed by long periods of denying it then considering it again.

I got referred to a psych earlier this year (I'm 20) after seeing a doctor about what I thought was something else. Both my doctor and my psych told me I have bipolar but it wasn't until recently I've started believing it. I still go through moments of thinking it's just all in my head - despite obvious history with depression and hypo/mania.

&#x200B;

Talk to your therapist and see what they think about potentially being bipolar, and getting referred to a psychiatrist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 08:23:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> THIS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 08:06:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some people will take a while to understand. Especially people really close to us - they have to say goodbye to the life they thought you would live and get to know the authentic you.

 If you are in high school, or younger, chances are you are the first gay person the people around you have ever met. People don't hear lgbtq+ people talk about their sexuality/ identity/ sex very much because we are a minority, so naturally when we talk about it cic/straight people think we're obsessed because they're hearing it 100% more than before you came out.

My biggest advice is to take this time to celebrate and love yourself. You get to be your own person and you don't have to hide anymore. Explore your sexuality and self expression. Research, ask questions, explore, but most importantly be safe!

Also know that it might feel like your sexuality is a massive part of your identity right now, partly because society treats it like it is, but there is so much more to you than your sexuality. Don't feel like you have to talk about your sexuality all the time, or feel like you have to come out to people if you don't want to, don't feel like you have to sleep with lots of guys, don't feel like you have to dress or act a certain way. Feel free to do that if you want, but there is so much more to you than that.

Coming out is the first step to uncovering who you are, it isn't the final step. Being in the closet surpasses so much more than just your sexuality. This unlocks so many more doors, it's just the beginning of your journey and I'm excited for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 18:38:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've just started as well - 2 days ago. Obviously haven't noticed anything massive, but the past 2 days have been good :)

Good luck <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 18:36:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I drive. But I can usually tell when I am in a bad place and try to remind myself not to drive during those times. Doesn't always work but I find driving actually helps - I zone out mentally (in a healthy and still attentive to road safety kind of way) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 18:33:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just started meds for the first time since being diagnosed earlier this year. Feeling really nervous but I think this is the right decision.

It's just difficult to imagine a life without my severe episodes - they almost feel like a comfort blanket. I am going to have to get to know a completely new version of myself, but I'm excited to meet him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 07:45:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It depends on who the genitals belong to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 10:23:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The classic side-eye smirk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 10:05:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree.

At the end of the day we all experience it differently, and bp isn't as consistent as we like to believe - otherwise we'd probably be a lot better than we are now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 08:55:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. 2.

Sometimes it depends on how high the mania was or how low the depression was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 16:45:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is exactly how I've been feeling lately. wow.

I've come to terms with the fact that my authenticity is multifaceted. There is no 'depressed' me or 'manic' me or 'baseline' me. They are all me - they just reflect different aspects of me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 05:03:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> School will always be there to go back to. Your mental health can't be put on pause. If I were in your situation I would see if I could maybe do 1 class per semester, whilst living somewhere I am comfortable and not stressed. I would also continue to see my doctors regularly for checkups and continue my medication/ assess whether I need to change doses/ medication with my psych.
Good luck, college is hard enough without bipolar, the fact you managed to try again is in itself amazing and not many people would have even considered that.

xx another bipolar college student <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 04:59:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been trained it's not a good idea to acknowledge the hallucinations, but you can 100% validate people's emotions. Saying things like "that sounds pretty scary" "do you feel sae?" "that must be pretty confusing/ conflicting, is there anything you'd like me to do to help you?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 08:22:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I loved Skam (norway)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 18:10:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I totally agree. There were times when I really didn't like Josh, and then there were times when I had the deepest of empathy for him. The entire series is comprised of shifting opinions and biases by the audience, it really made me feel like I was apart of the story somehow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 17:33:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interesting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 17:32:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No spoilers! But it is an emotional rollercoaster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 17:23:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An adjective is a descriptive word. In this example we're looking at the use of 'bipolar' instead of words like 'indecisive' or 'moody'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Using 'Bipolar' as an Adjective? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 17:03:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> eg : "the weather is so bipolar" "my cat is so bipolar"

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/icpbzu) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 16:50:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Please Like Me* Is my favourite series of all time. It's a quirky Australian series about a gay man. Can't recommend enough, might not be everyone's cup of tea though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 16:47:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know Schizophrenia has been ruled out, but her channel really goes into a lot of depth with psychosis - what it's like and how to help those during one. Good luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 15:19:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That must have been pretty scary for you both. The youtube channel  '*Living Well with Schizophrenia'* is run by a woman living with Schizoaffective disorder. She talks about her experiences, educational videos, but ALSO has videos with her partner and he gives some great advice into how he supports her.

Sorry I don't have the answers you're after, but her channel might! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 14:55:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your best bet is to get your hands on the syllabus for 2020:

[https://www.ameb.edu.au/shop/syllabuses-study-resources/digital-syllabuses-2020/woodwind-syllabuses/2020-saxophone-syllabus.html](https://www.ameb.edu.au/shop/syllabuses-study-resources/digital-syllabuses-2020/woodwind-syllabuses/2020-saxophone-syllabus.html)

Keep in mind it might be different between *Saxophone* and *Saxophone for Leisure*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 14:37:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - I'm so sorry this happened to you. You're right, it never feels good to stoop to someone else's level, but I don't think you stooped that low in comparison to what she did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 14:17:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not married - I'm a happily single 20 year old - but I like the concept of marriage. I think there are plenty of healthy and lifelong relationships out there that aren't married -   personally I like how it can symbolise the complete trust and unity between two people.

I'd also like to live the dream of my younger self and all those who came before me who thought they could never get married or live a 'normal' life as a queer person. I'd like to honour all those who died and would have died to see a day when two men could get married.

When it was legalised in Australia (2017) it marked the first moment in my life I felt as though I could live a normal life with someone I loved in the future - and I'd like to think that'll happen one day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 17:06:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - I'm sorry this happened to you and your children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 16:54:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That must feel a bit confusing. If it were me I would call my doctor and tell them this and see what they think - it might be a side effect from medication or it might be nothing to worry about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 13:18:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sexuality is a weird thing, it's completely normal to have lots going on in your head.

Just so you know, you can be impressionable and not be straight (I know you weren't implying that you can't but it may help to know that after coming out I feel a lot more confident in myself which makes me a lot more impressionable in my professional and personal life).

I'm sorry your exes reacted the way they did, just know that there are lots of women out there that wouldn't care and the fact that they reacted negatively has everything to do with them and nothing to do with you. Some might find it more attractive and mature to have a deeper understanding of themselves and their sexuality.

Feel free to keep asking questions and venting whatever is on your mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 10:54:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Age is relative. You're old to younger people, and young to older people.

When i was 12 I felt so mature but thought that 20 year olds were fully functioning adults. And now I'm 20 and think 12 year olds are small children, and I am definitely not a functioning adult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 10:44:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also as a gay man, I can physically and mentally not imagine being romantically or sexually intimate with a woman. That's just my experience, but it may help to give some reference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 10:42:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We're all individuals who happen to share an identity it doesn't mean all have the same experience with our identity.

If you are/were sexually and romantically attracted to females, chances are you aren't gay, but maybe bisexual if you are sexually/ romantically attracted to men also.

Internalised homophobia can cause a lot of anxiety and really skew the way we think about our sexuality (hence why a lot of homophobic bullies turn out to actually be a lil' gay). So if you can imagine a world without LGBTQ+ stigma and you imagine yourself being happy with a man, the same as you can be happy with a women, then you might be bisexual.

&#x200B;

At the end of the day a label is just a label, it doesn't define or dictate how we live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 21:19:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That must be really exhausting. I'd encourage talking to your doctors about this. Some people with ultradian bipolar might experience such quick mood swings, but it's pretty rare with bipolar outside of mixed episodes. From what I've gathered from others and my own experience being diagnosed, it seems more common for episodes to last several months. I can't even imagine how frustrating it would be to cycle more frequently than that.

Alternatively, my friend has borderline personality disorder and some of her symptoms sound similar to this. But once again, check with your doctors <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 11:41:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't imagine how difficult this must be for you right now. You didn't deserve that and there are people out there that will love and support you unconditionally. For right now, do you have any friends or relatives you might be able to stay with? If not, try searching for an lgbt/ youth centres near by. There are also international call lines you can use. The trevor project does amazing things for LGBTQ+ people and also homeless LGBTQ+ people : [https://www.thetrevorproject.org/](https://www.thetrevorproject.org/) . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 18:22:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go to a GP tell him you experience severe mood swings you're concerned about. They will likely want to run physical exams (blood, urine, etc), maybe some shitty screen tests for anxiety, ADHD etc. Then if that's clear they will refer you to a psychiatrist (hopefully one that specialises in mood disorder).

That's how things ideally will happen. This process can take a few days, or maybe a few weeks/ months. But it's worth it in the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 18:18:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Worrying about bulge when wearing certain pants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 11:39:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so much love <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 11:38:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fuck yeah! you just did that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 11:31:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Injuries are pretty common in all instruments when healthy practise techniques aren't followed. I've had a few RSIs from sax playing. You can also really hurt your neck and shoulder muscles/ back. Everyone is different, and every instrument has the potential for health risks. But sax is bloody amazing so I hope it works out for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 11:22:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 11:20:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can create so many different sounds with 1 setup. Your body creates the different sounds and timbres, different setups can amplify certain things though and can majorly change the game. But you can go really far without buying different mouthpieces, reeds, or even different saxs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 11:05:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  I'm in my 3rd year of university (in Australia) and have diagnosed bipolar 2, and a problematic history with food.

\-Anxiety-

University can be really intimidating, even without the added stress of mental health struggles. Some of your anxiety is natural, and everyone else is experiencing that as well. And some of that anxiety is unique to your circumstance and is completely valid. One thing that helped me was decorating my room as soon as I got there, it helps feel more safe and personalised. It's also really scary meeting new people in a new environment, but everyone else is feeling the exact same way and is jus waiting for someone else to talk to them - so try being that person or being open for someone to talk to you. That's how I met my best friends and we still live together.

\-Food-

Living at a residential college has been so great for me in terms of maintaining a healthy and regular daily schedule. Nutrition is super important for the brain and the body, and I don’t have to think about it at college compared to when I’m at home. Meal times are also the exact same time every day which helps keep a daily routine going. Because the meals are already made, it means that when I’m in a depressive episode, if I can bring myself to the dining hall, I can eat a nutritious meal, and if I’m hypo/manic I know eating won’t take as much time as it normally would so I tend to continue eating even when I feel like I’m too busy to eat.

But also I’ve found that I still get some intrusive thoughts at meal times, but it has helped me so much to have my friends go to meals with me and distract me whilst we talk about random things. I forget about the food and the thoughts. I’m thankful that the worst of my ED was a few years ago now, but this supportive format has really helped me.

\-Support-

I feel the most supported I’ve ever felt being at college. I live surrounded by friends who are there for me to go to when things are difficult, or are there to make sure I’m about to do something stupid when hypo/manic. My college also has a really great student support team that are trained in helping mental health situations. I also have access to the counselling/ doctor services at my university. I also have my private doctors and psychiatrists that I go to, but I like that the other options are still there.

\-Independence-

It’s scary having to be more independent but it has been so refreshing for me. In good ways and bad. I feel a lot more secure in who I am as a person now that I control my life. Once you’re at uni, you’ll be able to see what units you like more and what you choose to study may change. None of my friends have continued to study what they initially entered in 3 years ago, and are loving what they’re doing now. It’s your life, you make the rules and sometimes you suffer the consequences only to learn for the future.

Good luck, and let me know if you have any questions. College is an amazing experience, and there’s naturally going to be some bumps along the way but we’ll get through it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 06:57:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not everyone has the resources but I would look into seeing a different psychiatrist. There might be some online options as well especially because of the current COVID situation. It sounds really frustrating and I hope you can some answers soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 06:26:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I keep 3 journals. 1 is my scheduling and organisational  journal, the other is a diary where I write down what whatever I want - poetry, thought trains, really witty responses I thought of after a conversation. The last one is for drawing.

But just between you and me, buzzfeed quizzes are my ultimate go to when bored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 06:17:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It looks really nice :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 06:15:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't have advice, but just know that he loves you for a reason we can't control or anticipate what others feel. If it comes to the future and you've recognised your mental health needs to take priority instead of the relationship then you can sort it out then. But I don't think you should deprive yourself or your partner a loving relationship because of what might happen in the future.

Good luck <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 05:49:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ignored them, pretended they didn't happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 19:17:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OOft. That's how I got diagnosed. Was hypo and thought I had a physical issue, saw a doc and straight up told him about my suicide attempts and delusions with no remorse of filter.  A cheeky psych evaluation later and here I am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 19:02:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I sent very emotive and possibly aggressive emails to local, interstate and international governments. It's been a few months and I'm just now receiving replies. I cringe every time I get one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 18:55:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. &#x200B;

Sometimes you don't need to douche, you can just tell you're good. If you do douche, don't use too much water, you really just need to clean the rectum, not the entire colon. I use lukewarm water. You can buy an enema, or get creative. For my first time I just used a water bottle lol. I usually douche 2-3 times. Wait a solid 30 minutes after douching before sex.

2.

Lube is amazing. Being relaxed/ breathing and not stressed is also great for loosening up, but also foreplay is great. Also lots of lube. Both on the dick and on the hole.

3.

I use a trimmer without the guard. Less ingrown hairs/ razor bumps and itchiness. But if you have to shave, try using a mirror. At the very least use your free hand to 'see' where the blade is going. I cover my butthole with my finger when trimming or shaving because if you cut or trim that. My god.

&#x200B;

I was really anxious before my first time as well, but I got really lucky and I was with someone I trusted and who had experience and new to take it slow. Make sure to voice your concerns and remember that consent is everything. Tell him if it doesn't feel okay. Tell him if you change your mind. Porn isn't realistic. If it hurts stop. Also air might escape during sex and it might be embarrassing but it happens all the time so just laugh it off or ignore it. Remember that you're giving him something, he isn't taking anything from you.

Good luck! (it'll be okay) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 18:42:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not a psych.

I've heard it's common for this to happen depending on if you're having a depressive or (hypo)manic episode. When I'm depressed I'm either a full on vacuum or I don't have the energy to eat. When I'm (hypo)manic I usually don't eat or eat a normal amount when I remember to have a meal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 17:52:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cry if you need to baby <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 15:05:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The thought that I might be 1 bad episode away from being thrown in hospital or dying is pretty scary. But also I think about how far I've come and I'm still kicking so part of me wants to believe I'm too stubborn for that to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 14:50:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cut or tear paper into small pieces, go for a run, write down how I'm feeling. Or I lash-out and ruin a relationship, it's a tricky slope but I'm trying to be better. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 11:25:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think there are so many, but one that's been haunting me lately is the question "who is the authentic me?"  Is mania the real me, is depression the real me, when I'm baseline is that the real me even though I spend the least amount of time there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 18:43:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - I love this so much. xo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 22:44:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> PS: This is a long answer and I've now levelled up to 5am so bear with me xD

You raise some really good points in a very respective way! I think in a world where gender norms didn't exist, then yeah, terms like gay or straight might not be so useful as current genders exist with the reference being the gender norm. So in that world, essentially gender wouldn't exist either as it functions for the purpose of multiple sexualities.

However given that we don't live in that society, I think there are a few issues with this ideology. Whilst sometimes labels can seem complicated and overabundant, labels inevitably help a lot of people with accessibility. A quick example is the LGBTQ+ 'genre' on netflix, it's not to segregate queer film, it's to make it easier to access especially for queer people who want to consume something that is reflective of themselves and not have to seed through the millions of films that don't concern them.

On this as well, dating as a queer person is already hard enough WITH labels. The current possibility of asking "hey are you gay?" etc answers and implies soo much helpful information. I couldn't imagine how difficult it would be as a traditionally straight or traditionally gay person to date in a world where the only sexuality is pansexuality with varying personal biases. For example rather than asking someone their sexuality, you might have to ask things like "hey, are you sexually attracted to masculinity, and on top of that the male genitalia, also what pronouns do you use, and are you attracted to dating someone with the same pronouns" and once you've got that out the way, then you'd have to figure out if they're a top, bottom, or verse. And although it's more inclusive and specific, currently everything besides a preferred sexual role is implied when dating as a gay person.

But also, erasing sexualities erases gender. And for some it's pretty important that their sexuality reflects their gender. For example, some cultures around the world don't discern the difference between gay men and transgender women, which is unfortunate as they are completely different experiences and in combining the two it erases them both. For example if I were to be in a relationship I  would feel uncomfortable if it were labeled anything besides a gay relationship, because I am a man and I am sexually attracted to other male identifying people. Or if my partner didn't recognise our relationship as a gay relationship (regardless if they were pansexual, bisexual etc), I would feel uncomfortable that my partner might be attracted to me not because of my gender which plays a large role in my life, as I will never claim to be or understand the experience of women. Given some gay people might enjoy the fantasy, I've been with guys that called me their girl, or their bitch, or compared me to the likeness of women/ their genitalia, and I feel very uncomfortable with that.

In this is also the concern that many transgender people might feel a bit forgotten. I suspect a lot of transgender people are empowered when their sexuality reveals and reflects their true gender and documents that change. There are also transgender people that have no desire for their sexuality to focus on their gender either, and that is also valid.

Another side note: trying to hit on a straight guy without realising he's not attracted to your gender can be very dangerous in todays society, so if pansexuality were the only sexuality there would have to be a new elaborate way to say "gay bar" or "gay safe space" etc. However I assume in a more progressive world where your concept might be applicable, this wouldn't be a risk.

 This isn't to say that current pansexuals are erasing genders, their very sexuality defines the inclusiveness of all genders. However people that are not sexually attracted to some genders, or wish to be attracted to regarding a specific gender, are ignored in this label.  Eg, a man who is not attracted to other genders besides male, and a binary-identifying person wanting their sexuality label to explain their gender identity.

At the end of the day, I think (helpful) labels make us diverse and I enjoy belonging to a community that can generally relate to my specific experience. I think a world without labels has no diversity and that is not a world I am very interested in being a part of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 00:01:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 20 is an age where people are usually mid way through college, partying and pretty naive. 30 is often believed to be a time of financial stability (at least compared to their 20 year old self), and they might be considering starting a family. This isn't the rule, this is just the popular opinion. But 30 and 40 appear closer than 20 and 30, so it probably wouldn't  turn as many heads as the latter.

If you turn it the other way, imagine a 10 year old dating a 20 year old. First of all it's illegal, but also there was probably a visceral reaction when you read that right?

Society has a perception about when a larger age gap is appropriate and when it seems a bit unlikely based on the preconceived ideas of what people are like at certain ages in life.

keep doing what you're doing cutie x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 22:18:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lesbians make great friends for gay guys. Sometimes it helps to have an outside opinion that is also inside the community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 22:12:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yep! and I'm probably still suppressing it. I've been through a lot of counselling and therapy and have never teared up or came close once. But when I watch animal videos it's a full on sob-fest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 21:47:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> there's so much tradition behind drag shows. For a lot of queens it was a way of exploring their gender identity in a safe space, and a lot of the queens identified as transgender (or a different term more popular at the time) at least in Australia during the 1960s. So it was quite liberating for trans women.

Another counter argument is the fact that a lot of queens aim to show the absurdity of gender constructs and deliberately aim to portray how qualities used to pressure women are nothing more than performative and irrational. In some ways it highlights the issue of toxic masculinity on feminine people, and gives space to liberate feminism.

But just as transphobia has always existed in the gay community, it has unfortunately also existed in the drag community and in some areas it has fostered a space for gay men to exclude cis and trans women, verging away from the traditional values of drag.

&#x200B;

That's just my opinion though! There's a lot of prose about drag in terms of feminism out there though, i'd highly encourage looking into it. I'm not a drag queen, or a women so I'm just speaking from a particular consumer's point of view. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 21:31:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> B </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 21:19:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ESH - I admire your lack of social anxiety and ability to tell a stranger to walk on the a different side of the footpath, but at the same time assuming others will move for you is a bit of a power move, especially if they are an elderly person or have a pram (baby stroller?). But also, the husband is on a different level of asshole with a weird macho hero affinity.

disclaimer - I'm not american so my view on appropriate social interaction is probably different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For Therapists: What Are Your Thoughts on Dating? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 21:09:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would you date someone with a diagnosed mental illness (and are proactive about it)?

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/haah8h) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 20:55:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (20m) If they're younger than me, like 1 year maximum. But ive hit it off great with people that are 20 years older than me. Anything more than 8 years older and I'd be a bit worried about society's perception. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 20:45:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're so right.

I also agree, I think conformity is a form of self harm. People are going to give you shit whether you conform or not so you may as well just do whats comfortable to you (if safe to do so).

In regards to wearing makeup, experimenting is the only way you will find whats comfortable! I wear a bb cream, and for me that makes me feel confident and not self conscious I will get clocked. There are also natural male makeup styles that are popular around the world.

People tend to be less likely to call someone out if they're confident in their expression. Wearing makeup isn't a timid act as a man, it's a bold statement upon which people can only try and feed off your insecurities, so if you're confident and you're wearing makeup, you are the most powerful person on earth. Physical harassment is different however. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 20:35:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is a doosey to read at 3am. I think at the end of the day to be a heterosexual male is to be attracted to people that identify with being a woman/ feminine identifying people.

Whereas identifying as a homosexual man, in my case, I see it as being attracted to people that identify as male or masculine identifying. For this reason I would never date a trans woman, because I am not attracted to women regardless of their genitalia. This is the same reason that I am attracted to trans men, because I am attracted to men and people that identify with being male regardless again of genitalia.

Someone who is pansexual or bisexual can see the attraction in both groups of people. Those that identify with being masculine or male, and those that identify with being feminine or female.

I think rather than thinking of everyone as potential pansexual, think of sexuality as a spectrum upon which many people exist at different points and sometimes fluctuate.

Note: Preferences play a large role in sexuality. Some people have a sexual infinity for certain genitalia. As well as varying attractions towards femininity and masculinity. For this reason just because I am attracted to men, doesn't mean I'm attracted to all men. The same is probably true for straight people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 20:16:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy Pride!

I think you're onto something when you say it's complex. Straight passing is definitely a privilege in the sense that they won't be discriminated against on face value. But at the same time the feeling of having your sexuality insulted whilst you're in the room/ in conversation is a pain that only queer people will ever understand, and to a greater extent straight passing people will experience that more often. However the safety and identity of non-passing people is jeopardised in ways not experienced by straight/cis passing people.

I'm someone who moves pretty fluidly between passing and not passing. I've been called fa\* several times by strangers in the street, threatened, tokenised by friends and my current employer, as well as avoided and ignored when I've displayed "feminine" behaviour and dressed less "masculine". At the same time when I visit my hometown I am a lot more conscious of my mannerisms and voice as to pass as straight. And during this time I have never been discriminated against, however my anxiety is ten fold compared to when I am expressing myself comfortably.

At the end of the day, as a minority group we will never experience the true privilege of those outside the LGBTQ+ community. But in a society that rewards traditional conceptions of masculinity and femininity, it pays to conform albeit uncomfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 12:16:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're not relaxed or not using lube then it hurts so bad/ is pretty much impossible. But otherwise it feels really good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 07:21:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  I guess queer baiting (playing into the concept of a gaydar) is when a straight person creates a gay character using rhetoric they think they know about us, but in a way that is "safe" and for marketing purposes. It is concerned with the acceptance of the straight approval (because on paper nothing queer happens) compared to being unapologetic and a true ally to the queer community.

Queer coding (I think?) might be when an informed straight/ gay person creates a gay character using tropes that are easily understood as gay pop culture with no attempt to explain it to a straight audience.  Here, the concern is with the queer community. Although I think it's still in the realm of queer baiting if it makes no attempt to create an openly safe space for queer audiences.

eg: 2 guys have sexual tension but it's never fully realised or explained (queer baiting). Vs. A character saying something nonchalantly like "let me just make sure there's no douches in my bathroom before you use it" (cringe, idk I'm not a script writer lol).

This is just my opinion, cool question though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 06:41:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never experienced that. But maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 20:58:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In a healthy encounter, there is a lot more conversation.  "Do you like this" "can I do this.." "how do you feel".

Some porn shows it and some doesn't, but sometimes the bottom doesn't feel like cumming once the top has. Sometimes they cum together, and othertimes you might be waiting a little while before the other one does. In porn its pretty instantaneous.

Uncontrolled farting during anal is real and pretty normal especially if the top keeps going out and in and changing positions.

Body hair exists.

Aesthetic cum shots are rare. Sometimes it goes where you want, other times it's on the walls.

Sex is sweaty! If there's no towel, there's no way I'm sleeping in that bed until the sheets are changed. There's a lot of cleaning up afterwards, you don't just roll over in a pile of sweat and sticky cum all naked and cold then go to sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 20:53:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> aw this was lovely. thank you babe. I hope you can listen to your own words as well.

Take care, your mentally unstable writing this at 3am had 2 mental breakdowns today but will go to sleep soon I promise, queer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 20:47:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> &#x200B;

* Do bottoms find it hard to walk after some intense sex?

No, but your booty hole burns a little. You won't be wobbling or limping and shit tho.

* Does the bottom experience hip pain after?

No.

* Do people really do it in multiple rounds? I read a manhwa where they had sex from afternoon to evening and then the bottom was sick for like 10 days. Does that actually happen?

I mean naturally there is going to be breaks. The most energetic experience i've had was 3 times in 1 night (10pm, 3am, 8am)

* Does the top usually finger the bottom before they have sex?

For me, yeah. But as long as you're relaxed and you know you're not too tight then it's not necessary.

* Do you tell the bottom if you're going to put it in?

Yeah. Otherwise it's rape.

* Is leaving hickeys all over the body a thing gay people do? I swear some characters look like a dalmatian after they do it lol

Some people do it. I enjoy it but I tend to do it in discrete places.

* Kissing your partner in the neck, ear face, everywhere else?

Depends. The ear and face thing is a bit much for me. I feel like I'm drowning.

* Does the bottom get tighter when he gets turned on so much? Say like the top something said very hot

No, if anything the opposite happens. I love that idea tho haha. It usually tightens during orgasm though.

* Does sex usually follow after resolving an argument?

If it's a serious argument I ain't sleeping in the same bed. But being affectionate to make up for something is pretty common.

* Do you guys talk while having sex?

During it, it's a bit of a turn off if we start talking about groceries, but dirty talk is common for me and talking about boundaries/ consent as well.

* In general, is anal sex more taxing for the bottom? In most mangas/manhwas I've read, the bottom usually lies dumbfounded in bed after sex while the top acts like nothing happened.

I guess it depends on the position and relationship. I'm a bit biased but I think the bottom does a lot of the work (including preparation and facilitation). Maybe because all my partners have been tall, but laying on my back on a bed is the most uncomfortable position for me when receiving anal. The penis to butt angle is so random, I feel like a jigsaw piece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 20:18:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> respect the drip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 20:17:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> an ugly, lonely and starved for affection kinda person </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 20:15:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nah, we just have to suppress talking about sex until we come out. a lot of us experience the straight girl sexual talk phase experienced in high school, in our 20s+. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 20:13:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. Unfortunately when safety isn't a guarantee for LGBTQ+ people, coming out of the closet is like leaving the house to get groceries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 20:05:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If a straight boy is really getting offended someone said gaydar isn't real, isn't it safe to assume he's a right-wing conservative homophobe with a 2 inch dick? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 20:01:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> okay, I might get some hate for giving away our secret gay agenda but I think you're worthy to know. you wont know if someone is gay unless they tell you. there, I said it. the gay agenda is now out.

a gaydar is just straight girls getting excited they'll finally have a gbf, and gay people fantasising someone will have sex with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 19:55:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is no such thing as acting gay. Gay isn't a behaviour. Its a sexuality. If spongebob was having sex with squidward then yeah i'd say "no one who isnt gay acts like that if they aren't gay". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 19:50:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because assuming someone is gay from his actions and mannerisms isn't fair and is a rude generalisation. Also doesn't matter if I said I don't think squidward and spongebob should be friends because they're not the same race. That's still a racist thought whether or not it refers to fictional characters.

Gay people are as diverse as straight people. But the media usually only portrays stereotypes of the former.

edit: I know sponges and squids aren't races but its a metaphor innit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 19:48:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because assuming someone is gay from his actions and mannerisms isn't fair and is a rude generalisation. Also doesn't matter if I said I don't think squidward and spongebob should be friends because they're not the same race. That's still a racist thought whether or not it refers to fictional characters.

Gay people are as diverse as straight people. But the media usually only portrays stereotypes of the former.

edit: I know sponges and squids aren't races but its a metaphor innit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 19:47:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you missed the point baby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 19:42:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because assuming someone is gay from his actions and mannerisms isn't fair and is a rude generalisation. Also doesn't matter if I said I don't think squidward and spongebob should be friends because they're not the same race. That's still a racist thought whether or not it refers to fictional characters.

&#x200B;

Gay people are as diverse as straight people. But the media usually only portrays stereotypes of the former.

edit: I know sponges and squids aren't races but its a metaphor innit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 19:32:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TLDR (because its 2am and I'm manic):

Go into it like it's a debate, have receipts and a structure to the conversation. Listen to her as well and she'll listen to you. Conversations like these aren't going to be revolutionary, they will usually have little impact on both parties, but they are important.

\--

&#x200B;

I'm not American so I can't offer the best specific advice. But I can share some things that have helped me (gay m) with my conservative mother.

The first thing is to treat it like you going into a debate. First, set some ground rules. I say things like "It would mean a lot to me if we could have a conversation about \_ and listen to each other respectfully." Make sure you allow for everyone to speak, even if they are saying things that are false or are hurtful. It's so easy to interrupt someone who we don't agree with, or walk out when someone says something you disagree with so intensely. If someone hears you out, you're probably going to hear you out as well. As soon as someone starts getting angry, then it's no loner a constructive conversation and the entire conversation past and following is pretty well disregarded entirely.

&#x200B;

Get into the mindset of a conservative person, google things you can imagine coming out of their mouth so you can better understand what is a popular opinion amongst that demographic so you can form some counter arguments. I had a conversation with my mum last night, she bought up that more white people die in custody compared to indigenous australians, and because I knew that was a trending conversation amongst conservative news, I could talk about the exact numbers and disproportionate percentages, to let her know why that doesn't actually mean anything.  And when she understood. She also mentioned things I was unaware of, so I acknowledged I didn't know about that and that I agree why she find it frustrating, but I'll need to look into it before I form my opinion. She agreed to sit down with my later to talk about it.

&#x200B;

It's easy to get defensive, but think about some things you want to talk about and make notes like you're going into a debate so that you can stay focussed and structures so that the conversation is constructive and not just 2 people talking about their feelings, because trying to change someones feelings is almost impossible within a single conversation so we need to give them some points to take with them and think about.

&#x200B;

Finally, and it's probably the hardest thing to do. Be vulnerable. At the end of the day this is your mother, and she cares about you (or not, but there is a relationship there regardless). It's difficult to rebut someones experience and personal story without appearing like an asshole (mot of the time) and for that reason it's so effective in a debate with someone who knows you. Talk about your experience and how conservative ideals have and will impact your existence. I've spoken to my family about how I have been threatened and feared for my life because of my sexuality and encounters I've had from people using conservative notions to discriminate against me. Lean into that, and share that raw moment with someone so that when they vote they have that story in the back of their head knowing that they are choosing to support or not support that. Alternatively, use someone else's story to reiterate why you have the political stance you have. I spoke to my mum about a girl my age who died because police dealt with her restrictively and violently in when she was having a panic attack and she was just as emotional as I was in that moment.

&#x200B;

At the end of the day, we need to get rid of the romantic idea that we are going to have a life altering conversation with someone who doesn't share the same opinions as we do. The best case scenario for these situations is that no one gets angry and both sides feel understood and take something away with them. The way we view our political opinions are the same way that conservatives view their political opinions. We might be wrong sometimes, and we also need to recognise that other wise we aren't wanting to have a conversation, we're trying to have an argument or at best a lecture.

&#x200B;

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 18:58:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the reply.

I don't have good sources on my mind for dealing with homophobic thoughts for a straight person, but try googling things like "I used to be homophobic" "how I learnt to accept the lgbtq+ community" "gay men make me uncomfortable" "what it's like to be gay/ lgbtq+" "issue faced by the lgbtq+ community". You're so right, some people do unfortunately use their religion to discriminate, there are also quite a few countries where homosexuality is illegal, and punishable by death and in other countries including the USA, Australia and England, there are state or national laws that allow for people to discriminate towards lgbtq+ people. Homophobia is everywhere, the first step to changing that is finding how closely it is in relation to your own life.

Analysing your own mind is also a good place to start, who were you surrounded by when you were growing up/ now and did they contribute to your thoughts on gay people, asking yourself questions like that is important.

I can't answer why you find men kissing uncomfortable and not men holding hands, but there are lots of subtle ways homophobia can manifest and it's so sad because no one want's to feel uncomfortable for something they cant control! I am a gay man and the idea of straight sex doesn't make me uncomfortable or envious, I can appreciate the vagina but I don't see it as a sexual thing. To me it's just a body part (that happens to be incredible and complex).

I don't blame you for being uncomfortable with gay sex, it's not in mainstream media and we didn't grow up knowing about it or seeing it portrayed in media the same way straight sex is, and when gay sex is discussed or portrayed it is it's usually grossly vulgar and unrealistic. Sex is beautiful, regardless of who is involved. Sex can also not be beautiful, but that is also regardless of who is involved.

At the end of the day you are uncomfortable with aspects of the gay identity, and that's not a nice feeling for you or for gay people. But as long as you're not spreading hate, and trying to better yourself then that's a good place to start. Just be aware of your reactions to gay people and I think you will be an excellent ally to the lgbtq+ community and I welcome you and thank you.

This isn't an issue that can be fixed over night, or even within a few weeks or months. This is a process of unlearning so much that we have learnt for many many yeas, and that has been instilled in society for hundreds of years before that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 18:32:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im lonely for dick, but I've been chilling with fabulous self. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 18:31:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - It ain't his house, ain't his mailbox, ain't your mother's business to deal with his shit. He's a grown ass man, if he isn't responsible enough to ask politely for your mother to store any incoming mail so he can collect it (promptly), or change his address then he needs sort some shit out. Family drama's fun ain't it. xoxo a bitch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 18:25:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess I'm pretty cynical but I'd stop talking to them. They sound like a catfish, but even if they weren't they don't sound comfortable with you or themself and that's not a sign of a healthy friendship or relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 18:22:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> exciting! Good luck king. shoot your shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 18:19:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - thank you for doing so  <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 18:18:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely suspicious. It's a good rule of thumb not to get too attached until you know that the person you're talking to is real. Have you tried asking to follow her on her social media? What's her response to that? The longer this lasts the worse it gets. Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 18:08:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a few things to unpack here, thank you for asking for advice!

Homophobia is a blanket term for the unreasoning fear of or antipathy toward homosexuals and homosexuality. If you saw two men kissing, or two men holding hands how would that make you feel? How do you feel about feminine gay men?

I'm sure you didn't mean it but "freedom of choice" isn't relevant to sexuality since sexuality isn't a choice :) I don't think anyone would choose to be discriminated against.

When you call an aspect of someones life "gross" or "disgusting" then that's a bit rude in my opinion. At the same time thinking of lesbians as "hot" or purely sexual is another form of small minded thinking. It's the idea that lesbians aren't real, but are to serve male sexual desire.

Whether your intent isn't to discriminate or be hateful towards LGBTQ+ people, you can still be homophobic because it's a learnt behaviour and mentality. Just like men are raised largely to be misogynistic, and white people are raised to be racist whether directly or passively. It isn't your fault, but it is your fault if you recognise homophobic attitudes and do nothing to change them. Proper education is the best medicine for this! Listen to LGBTQ+ people's stories with coming out, their struggles with their identity. Read into some of the laws that encourage discrimination towards LGBTQ+ people. Read into how we are treated globally not just locally.

You will be uncomfortable when trying to make change to your thinking, but eventually you wont  be uncomfortable and thats when you know you aren't homophobic.

&#x200B;

Good luck! Thanks for reaching out, it means a lot :) If you have any further questions feel free to ask away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 15:34:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> puberty is a weird time yo. it does all kinds of funky stuff to your sexuality but itll make sense in time. Im hella gay but during high school I wasnt so sure. dont stress, just experiment if its safe and do whatever makes you feel good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 15:13:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel the exact same way. My experience was 6 years ago and to this day it still effects me. For me I've accepted that they had things going on in their life that they felt they couldn't be themselves and they will live with this guilt for a very long time, so I am sad for them not angry anymore. In someways I do feel like I was stripped of a lot of things, considering I was catfished by an older person when I was 14 and I feel like I was boosted into a maturity that I wasn't ready for. But I see it as a lesson and I see ways in which my life has been benefitted from the lessons I learnt.

When a catfish uses you for your body and emotional gain, in many ways they take so much of your worth and belittle it to a screen and sweet meaningless words. I've learnt to never  accept someone's words as having any power over my life, instead actions will always be so much more valued to me and I think this had helped me avoid a lot of potential bad situations and relationships so far.

It's hard not to feel embarrassed, but just know that your catfish has made you feel that way. It's their attempt to make you feel like you were to blame. "how could I have been so stupid", is probably a mantra people that were catfished recite every day, but I think it's important to recognise that you were not stupid, your catfish was clever and fooled you. If a magician fools a volunteer we don't think of the volunteer as stupid. Feel empowered  that you were the volunteer that eventually found out and understood what was going on. Not a lot of people can do that, so it's pretty remarkable.

This was a traumatic experience, whether it feels like it or not and whatever feelings you hold are valid and real. You deserve so much better, and I think you know that as well which is amazing hindsight that not everyone gets.

keep going, you are not alone and there was nothing you could have done with the resources you had at the time that would have prevented this from happening. <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 20:40:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That must be really difficult for you. I know that you don't want to tell anyone, but I would really encourage seeking out a student counsellor  if there is one available. They are bound to confidentiality in the countries I am aware of, so what you say to them stays between you and them unless it's a crisis situation, then they will ask permission to seek help from other sources. Some towns or local areas also have designated counsellors.  In the meantime here are a few useful and anonymous resources.

Beyond Blue [https://www.beyondblue.org.au/](https://www.beyondblue.org.au/) has a help call and message service as well as a bunch of great resources. They are an australian organisation so be mindful of the available service hours.

Lifeline is another great service that offers crisis support [https://www.lifeline.org.au/](https://www.lifeline.org.au/) . It can be scary to call these services or message their team, the first time is always the scariest but trust me they really can help!

Kids helpline [https://kidshelpline.com.au/](https://kidshelpline.com.au/) also offers a variety of support and resources especially for teenagers.

&#x200B;

Whatever is going on can be scary and you can feel so alone, but just know that your experience and emotions are valid and you are not alone. I know what it's like to be scared your parents might disown you, but your life is more important than the approval of society or those close to you. Things will get better, not right away, and maybe not for a little while. But eventually, and slowly, things will be okay. And I know how frustrating that is to hear and you don't have to believe me. But you will find people that understand you and will be able to help you, you just have to reach out.

&#x200B;

Good luck, I believe in you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 11:03:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do this often as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 10:55:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow that was a really powerful comment. Thank you so much. I still feel like I could be making this all up. But I guess we'll see what the doctor says on Monday. Whatever he tells me, this advice is really helpful :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Scared of Potential Diagnosis </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 10:38:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Update: I was diagnosed with bipolar II by my psychiatrist.

Hello, I hope this is okay to post.

I've been suffering turbulent mental health issues since I was a child (20 now). After a depressed episode I tell myself I'll get help, then it passes and I can't even imagine being sad I am so pleased and happy with life, so I don't get help. This cycle has been happening for the past 6 years. But yesterday I finally saw a doctor about it, but with a cover story that I was concerned with my thyroid. I've seen a therapist before but I also had a cover story that I wanted to learn how to better help a friend, and I have never had a session when I was depressed.

After the doctor saw through my thyroid issue, he began running physical and mental health tests on me and I am definitely uncomfortable with the amount of information I shared. I feel like I was faking it, like this is all in my figurative head and that I'm a phoney. (this is typical when I get out of my depression and into these weird states). One thing has been playing on my mind a lot, he seemed really concerned with the information I was telling him, and I saw him write down manic depression in his notes. He then asked to see me for a long appointment after the weekend as we wait for the blood test results, although he told me a few times he didn't think this was a thyroid issue (I was pretty persistent).

I am really scared that I might get diagnosed with bipolar, not because of the disorder but because I've been running from this for so long and I don't think I'm ready for this to be real, and that I won't just grow out of this. I'm unsure if I'll go to the next appointment, and I've been considering telling him that I've been making things over dramatic and that I'm actually fine.

I'm not sure why I'm posting this, but I think it might be a way to keep myself accountable.

Thank you for letting me get this off my chest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-17 11:00:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you with all my heart. these comments mean a lot to me :) I wish you all the happiness too <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-17 10:58:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand. Maybe tell her something like you're not ready for a relationship, you need to work on personal stuff, and that it would be best for both of you to stop talking. Seems like you're trying hard not to come across as an asshole but you can't avoid that. I'm sorry you're going through personal things, I hope you find clarity and peace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-17 10:48:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for realising your mistake. Unfortunately, as soon as you catifsh someone the damage has been done and they are going to be hurt regardless. I would tell them that something has come up in your life and you can't be in a relationship anymore. If you truly want a clean conscious then admit you are a catfish and are deeply embarrassed, sorry and that you have no intention in staying in contact with her. I hope she will be okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 22:30:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. This was very reassuring. Take care of yourself too :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 20:52:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you from the bottom of my heart. I was half expecting these comments to be judgemental and calling me stupid. *hug* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 20:36:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand where you're coming from and it must be super interesting to experiment with another persons profile. But I think this might do more harm than good especially for your mental health. Also I can imagine the girls profile you are using probably would feel a bit violated knowing she's on a dating site without her consent even if you aren't engaging with the matches (which I really hope you're not). Hang in there girl, you'll get the love of your life someday and it'll be real not superficial like a lot of the matches this girls profile is getting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 20:31:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw thank you so much. This means a lot. I have suppressed this for a long time, so it's so healing to have someone acknowledge my experience. I can say that I am truly happen with the person I am today and no longer seek worth from other people or form relationships with people online. Good luck to you too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 20:24:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope you have come clean and she is doing okay now. It takes courage to confess so thank you for doing so. There's no need to hide who you are, there are people that will love you for you and it will be a lot more sustainable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 20:22:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think there's a way for you to come clean and maintain the relationship. But I also think that you are doing something very wrong by catfishing him. I would come clean and then delete the account. I don't think there's any redemption from catfishing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My Catfish Contacted Me After 6 Years </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 20:13:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never told anyone this, but I think it's time to share my story and  how my catfish contacted me afterwards. I'm still embarrassed this happened and that it still effects me, so this is me trying to let go for good.

(Disclaimer; Mentions of the word 'suicide attempt', some of this information might be slightly inaccurate)

When I was 14-15 (I am now 20) I had a psychotic break. I was going through a lot and needless to say I wasn't thinking straight. One day a person slid into my DMs on instagram and we started talking. He made me feel worthy and attractive, on top of this his instagram photos and profile picture was gorgeous. He was very fit, had blonde hair and blue eyes. We would message each other constantly throughout the day. He was from the other side of the world so I would often sleep only a few hours or not at all just so I could talk to him longer. He was a year older than me and made me feel invincible. But things started to get weird and it's only in hindsight that I noticed how bizarre things were since I was very out of it.

After a few weeks of messaging he asked me if he could be my boyfriend and I accepted. We started calling on the phone, I loved hearing his voice and wanted to facetime him so badly but his phone camera didn't work... Besides, I would sometimes get glimpses of him on his cousin's snapchat however his face was always drawn over due to his insecurities.  It was also around this time that he told me about his son who was 2 years old to his ex who was significantly older. I slowly became invested in this child's life at 15 and I thought I was ready to become a step parent. (I'm cringing as much as you all probably are) It got to the point where I began applying for work in hopes that I could send him money to care for his child until I saved enough to move to his country. I had no intention of telling my family about this.

We would bond on our struggles with mental health, and would talk in depth about our suicide attempts. One day he stopped responding after sending some alarming messages. I didn't hear from him, his friend (15M) or his cousin (16F) who I had also been introduced to by him. Until eventually his cousin told me he was in hospital. A few weeks later I got a reply and he was ok. I was so happy, unfortunately he would repeat this a few times later.

It was also after his reappearance that his ex started messaging me about what a terrible person he was and that he would never be as into me as he was to her. I ignored this and blocked her.

Thankfully I don't recall ever sending him naked pictures of myself, but I remember him offering to send pictures to me (I never accepted them) however we would sometimes talk sexually. (I know what you're thinking, how could he send nudes if he couldn't send a face pic. DW I get less naive). From here on things slowly began falling apart and I would occasionally get doubtful but the thought of questioning him and losing him was too scary.

One day he sent a photo to me. Only something seemed different than the previous photos he sent me. Then it clicked. He had a different hair colour and a nose ring. I asked him about this, and he said his brother dyed his hair in his sleep and he doesn't wear his nose ring often, and I thought fair enough. (jesus christ..). In retrospect he changed his catfish appearance and began using someone else's photos but unfortunately my brain was too unstable to recognise my boyfriend now being a different person. I don't know if it was a combination of my psychotic episode and me starving myself for days, or the lies he told me but things like this seemed completely normal to me.

The curtain began to slowly crumble in the following month. I noticed that someone followed me on instagram, the handle was something along the lines of  '(unrecognised name) fanclub' with my boyfriend as the profile picture and no other content. I was confused so I messaged him about it. He told me to ignore it and that it was just his ex trying to get to me. So I ignored it and things were fine, only I began to get suspicious. I remember drawing a table called "reasons my boyfriend is real and reasons he is actually his cousin (16F)". (Yay me!) Now I don't know why I thought he might be his cousin, I have a lot of blank pieces of memory from this period but I remember little bits and after the years I've slowly began putting pieces back together. I tore this piece of paper up (dang it), threw it away and tried not to think about it, because the thought of losing him broke my heart more than if he weren't actually real. I had already dealt with losing him to suspected suicide attempts, gone through the pain of a long distance relationship, invested myself in his child and he had saved me from my own suicide attempts.

But I couldn't stop thinking about it, and later his ex messaged me again telling me to look up an instagram handle. So I did.... And it was pictures of my boyfriend, only he had a different name and was actually in university. It then dawned on me. My entire world collapsed. I had been catfished for the past 6 months. My entire world, the person I messaged up to 22 hours a day wasn't real. The person I was preparing to move across the world and begin a family with at age 15 wasn't real. I confronted him and he admitted it wasn't him. He then sent me a picture of his real face and name. He wasn't unattractive but my heart was broken and I was finally mentally coherent enough to understand what was going on. Or so I thought (this was also a fake profile)... I blocked him and everyone else he introduced me to. I don't remember much of what came next, but I remember taking a long bath and laughing hysterically proving I probably wasn't as mentally coherent as I thought (oops).

Queue me having what I think is another psychotic episode and not remembering the next 6 months but some where along the lines I began eating again and going to sleep more regularly (things seemed to turn out alright for me!). I did well in school and got into my top university, started therapy and am now in my 3rd year of university.

The story is almost over I promise!

So a few months ago someone messaged me on instagram. My stomach sunk once I saw the profile and it looked just like my catfish's cousin who was the same age as him and female. They then messaged me and confessed that they were my catfish however now identify was a transgender male. It all made sense and I wish I could go back in time and tell 15 year old me that I was right. I thanked my catfish for contacting me to apologise and said I needed time to process and ask questions. Turns out they were the age they said they were, they were going through mental health issues and were using other peoples photos to catfish me, and during our phone calls they had their male friend on the phone and was telling him what to say to me. I told that person i love them, and they told me they loved me and i think that's what I'm mostly uncomfortable with to this day. My catfish was also apparently unaware of how sick I was which I'm not sure if I believe. But I am not angry anymore, I am more sad for who we both were back then. I blocked him after getting my answers however I still don't know what the deal with the baby was, who the friend he introduced me to was, or anything about the ex that was trying so hard to tell me he was a catfish, and I'm okay with not knowing.

I know I will never be able to forget that period of my life, but I think I'm ready to move on and to forgive not only my catfish but also myself who I have blamed for this for so long. It's been my dirty secret for 6 years but I think I'm ready for this to end. Thank you, genuinely, if you read this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 05:11:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - Sounds like you're surrounded by a bunch of Karens. I think your neighbour was expecting a bigger confrontation so when you were a normal human being and not this trash hoarding monster with no self awareness they were all ramped up on angry adrenaline that instead of understanding the situation they kept going so they didn't feel like an idiot for being so confrontational. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 05:05:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ESH - I totally get where you're coming from and I think any mature person should be able to respect boundaries when it comes to someone's possessions. I don't think that giving a bottle to a potential buyers kid is something that I personally would get very upset over given the fact that it may help the house sell, it is annoying though since you weren't asked. Talking to your mother about how these belong to you and are important for you is completely just and I'm sorry your mother reacted that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 04:59:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - I'm sorry you have to go through this. You sound like an amazing and strong person. Unfortunately we can't always make those close to us happy, just as they cannot always make us happy. Be kind to yourself, I think your efforts on mothers day were really thoughtful and kind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 04:54:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - If this is real, I am so sorry and you do not deserve this. I would speak to a student councillor if you can, they might offer facetime sessions as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 21:14:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a really tricky time and it's going be pretty difficult to deal with sometimes, but it will pass and I think time does a lot of good to people in these situations. I had a similar experience with my mum, but 3 years later and we're best buds again even if she might still hold some misinformed opinions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 21:11:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - Think about your future self and what you want them to feel when they look back on your graduation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 21:01:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA -  I'm sorry you had to go through that, but you should know that coming out is incredibly personal and you do not owe it to anyone to have to hide who you are because
someone else isn't ready. (you should not come out if you are fearful of your safety however) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 20:34:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Internalised homophobia is tough and I think you're on the right track in wanting to mentally prepare yourself for gay sex, but also recognising that it exists is huge. For me coming out was obviously no. 1 in helping me feel 100% comfortable with my sexuality. But besides that,  educating myself on lgbtq history and media, listening to others stories, and making friends with openly and empowered lgbtq people has also helped tremendously. But I identify as gay, I don't know if this is helpful for a heteroromantic person. good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 18:30:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA - But I feel like you already knew this.

Edit: Try to imagine yourself in their shoes. Sure they might be gullible but you never know how much this might impact them. Playing with emotions and manipulating people under the false idea that you are somehow making them better people is actually quite frightening </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 18:17:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 18:08:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll study tomorrow mum! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 18:03:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live away for college and because of miss rona I can't travel back home. So I sent her a text telling her how strong and amazing she is so she would wake up to it (I sent it at 5am pretending I'd just woken to go to the toilet, not that I'd been on tiktok for 5 hours straight.) Then I facetimed her and we just had bants for an hour. She knows I'm a broke uni student who isn't independent enough to send her anything by post that would arrive on time, but I hope she felt appreciated. My brother took her out for dinner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 17:59:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - but doing this will start an even bigger drama when I can imagine all you want is to recover peacefully. If she is the kind of person to regularly make you feel bad when you are in a vulnerable position then I think a bit of pettiness might not hurt. If this seems out of character for her, then maybe she's going through shit and you might just be acting out of frustration because you have been through something intense so you're probably not thinking 100% clearly which is absolutely normal. Your brain and your body need time to heal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 22:27:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> F. yeah this sucks, my mum is the same sometimes. I came out to her she was a mess, now we're fine again but she still thinks I'll eventually marry a women and whenever I tell her that won't happen she denies it.

I dunno man, I would do this like a week before heading back to uni, not in the middle of quarantine. This seems like the absolute worst time to bring up any drama with the family. But at the end of the day you are your own person and you shouldn't let people corner you if you've established that you're in a safe environment since they 'accepted' your sexuality initially.  Maybe just bring it up in subtle ways, like mention how attractive a certain guy is on TV or flaunt your femininity a little (being feminine is a gay stereotype but sometimes it helps to play into those stereotypes when wanting to come out to people without directly doing it).

I've kind of learnt to have fun with it and sort of force my mum to deal with my gayness. When I give her fashion advice I say things like "what kind of gay son would I be if I didn't give you fashion advice" which is super obnoxious and I'd hate to witness that which is kind of the point. This is all in good fun though, my mum and I are super close and we love each other so much but she's from a miseducated generation and sometimes forgets that sexuality isn't a choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 22:08:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're probably right haha. I've noticed that I have a mix of straight friends that either do not want kids, and those that do eventually, whereas I'm the only gay person I know interested in having children down the line.

Edit: I don't have straight male friends, sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 21:57:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never had a one night stand from grinder because I'm scared of this or worse things happening. But I have gone on a date with someone from grindr and the next day had sex with them after I felt I could trust them. This isn't the quick fix you're after though, sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 21:53:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I bought a hair trimmer and I use that. My parents just thought mine was for side burns but I used it without the guard for trimming the hair down there. It won't be as smooth as a razor, but you won't be able to see or feel the hair for the first 2ish days but  I rarely get razor bumps from it compared to a razor. It doesn't irritate my skin either and it has never given me ingrown hairs unlike when I used to use a razor. Also it doesn't give me itchiness. 100% recommend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 21:45:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi, thank you for posting! This is such a difficult time and being in a non-supportive environment makes things a lot more challenging. I grew up surrounded by homophobic people and the best advice I can give is to focus on school and friendships with supportive people. It can feel like this will never end but I promise one day it will get better and you will be able to live authentically and happily.
I would love if you could come out and everything would be fine, but the reality is your safety should always come first. Look at your local community and see if there are any lgbt support groups that will give you space to be yourself whilst in company with supportive people.

I would avoid the temptation to go onto gay websites or gay chat rooms as these will be very sexual and dangerous for young people, this is speaking from experience.

There will come a day when you can be free and safe, but until then work on yourself and let this be the fire beneath you to do amazing things so you can get away from your homophobic environment. Good luck darling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 21:36:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I totally agree with you! The people that are around me just happen to fall into that category of not wanting children and are also not fans of children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 21:25:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - Thank you for not dismissing his behaviour and for not being compliant to those around you. The teacher must feel absolutely horrified and I would be surprised if your sons comment didn't impact her mental health. These comments are what minority teachers fear and sadly have to face everyday in subtle and direct ways. Here is a website that lists some great African American specific charities [https://www.huffingtonpost.com.au/entry/28-organizations-that-are-empowering-black-communities\_n\_58a730fde4b045cd34c13d9a?ri18n=true](https://www.huffingtonpost.com.au/entry/28-organizations-that-are-empowering-black-communities_n_58a730fde4b045cd34c13d9a?ri18n=true) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 14:11:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> aw this was really wholesome and cute. thanks for sharing :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 14:06:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm cis and I'm not a fan of my name. It's a nice name but I just don't feel connected to it at all and I've always felt uncomfortable telling people my name or when people refer to me by my name. But I don't feel gender dysphoria around it (it is a gender non specific name though) and I don't feel that changing it will improve my quality of life. Because I've only ever heard 'deadname' as a term used by trans people, if I changed my name I wouldn't refer to it as a deadname since I don't identify as trans. Even if the meaning is 'previous name' I think we need to take into account the cultural meanings and implications as well. I think it might be similar to other LGBTQ+ terminology like 'queer' or even 'gay', when in the past these were adjectives, now they are identities of LGBTQ+ people and so I can't imagine a straight person using those words as adjectives in everyday conversation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-07 19:52:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA - Thanks for being chill with her being bi though, that's NTA material. She's probably still figuring out her sexuality and although she's accepted the fact that she's attracted to women, she's probably not ready to take the next step with women - it's a process and it takes a time. She might not be super comfortable with her sexuality or she might be a bit embarrassed because she's suppressed it and demonised it in her head. its a process my dude, it helps to have friends that are supportive but being pushy aint it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 22:29:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Been talking to this guy for a while and I'm really into him. It's a 13 year age gap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 22:02:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Might be different because I'm an RA in an Australian College. I've been an RA for 2 years now and this is my general vibe.

The interviewers are interested in your ability to connect with a wide variety of people and also your ability to work as a part of a team. Things that might help include academic success but also times you struggled with class and how you overcame those challenges. They're looking for someone who is caring, obviously, and who can fill a role no one else can - for example introverted people can connect with residents that might be more shy - people from locations far away from the college can connect with people of the same experience - people of a minority group who can act as a relatable and safe person to talk to - extroverts who can bring people out of their shells. Really look into who you are and how you can use that as a strength when creating connections with people, don't try to fit a mould of what you think an RA should be. Another important one from my interviews was not caring about where you would be placed and the room you got because it shows you're an RA because of the job not the room. Also like others have said, being an RA isn't about the money (although it's nice). Finally something that was stressed in all of my interviews was how comfortable you would be to address an issue you had with a choice made by administration. Good luck! In my experience being an RA has been one of the most intense things but also the most rewarding things I've ever done. I love my job and my residents :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 21:50:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My college has 300 students. (Keep in mind colleges in Australia are for residential purposes only and it's not particularly common to stay at a college opposed to renting an apartment or staying at home). So last year I only had 15 residents, and this year I have 21. I've found its worked really well in building genuine connections with my residents. I remember last year at the end of the year some of my residents and I were crying because we wouldn't be in the same building next year. It also means that my residents and I can regularly message each other on facebook to keep in contact and I still have a close connection with my residents from previous years. Maybe it's just me but I end up feeling so emotionally connected with my residents that I've cried when talking about how proud I am of them in the past. Maybe I'm just a mess haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 21:43:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Taking on other people's emotional distress and responding to emergencies can be super emotionally and physically draining! Professional psychologists also talk to other psychologists and colleagues regularly because of this. If you can try to see a councillor at your university, or talk to another RA. You can keep confidentiality of your residents whilst talking about particularly draining scenarios. I did this in my first year of being an RA and it helped a lot to get alternative advice but also to get some pretty heavy stuff off my chest. There is also a suicide call back service in Australia that I've used in the past to debrief with someone after someone has come to me with suicidal behaviours or thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 05:13:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow, you actually look really good today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 04:57:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the bigger the guy the more facial hair I like. But I like stubble on anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 04:53:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There have been so many I've lost track. But recently my friend introduced me to her boyfriend whilst i was practicing, he approached me kind of awkwardly as I was putting my guitar down so I stood up and went for a hand shake because I thought that's what straight guys do (I'm gay)... he was going in for a hug but changed his mind half way through so we kind of held hands whilst hugging with the guitar in between us... After that encounter the three of us stood silently and he sat down and asked if I was going to play something to serenade them.I don't know if it's because I'm an introvert but for some reason weird social interactions like this happen to me often.

Yesterday I was walking to the dining hall at college and I bumped into this guy I've been kinda avoiding, we talked then I tried going to the bathroom because I need to but also so we wouldn't sit together, he followed me in. Then whilst eating he accidentally spills food on me, I pour him a cup of water and I spill the water on myself and the floor.

There are so many more but I think the moral of this story is that I don't avoid social interactions on purpose but otherwise shit like this happens to me daily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-05 19:48:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no one ever has any obligation to change their bodies for other people. But if he's implying that it's weak to shave, then he might just be scared to come across as 'feminine' for fucked up reasons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-05 19:43:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im a gay man. Just sounds like you like romance that isn't based off power play and outdated gender roles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-05 19:37:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It sounds like you're struggling right now, but it will be okay eventually :) . It might not seem like it right now but there is nothing wrong with being gay if you think you might be. A lot of us have struggled with what you are going through and have turned out happier than you could imagine. Just hold on and try not to worry about what those around you might be saying or what pressures you feel under, you're in a part of your life that you're discovering core parts of your identity and it's normal to feel confused.

We can't change who we are and we sexuality isn't a choice as unfortunate as that may seem right now. I was also more feminine than other boys in high school and I only had friends that were girls, and I was super self conscious of that. But eventually you'll learn that what makes you different is a strength. I'm in my 3rd year of university and it's only been in the past 2 years that i've made friends with straight guys and learnt to explore my femininity and masculinity unafraid and unapologetically. It'll be okay, whatever your sexuality is :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-05 19:21:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Disclaimer - these are gay male specific.

There are a lot of great short movies out there as well. From memory I recently rewatched "are we okay" but there's so many on youtube to binge you might have to weed through some cringe ones though but once you get deep into it theres soo many high quality ones. They are a lot more thought provoking and emotionally intense than quite a few queer movies i've watched. Although a lot of them are quite sad there are a few that have happy endings, unlike queer films that seem to only be sad besides love simon. But to this day my favourite queer media is actually a series called "Please Like Me" it's also pretty sad but it's nothing has ever moved me or felt more authentic than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-05 19:13:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Loved it my first time and thereafter. I can't imagine having sex without giving head first or after. I think I need to be comfortable before doing anal so it helps break the mood and get things relaxed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-05 18:48:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - I don't know if pansies is as derogatory for you as it is where I live but that sucks. I know the struggle of being vegetarian/ vegan in a meat eating family where people seem to take it as a personal insult. It's 1 maybe 2 meals that have no meat in them, it puzzles me how people would get upset over that unless they had allergies to a large number of vegetables. However I think that in these scenarios apologising to make your partner happy should take precedence over maintaining face and having 20 people your partner cares about not come,  especially if you're about to marry that person. When it comes to family gossip and drama I think people are going to remember the time that 20 family members actively didn't go to a wedding opposed to the time someone 'insulted' an aunt and then the wedding went ahead fine.

Good luck, maybe give her fake meat and tell her it's real to maintain pettiness and also a good relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 21:55:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi! This is going to be long. It's 3am...

I grew up with a mum that wasn't blatantly homophobic but made some comments and we had complete opposite political views. Regardless she was my best friend, we would gossip and talk to each other like it was nothing.

I came out at 18 after overhearing that she apparently voted yes in the Australian vote for marriage equality. I was expecting her to maybe already know and say she loves me and have one of those happy movie type moments. But unfortunately she was hysterical and said a lot of really messed up things to me. Following this we had a rough few weeks where she could barely make eye contact with me. She eventually saw an anglican bishop after I refused to see one and he was surprisingly accepting.

But (and I promise this gets better) she slowly came around to where she started speaking to me again and said she just need time. Flash forward and I went to college and came back after a year and she was actively trying to understand. We were back to talking like a son and mother again and she even asked if she could watch love simon with me which was a huge moment. It was a bit awkward and we didn't speak about it for months. But she has been slowly getting warmer and last year she started asking me about my dating life and the guys I was seeing. She was still persistent in the fact that she wanted me to eventually end up with a girl.

So now we're back to this year and we are talking like we used to, we text and facetime regularly. And although it's not like we're talking about it often at all, it is clear that she loves me and supports me if it means I'm happy.

\----

So here's why I think she came around.

I was a noticeably depressed teenager and after coming out and coming back from college i was completely different and happy. I think a lot of the fear that parents have is that their child will have a difficult life and won't find happiness so seeing your child flourish is a wake up call. I was thankful in that my older brother and other extended family were very defensive and in support of me when she tried to consolidate with them and talk negatively about me. In my first year I also became close friends with a proud lesbian and I think her seeing that there are others who are also thriving normalised it a bit. But primarily I think it's just time and knowledge.

My mum wasn't homophobic, she was just had false ideas of what being gay meant. Good luck :)

&#x200B;

TLDR : ye went shit but got good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 21:32:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, depending on the person and if we get along </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 16:37:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that I shit during sex and that we don't do any of the work. also people treating bottoms (esp twinks) like they don't have a fully formed personality or are only interested in fit model types </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 16:28:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, i'm sorry this has happened to you. I can't begin to know what your experience is but living your life and not giving up is a pretty incredible thing. You being open, or at least acknowledging your sexuality has pathed the way for so many around you even if you can't see it. you'll get through it <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 16:23:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally get where you're coming from. Like 90% of music I listen to is about being heart broken and it ain't fair when a relationship just ends undramatically. My inner adele needs to be heard! Sometime's shit ain't meant to be and you need to realise that there's no point trying to love someone who will never love you back because you deserve more than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 16:05:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought otters were lean and hairy whereas twinks are just skinny and typically young guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 12:24:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a lovely message. I would still be wary of mentioning him being gay at all if you have a conversation with him. He might feel 'found out' and become further withdrawn. I'm so happy to hear you've allowed him to see that you're understanding and I was super shy when I was a teen dealing with my sexuality. I think having that little chat mentioning that you are there for him might be a nice little bonding moment.

I have an older brother and before I came out I was scared to tell him. If he had  said he was there for me without referring to sexuality I think I wouldn't have felt that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 10:28:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Next time you are both awake at the same time. tell him how you are feeling and ask if he can be a bit more considerate. Open communication is the most vital thing in a healthy long lasting relationship </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 10:26:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dont know about this straight shit but it depends on what position you're in? If shes laying and you're ontop i'd probably say cowboy for your own sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 10:23:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im a twink and im into bigger guys with hair. So I guess like anything otter-bear with definition. I've dated skinny and lanky guys and it just aint the same personally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 10:20:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> have you told him that it bothers you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 10:18:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi, kinda emosh reading this - you're a great sister. I think it's important for someone to come out in their own time and we can't force people but in this case I think some prompting might help because I'm concerned for his mental health. Once corona is over or if you can get into a situation when you are both alone and comfortable try having a chat with him and say that you love him and if there's anything he wants to talk about ever you are accepting and there for him. Or you could also show signs that you support lgbt+ as long as you are safe to do so, things like posting on your instagram story (if he follows it) that you support lgbt+ people. You have to wait for him to come to you, you can't force people without doing damage but you can help them know they're safe. Don't say "I know you are gay" or "someone told me you are gay" or "I saw your instagram account" (his instagram is his safe space don't take that away form him) instead if he questions you say things like "I'm your sister I know things",  "sisters intuition". Good luck and honestly you are an amazing person :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 10:11:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a very optimistic approach and won't work for many siblings. But try asking if you can have a mature discussion with her. It feels awkward as hell but literally say to her "can we have a mature and open discussion?". Then talk to her about this (or like text her or some shit). If she gets angry and physical then she hasn't reached that maturity level yet. But also you need to recognise if you're being constructive or are responding in anger and emotion. Once again - this is a very rainbows and sunshine approach not all families are like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 10:06:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> there's some internalised homophobia going on there. a partner should be receptive within their comfort levels and boundaries. If he's comfortable with bottoming just not to you thats a shame. I think it's the fear of being emasculated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 10:00:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like otter's have some muscle. Hairy twinks are definitely a thing (maybe not in porn cz that shit aint real) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 09:58:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a super personal decision. If you feel like you are lying to him, or you are holding your breath because you are not out to him then I think tell him - it'll make you feel a lot better and it's the only way of knowing if he'll react bad or not. You'll either gain a closer connection with your friend, or you'll figure out he isn't that great of a person leaving you with 1 less toxic friend- win win. Coming out is primarily about giving yourself closure, if this relationship doesn't need that then I don't think there's a need to come out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 09:49:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've come out to a few religious people and this is generally how it went.

My mum (she's only christian when convenient) - came out at 18 - was hysterical and said all kinds of fucked up shit to me, she wanted me to see a bishop and get help.. obviously wasn't going to do that so she went to see an anglican bishop for herself and he told her that "there are somethings that we love and other things we cant change about our children" and after a few weeks she slowly came around and began talking to me again. It took about a year before we talked about it again and now she's my best friend. She still says she wishes I was straight but has embraced me and has asked me about dating guys and we've watched gay films together.

My step dad (devout catholic) - came out at 18 - He already had 2 gay children and when I came out it was the same reaction. He didn't care but he was insistent that he didn't agree with it. He was a pretty quiet guy but he didn't attend his sons wedding and I don't think he talks to them often. He did say that he will always be there for me (ironic because they broke up messily) so that was nice.

My Grandmother (born again christian) - didn't come out but my brother told her when I was 19 - We had some pretty lengthy chats about it which was weird but good. She said she doesn't support it and thinks it's against god but she loves me because I'm still her grandchild. She doesn't want me to bring a man into her house or display any signs of being gay which is fair enough. She was from a different generation and grew up in a rural area so she really had no idea. I told her a lot of things but she still doesn't quite understand why some gay men 'act' feminine. Overall I totally thought she would disown me if she found out so this was honestly best case scenario.

My Dad (not religious but whilst we're on the topic) - didn't come out but my brother told him when I was 18/19 - Told me he straight up loved me and didn't care. We haven't spoken about it since. He's a mechanic, really macho biker guy and thought i'd never come out to him so this was nice. My dad is pretty racist and ignorant if that helps.

&#x200B;

TLDR : Those you expect will react badly might actually react really well. Those who you think would react fine might unfortunately react the worst. Either way if you are in a safe environment, coming out is one of the best feelings you will feel. I am a completely different person and have a different view on life since coming out. Good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 09:33:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> there might be something there but I know plenty of queer people that didn't experience that. It's unfortunately really common  for straight people as well. I'm not a fan of people (usually homophobes) arguing that being abused as a child is the 'cause' of being gay. I'm sure there are genuine people out there interested, I just think you've got to be a bit careful here to not give fuel to damage gay people and people who had to go through child abuse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 09:26:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bruh there are some issues going on here. You're just attracted to him because he fits the 'straight guy' mould and on top of that he has the self degrading qualities that appeal to you for some reason. Had this too when I was in high school - id fall for the trashiest guys because i thought thats all i deserved and it fit the mould of all the straight girls and their boyfriends around me. For the love of god please don't tell him you have a crush on him unless he comes out to you. Even if ya'll got together he would still be in the closet and that shit ain't fun to deal with in a relationship. I also had a gay guy tell me he had a crush on me before I was comfortable to come out and that was awkward for him to get let down and for me to pretend to be straight. jesus im so glad im not a teenager anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 09:18:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Had the same thing happen to me last year - got with a guy and fell for him then something changed and he felt way too clingy. For me it was a slow build up of pet peeves that ended in me really not liking the guy. When we start talking to someone new we're kinda "love" or "dick" blind so naturally once you're removed from that like on spring break we see things clearer and realise this ain't it fam. I think being angry at a bottom because of an accident is fucked up - he obviously didn't mean to be messy and it's such a traumatic experience for bottoms and tops to a lesser extent. Bashing you on social media is a shit move on his behalf and shows his true colours so I think you averted a crisis like I did last year. But don't go bashing on him, there's no point and it'll just fuel the agitation you have towards him. Somethings are just a bit of fun and other things are serious. this seems like it was just a bit of fun and thats totally ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 09:09:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think thats a weird age gap. If you feel comfortable inviting him into your house then go for it. Just remind yourself of your boundaries and expectations some guys can try to manipulate that. The only concern I see here is to check if he is actually 18. I know a few people that were using dating apps when they were a lot younger than 18 and were just pretending to be older. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 20:38:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If this isn't a troll - Bruh don't do this. You're just horny and there are other ways than incest to get that tension out. Use google if you have questions about your body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 20:36:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take it slow, use lube if you can or at least use water. You'll see some shit and probably wont go too deep. Try pushing up towards your prostate, you don't need to go very far in to do so. Breathe and try opening your hole like you're taking a shit. Don't rush into using more fingers until you're fully relaxed at that level. Honestly it might take like 15 minutes before you're ready for a second finger. I dont think there will be any harm if you don't wait for your body to be relaxed but it can feel like a burning pain afterwards if you don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 20:30:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 100% agree. I'm sure some people have been lucky enough not to have noticed transphobia in their local gay community but I see it a lot around me. I think some people think that because they are apart of the lgbt+ community that they have a free pass to say derogatory things about other genders/ sexualities. I think it also comes from the fact that a lot of straight people (more popular in certain areas of the world) don't see a difference between trans females and gay men so to distance ourselves some gay men say shitty things about trans females. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 20:24:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I totally understand where you're coming from. I had to exact same feelings when I was first realising I was gay. I'd feel dirty unless I finished watching straight porn. I think for me it was making friends that are also lgbt+ and hearing their experiences and telling them mine. Also watching a lot of educational and not thirsty gay youtubers. watching gay movies - love simon was a great one, please like me - is a great comedy series thats also kinda sad. I think it just comes with time and for some it might take longer than others. Focus less on the sexual aspects of being interested in guys and more on you as an individual and how you feel about being gay. Once we disassociate gay with meaning gay sex then lots of this goes away. good luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 20:18:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lots of buff tanned guys who seemed to not be afraid to message first. Also lots of other european tourists who weren't shy because they weren't there for long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 20:15:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wasn't there long enough to fully experience it but man, Paris tinder and grindr was on a different planet. But that's coming from western australia where its like 80% closeted 60 year old married farmer men </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 20:14:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you can kind of tell sometimes if you're ready to bottom. If you feel pressure down there or feel like you need to shit then don't have sex and wait until you've gone to the bathroom because there's probably too much there to douche. If you feel fine then maybe douche to make sure. I think it's silly not to eat before sex because you're worried about shitting. We know our bodies and if the top is that up tight that they demand your entire bowel system is empty and clean then I'm sure there are plenty of bottoms out there that will degrade themselves for a quick fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 20:07:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think most gay men have some level of internalised homophobia. It's the idea that you can be gay but still have small microagressions towards the gay community. I think this comes from the fact that we grew up in a homophobic society and had to deal with the idea of being gay a lot sooner and with less maturity than others. Gay men have to go on a journey of acceptance with the baseline of being slightly homophobic. Some things are easier to change our thinking of and other things are "internalised" meaning they're suppressed and we haven't dealt with them yet which is fine. Your journey doesn't end once you come out of the closet. I don't know if preferences are internalised homophobia but I think our preferences will change over time so if in 20 years we are attracted to slightly less masculine men then maybe there was a little homophobia there. I'm also attracted to masculine men and I'm slightly feminine. I don't know the answers to this question but I think its exciting that we have such a direct way of working on ourself and connection with our selves that straight people might never experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-04 18:25:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - Sarah needs professional help. I went through a similar situation and it sucks, its completely draining and this goes way past a normal friendly advice conversation or being there for a friend. I think you should tell her your boundaries and that she you cannot help her in the way she needs. You can be a friend for her and offer her friendship level support but you cannot be her on call therapist and that it feels like she is diverting all of her baggage rather than dealing with it. I would encourage you to also use the free counselling services, they can give excellent advice on how to deal with this and also are there to listen to you. I work in student counselling and even I regularly see counsellors to talk about this stuff in confidence the way you are doing here. Good luck, remember you can't be a help to anyone if you're not helping yourself.

&#x200B;

edit: when this happened to me I straight up told my friend I am there for her and love her but I cannot talk about such dark topics without feeling drained anymore and she needs to respect that so I can continue to be there for her. She was a bit upset a first but this strengthened our relationship a lot for a few years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 20:00:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ESH - that shits gross why would you let anyone do that, tax them higher so they stop and sanitise your laptop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 19:58:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - he's entitled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 19:55:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ETA - Don't out your sister like that. She's being super disrespectful towards you and you gotta take the high road and be better than that. Maybe look into some legal stuff like identity theft if you really want to get sneaky with it. Talk to her manager or the club or something before you even consider telling your family and risk putting her life in danger. This is so shit and i'm sorry this is happening to you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 19:49:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - this is such a win. eat the rich. If it's playing on your conscious and your mental health then send it back but like it's not like you stole the employee's money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 19:45:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yup. and I stand by the fact that if a gay couple were having a conversation about abortion - their arguments aren't valid because it's not their bodies. Im a gay man and my opinion also doesn't matter on this subject </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 19:40:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - aint his body aint his decision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 19:37:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ETA - Your friend is overreacting and is taking projects a bit seriously for a 14 year old especially if she was procrastinating as well. If all you did was quickly send a reply then all good, but if you've got allocated time to doing an assignment you may as well just do it. Maybe I have a different opinion than others in the comments because I'm a university student in an intense degree and I've seen people fail a unit because their group members didn't do their end of the project adequately. If you've got another group project coming up tell your teacher not to put you with her for both of your sakes. good luck with everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 19:30:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - I'm trying to see your mums point of view to be as unbiased and give constructive feedback but I just cant unless you were being super obnoxious and disturbing others with your laughter .. that shit's funny. Also you tried to be mature about it in the car and give an honest apology which is super admirable. You're not even slightly an asshole in this situation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 19:24:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA - Obviously having your rent raised is a shit feeling and your tenants are totally valid in feeling this way if they decided to rent under an agreement of the initial prices. But also you're in such a tricky position right now and It seems logical for you to do this. I think the more you raise it the more of an asshole you are so that's really up to you to decide AITA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 19:20:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - You would rock this haircut but I think for your safety it's best if you follow their requests for now. Especially in self-isolation when you're going to be spending an increasing amount of time with them at home. I know it's hard for you but I just want you to be safe especially right now. I couldn't imagine a scarier time to be kicked out. Be persistent and they might change their minds, maybe try asking if you can have a mature discussion sitting down without any yelling or judgement to hear their concerns (and without reacting right away even if they say something rude), and then you state your arguments. Good luck, and I'm so excited for you in the future when you get to shave your head :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 19:13:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - You have an established relationship with him and he's obviously important to you. I think it's tricky because in my opinion he did a really shit thing to your mum and in her eyes you remaining close with him is like you've chosen a side. And if you have then its your business but I think it might be worth explaining to her that her feelings are valid and that what she had to go through must have been tough and you recognise that it was a really hard thing to go through - but that you have a bond with your stepdad and he is important in your life and your children's life. My dad cheated on my mum and after they got divorced i was still expected to have a relationship with my father - wether he's biological or not. Good luck with everything, just remember that it's okay to be selfish sometimes and put your own happiness first as long as it's not directly harming those around you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 19:07:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - this is straight up not how anyone should behave towards someone with a disability, but for a friend to act this way? I'd strong encourage you to rethink wether she is worth your time of day. I'm sorry this happened to you and I hope you don't have to be put in that scenario again, if I was there I would have thrown it down for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 19:03:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - wtf who would care enough that you have a tattoo in your ass crack unless you're going to be naked. Snitching on a co-worker is such a shit move when they're not doing anything to harm you. Also who be looking at someone's ass hole during changing time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 19:00:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA - You called your girlfriend out and made her look like an idiot in front of her friends. Wether it was true or not we shouldn't be publicly shaming those we love. If you don't feel appreciated or wanted to talk to her about that fact that she didnt actually buy the dog, wait for the skype to finish and chat to her in private. It's more mature and you're going to have a more meaningful conversation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-22 19:34:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ESH - Sorry this is happening to you but I wonder if it's a bit emotional right now and we aren't fully reflecting on how things are going. I understand where you're coming from as someone with mental health issues and education can be so difficult at times - just remember that you're the only person that can give yourself validation and that it's okay to ask for help from tutors, your parents, or counselling. Try having an open discussion with your parents saying that you're struggling right now and it feels like they're not listening to you and by comparing you to your older siblings it's putting a lot of pressure on you that is having a worse effect on your mental health and therefore overall performance. It's important to have open discussions like this with your parents especially when you're going through high school. I'm in college now and man were my teenage years rough - I wish I had of just invited my parents to have an open discussion about what's going on in a mature and judgement free space. This might seem very unobtainable right now but just remember that you're 16 and things will change you just have to focus on being healthy. Maybe try making a study plan or if studying at home isn't great try studying in the library or at school if they have dedicated spaces. good luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-22 19:26:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - I hate confrontation so would have gave her the seat and asked someone else if I could take theirs. But I understand I wasn't there and this probably wasn't an option especially when someone is yelling at you in a foreign language. The lady was way out of line for yelling at you in public rather than trying to talk to the person who spoke Chinese to figure out what was going on. Just remember we never know the full story and she might have had the worst day imaginable, it wasn't your fault she reacted the way she did. I hope this post puts you at ease, its such a shit thing to go through especially with an invisible disability and anxiety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-22 19:18:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - I don't know if your parents are superficial but a gift doesn't have to be something expensive or even monetary at all. You can make them a nice card, put together a slide show of memories on a computer, clean their house or garage, surprise them and come home early and volunteer to help out for a little while, you could write them a heart felt letter about how much they mean to you on a sincere level. You could bring them breakfast in bed. If they're really just after something expensive that they'll never use or throw away then I'm sorry, from a broke uni student, that's super difficult and it might be worth talking to them about your current financial status. good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-22 19:07:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA  - this shits funny. (im a gay man and also think men are overrated even in self-isolation).  There's a difference between offending peoples ego's and offending a persons existence. In this case, you hurt a few little egos (even in the comment section). If you were to say some shit like "hope coronavirus targets men so we won't have to deal with them anymore" that might hurt a little that might just hurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-22 19:04:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NAH - She might have just had a bad day, or like you said she's been fetishised in the past for being Japanese so in that moment it might have brought her back to that. You were just being funny and acknowledging she spoke the language without actually requesting she narrate. There is no sarcasm in Japanese and if she had had a long day at work and was tired she might not have picked up on the English sarcasm (I do the same) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-22 19:01:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA - Negotiate. You don't need to be going to intensive language classes but maybe tell her that you'll start watching Japanese for beginner videos on youtube and ask her to practise with you every now and then. It's an intimate and special part of any Interracial language and especially with Japanese people if you show that you can speak a little bit of japanese it will impress her parents a lot (trust me) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-22 18:49:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - If this is true this is psychotic and you could probably get the police involved. good luck girl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-22 18:45:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> okay NTA, thats a grown ass adult </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-22 16:02:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personally, I think it's easier to come out to people you've just met because it means the connection isn't so deep that if (and we almost always expect this) they react badly and cut you off then it doesn't hurt as much as it would if you came out to a friend of 5 years and they turned their back on you. I'm sorry he didn't come out to you first, but maybe its because he values your friendship so much he was worried. Coming out is really awkward and i had the same experience having serious chats with people i'd only ever joked around with. Take your time writing an apology, it's okay to be vulnerable and serious in apologising when it's such a vulnerable and serious topic :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-22 15:16:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA - (disclaimer: I'm a gay guy who went through a similar experience) Thank you for being a supportive friend and not being bothered when you found out. You need to know this is an incredibly sensitive topic and lgbt+ people need to be in control when it comes to coming out especially when they're coming out for the first time. LGBT+ people are significantly more likely to experience poor mental health compared to straight people [https://lgbtihealth.org.au/statistics/](https://lgbtihealth.org.au/statistics/), and when you keep a secret in for that long and you finally decide to embrace it - it's such an empowering and overwhelming feeling that when someone tries to out you or asks  if you're gay before you're ready it feels like the carpet has been taken beneath you and the power you finally gave back to yourself has been taken away again. LGBT+ teens are so used to being worried about gossip in the halls and that people are talking about their sexuality behind their back that it becomes a default mindset that people are out to get you and it takes many years before this paranoia goes away - So even when you've finally came out to some people, having someone ask you or tell you that they know you're gay, it means that the paranoia that caused so much anxiety was true in that moment - people were talking about his sexuality behind his back. Which isn't a bad thing because it was in good nature but his automatic response was of anxiety and being upset because that's all he has known for so long. This is an incredibly personal thing that non LGBT+ people can never understand, but when you ask someone if they're gay before they're ready to tell you, then it takes the power out of their hands and makes them feel worthless and embarrassed because; 1) all the anxiety and fear was for nothing if this person was going to be okay with my sexuality (which sound silly to be embarrassed but emotions are so raw and high during this period) 2) I will never be able to share the experience of coming out and performing such an intimate act of trust with this person because they outed me instead, 3) people are talking about me behind my back and that means that I might be unsafe if people have overheard and had a bad reaction without me witnessing it. You were just trying to be supportive and I think he knows that, and I'm sure he's so relieved that you don't care. But I think it would still be a really nice opportunity to apologise to him and tell him that you didn't realise this would make him feel this way and that you are open to talk about his sexuality if or when he deicides to and that it doesn't change anything between you to.

&#x200B;

\- Also there are some LGBT+ people that don't feel this way and that would prefer if people told them that they know they're LGBT+ and they're okay with it. But to me it sounds like your friend reacted the same way I did when I was a lot younger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-22 14:54:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ETA - I totally understand where you're coming from and that it's possible to not like someone because of their personality and it not being homophobic. I'm gay and I can't stand this gay kid in my class who acts like being gay is his entire personality. If your brother has just come out, this is pretty common as gay people finally discover who they are and it will settle down when he realised that being gay is just a part of his life and not his entire identity. I would be concerned however if you can't stand him because he is flamboyant whereas your cousin might not be an effeminate gay person. If this is the case I think there's some underlying homophobic and toxic masculinity going on and I would really courage self reflection and therapy to try to deal with that. It's not a nice feeling to dislike someone so close to you, and I hope things work out. Sometimes personalities just don't match but under no circumstance should you attack him for being flamboyant or being gay - if he is doing something annoying try to figure out why it's annoying and if it's related to him being flamboyant then thats kinda fucked up. If he's being annoying because he's telling a story he's told for the 100th time and he's being super loud and obnoxious - then you have a reason to be annoyed. This is a shit situation but I'm sure time will sort it out. Just remember he's a person too and he's dealing with a  lot of personal stuff the same way that you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-22 14:35:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - I just want to let you know you're super brave for coming out in the scenario you were in. Your son is definitely out of line and is probably finding any excuse to justify his behaviour . I do think that maybe you shouldn't have walked out of the therapy session though, after all the therapist has an obligation to remain unbiased and was just trying to let your son get all of his frustration out so that he could have a meaningful conversation with him and yourself. But I totally understand how difficult that must have been for you in that moment. I think time can change a lot of things and my mum was very disrespectful to me and disowned me for a little while after I came out. But time changes people and we both individually got counselling separately on our own terms.  Maybe in a non-hostile situation suggest that your son see a councillor by himself to talk about his anger, and maybe it might help you to do the same. You're not an asshole but you might have made a mistake walking out of the therapy session opposed to voicing your frustration in a safe environment, but I think a lot of people would have done the same if they really knew what you were feeling in that moment and what you've had to go through. I hope things turn out for the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-22 14:25:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA - I speak Japanese and I'm thankful you did this. You helped her to see that she's learning a language that is useful and will allow her to communicate with real people rather than just be able to understand anime without the subtitles. I think she might have been bummed out not because Japan isn't like Anime but that she was called out on something she was proud of and maybe feels embarrassed? Maybe in your next lesson open an anime and pick a scene to watch and then dissect what the people are saying and have a lesson around the vocabulary and grammar used in that segment. She'll feel appreciated that you acknowledge anime as valid but also you can teach her how to apply what she learns in anime into the real world? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-15 19:58:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry that happened to you. I never thought about it in that way before. I've been feeling like an evil person for a while now because of this but I'm starting to feel like it wasn't 100% my fault. Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-15 18:41:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When everything went down I said in this order in between all of his questions; I wasn't sure If I wanted a relationship, I didn't want to be exclusive, I cant give him what he deserves,  I'm not ready for a relationship x2, I don't want to be in a relationship x3. He finally understood and said he wouldn't mind being FWB and he'll try to not get emotionally attached. He continued to text me for a while asking how my day etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-15 17:24:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We have a lot of mutual friends and I didn't want everyone to turn against me because I broke up with him since everyone knows he's a nice person. I guess I should have </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> AITA I ghosted a really nice guy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-15 17:19:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I met this guy who was honestly everything I thought I wanted, but slowly I started developing pet peeves towards him. He was needy AF and needed to stay over every other day and asked me out 2 weeks after meeting. I turned him down and said "maybe one day"... He also said my name in like every sentence and by the 2nd date was already burping and farting around me and was so affectionate in public.

He was also very emotional and whilst I was working he sent a massive paragraph saying how he is so confused about this "relationship" even though I never said we were in a relationship and even denied it. Essentially I told him I didn't want a relationship with him and he continued to tell me how confused he was and just wanted me to tell him whats going on. He kept saying things along this line and in the span of 30 minutes I told him I didn't want a relationship 8 times and he was still confused.. He kept going on about how he wants to make this work and I gave him so many hints that eventually I just decided to agree to be FWB with him even though all I wanted was for him to "break up" with me even though we weren't a thing. He's tried to chat to me since but I just say I'm busy because I don't really know how you come back from that.

I really enjoyed the experiences we had together but ultimately he just started to get on my nerves and I didn't want to lead him on any more than I guess I had. He is 2 years older than me but honestly acted pretty young especially considering I had less experience with dating than he had.

Am I the asshole for ghosting a nice guy and not breaking things off or could he just not take a hint?

\- Some Extra Info-

We were "seeing each other" for about one or two months in total during which we saw each other often and he took me on some early cute dates. Pretty early into meeting up, he was telling all of his friends and family about me and saying how he wants a good life so he can support me. I met his brother a few times. I guess I selfishly didn't want to cut it off completely because I didn't want to be the person that breaks someones heart and it was pretty new to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
