<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject63</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 23:33:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sleeping pills a whole lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> WHERE HAS WONKA GONE ? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 07:21:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 07:45:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Needed that, Thank you : ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 05:52:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try smoking kratom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 22:09:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well is not a TV  but my edgenuity lessons have ass resolutionp . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 09:16:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks!

Do you have any Netflix recommendations?
That is all b4 we part ways. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 09:14:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BTW on your post to clarify I thought you comnent on the post was from a different account didn't double check it i totally missed... i do apologize person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 09:12:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mmm I'm just venting on the mental health forum.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 09:05:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 08:53:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope not!!!!
TROLLS WORLD TOUR 2 !!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 08:51:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, I needed clarity. I appreciate your response :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 19:53:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Second oldest (INFP) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 20:49:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If the ultrasound looked good I don't think you have  anything to worry about sometimes during the insertion they cut the strings too short to long it happens just be aware of your situation and watch for intense lower abdomen cramping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 20:44:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you had the Mirena it's probably the Mirena crash taking its course.

   *Here a link to read all about it!*
https://www.healthline.com/health/womens-health/symptoms-after-mirena-removal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 20:36:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here's the thing with kyleena its smaller then the regular iud hence why she probably told you not to touch it. The iud has a higher chance of moving when its new so its recommended to wait about a week then check your strings you should be okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ringing in my ears... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 20:36:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm currently learning about the structure of the ear and since it's online and im learning through watching videos of lectures i don't really have anybody to answer my questions. It was mentioned in the lecture that hair cells are found in the cochlea and something about hearing damage and how ringing in the ears might be a sign of early hearing loss...idk i wasn't really paying attention because i was too busy wondering where exactly the ringing is coming from and what exactly is behind the random ear ringing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 00:44:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have and it was horrible I have pictures videos EVERYTHING to convince me to never do it again. I thought It was going to be a life changing high mixing weed with alcohol but no... so for starters it totally killed the high and brought on intense dizziness i couldn't walk straight everything was kinda distorted my speech was slurred my heart felt like it was beating once every hour. And after about 30 minutes of that I was stationed by the toilet for the rest of the night.... Don't do it horrible trip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 22:31:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This was a great first step towards something great. I'm glad your parents understood that sometimes there are things that they can't always help with. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> JUST keep scrolling. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 20:46:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Last week I wrote my suicide letter and
I looked at it again last night.


< I hope you are content with who u are>

Over the years I've contemplated suicide many many times but I was always never willing to go forward with  it does me writing the letter mean that I've come to terms with everything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
