<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject53</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 21:53:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is incredible!!!!!!! im literally blown away 😭 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 20:33:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. All Too Well -- I feel like this is probably a popular top pick for track 5. This will forever be one of my favorites. Especially the line "Time won't fly, it's like I'm paralyzed by it / I'd like to be my old self again but I'm still trying to find it." OOF.
2. Dear John -- Speak Now is still one of my top favorite albums of hers and this one always sticks out. I love the twist in the bridge, it kind of reminds me of the twist at the end of White Horse a bit. Also like please, drag John Mayer.
3. Cold As You -- Still can't believe she wrote this song when she was a teenager, it's honestly so lyrically beautiful and definitely the best written of that album. The line that always gets me is, "You come away with a great little story / of a mess of a dreamer with the nerve to adore you."
4. White Horse -- There's something kind of elementary about this song but I think that's the beauty of it. It's about realizing how naive your view of love was and then coming to terms with the fact that it's not going to be like you thought it would. Also, again, love the twist in the final chorus.
5. My Tears Ricochet -- I love this song!! But I can relate to the other track fives at least on some level and I can't really relate on a personal level to this one even though it's beautifully haunting. I also think I need to listen to it a lot more before it moves up on my list.
6. The Archer -- Again, love this song but love the others more. I think sonically it's a little less than the rest. I do especially love the chorus though, the juxtaposition of "who could ever leave me, darling? but who could stay?" is so heartbreakingly beautiful.
7. AYHTDWS -- I have a love/hate relationship with this song because I love the lyrics but sonically, parts of it feel a bit off. I would *love* for her to do some sort of piano cover and slow it down!
8. Delicate -- I never really got into the *reputation* era and I can't really relate to this song at all. I understand the meaning behind it but it's just not something I can relate to at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 23:52:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> kinda sad that this isn't getting a theatrical release (totally understandable though). but this honestly looks really good -- i was a little skeptical about this at first, but looking at the trailer, it exceeded my expectations. it seems like a really personal look into pete's life and it looks like there's a lot of heart in the movie. excited to watch this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-01 20:42:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> he did deserve so much better than what the writers gave him in s5 😭 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-01 00:14:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> **I Knew You Were Trouble.** vs I Did Something Bad

**Lover** vs Love Story

**Cruel Summer** vs Getaway Car

**All Too Well** vs Last Kiss

**Picture To Burn** vs Better Than Revenge

Enchanted vs **Cornelia Street**

**Shake It Off** vs We Are Never Getting Back Together

Miss Americana & The Heartbreak Prince vs **New Romantics**

**The Moment I Knew** vs If This Was A Movie

Dress vs **Wildest Dreams**

**Clean** vs Daylight

**Blank Space** vs Delicate

**Change** vs Only The You </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-01 00:10:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when i first heard you belong with me, i thought that she was saying "walkin' the streets with you are your ONE EYED jeans" and i was like wtf are one eyed jeans 😭 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-31 23:58:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i think maybe a movie or a single episode to wrap everything up. the last season was such a let down because it didn't have a proper ending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-31 23:09:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> mine too <3 thanks for watching </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-31 23:09:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it hurt me to make it as well :( thank you for your kind words <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-31 23:08:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you so much <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> be alright - jane & michael </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-31 08:59:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hey jtv subreddit! this is my first time making a post in this subreddit so let me know if i got anything wrong! i recently made an [edit](https://www.instagram.com/p/B-XmVHbDqct/) to jane & michael on my instagram & i thought i would share here :) there are slight s5 spoilers so you have been warned! please let me know what you think <3

song: be alright by dean lewis
pairing: jane & michael
program used: video star & adobe audition </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 06:00:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you! stay safe <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 10:12:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Her standup special on Netflix *Stage Fright* is really quite good imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 10:02:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you're never gonna get that best buy rewards card!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-27 04:41:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i love their friendship </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-15 10:14:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i agree. if they were going to make a meaningful storyline about grief, which it seemed like they wanted to do, they should've let michael rest in peace. him coming back completely ruined jane's grieving and healing process, and also ruined his character and his relationship with jane. i really didn't like how they handled michael coming back and i wish he would've just been able to stay dead so that his character wasn't ruined. the way they treated michael in season five was just not it :/ like, i get that jafael is endgame but they really brought michael back for the *sole* purpose of showing that rafael wasn't a "second choice" and used michael to prop up jafael, which is just a gross disservice to his character. i will die mad about it. and then be brought back to life to prop up a relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 23:24:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it's like sophie's choice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 04:26:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i got 72 lmao that's sad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 04:12:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Debut: Stay Beautiful or A Place in This World

Fearless: Change

Speak Now: Enchanted

Red: State of Grace

1989: This Love

Reputation: So It Goes...

Lover: Daylight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 04:07:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is so cool!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 05:21:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> have you gone through your email to determine that you never made an account? if they're saying you have an account with them, there's probably an email confirming that. you should search your email for any emails from instagram, because i find it unlikely that they would say your email was taken if it wasn't on file. if there isn't, i would try forgot password. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> vent // suicidal ideation tw </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-20 03:24:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hi, this is my first time posting on this forum but i just really need to vent and this is going to come off as very jumbled and inarticulate but i think i just need to get it off my chest.

ever since i can remember, i've had more emotions than i know what to do with. when i get frustrated, my brain goes from zero to one hundred in a split second. i feel like i'm never in control of my emotions, rather that they're in control of me. no matter how minuscule the frustration is (spilling something on my shirt, getting on the wrong elevator, etc.) it often feels like it's the end of the world even when it isn't. something very minor that feels major will happen and before i can even do anything, my brain tells me that i should kill myself. i feel like my brain is lying to me all of the time.

the frustrations become more and more of a problem when i'm around my parents/family and i'm not quite sure why this is. one of my theories is that i control my frustrations so much during the day that when i get home and/or around my immediate family, i kind of release all of the frustrations. i'm not sure if that's what the case is but that's one of my guesses.

(this part is a little unrelated but somewhat related) sometimes i feel like a test subject. on whether or not my parents can raise a mentally unstable child. on whether or not someone with all of my issues can be successful. on whether or not someone as fucked as me has a chance at life. and i don't think the way my mother looks at me helps much - she looks at me like i'm some helpless fucking child and it's getting to the point where i hate being around her because she looks at me like that so much. sometimes i feel like i'm her test subject to prove that she can be a parent to someone like me, but i feel like the results would read: negative.

anyway, that's all i have to say. thanks for listening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-18 08:39:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hahah i remember this, i followed the girl on tumblr who posted this. it's still funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-13 03:51:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lmao i snorted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-30 07:20:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes! katherine hahn is incredible and i would love to see this! the comedy would be amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-30 07:09:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i got 32/35, mostly because i didn't really get that into reputation so i couldn't remember a lot of the lyrics for those ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-08 08:28:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i like tori fine. she's not my favorite character but i like her. like yeah, at times she can be annoying but i think the whole 'i hate tori' thing is getting old and tired. and i do feel that sentiment of people saying 'unpopular opinion i hate tori' when literally everyone says it lmao. one of the things i really don't understand is when people point out how much less talented she is than some of the other singers. which i believe was kind of the point? like in the first episode, it was established that she felt like she didn't belong at hollywood arts and didn't fit in with all of these talented people. i think the point of having her be the main character and not being as talented as cat and jade was to deal with that kind of issue. and that's also one of the reasons that she's not as "whacky" as the other characters. i do agree that her flaws could have been addressed but i think it's silly to act like the other characters didn't have flaws that weren't addressed either. i feel like a lot of the hate is just due to the fact that people like cat and jade (and ariana and liz) more than they like tori/victoria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-02 19:44:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ve met people like this who because of anti-choice rhetoric assume that being pro-choice is pro-abortion. But in reality, if you believe that life begins at conception and that abortion is wrong, but you don’t impose on other people’s beliefs/how they deal with the decision, then you are pro-choice. Pro-choice is simply believing in every persons’ right to choose. For this reason, I don’t think it’s really possible to be both pro-life and pro-choice - there are just people confused and misinformed on what the terms mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-18 03:26:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "who sings that song?"
"carmella!!! :)"
🥺

as someone who is a huge fan of both christina and taylor, this warmed my heart. i really hope they collab on something 🖤 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-18 03:18:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> according to the production order, the last episode filmed was the slap fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-18 03:14:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i think my favorite is take a hint. did what no by meghan trainor couldn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-15 06:28:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> she's not on social media so i don't know if there's any way to tell. but if i'm not mistaken, she was at [katie's bridal shower](https://hestershigh.tumblr.com/post/184483974721/the-faking-it-fam-at-katies-bridal-shower/) so it's possible that she attended the wedding as well! i hope she did at least lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-15 06:16:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First off, I want to say that your friend really has no right to say things about what you should and shouldn't want, it's your gender identity and it's really fucked up that she would say something like that. And as for the period issue, I can see both sides. I mean,  I take birth control solely not to get my period because I hate it so much. But I think the reason for the pride in which some women take in periods is that we've been taught that this natural bodily function is somehow shameful and we should hide it. And there is a sense of cis males never being able to get it, because I think it's something that's just unique to our experience, which is probably another reason that women take pride in it. I think it's more about the stigmatization of periods than enjoying periods. I really don't find my period *enjoyable.* I get really bad cramps and my mental health plummets, but I can understand why someone would take pride in it in order to destigmatize the issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 00:20:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is so cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 00:18:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>

* IFTYE vs **Paper Rings**
* London Boy vs **INTHAF**
* Cruel Summer vs **The Man**
* **Lover** vs The Archer
* ITHK vs **DBATC**
* **Afterglow** vs False God
* **Cornelia Street** vs Daylight
* ME! vs **YNTCD**
* **SYGB** vs MAATHP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 00:17:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>

* IFTYE -- I thought that it would kill me but it didn't
* Cruel Summer -- I love you ain't that the worst thing you ever heard?
* Lover -- Have I known you twenty seconds or twenty years?
* The Man -- I'm so sick of running as fast as I can, wondering if I would get there if I was a man
* The Archer -- Who could ever leave me, darling? But who could stay?
* ITHK  -- I am an architect, I'm drawing up the plans
* MAATHP -- Play stupid games, you win stupid prizes
* Paper Rings -- I hate shiny things but I'd marry you with paper rings / I hate accidents except when we went from friends to this
* Cornelia Street -- That's the kind of heartbreak time could never mend, I'd never walk Cornelia Street again
* DBATC -- But if the story's over, why am I still writing pages?
* London Boy -- They say home is where the heart is, but God, I love the English
* SYGB -- And I hate to make this all about me, but who I am supposed to talk to?
* False God -- I know heaven's a thing, I go there when you touch me, honey
* YNTCD -- Cause shade never made anybody less gay
* Afterglow -- Fighting with a true love is boxing with no gloves
* ME! -- I'm the only one of me, baby that's the fun of me
* INTHAF -- Church bells ring, carry me home
* Daylight -- I've been sleepin' so long in a twenty-year dark night and now I see daylight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 23:58:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These are just my favorite non-singles, I'm doing them in order of album release

1. Cold as You
2. Tied Together with a Smile
3. Mary's Song (Oh My My My)
4. Invisible
5. White Horse
6. You're Not Sorry
7. The Way I Loved You
8. Never Grow Up
9. Dear John
10. Last Kiss
11. Innocent
12. Haunted
13. All Too Well
14. I Almost Do
15. Holy Ground
16. Clean
17. All You Had to Do Was Stay
18. How You Get the Girl
19. Dancing With Our Hands Tied
20. Soon You'll Get Better
21. Cornelia StreetPaper Rings
22. Afterglow
23. Daylight
24. Death by a Thousand Cuts
25. Cruel Summer
26. The Man

And then also maybe some unreleased songs? Classics like I Heart ? and Til Brad Pit Comes Along. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 23:47:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. *What song will they play at your wedding?* Tied Together With a Smile (yikes)
2. *When someone says "everything will be okay", you reply with?*  I Almost Do.
3. *What do you look for in an ideal mate?* The Best Day
4. *What is the purpose of being here?* Begin Again
5. *If you had a theme song, what would it be?* Ronan
6. *What is your motto?* A Perfectly Good Heart
7. *What is your life story?* Wonderland
8. *Why us the sky blue?* Should've Said No
9. *What do your parents think of you?* Style
10. *What are you afraid of?* Welcome to New York
11. *What do you think of your friends?* The Story of Us
12. *What makes you cry?* Fearless
13. *The world is ending tomorrow! What song will you play?* Long Live (that one actually works perfectly lmao) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 07:51:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this looks great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 07:44:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> background check for sure. the chaotic energy in that episode is so palpable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 07:31:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> taylor swift: cold as you, teardrops on my guitar, invisible
fearless: superstar, fifteen, you're not sorry
speak now (this is really hard because it's my favorite album of hers): dear john, never grow up, back to december,
red: all too well, i almost do, begin again
1989: clean, wonderland, blank space
reputation: new year's day, delicate, call it what you want
lover: soon you'll get better, cornelia street, lover </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 07:19:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm two weeks late to the party but here's [mine](https://i.imgur.com/FwTIY40.png)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are your Track Fives ranked? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 07:10:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I recently saw a [video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=43BTgxSSr-E) where two friends ranked their top track fives. It got me to thinking about what mine would be. My tentative list right now is probably:

1. All Too Well
2. Dear John
3. Cold as You
4. The Archer
5. White Horse
6. All You Had To Do Was Stay
7. Delicate

My top three sometimes change order depending on how I'm feeling but they're definitely always in my top three. What are yours?

&#x200B;

Edit: In case anyone is confused, track five means the fifth track of the album, which is usually the most vulnerable/emotional song on the album. The only track five tracks are the ones above. Sorry for any confusion, it's my first time posting in this subreddit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-06 01:23:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lisa's reaction makes me laugh every time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-06 01:21:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She doesn't die. The show ended because Disney Channel canceled it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-05 00:07:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want to preface this with saying that I'm a fan of both of them but I think Ariana's reaction was sort of uncalled for. He's a comedian who makes jokes about his personal life all of the time. If you've seen his comedy, he makes jokes about things that he struggles with. I also know that humor is a really common coping mechanism for people with BPD. And dealing with a breakup while having BPD can really *really* hard and it must be amplified because it's in the public eye. I think getting mad about Pete making a joke about it is equivalent to getting angry at Taylor Swift for writing a song about her ex. Like I love Ariana but what did she expect dating a comedian? And the joke, in my opinion, wasn't a dig at her or their relationship. It was completely self-deprecating which is how Pete's comedy has always been. It was making fun of that fact that he's bad at relationships. I think it's kind of ridiculous that Ariana's fans were dragging him for making a joke when it's literally his job. They wouldn't drag her for releasing a song about their break up so why is this any different? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-11 02:42:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I figured out that the problem was Instagram thought I had too many stories in the highlight because when I removed some, the old ones popped right back up. It's really weird because I only had around 80 and I believe the limit is 100. I think it's some kind of glitch because I used to have some that got deleted due to the people's posts that I was sharing deactivating or deleting/archiving their posts so maybe Instagram was counting the ones they deleted as well and it added up to 100. Who knows lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 09:10:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, I logged out of the account and went on my personal and the highlights were gone when I viewed through that account as well unfortunately :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Stories Mysteriously Disappearing From Highlights </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 07:21:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is my first time using Reddit so I apologize if I do anything wrong lmao. So basically I have an Instagram account (it's a fandom one) and I have highlights for things like "song of the day", "ship of the day", "character of the day", etc. And recently (aka today) some of my highlights have been mysteriously disappearing? I had around four in my highlights go missing. But the weird thing is, if I go into my archive, the story is still there and says that it's in the highlight. I don't know what's going on but it feels like I'm going insane. I've tried force closing the app to see if that changed anything but it didn't. I don't really know what to do because Instagram doesn't really have customer service and I've never seen anyone else with this problem. If anyone has any insight on what's happening, please let me know. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
