<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject61</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 22:56:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty sure they are a looser fit. Don't quote me though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-05 06:39:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This plus the caps 2015 winter classic are my favorite jerseys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 19:10:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I meaaaan look at that lets get havertz now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I am looking to buy a GTI but have some questions! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 17:11:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m in the market for a GTI but I don’t know the common issues or things to watch out for.

What are some specific things I need to ask about and look for when I’m car shopping?

How reliable is your GTI? I plan to take good care of it!

I want to buy a newer model, but any GTI works if there are less than 70k miles.

Are there any good places to look at for a good price?

Any other information and the “scoop” on GTIs is appreciated greatly!

Thanks so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 16:24:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dang i really like the white shorts combo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-02 07:06:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Before his reactions to COVID and George Floyd I would’ve said yes. But now.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-01 16:00:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m no expert but I think it may be a fake. Good looking though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-01 00:14:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its also dumb how FC Bayern II is treated as a completely separate club. Players cannot jump from one club to the other :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 17:24:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Grape Mo look is in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 03:19:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Havertz next. The kid is too good to let him leave Germany under our watch ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 08:17:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> With our bullpen no way. He’s a gem too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 08:14:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aachen is seriously such a gem! I went there on a student exchange and the city is 100% amazing if you are willing to just explore and appreciate a place. Not the biggest of sights or culture or anything like that! But the people there and that city will always have my heart! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 08:04:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any other Nats fans here to protest this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thoughts on Havertz transfer this offseason? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 05:24:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 08:15:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like em actually! Take away the gradient numbers and the Rams tag lookin thing and its great. But with it its 8/10 should look dope on the field. No where near the other LA team! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 08:11:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My wish for our kits would be to wear white shorts with the red shirts for the home kit, a white or navy blue away kit with red accents, and a black or white 3rd kit depending on the away kit color. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 00:29:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it shows his fight for the team if he calms down a little bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 00:28:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think he needs to dial it down but that will come with age. Shows fight and leadership if calmed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 16:16:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well Jeremy Clarkson... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 21:22:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you know when the deal ends? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 21:19:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> James by a good bit but he had 2 seasons here unlike Coutinho whose about to have 3/4 worth of a season. Both players are very similar in how their peak performances seem to be in the past for whatever reason. They are both enigmas for sure. James is less 1v1 oriented and was able to pass and affect the game better than Coutinho for us imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 03:24:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We can use the money saved for Havertz 🙏🏻 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-04 02:24:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> German Knoppers good. American Knoppers bad. Most German candy in the States is good but not as fresh as "echte deutsche Süßigkeiten". However Knoppers don't make the transition well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-01 20:31:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Federals is way better than wizards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 22:36:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sané and Havertz pleaaase I want nothing more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 03:03:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Football without fans is truly nothing but the fans can still watch from home... This is only temporary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-20 20:38:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I might just have to do this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-17 19:30:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally bamboozled /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 20:37:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you remember Marcelo Sarvas' quick stop in DC, I saw him in Alexandria eating at a cafe but he was with his wife and baby didn't want to interrupt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 19:15:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Huddy took over alot of closing the back end of the season and in the playoffs they split duties so I think Huddy was the man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 18:57:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will not allow the golden knights </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 15:51:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [wrong kit](https://www.reddit.com/r/DCUnited/comments/fle3es/they_took_away_our_red_shorts_on_fifa_20_that_is/?utm_source=share&utm_medium=ios_app&utm_name=iossmf)
[right kit](https://www.instagram.com/p/B-XWQy_D6Wz/?igshid=5dh1yjmz533o)

Unbelievable levels of incompetence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 15:48:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its all down to kit licensing so its kind of tough but what I’m saying is if you have a kit licensed to be in the game it should probably be correct haha! I’ll link the wrong kit and and real kit just give me a second! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 15:45:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bayern for two reasons! Found my love for football with Müller, Schweini and Lahm at the 2014 WC and then the biggest Bayern fanclub in North America is in my hometown so I would go watch the matches with them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 15:40:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Skyrim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 15:34:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They didnt make a caps one ;( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 15:32:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trophies disappear, untitled players and out of position in the lineup screen, clubs playing their bad players, this! Also i follow DC United and tall of the new MLS kits are in fifa and they had the DC kit wrong with white socks instead of black but THEN they changed it AGAIN to have black shorts instead of the correct red. They CHANGED the shorts of the kit to be the wring color and didn’t change the wrong colored socks. The. Worst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 02:53:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unfortunately im keeping one to frame/sell when they are really rare with the tags still on sorry man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 02:44:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had this happen when I ordered my miami heat vice city Wade jersey! They sent me two! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-13 02:40:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Poster im the back from the Box set? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-11 15:08:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Use sofifa bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 18:06:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Soto is going to be so hilarious doing this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 18:32:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That 0-1 on October 27th was the worst birthday gift ever... until I realized my gift came 3 days late. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 16:28:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://images.app.goo.gl/uQFw8WuwUzmUzs1p7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-08 03:23:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've quite literally grown up with/alongside the nationals. I was born in 99 and the Nats came to town in 05 (right when my memory starts to kick in). My dad was an Orioles fan but when baseball came back to DC he immediately became a fan and I followed suit. I still faintly remember going to games at RFK (I was 5-8 years old) and even have a foul ball from that era (my dad caught it naturally). I even remember being destroyed by Roger Clemens and the Astros (both cheaters) 14-1 in 2005 (thanks baseball reference). I went to the first ever game played at nationals park, alas not the famous walk off opening day game, but the forgotten preseason tune up game the night before. I feel i've grown up with the Nats and I feel a special connection because of that (I wonder if some of my peers feel the same way). I went to the disappointment playoff games against the Dodgers in Dodgers and Cubs which makes our title that mush sweeter. I go to multiple games every year and I'm so proud that this is my team. I would've said that even before 2019 but especially now that we've finished the fight! I got my dad tickets for the second home game to see the WS banner (the first game tickets were at the lowest $150 each) I hope I get to go to the ballpark soon! Stay healthy and go 1-0 everyday! Go Nats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-07 16:46:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> JAAAA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-07 07:52:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It would be a huge mistake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-07 03:51:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! I’ll check him out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone know if the team store (or anywhere for that matter) does jersey customization? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 17:17:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a blank red jersey I would like to customize with Zimm on the back. Does anyone know where to point me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-02 05:32:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for doing this man! Could you maybe put the "nationals" on nationals blue one a bit lower? It gets covered up by the big head of the character </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 17:36:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have one that is almost just like it. Must've been the next season because mine says Washington DC United instead of inaugural season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 01:39:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But it sounds weird to be the washington monuments when there is a washington monument </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-21 19:32:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cannot tell you how many times Lloris has robbed me but this is a whole new level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-21 19:29:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do you make these? Any tips for one who is not artistic/if you found them somewhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-21 19:29:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This game is great. I hadn't played until yesterday (release day) and have played for many hours already </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-21 19:28:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Caps throwback or screaming eagle (your choice) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-20 00:50:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why why why that makes zero sense this game is so broken </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 23:33:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Old one is a definite classic and holds a special place. But the new one is probably the best we could’ve done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-15 13:54:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now this is a whole new spin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-15 00:08:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All quiet on the western front. You really see humanity more vividly after reading! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 22:45:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get him his money! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 22:44:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Diggs on one side and terry on the other would be the best WR duo in the league in a few years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 00:40:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They look the weird DnD kids and look where they got! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 00:37:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If they did the bayern title celebrations the game would have to be rated teen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 06:36:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I took my grandpa to get his vision test and he literally tripped over the seats at the dmv (he was alright thankfully) and then the lady wouldn’t end the test until he got all the questions right. So it is definitely a joke. He chooses not to drive anymore thank goodness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-27 23:58:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See if you get the regular souvenir cup and bring it into the next game and the next game... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 21:57:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Striker Gnabry hes played it for germany </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 19:20:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Davies has a few more years to be 100%. He's still young and Alaba seems like a one club man. When davies is hitting his prime and Alaba is going downhill should be around the same time so Alaba can take a back seat then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 19:11:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like Gnabry up top ftb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 17:18:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shooooot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 09:21:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Deuces if he continues to perform </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 03:09:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> $175 is a big nope from me but its a nice jersey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-25 06:06:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hawt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-24 19:15:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m from the USA and the biggest bayern supporters club in north america is in my hometown! Albeit I find way more premier league and Barca/Real fans around. I feel my club and I add a much needed germanness to the supporter scene of my friends and peers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 20:55:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Without thomas the assist king 👑 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 20:49:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NBC Sports Washington would’ve been A+ but at least we’re on TV again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-19 06:07:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is fantastic. what we need on D is toughness and this guy is the definition of it. Dare i say GRIT? Just for kicks [these two are now on the same team.](https://youtu.be/Cd1axsDefq8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 06:33:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Part of the DC Bayern fanclub the largest fanclub in north america i might add ;) Allianz for a Bayern match is number one on the bucket list! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-17 19:05:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That could work too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-17 15:49:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Grey should be home and white should be away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-14 03:31:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  there is no rivalry at all. How are you about to say that any other team is our rival when RB and DC have a literal trophy that goes to the winner of the series... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 17:12:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Asad isn’t even in the game :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 17:11:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That looks so good. Best kit since the good ol days! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 16:06:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/ATBGE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-11 07:11:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank goodness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 23:46:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Inter miami take notes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 14:50:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hamid would be up there if he didnt have a vacation in Denmark... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 20:41:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everyone will hate except for us. This is good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-06 06:51:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My (biased) opinion is that DC has the best considering the three stripe history. Especially if they wear red shorts with the stripes on the back like [Argentina's copa america shorts](https://www.gettyimages.co.uk/detail/news-photo/lionel-messi-of-argentina-in-action-against-junior-moreno-news-photo/1132062346?et=TdxpJahzSmdwEIMLNsC8nQ&referrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.footyheadlines.com%2F2019%2F03%2Fon-pitch-adidas-argentina-2019-copa-america-kit.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-06 06:41:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally an ESPN article yesterday [https://www.espn.com/nhl/story/\_/id/28629810/nhl-awards-watch-calder-norris-trophy-races-state-chaos](https://www.espn.com/nhl/story/_/id/28629810/nhl-awards-watch-calder-norris-trophy-races-state-chaos)

Rocket Richard Trophy (leading goal scorer)

**Current leader:** [David Pastrnak](https://www.espn.com/nhl/player/_/id/3114778/david-pastrnak), [Boston Bruins](https://www.espn.com/nhl/team/_/name/bos/boston-bruins) (38 goals)**Watch out for:** [Auston Matthews](https://www.espn.com/nhl/player/_/id/4024123/auston-matthews), [Toronto Maple Leafs](https://www.espn.com/nhl/team/_/name/tor/toronto-maple-leafs) (36 goals)**Dark horse:** [Nathan MacKinnon](https://www.espn.com/nhl/player/_/id/3041969/nathan-mackinnon), [Colorado Avalanche](https://www.espn.com/nhl/team/_/name/col/colorado-avalanche) (30 goals)

buncha clowns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-01 00:02:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What teams are there? You said Bayern and FC ST. Pauli! I’m interested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-28 05:12:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sweet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-28 05:12:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry :p no take backs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-28 02:46:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 🤢🤮 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-28 01:12:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gosh those are so bad. I didn't know they moved. RIP PNats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A Johnny Norris mailday! (With a sweet cap) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-28 00:47:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-28 00:39:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Minnesota is really sweet too. Cream and green 🤩 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In honor of Neil. A starman shirt with a sweet belt buckle! RIP to the greatest drummer of all time! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-27 23:38:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-27 20:31:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ovechkin falling goal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-27 20:31:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SB Nation Beef history does a great video on this for us youngins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-27 19:29:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Search it up on google maybe the link is bad its an iranian site </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-27 18:50:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The panthers have some sweet jerseys! The new ones are executed so well. The florida flag laces, the new logo, and the side logo that says alternate and captain. Pure class. The caps need a rebrand with the weagle on the front and the dc flag inspired laces! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-27 18:46:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These are so sick! I love it in pictures too. Haters gunna hate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-27 16:33:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use myteams but you should check out [NHL.ir](https://NHL.ir) it has all the nhl streams and has fun predicting and free betting features. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-26 18:15:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would one like [this](https://www.amazon.com/Tiger-Pumps-Submersible-Powerheads-Hydroponics/dp/B01NBKNG4K/ref=mp_s_a_1_4?keywords=mini+jet+404&qid=1580058742&sr=8-4&utm_source=share&utm_medium=ios_app&utm_name=iossmf) work? What gph should I look for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-25 23:57:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is the mini jet 606 the smaller version of the 404? If so, what should I out the flow rate at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-25 23:55:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What flow rate should I look for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-25 22:50:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fantastic story about the kits! Its not often you come across any DCU coverage anywhere so props to you! You do a great job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-25 22:33:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That wouldnt be bad for our boys either :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I need a replacement pump for my aquarium! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-25 02:26:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I recently purchase a topfin retreat 2.5 gallon tank for my betta and I mistakenly broke the pump for the filter.

Does anybody know of a replacement filter I could buy? Images of the tank and pump are below. I need a pump that is not too wide as to fit in the filter compartment shown.

[Pump and compartment ](https://imgur.com/gallery/gNhNEVt) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 09:50:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How would I go about setting that up. Beginner here haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 04:36:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a topfin retreat 2.5 gallon tank and I broke the filter pump when setting it up (or it didnt work) I need a replacement. Does anyone know what would be compatible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-21 09:24:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hm i see. I dont think it looks too bad is it foul? Can you see if it would be weird in person? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-21 06:40:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How is the customization off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-21 05:16:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://rover.ebay.com/rover/0/0/0?mpre=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ebay.com%2Fulk%2Fitm%2F233466698801


https://depop.app.link/PYnVKtFlo3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-18 20:53:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He needs to do that for us to catch the isles... im all for it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-18 20:52:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He will never score again mark my words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-11 23:11:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sammmyyy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-07 00:28:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well yea but it shows resilience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-06 11:32:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Searching for my stadium series was so laborious but I got lucky with an indo Ovi on ebay. But this. This is a beaut! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-06 11:30:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which is the best company to do customization for a caps blue screaming eagle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-06 05:38:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Play call of duty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-06 04:00:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone get this guy a f*ckin puppers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> That was the best game I’ve ever seen! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-06 01:33:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stanley cup run aside, that was the most fun I’ve ever had watching hockey! It was my brother’s first game and he now loves hockey! Me and him were fans of the game just to cap it all off!

Love this team! What a game! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sammy is 11-2-1 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-04 07:32:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This guy is amazing! As a starter he’s 11-1-1 the guy is on fire! Props to him and we’re so lucky to have him and Holts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-03 16:56:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where do you see if someone is verified? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-30 16:17:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We aint done yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-30 16:15:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes definitely! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-30 15:47:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I went to my bank and they blocked it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-30 15:47:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Live and learn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-30 15:46:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you link that FB group? Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-30 15:46:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just went to my bank and they blocked it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I got scammed! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-30 06:00:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I requested tickets for some games on the ticket thread and u/tina-williams messaged me. I fell for it and they scammed me!

I already contacted u/vtcapsfan and they should be banned by now, but if they message you do not respond! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-30 05:59:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Use the my teams app! For some reason they make all local customers do it. At least when I click on the NBC Sports washington broadcast on the nbc sports app it says im in a blackout zone. Use the my teams app is what I would say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-29 07:02:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got scammed! If a username tina-williams messages you, block them. They said they had tickets and did not. I will be sending the mods a message to ban this person! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is it cheaper to get tickets at the door? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 20:37:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-26 22:58:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a Johnny with the alternate captain coming in the mail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 20:41:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Add faroe and åland islands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 16:08:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If he said it was true he wouldn’t even get to finish out the season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 02:13:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Johnny 4 norris baby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 00:47:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My wilson isn’t the cream of the crop but 9/10 i would say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 00:47:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do they do adidas well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 00:39:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Recently got a wilson on nhl.com and that was good. Is that my best bet for right now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is River City Sports a good place to get a customized John Carlson alternate? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 00:20:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-23 21:48:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looking for 2 tickets on 12/27. 400 level </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Caps need to do a nats warmup </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-23 19:40:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The kings did this a couple years ago by doing warm ups for the [lakers](https://www.google.com/search?q=la+kings+lakers+jersey&safe=strict&rlz=1CDGOYI_enUS722US722&hl=en-US&biw=375&bih=551&tbm=isch&prmd=sniv&sxsrf=ACYBGNQEJ1jxlqlNvoi-g6v1u115vCJm2Q:1577126293828&source=lnms&sa=X&ved=0ahUKEwig0oektczmAhWGr1kKHXFPASYQ_AUIICgD#imgrc=cuK0qVWEzQVfyM) and the [dodgers ](https://www.google.com/search?q=kings+dodgers+jersey&safe=strict&rlz=1CDGOYI_enUS722US722&hl=en-US&prmd=sinv&sxsrf=ACYBGNTeWoLkUncvMWctDPXdG5djbfvGvQ:1577126376956&source=lnms&tbm=isch&sa=X&ved=2ahUKEwiF_trLtczmAhUo1VkKHZL_CxEQ_AUoAnoECA8QAg&biw=375&bih=551&dpr=2#imgrc=tqpUP0ZV5B1B3M) Considering how well the Caps and Nats mesh and support each other this is a no brainer. I just want to buy it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-23 17:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The most maddening thing (also rubbing salt in the wound) was when I managed the US in FIFA 19 and made it to 2022 and was not included in the world cup because the teams that were in it were programmed to be the teams that were in the last world cup... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 16:40:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They stopped using it on the score posts but they continue to use it on everything else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 07:26:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For Adidas or fanatics its very difficult and the web is wrought with fakes. r/hockeyjerseys is the place for any and all jerseys but you need to be constantly searching and get lucky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-19 19:41:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Peaked? he hasn’t broken into a first team yet in Hamburg or here and the dudes 19 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-19 16:19:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DC UNITED 👏👏👏👏👏👏 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-19 06:52:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this inside of a cookout? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Any news on our new kit? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-18 05:39:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-17 23:17:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hafencity is beautiful during the day too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-17 21:16:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good ebening </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-17 05:20:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Solo on goodbye angels is the most mindblowing thing ever. Thank you Josh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-15 16:19:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-12 18:11:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nhl66.ir is a fantastic website </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-12 03:02:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sweet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-09 22:38:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This sucks in theory but not in practice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone have any vintage JMU gear that they would be willing to pass on to a current student? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-08 07:44:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m a guys size L-XL
Thanks! Go Dukes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-03 05:18:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The crests look too big </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-29 23:10:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good Ebening Arsenal fans, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ISO Capitals CCM vintage hockey hoodie size L or XL </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-27 00:10:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-26 21:55:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Crystal has always been nuts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-25 18:08:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pm’d </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-25 16:11:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think its worth saying that we’re a DC team. If other teams want to skip out on the white house, whatever. They don’t play down the street from 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-22 23:53:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you have though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-22 23:53:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably under $100 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-21 21:14:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s just reporting the facts. If they did this midseason, (if all the seasons were at the same time) the results wouldn’t be as stark but still more of the same upward trend for caps and nats downward for skins its been like that for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-21 20:56:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This article from Tom Boswell of WaPo puts this perfectly. https://www.washingtonpost.com/sports/what-once-seemed-impossible-is-now-undeniable-the-redskins-have-lost-washington/2019/11/17/c215e596-0975-11ea-8397-a955cd542d00_story.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-21 20:54:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its just the hockey isnt as popular. Most hockey fans are football fans too but not all football fans are hockey fans. Its the 4th sport unfortunately. I would put nats and caps atop the list. Tom Boswell had a fantastic article about this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-21 20:49:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are these stats for the district of the DC area? In NOVA the Nats and Caps probably kill the skins but in Maryland it would probably be a different story. Even though thats known I want to see a map of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ISO LA Kings purple and gold size L or XL </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-21 07:52:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-18 08:43:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mulch and Woodchips are two different things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-14 20:00:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh i thought you wanted the black and gold snapback instead of the other one. My bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-14 19:36:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just checked and they have the snapback 25% off right now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-13 23:08:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im not sure i wanted that one too but bought the onfield one. Thought I would regret it but it looks really good in person! Hope you find it though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-13 22:59:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fanatics is horrible at this one of the things came in a separate order and they never told me when it shipped. A shame they’ve taken over the sports shopping world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Got a big reminder today that THE FIGHT IS FINISHED!!!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-13 22:37:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-12 03:56:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that BOOMER? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-10 08:48:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> New jumbotrons making me excited for my next game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-09 20:49:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Theres a red version of the hat with world series champions in blue if you dug a little deeper on the website so i’m happy with that cause I share your opinion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-08 02:35:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://rover.ebay.com/rover/0/0/0?mpre=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ebay.com%2Fulk%2Fitm%2F392520130884

https://rover.ebay.com/rover/0/0/0?mpre=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ebay.com%2Fulk%2Fitm%2F233378683928

Still have nats fever sorry for baseball jerseys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 07:19:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> !wave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 06:47:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> !wave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 16:25:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> REMEMBER WHERE YOU ARE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is this a legit Nationals jersey? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 16:23:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 16:22:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://rover.ebay.com/rover/0/0/0?mpre=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ebay.com%2Fulk%2Fitm%2F323964070698
Not a hockey jersey but does anyone like the nats? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-31 00:14:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aside from his actions as a manager which haven’t been horrible but definitely not stellar, the optics and effect of his last two statements are so bad! Saying his players aren’t fast enough to compete with opposition. Even if they aren’t, come on there’s work to do then! And then he said that the best fans in the league aren’t his own fans!? He was the manager at Frankfurt but you DO NOT say that when you’re managing a club! Its horrible publicly and turns fans and players against him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 02:13:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean at least make the signs [realistic...](https://www.google.com/search?q=dan+synder+fan+sign&tbm=isch&ved=2ahUKEwj9uYGHpcDlAhULkFkKHfl1C8UQ2-cCegQIABAC&oq=dan+synder+fan+sign&gs_l=mobile-gws-wiz-img.3..33i10.15090.17387..17593...0.0..0.108.881.9j2......0....1.........30i10j0i13.L0fQc7kvpYQ&ei=FpK3Xf3WIIug5gL5662oDA&bih=551&biw=375&prmd=insv&rlz=1CDGOYI_enUS722US722&safe=strict&hl=en-US#imgrc=AZgTEg-kfKxggM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 02:08:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why cant we just play Javi at the back instead of having an unproven youngster play! Might as well play Mai if you arent going to play Javi but my goodness this is dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Away team has won every game... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-28 05:22:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 05:12:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> !wave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 18:53:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://depop.app.link/SOTF28riT0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 09:22:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A damn shame DCU didnt go with [the cherry blossom](https://www.google.com/search?q=dc+united+away+kit&safe=strict&rlz=1CDGOYI_enUS722US722&hl=en-US&prmd=isnv&sxsrf=ACYBGNTS77zCTRdosUDUIKQGLcdzd-AcZw:1571383271606&source=lnms&tbm=isch&sa=X&ved=2ahUKEwiw59btoqXlAhXGjFkKHUaEBqEQ_AUoAXoECA8QAQ&biw=375&bih=551#imgrc=VHnA3KPdQvN0iM) . So much better than the [white t-shirt ](https://www.google.com/search?q=dc+united+away+kit&safe=strict&rlz=1CDGOYI_enUS722US722&hl=en-US&prmd=isnv&sxsrf=ACYBGNTS77zCTRdosUDUIKQGLcdzd-AcZw:1571383271606&source=lnms&tbm=isch&sa=X&ved=2ahUKEwiw59btoqXlAhXGjFkKHUaEBqEQ_AUoAXoECA8QAQ&biw=375&bih=551#imgrc=5TqC0ApeOIhUPM) that they went with. Big miss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 05:30:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Als is referring to one moment in the past. Als Ich klein war...

Wann is referring to a specific time when something happens or happened. Wann kommt den Zug?

Wenn is everything else (multiple past events and especially hypotheticals). Wenn ich müde bin, schlafe ich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 04:58:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Didnt he also go to dematha? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 17:59:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> !wave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 23:33:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interested in the centennial pm'd u </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-12 08:01:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This result is what should’ve happened but these results have not happened for the US in a while. We’d be beating the Cuba’s of the world 1 or 2 nil or maybe even tie or lose. Of course we can’t judge our progress on this game, but at least we dominated a team we were supposed to dominate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 07:27:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Woo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 23:53:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im not sure they wore it but I think they did. But adidas made a reproduction like they did for the 2018 world cup for the home kit from this year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anywhere I can find a replica 1990 Germany away kit? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 23:41:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://imgur.com/gallery/r6k1u8R

Adidas made a reproduction of this kit a few years ago. Anyone know where I can find one. Size XL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 18:32:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Brand new game with dozens of bugs and downright errors. What a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 18:27:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Danke! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 18:24:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it a limited time one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 18:23:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How’d u get the oktoberfest kit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 20:08:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Redemption time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 07:42:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you happen to do the American junior year? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-12 19:36:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ve been an international student of sorts in Germany (American here) and I’ll share some about the major cities I spent time in!

I would recommend Aachen very highly! I went there for an exchange student program in high school and loved it so much. It’s a real gem that not many people know about. An authentic German experience with enough international presence to help you along. Kind of seems like a blend of both Berlin and Munich in terms of cleanliness, night life, (pontstraße) and history.(Aachener Dom) Much smaller than both Berlin and Munich though. Another plus is that it is close to Cologne and many other cities in the Rheinland.

My family lives in Hamburg and it is quite similar to Berlin but a bit less international. Parts of the city are really beautiful (Hafencity und Blankenese) and the night life of the Reeperbahn is awesome albeit risqué. If you’re into soccer, St. Pauli is something to see. The whole port “vibe” of the city is very charming and the location near both the North and Baltic seas makes for a great but cold beach experience in the summer! Would recommend visiting Lübeck if you like marzipan!

I spent less time in Berlin than in Aachen or Hamburg but I got a feel for the city. It’s a great experience but very international. If you’ve ever been to NYC it seems like that. The history in Berlin is 100% fascinating and the nightlife I can attest to being very cool. If you’re going for international then Berlin is perfect for you! If not Berlin is the least “German” city in Germany

My dream is to go to Munich (American FCB fan here) so I’ll encourage you in that but I’ve never been there sadly!

Viel Glück und Viel Spaß!

(TL;DR) Aachen: hidden gem, very german Hamburg: great vibe and nightlife, less international than berlin Berlin: International, fantastic history and night life, less “German” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 00:58:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to run circles around my house in the exact same way and one day a drawer was left open and I ran straight into it. That’s how I have this tiny little dent in my forehead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Any Athletic Club Bilbao home kit size XL </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 00:55:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can’t find one in my price range online. Anyone have one they’re willing to sell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-01 23:28:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely interested! Love this sub! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-29 20:25:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They don't even seem prepared for the DCU games. It's not 45 mins for some chicken tenders but it could be close to 20 if you go at a bad time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-29 20:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think this is fantastic. Secures him as a Bayern legend and gives him time to help us win the UCL. If he starts to age down the end of his contract we can/ will have replaced him and he can be an impact super sub. Class is permanent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-29 05:28:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do i decrease the likelihood of it staining? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 23:11:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sweet! Any directions with that or just apply the nail polish remover to the surface. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone know a way to remove a sponsor from a jersey? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 07:49:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want to buy a Bayern kit from last year but I don't like the look of the qatar airways sponsor on the sleeve. Is there a way to take it off? I've heard acetone is a good way but I'm not sure.

Thanks for any help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone know of a way to take off the sleeve sponsor? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 07:47:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-23 19:21:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its a brown name and number that they used for just that season do you think they have them? Whats their contact info? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bayern 2013/14 away “lederhosen” kit numbers </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-23 06:40:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anyone know where I can get one of these? I have the blank shirt but need some numbers to put on it! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 20:47:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Perfect! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 05:18:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks pretty legit but im not 100% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is this kit legit? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 05:15:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I posted this in the legit check thread as well but it seems a little dead. Is this Bayern kit legit? The sellers ratings check out but he’s selling multiple sizes so thats always questionable.

[link here](https://rover.ebay.com/rover/0/0/0?mpre=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ebay.com%2Fulk%2Fitm%2F323573515506) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 05:13:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this Bayern kit legit? I checked the seller and he seems reputable, but selling multiple sizes is always iffy

https://rover.ebay.com/rover/0/0/0?mpre=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ebay.com%2Fulk%2Fitm%2F323573515506 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 06:41:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2014 home also 2017 third kit although I don’t have anyone on the back of them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 06:39:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmm I have a liverpool kit also a few bayern shirts i’d be willing to part with </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 06:38:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are you looking for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 06:37:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I may be interested in this! Can you link a picture? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 00:59:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe not rocket league but FIFA made me drive into the triangle intersection on r/idiotsincars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 00:54:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They look like adidas soccer socks if you want some you can easily find and maybe play some footy in ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-14 00:52:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think they compliment each other very well with Bob being a classic voice and play by play and FP being the color commentator who is hilarious (and makes some good points)! I don’t see why people don’t like them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-13 23:54:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought Xabi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-13 14:20:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a Mehmet Scholl version of this jersey! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-13 14:19:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think so! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-13 14:13:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ding ding! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-13 06:04:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dang I have that one already! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Looking Bayern, Germany, DC United, and USA shirts! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-13 05:33:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a size large or XL (leaning towards XL) looking for kits or anything else you may have!

Preferably vintage or  a few years older

Willing to pay through venmo or paypal!

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-06 06:37:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You’re new trunk comes with vents! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-06 06:36:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We just need to string a few wins together and all of this talk will go away. Think of the beginning of this season! Although I think Olsen’s ceiling is being competitive and then disappointing in the playoffs (last year) and his worst is the 2 wins in 10 streak we’ve been on now. I think its time for a new manager but all hope is NOT lost! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-05 08:02:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is the DCU away kit still available? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-05 05:50:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3 man back line is one thing, but how it was put in place was horrible. Watching the defense shift was so bad. I totally agree. Only play a 3 man back line if you have the players to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-05 05:30:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Deposit that into my bank account thank you very much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This is bad </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-05 05:17:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-03 15:49:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You here a sound </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 02:58:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is what I was about to say. The pilot is one of my favorites </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 01:29:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its fantastic! Also all the 30 for 30s and shows all in one place. At first it seemed like espn plus was taking stuff that used to be free and making it cost money but it has certainly upped its game! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-29 22:43:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dont u mean inSANÉ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-26 22:49:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Polos have a huge spectrum imo. A great polo can look amazing but bad ones are horrid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-26 20:55:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Moving Pictures by Rush! The hits are amazing but the deep tracks tell cool stories! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 05:43:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Listen to good time boys it changed my life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-19 23:19:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bUt BaYeRn R tHe eVil EmPiRe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-19 23:17:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If he said “I’m transferring to Bayern next year” that would be bad for his next season with Leverkusen. I like his class ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-19 23:15:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He reminds me of lucho when he first came here. He needs to find his feet and he will be a beast (hopefully with a better attitude) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-15 07:40:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw it early at a store in the US and was underwhelmed, but as a full kit it looks pretty clean. I think it shoulda been white with red accents instead of grey though. 7/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-11 02:10:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sports jerseys. Not up to huge collector amount yet but I definitely have way too many </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-09 04:56:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was lucky enough to see this game in person. Going to a skins game in Baltimore though made me hate fedex that much more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-09 04:54:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So the Red Bulls have 3 real rivals now /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-04 20:14:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BERNAAAA-DINAAAA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 06:59:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shredddd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-30 06:51:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to do that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-29 18:46:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pm’d </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-28 02:18:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea! Taken at Tysons mall! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ran out of paint </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-26 02:00:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-23 23:22:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get some chubbies! They’re perfect for us big ass and thigh guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-23 07:53:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are the posters inside? I would love a few! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-22 20:44:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously, we need to replace Ribery and Robben in our attack. Having Werner would definitely help that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-21 02:47:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What shirts go with [these shorts?](https://imgur.com/gallery/hfGLqux) I normally wear vintage looking graphic tees with them but I’m feeling a switch. I’m going for a vintage/skater look. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are some good shirts to wear with adidas shorts? (link below for the shorts) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-21 02:44:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are some good shirts that go with Adidas shorts? (I’ve linked the ones I have below) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-21 01:33:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-20 18:03:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Coman and Gnabry can't get injured too. We need Sané so bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-20 18:02:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope so too! Assuming we bring in some signings (i'm hoping) he'll have the chance to create his own culture instead of having one left over from Pep and Ancelotti. Also managers aren't given enough time these days so we shall see! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-19 22:28:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 40€ is a good price tag but unfortunately we’re not going to land someone who can replace him   :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-19 18:02:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He and Pavard were bright spots for VfB this season but signing two defenders from a team that was relegated.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-18 01:50:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really love their new uniforms and colors (although they need purple) but their logo is atrocious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-15 03:34:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please no :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-30 07:21:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God was having the best game of his life... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-30 07:19:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spaghettieis!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-30 05:25:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m not necessarily opposed to a bar area. But right there?! It looks so bad and obstructs the view! This would be a sham! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-21 20:36:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Playlist followed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-21 00:05:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel that if he wants to make a quick stop at Bayern like Wagner did, it could work. But considering the other signings being thrown around (Werner this year, Havertz next year) that spot on the bench will be filled up quick. If he wants an extended stay and lots of games i’d say this is a no. Saying that, I would love to see some Kruse bangers for bayern! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-20 21:29:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How Hamid is not on the roster after his performance against Toronto and his play this season is beyond me. Shows that he’ll never get his chance :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-20 15:18:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was there too!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-18 19:47:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-18 18:29:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stuff of dreams that he and Robben both scored! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-13 04:05:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Phenomenal from Arriola for the goal and how he busted his ass the whole game. Also Hamid with the saves and SKC showed some grit! Overall great game to attend! Especially being a wet rat right now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-13 04:02:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely beautiful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-13 03:48:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go Nats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 21:15:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-08 17:57:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pleaaaaseee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-07 17:53:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wear my newer ones for gamedays but my older ones for style ;) along with my DFB jerseys I probably have one for every day of the week (for 2 weeks tho). Its true, you can never have enough jerseys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-07 05:06:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have wayy to many bayern kits! Of the ones I have 2 Müllers, 1 kimmich, 1 Mehmet Scholl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-07 00:19:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its the footy headlines one, they pretty much always get it 90% right. Hopefully theres some white accents that they missed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-06 06:07:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Proud to say I saw this live #vamos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 07:47:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not sure if your into sports, but I love jerseys! When your team is playing/won the day before they're fun to wear as well as a style item! I have a bunch of vintage jerseys, new jerseys, and accessories (hats, jackets, etc.) from all the teams I support! Not the most helpful tip but, a simple improvement! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-04 22:11:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I need to replace the stylus and cartridge for my Pioneer PL-518X. I’m not sure which stylus replacement I need to buy, and how to replace it properly! I’m not sure of the specifics of this turntable as I just got it as its a real vintage piece. Can anyone help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I need to replace the stylus and cartridge for my new turntable and I’m not sure how! Anything helps! Thanks! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-04 22:07:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-02 03:42:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lets hope they turn back the clock this year.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-30 22:14:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ve done this before haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-30 16:33:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That means i’m almost 20.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-30 16:31:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/hockeyjerseys is probs your place. That’s where I’ve found my caps grails ;) although you may have to search for a while. Goodluck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-29 18:53:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think i’m more B1-B2 I plan on ordering Tschick! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-29 18:49:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plan on ordering it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-29 18:49:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ll have to look! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-29 18:49:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I try to read Sport Bild whenever I can because I’m into The bundesliga :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-29 18:48:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! I’m planning on ordering Die Verwandlung (english-german parallel) to start, along with Grimms Märchen and Tschick. Does that sound good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are some good books to get to keep learning German? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-29 08:55:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm in college in the USA and I'm about to enter meine Semesterpause and would like to keep up on my Deutsch!

I'm about to enter higher level German so intermediate-high level books should be a nice challenge that wont be too hard.

What are some books/short stories I can read? I've looked online and the short story books like Café in Berlin seem to beginner-level for me. Are there intermediate level short stories out there? Also any guides/textbook like books would be useful!

Danke! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone know if Adidas Spezials are a good look/any other thoughts? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-27 08:26:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-26 23:23:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow a few weeks back i wouldve droped dead knowing somebody had 3. But i got my Ovi grail a little bit ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-26 17:50:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ecosia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-26 09:26:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bumass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-25 21:07:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love it but its opposite to what our kits should be... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-25 21:06:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wowowowow dream jersey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-24 07:58:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I stay away from that place. People are gunna see whatever they want to see </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-24 07:34:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> LETS GO -Jesse Pollack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-24 07:31:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm very nervous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> VEGAS BLEW A 3-1 LEAD UPVOTE PARTY!!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-24 07:26:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-24 05:30:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sharks east fan coming to send grit to you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-23 21:26:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The last time Hagelin went up against Williams in a game 7 we all know what happened... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-23 05:59:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think It can work both ways! If Ovi channels his frustration into scoring 2 goals in game 7 then it works but if the caps get a bunch of shitty penalties then maybe not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-23 00:17:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sweet sweeet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-22 23:37:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WHO ELSE WILL BE GRITTING IT OUT AT BDUBS TONITE? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> LETS TAKE IT IN 6! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-22 23:35:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-22 23:24:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got one too! Mine's an ovi tho ;) still happy for ya. I know how hard this experience was </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-22 20:42:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’d be so noice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-22 08:05:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Danke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-22 07:47:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha sorry mein Amerikaner slang. An overview or summary I'll edit now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Transfer Rumors </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-22 07:23:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can someone give me an overview on where we reportedly are with transfer targets?

Werner, CHO, Pepe, Brandt, Havertz, Sane? players leaving etc.

Would love a good discussion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-22 05:30:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was thinkin he’d be pissed and play well :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> We haven't played well today and we deserve some criticism but... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 23:50:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Taylor Twellman has spent the entire game ripping us and saying our attack is nothing without Acosta when he leaves etc etc. We've been bad today but its all that I hear from him. Just annoying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What the deal with the turquoise kits? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 23:16:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 22:50:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Playoff hockey for $112 aint bad either 10/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 08:08:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand some of the older stuff just cause it's less "mainstream", but anything off stadium arcadium being hated i just dont understand. esp. this song </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Checkin in with the chel view from section 424! GET THIS GRIT! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 02:46:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-20 16:43:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I DROVE ONE HOUR TOWARDS HOME YESTERDAY BUT FORGOT MY OSHIE JERSEY SO I HAD TO GO BACK AND GET IT CAUSE I’M GOING TO THE GAME! THATS SOME GRIT FOR YA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> WE GOTTA BELIEVE! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-20 06:10:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WE'VE BEEN HERE BEFORE! SO WE DROPPED TWO GAMES, WE GOTTA WIN OUR HOME GAMES AND WE GOT THIS! SO WHAT OSHIE IS OUT, WE GOT DSP FLYIN IN HOTTER THAN HIS GOAL IN VEGAS! NEXT MAN UP BABY!

LETS GO! LETS AVENGE OUR OSHBABE! RELEASE THE WILSON ONTO FOEGELE!

I DON'T WANT TO HEAR NEGATIVITY! WE GOTTA BELIEVE!

DO YOU LIKE MY ALL CAPS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-20 05:42:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-20 05:38:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate the pens and gradients. But this jersey is my only exception. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-20 01:36:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw im 424 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-19 18:48:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 16:27:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We’ll finally get to be on the winning side of a Kirk Cousins prime time performance... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 16:18:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Both teams missed wide open nets in that OT. Glad I tuned in just in time haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 07:51:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looking for the cheapest tickets possible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-17 07:44:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry you're bday was ruined but I'm laughing at your sadness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-17 06:53:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You called it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bayern Insta says "no worries" to our worst fears! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-16 20:37:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-16 20:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's gunna be a Bayern lifer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-16 07:27:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Blankenese is a really underrated place! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-16 07:23:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Listening to them as I scrolled to this 👀 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 08:07:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get really fat because of all the mozarella bites from sheetz I have to eat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 07:50:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats your lowest price one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-14 17:16:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-14 07:46:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can someone ELI5 the different reebok and adidas jerseys. What the different ones are called (authentic vs. replica) and how they're different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Grail day featuring my playoff shrine and an overtime win! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-14 06:57:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-13 08:54:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does the milk last as long?

edit: I just "that what she said" myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-13 04:35:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone’s frustrated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 15:52:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 06:44:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you want more jerseys check out r/hockeyjerseys but wallets beware </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 06:38:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You need a Scherzer and Beal. Also Rooney for good measure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 19:56:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And I was excited when I got my screaming eagle for $75.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-10 18:54:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe if we're really lacking or someone gets injured, but he's probably gunna stay with Hershey. esp. cause they in the Calder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-09 19:47:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://m.imgur.com/gallery/ilbHfnl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-09 04:13:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What was the “audi field effect” last year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-09 00:16:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pm’d </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone selling a Caps stadium series size L or XL? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-08 18:38:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-07 19:42:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When its playoff hockey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-07 19:37:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you really work on your accent then most people will reply in German! But if you have an obvious accent then younger people may reply in english. It depends on the person and region you’re in. In Aachen, where I was, I spoke German with almost everyone (ordering food, getting bus tickets, simple conversation etc.) but for more complicated stuff resorted to english (like when I got busted for not buying a bus ticket, i pulled the American foreigner card lol). In Berlin since its very international, or bigger cities in general you’ll get more English. Good luck! Also pick German!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-06 13:16:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love you’re collection! If you’re ever selling lmk haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-05 06:38:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the stuff of dreams. Puts my mini caps collection to shame!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-05 00:56:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw this but do you know if its legit? I can’t find it anywhere else and they seem to have every size... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-05 00:38:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ball out with Rooney learn even more from him win a cup boom to europe u go  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone know somewhere I can get this hoodie? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 07:26:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 07:25:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SOng is a bop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I love our fans! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-03 18:46:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-03 17:28:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vielen dank!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-03 07:09:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m in a class doing relativpronomen so it requires a 100% knowledge of it which I don’t have! I’ll look at videos and stuff and practice everyday and in class obviously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is there a secret to akkusativ und dativ? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-03 06:03:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty good at it but if you have a better way to remember it then shoot it my way!

Of course, practice and memorization are what is required, but I'm looking for tips!

Danke! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-03 04:34:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sit down  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-03 01:19:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ocean spray cranberry sauce colored </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 22:39:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “That’s one big bison!” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's the style of this sweater called? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 06:34:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-30 17:42:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you’re from DC sure haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-30 15:19:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-30 06:54:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I currently take German in college and I use “Sag Mal” i’d say its 8/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 23:03:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 18:22:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just a question. What position does he/ will he play? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 06:33:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same night as the Caps earning their playoff berth! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> CAPS CLINCH PLAYOFF BERTH UPDOOT PARTY!!!!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 02:27:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-28 19:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hush hush ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-28 15:08:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any thrift store  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-28 07:12:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I noticed the numbers look a little darker but it could be the lighting. Also it's from Ukraine and I saw a few fakes from there when I looked up the jersey on ebay.

Danke! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-28 07:10:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just add Brandt, Havertz, and Werner :0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-27 14:08:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fisher in the background 👀 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-27 13:41:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For a blue caps screaming eagle which is best u think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-27 04:33:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which jersey customizer is best for taking off numbers/nameplate and recustomizing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-26 23:19:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sexyyy! I need this one for my caps collection I just got blue screaming eagle though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-26 23:18:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about the ESPN+ blackout range? I’m in harrisonburg and I’m blacked out i think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Where can I get a customized jersey? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-26 04:41:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For some reason I can't find a website where I can customize jerseys! I've tried my usual sites: [worldsoccershop.com](https://worldsoccershop.com)  and [soccer.com](https://soccer.com) and looked at the official site and I can't find one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-25 17:40:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please watch Dark! It's kinda like stranger things but 3X more intense. Also, its on netflix! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-25 05:08:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would be watching if Flo didn't exist... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-24 05:20:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wah! wah! wah! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-23 14:56:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All he’s gotta say is that he’s a 20 goal scorer and other teams have to injure him or play dirty back to stop him ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 14:27:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never been amazed by the Caps' aways but this is hot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 14:25:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have the Caps Backy too! Two hot pieces right there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 07:05:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Meat on the table (Ryback)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 05:19:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like how they aren’t “lowering” themselves. If theres lower attendance make it cheaper and create new fans. Its not embarrassing lol idk why clubs are so stuck up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 20:52:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got this too  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 16:02:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And it looks like we were just as active but either a few votes or MLS tipped the scales </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 03:36:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought Orlov just never challenged Hedman on the last play... turns out he literally fell over and died </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-20 18:06:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-20 17:33:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could you link a picture of it. I'm not a subscriber. I saw one on footyheadlines that looked dope, if its the same one.

Edit: Its the same one, still disappointed that I can't buy it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-20 16:55:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Brandt, Havertz, Werner, we need some new German kids on the block </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-15 15:43:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats what mine used to look like. I got home from school to see it bulldozed and their building a new one now. Damn shame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 19:39:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sergei Gonchar wore #55 for the Caps but he also wore #4 for a season. I’m getting a jersey with the number 4 but i’m taking off the custom name and putting Gonchar on it. I know if he wore it its not foul but would it be weird? I was thinking it would be cool to have a different one thats still legit but just looking for thoughts. [This link ](https://www.hockey-reference.com/teams/WSH/1999.html) shows he wore #4 but also Alexei Tezikov did too. Does anyone know why this is?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 17:25:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sweet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 04:58:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m just seeing the new away as like a training kit tbh so i dont mind it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Will they sell long sleeve blank white tees at the stadium? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 03:41:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m not in love with the away kit but a long sleeve training top look alike would be kinda sexy 👀 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 03:30:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beauties </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 03:29:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can a customizer take off the just name plate of a jersey and add a new one? Found a personalized jersey with someones name on it. Figured it’d be cheaper to get this one and get it recustomized (cause the number still applies)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 02:31:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hehehe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 02:06:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kucherov caps? I’d never buy that haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 01:59:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dang i gotta shave some pounds then hehe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 01:57:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel the pain too i’m in college so i’m a broke boi too  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 01:53:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trueee i kinda have a rule that i only buy jerseys with names on em they’re just cooler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 01:45:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too! I need the SS (obv), the away one, blue screaming eagle, and capitol building. I’m counting winter classic 2011 and current alternate as the home and away ones from the old days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 00:06:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pm’d </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 00:00:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Big ego 🤪 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 23:59:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Worth a shot enjoy my grail 😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 19:25:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do they know what address to send them to tho? #theyknow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 17:56:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wanna sell it to me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 16:14:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love the album! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 13:44:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I go here! Maybe i’ve met you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 05:43:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The pain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Looking for Caps stadium series </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 00:48:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Size L or XL

Send me offers! I'm sick of seeing all the fakes on ebay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-12 19:22:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly both of you guys are right! We’re doing so well right now despite of how utterly broken the FO is. Almost every decision reeks of incompetence but somehow we have a great team with great fans and a beautiful stadium! Who knows how much better we’d be (as a club) with an FO that knows what they’re doing. Despite that, I’ll take what we have even with the issues. Vamos! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-11 04:33:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3 games... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-09 07:06:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you lose at least 6 games, you’re better off in the long run losing 7 more. No more no less.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-09 04:21:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good as in “i’m good” its clearly outside but its close is what i meant lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-09 00:30:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Harrisonburg is so close i think i’m good though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-09 00:28:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It might be listed but it’ll say when you click on it that its “not available in your area” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 19:19:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sweet thanks man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 19:19:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll just wait and see thanks man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 19:08:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You think it works? I just got the espn + free trial cause i saw the next dc games on there. I’ll try the vpn for games that arent listed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 19:06:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about In the Shenandoah Valley. I’m at school and i’ll just go to games in person when im at home in the DMV haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Are all MLS (DCU) matches streamed on MLS live with ESPN plus? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 18:30:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 16:30:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ATL has been on the precipice of defeat for an eternity! UNITE with DC and shut them out just like Saturday!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 09:24:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess i’ll just stick to the team Leonsis actually cares about running. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 07:48:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This would be the dumbest move of all time they better let that man retire in the booth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-04 20:12:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I meaaaaannn he’s played in Europe and he’s been GK of the year in MLS before. He’s just entered his prime. The only GKs that anyone can say are better are Howard and Guzan. Howard isnt in the mix and Guzan is gettin older. Hamid has a point  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-04 18:24:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats hotttt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-01 17:50:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So he knew Boateng was gunna fall down the whole time?! I cry... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-01 17:41:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We’ll see about that but I like the attitude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-01 17:41:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Onlyyy thing we can complain about is 3rd period (late) goals. Without those we’d probably have an even better record. Dw we’re goin back to backkk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-01 06:41:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will this album be very available or does it being a RSD release change anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-28 21:50:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-28 18:10:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep that was it. It was almost a breaking point but hey happy mems just a year after :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ISO Caps stadium series jersey (preferably blank) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-28 05:26:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Size Large or XL

Shoot me any SS but probably blank cause i'm a broke boi :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-28 03:02:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Our system has been broken for years. Still half tiki taka and (other than Lewi) relying on aging talent. I love this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-28 01:17:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love the Pedro and the Caps! How much u get the screaming eagle for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-25 20:29:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have it as my background. This is the next best thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-25 05:22:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where can I get a Caps 2018 stadium series jersey? (preferably on the cheaper side) Every single one online is fake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-25 05:20:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most of the kids just cheer for their parents' teams. Being a recent high school grad is my source. So many pennsylvania fans I wanna puke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-24 17:05:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love it! Did you get them new or not? I always look for them at stores but I can never find em. What I have found is their EP and a money for nothing and love over gold (live) west german 45 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-23 07:09:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sweeeeet! I'm about 1/10th of ur level but I play bass. I've learned the opening to highway tune! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-23 07:03:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [**https://www.ebay.com/itm/Alexander-Ovechkin-8-Washington-Capitals-Stadium-Series-NHL-Jersey/192833594916?hash=item2ce5c72624:m:mbBlHkQwN9Iw8e93y\_r74hg:rk:1:pf:1&frcectupt=true**](https://www.ebay.com/itm/Alexander-Ovechkin-8-Washington-Capitals-Stadium-Series-NHL-Jersey/192833594916?hash=item2ce5c72624:m:mbBlHkQwN9Iw8e93y_r74hg:rk:1:pf:1&frcectupt=true)

**I'm thinkin fake but worth a shot** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-23 06:24:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lookin sexy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-23 06:17:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jeeeezz bands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Trade rumors? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-22 14:49:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who’s comin? Who’s goin? Is there something I (we all) don’t know that you do?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-22 14:32:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Class act </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-22 14:25:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gotta love liberty? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-21 19:33:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guys got flow what more can u ask for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-21 17:15:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dana Scully? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-21 16:46:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just ordered a finals patch and put it on my jersey. Seems to be the easier way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-21 06:18:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This! Kahn the crazy and unexpected, Lahm the cool working behind the scenes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-19 20:58:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-19 17:37:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Swweeet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-18 15:14:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do this too dw ur fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-18 15:11:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's on the sleeve chill ur beans  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-18 15:04:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doooo it we need wingers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-18 07:42:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahaaaaaa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-18 07:42:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-18 07:41:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doesn't help we got boatraced by the Ducks tonite :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-17 21:23:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Danggg i wish! Gotta get the greatest hits one and the anthology! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-17 17:50:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw man! Its a red jean jacket so i’m doing mostly modern and really old caps stuff. I’ll let u know though thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-17 07:08:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A Cup easy. The game is about winning. You can be the best goal scorer ever and never win a cup (what many thought Ovi would do before our babe came home). I want 2,3,4 and the goal record will come along with 'em. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-17 07:00:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We're the only team that has that big of a drop from making the playoffs to winning the cup. Carolina with less odds to make the playoffs, but higher odds to win the cup? Does whoever made this know how the playoffs work? We have the smallest percentage of all realistic playoff contenders to win the cup. Even the Wild and (never won a playoff series) Columbus have "better odds". This says we're on par with the Habs but even they are higher than us. This chart is BS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-17 06:46:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is tasty

&#x200B;

&#x200B; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-17 02:50:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I found a retro one on ebay for $10! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anywhere I can find the front crest of a caps jersey? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-17 00:18:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m making a caps jean jacket by putting caps patches all over it. I want to put a jerset crest on the back. If I could get my hands on the front crest from the old red or white jerseys (preferably) or a modern jersey i’d be hype! Anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-16 22:28:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What record? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-15 22:55:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dorm room is too small :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-15 22:55:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t go to BC so at least thats cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-15 22:54:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yess. Got it cause I love Vrana </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-15 21:30:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sweeet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-15 20:25:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /u/phelpstheory on this sub just scrollin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-15 20:24:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I forgot your username so I didnt shout u out haha. I commented on ur post! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-15 17:06:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My first Adidas and Under Armour. Also my first international and college. Also my first non caps jerseys! I’d say I picked up some heat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My floor’s not so clean but these jerseys are. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-15 17:05:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> OSHBABE 500th POINT UPVOTE PARTYYY!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-15 06:56:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-13 14:48:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The caps better do a chinatown one! I always loved the Wiz jerseys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-12 22:27:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-12 16:59:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey thanks man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-12 16:58:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m breaking the bank hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-12 16:57:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got the same shoes yeet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-12 16:57:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish more jerseys like this existed. If i EVER see one of these its an”must cop” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-12 07:39:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dm’d </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone have a Germany 2018 Olympic jersey for sale? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-12 06:24:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Size L or XL

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-11 01:33:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Given by the amount of Pens/Knights jerseys an Ovi should be your next mailday hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-09 08:01:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like it but they ripped off sb nation hard lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Easiest way to make alot of cash? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-09 07:54:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im in Spring year 2 on a standard farm. Just picked the game back up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-08 22:12:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Abc 7 DC? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-08 17:08:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Off the players, it is... so bad 0/10. On the players its... better still bad though 5/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-08 07:18:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Justice is swift </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> FLY THE BIRD BABYYYYY!!!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-08 03:51:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> KUZZYYYYYY!! He's really killin it right now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-08 03:35:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These quick whistles are killin us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-08 03:30:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone explain why Wilson was ejected but Cole wasn't. Willy was sticking up for his teammate! Everyone would be out for Wilson's head if he pulled what Cole just did. He'd be so far ejected and suspended.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-08 02:35:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree. What he needs is PT in Hershey not a bench spot in the NHL. Djoos back on saturday (maybe) will be good. Siegenthaler gotta stay up for the scratch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Do you think Burakovsky will be traded before the deadline? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-07 05:43:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If so, what/who will we get in return.

Gimme legit rumors or just spitballin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-07 04:31:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But what if he’s a beast tho? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-06 22:46:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I looked and its good enough for me. As long as it doesn’t look horrible I think its fine. I’ve wanted a Vrana jersey for a while (caps fan here) and the jerseys he has worn are almost identical (minus the WCH trim). Also who the heck has that! Its unique and not a caps jersey but still the right colors. I’d say there are greater sins of jersey foul.  I’m just explaining my thoughts lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-06 22:43:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think its more like putting say Eller on a reebok caps jersey. Not switching teams here. Can you tell me if the jersey is relatively the same to one he wore?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-06 22:13:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! How bad of a jersey foul tho? Just wondering haha. Have czech changed their jerseys much since then?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-06 21:22:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3 questions:
Where can I get legit customization for WCH Czech jersey?
Did Jakub Vrana play in the WCH?
If not...
Would it be jersey foul to get him on a WCH jersey?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-06 21:06:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Read your comment about the seller immediately searched him up! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-06 20:22:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you/Damn you for posting this! Rip my bank account! Just bought one. Been looking a czech republic jersey for a while! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-06 19:49:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was not touched at all idek what their talking about! It looks like Kuzy is flailing his stick to no avail. Was not touched. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Vrana from behind the back board! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-06 06:18:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Funniest shit i've seen all year [https://youtu.be/u096eiyrYlY?t=560](https://youtu.be/u096eiyrYlY?t=560) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-05 08:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that North Korea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-04 16:50:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That doing whatever makes you feel good is the best way to go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-03 19:38:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> key bridge babyyyy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-31 05:54:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [https://www.ebay.com/itm/2006-Alexander-Ovechkin-Washington-Capitals-Black-Jersey-Size-Mens-Large-/323667785133](https://www.ebay.com/itm/2006-Alexander-Ovechkin-Washington-Capitals-Black-Jersey-Size-Mens-Large-/323667785133)

[https://www.ebay.com/itm/Vintage-NHL-Washington-Capitals-hockey-Jersey-Adult-XL/202576295721?hash=item2f2a7cf729:g:meYAAOSwVAtcS6YD:rk:1:pf:0](https://www.ebay.com/itm/Vintage-NHL-Washington-Capitals-hockey-Jersey-Adult-XL/202576295721?hash=item2f2a7cf729:g:meYAAOSwVAtcS6YD:rk:1:pf:0)

[**https://www.ebay.com/itm/CCM-Washington-Capitals-Stadium-Hockey-Jersey-XL-Black-Vintage-1999/323663601435?hash=item4b5bda9f1b:g:0H8AAOSwxqtcN4t0:rk:34:pf:0**](https://www.ebay.com/itm/CCM-Washington-Capitals-Stadium-Hockey-Jersey-XL-Black-Vintage-1999/323663601435?hash=item4b5bda9f1b:g:0H8AAOSwxqtcN4t0:rk:34:pf:0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-31 04:24:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Looking for caps stadium series </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-30 06:13:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anyone got an adidas size 52 or 54?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-30 06:11:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just ew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-29 20:48:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. Ovi, Kuzy, Backy, Holtby, Oshie, Carlson, Wilson to name a few (couldn't stick to 3, gave u the essentials)
2. Backstrom. I read somewhere that he has the highest assist total since he entered the league and most people don't think he's all that good.... (not sure of the source but the point stands)
3. Not really... maybe Burakovsky though lol I don't like him too much.
4. Jakub Vrana. JAKE THE SNAKE! He's an absolute hoss! Our second leading scorer and the future!
5. Dudes and Babes (what we call each other and Ovi calls everyone babe), "not suck back to back" (ovi and oshie said those at the stanley cup parade) Wednesday frog (you'll see). Stanley Cup champion Tom Wilson.
6. Strengths: one of the best rosters in the league. Our offense is filthy. We seem to have an awesome team culture and they seem to love each other and the fans.  Weaknesses: INCONSISTENCY and our D definitely needs a boost. Recently Holtby the backup Copely have been shaky. We're on a 7 game losing streak lol
7. Rock the red babyyyyy. Won our first cup last year (duh) we've been to the Stanley cup twice (first time 1997 got swept by the Red Wings)

Hope this helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-29 20:32:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Orpik is your batya  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-29 05:02:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Capital one arena. Pretty penny though :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-29 03:21:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Roolll dukkkess! I was wondering if someone would mention! Pic taken in my dorm! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-28 22:47:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yes! Huge! We gotta prove ourselves again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-28 22:46:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ayyee i bought that pin on ebay a little bit ago! The circle with the screaming eagle! Makes my backpack look so much sexier! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-28 22:45:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There’s hope isnt there? Dont jump ship just yet!We’ve been through worse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-28 22:42:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> USD Whoops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Jumping on this Caps Cap hypetrain! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-28 22:39:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Montreal Canadiens jersey for sale! Adidas authentic Size 46 $70 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-28 22:35:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-27 17:08:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And ultra balls 😏 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-26 06:28:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got a Backy for xmas. My fav jersey ever! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-25 04:58:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Solid top 4 D plsss we need </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-24 23:38:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well we’re about even with them right now so what if we round out the season like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Calm it down </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-24 18:30:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate this losing streak as much as you. I love watching the Caps win and I live on highlight repeats on youtube of the Caps winning. But even though we have lost 7 in a row. Here's the bright side.

We're still 2nd in the division!

All star break we can get some rest and work the kinks out

We went on this kind of slump last year and we all know what happened.

All this talk about firing Reirdan and not making the playoffs in nonsense.

R-E-L-A-X </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-24 06:03:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cry so much  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-22 17:13:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sweeeet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-19 00:51:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now its just hitler conspiracies and aliens. Or both! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-14 16:53:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We want em to write us off 👏👏👏 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-14 07:43:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sweet collection. Shame about the team, but I got 5 Caps jerseys that look like the yin to your yang! Started collecting in 2018 too ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-14 07:10:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anything "need my coffee" related. Shirts or travel mugs that say "don't talk to me before my morning coffee". They're just weird and not funny at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-14 07:04:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This

&#x200B; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-13 21:41:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats true but at least the bad lines fit in with everything being bad lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-13 21:27:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yupp ;) I saw $70 for an adidas and i pounced! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-13 20:05:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Concessions is craaazy! The lines are ridiculous at halftime!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-13 20:00:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://rover.ebay.com/rover/0/0/0?mpre=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ebay.com%2Fulk%2Fitm%2F132904982348 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-13 18:50:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eww </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-13 08:06:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [https://www.ebay.com/itm/Vintage-KOHO-Montreal-Canadiens-Red-Retro-NHL-Jersey-Size-Adult-XL/264115476754?hash=item3d7e825912:g:5FUAAOSwOShcLS6q:rk:22:pf:0](https://www.ebay.com/itm/Vintage-KOHO-Montreal-Canadiens-Red-Retro-NHL-Jersey-Size-Adult-XL/264115476754?hash=item3d7e825912:g:5FUAAOSwOShcLS6q:rk:22:pf:0)

Do Koho's run big?

[https://www.ebay.com/itm/Authentic-Reebok-Montreal-Canadiens-Hockey-Jersey/173376523719?hash=item285e0bcdc7:m:mZxR5kTes44uGIuVyqLO8hA:rk:52:pf:0](https://www.ebay.com/itm/Authentic-Reebok-Montreal-Canadiens-Hockey-Jersey/173376523719?hash=item285e0bcdc7:m:mZxR5kTes44uGIuVyqLO8hA:rk:52:pf:0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-13 07:53:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pm'd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-13 07:27:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Woah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-13 07:24:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Put those losers in their place. ready for another first round exit Columbus? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-12 17:22:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same batch of bud light that Oshbabe chugged through his shirt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cheapest Habs Jersey </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-12 08:49:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Size Large or XL

Cheapest one ya got! Send it my way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-12 08:43:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been looking for cheap Habs jerseys and this was so close yet so far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-12 08:42:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude I got so excited but I wear a large :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-12 08:35:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interested in Caps teal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-12 08:30:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Boston college jersey for $30? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-12 08:27:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interested about USA jersey! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-12 08:25:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pm'd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-09 08:18:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [https://www.ebay.com/itm/CCM-Team-Classics-Washington-Capitals-Vintage-Hockey-Authentic-Jersey-Men-sz-XL/372560926197?hash=item56be5c95f5:g:wAcAAOSwCNlcM8tN:rk:21:pf:0](https://www.ebay.com/itm/CCM-Team-Classics-Washington-Capitals-Vintage-Hockey-Authentic-Jersey-Men-sz-XL/372560926197?hash=item56be5c95f5:g:wAcAAOSwCNlcM8tN:rk:21:pf:0)\\

[http://depop.com/montanaskicks/montanaskicks-montreal-canadiens-hockey-jersey-sz](http://depop.com/montanaskicks/montanaskicks-montreal-canadiens-hockey-jersey-sz)

[https://www.ebay.com/itm/WASHINGTON-CAPITALS-Vintage-NHL-Hockey-Jersey-Screaming-Eagle-Blue-CCM-Large/254059412500?hash=item3b271efc14:g:HasAAOSw\~5ZcNXix](https://www.ebay.com/itm/WASHINGTON-CAPITALS-Vintage-NHL-Hockey-Jersey-Screaming-Eagle-Blue-CCM-Large/254059412500?hash=item3b271efc14:g:HasAAOSw~5ZcNXix) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-09 08:03:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ewww... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-09 06:33:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hes so fricken good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-05 06:26:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely. along with Flames 3rd. so sexy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-05 04:50:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The most bonafide sexy jerseys in the league.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-01 09:11:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 400s are sweet. Its where the real fans are. And if you sit in front of our [beauty](https://www.google.com/search?q=stanley+cup+champions+banner&safe=strict&rlz=1CDGOYI_enUS722US722&hl=en-US&prmd=sinv&source=lnms&tbm=isch&sa=X&ved=2ahUKEwiG5MPykMzfAhVvc98KHWptDsEQ_AUoAnoECBAQAg&biw=375&bih=551#imgrc=OBG9iOpyUD4-1M) it provides a good foreground ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-30 22:42:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont think so. Have you heard if anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone else have this problem with Red Dead 2 on Xbox one? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-30 22:17:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ve been having a lot of problems with the game since i started my 2nd play through. Sometimes the ground doesn’t exist. Sometimes I can play for a while but then people won’t talk and guns morph into people’s arms. Sometimes horses don’t exist either. The game freezes up when I pause and the menu doesn’t come up. Also this can like screw up my Xbox so nothing will click so I have to restart. Does anyone know anything about this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-30 22:12:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats crazy too man! I hope rockstar fixes this. I’ve seen some posts on r/xbox  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-30 17:48:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> !3flair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone else’s RDR2 glitch out and freeze on Xbox One? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-30 17:39:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ve been having a lot of problems with the game since i started my 2nd play through. Sometimes the ground doesn’t exist. Sometimes I can play for a while but then people won’t talk and guns morph into people’s arms. Sometimes horses don’t exist either. The game freezes up when I pause and the menu doesn’t come up. Also this can like screw up my Xbox so nothing will click so I have to restart. Does anyone know anything about this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-30 09:23:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get that baby stitched on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-30 09:23:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd say pretty rare but, its a grail for me thats more of what I meant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-30 09:17:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not too sure but its so sick! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-28 00:18:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty long. I’ve been looking for lowball prices but settled on getting it for xmas ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-27 19:59:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m goin to the game against the preds on the 31st! See you there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-27 07:32:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want to get this for my friend whose a Bolts fan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-27 07:06:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Caps Preds tickets and a Backy 2011 winter classic babes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-27 06:13:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love it hope u love yours! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Grail day a day late </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-27 00:49:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-26 03:54:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love those speakers! I have them with my player in my college dorm and they crank! (Gotten many complaints lol). Just got gifted a HUGE vinyl collection for xmas from a family member who doesn't play them any more. Gunna have to go buy some more edifiers for back home! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-26 00:11:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When does the event usually fire? and how many tries did it take you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 05:59:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [https://www.ebay.com/p/Ccm-Patrick-Roy-Montreal-Canadiens-Red-Heroes-of-Hockey-Alumni-Jersey-L/1332884373?iid=113460893685](https://www.ebay.com/p/Ccm-Patrick-Roy-Montreal-Canadiens-Red-Heroes-of-Hockey-Alumni-Jersey-L/1332884373?iid=113460893685)

[https://www.ebay.com/itm/NEW-MENS-REEBOK-WINTER-CLASSIC-MONTREAL-CANADIENS-HOCKEY-JERSEY-VARIOUS-SIZES-/141945951556](https://www.ebay.com/itm/NEW-MENS-REEBOK-WINTER-CLASSIC-MONTREAL-CANADIENS-HOCKEY-JERSEY-VARIOUS-SIZES-/141945951556) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 05:55:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good deal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 05:50:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are the M&N ones worth buying? I don't know much about them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone know about these Mitchell and Ness jerseys? Are they worth buying? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-24 04:50:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [https://www.ebay.com/itm/Authentic-Washington-Capitals-Hockey-Jersey-Mitchell-Ness-Vintage-Stanley-Cup-/382686646089](https://www.ebay.com/itm/Authentic-Washington-Capitals-Hockey-Jersey-Mitchell-Ness-Vintage-Stanley-Cup-/382686646089)

[https://www.ebay.com/itm/Authentic-Washington-Capitals-Bryan-Watson-Hockey-Jersey-Vintage-Stanley-Cup/202544779494?hash=item2f289c10e6:g:rFoAAOSwsGpcFF44](https://www.ebay.com/itm/Authentic-Washington-Capitals-Bryan-Watson-Hockey-Jersey-Vintage-Stanley-Cup/202544779494?hash=item2f289c10e6:g:rFoAAOSwsGpcFF44) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-23 08:53:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [https://www.ebay.com/itm/Authentic-Washington-Capitals-Hockey-Jersey-Mitchell-Ness-Vintage-Stanley-Cup-/382686646089](https://www.ebay.com/itm/Authentic-Washington-Capitals-Hockey-Jersey-Mitchell-Ness-Vintage-Stanley-Cup-/382686646089)

[https://www.ebay.com/itm/Authentic-Washington-Capitals-Bryan-Watson-Hockey-Jersey-Vintage-Stanley-Cup/202544779494?hash=item2f289c10e6:g:rFoAAOSwsGpcFF44](https://www.ebay.com/itm/Authentic-Washington-Capitals-Bryan-Watson-Hockey-Jersey-Vintage-Stanley-Cup/202544779494?hash=item2f289c10e6:g:rFoAAOSwsGpcFF44)

[https://www.ebay.com/itm/Washington-Capitals-2018-Stadium-Series-Jersey/282886507471?hash=item41dd598bcf:m:meRgm6iVsRNm92Jki8Awb5g](https://www.ebay.com/itm/Washington-Capitals-2018-Stadium-Series-Jersey/282886507471?hash=item41dd598bcf:m:meRgm6iVsRNm92Jki8Awb5g)

[https://www.ebay.com/itm/NHL-8-Alex-Ovechkin-Washington-Capitals-Mens-Jersey-Size-54-XL-Navy-Blue/223290280086?hash=item33fd234896:g:yVgAAOSwMjpcEJXM](https://www.ebay.com/itm/NHL-8-Alex-Ovechkin-Washington-Capitals-Mens-Jersey-Size-54-XL-Navy-Blue/223290280086?hash=item33fd234896:g:yVgAAOSwMjpcEJXM)

[https://www.ebay.com/itm/Ottawa-Senators-1992-2007-Style-CCM-Replica-Jersey-White-Size-XL-/223290989864](https://www.ebay.com/itm/Ottawa-Senators-1992-2007-Style-CCM-Replica-Jersey-White-Size-XL-/223290989864) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-19 21:46:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Convert!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Glitch in the first Uncle mission in the Epilogue pt 2 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-16 07:04:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For some reason when I get off the train in St. Denis one of 3 things have happened. Either, the ground is invisible, the ground is there but with no texture and carriages are drawn by invisible horses, or the ground is fine but the horses are still invisible.

Is it a game issue or an Xbox issue? (I have it on Xbox One).

Is this a problem anyone has had?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-13 07:56:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Size large willing to work on price </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Caps jerseys? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-13 06:01:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looking for Stadium series, Capitol Building, and Blue screaming eagle
Size L
Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-12 16:46:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jeez this is sexy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-10 05:32:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TJ could be back any day but probably later this week early next. He was placed on IR but it was retroactive so no biggie. Willy idk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-07 14:43:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-07 14:18:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where can I listen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-07 14:04:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He’s salty of a stanley cup champion... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-07 04:28:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Niskyyyyyy! Bday goal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-07 04:26:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amen bro my feelings pretty much exactly add on the”show” they put on I hate them all the way up the ladder. I still hate the pens more but only just. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-07 04:15:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does it seem like we’ve been chasing games ever since we started collapsing against the Ducks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-06 18:03:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those would be sweet except the “S” on the shoulder looks dumb  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-06 05:54:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And the Oates jeez i want so bad wish $600 just landed in my lap rn  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-06 05:51:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bondra is the sexiest thing i’ve ever seen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-05 21:51:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Goalz 😍 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-05 06:17:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seems like it at least we dont boo injured players </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-05 06:08:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He asks for id’s at vegas casinos thats his side hustle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-05 05:56:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously guy was on the ice for a solid minute then gets booed smh classy vegas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-05 05:44:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty much  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-05 05:41:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-05 05:41:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know fuck that guy and the fans fricken boo wilson when he gets up. no class </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-05 05:36:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I forgot how much I hate Ryan Reaves and his smug face </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I forgot how much I hated Ryan Reaves </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-05 04:38:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hit after the whistle on Willy. I hate his smug face man

Edit: Literally goes out of the way to blindside him and Vegas fans booed wilson when he got up god I hate them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-04 23:00:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If anything Dark is a better 100X more mind fucking version of stranger things. There are similarities but like what. One is about time travel and the other a big monster lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-04 22:56:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He’ll retire from NHL here fo sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-04 22:03:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.ebay.com/itm/NICKLAS-BACKSTROM-WASHINGTON-CAPITALS-2011-RBK-PREMIER-WINTER-CLASSIC-JERSEY/270912258632?hash=item3f13a10248:m:mya5WS00Fz3nJXgAM3b176A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Help finding Backstrom winter classic 2011 or any other caps jerseys </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-04 08:00:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Size large

If you know of legit customization for a blank that works too

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-03 23:15:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Easy pz next cup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Well... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-03 01:56:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-01 22:57:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pm’d
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-30 13:12:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He doesn’t get recognized much.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-29 23:44:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got METN at one of the shows I’ve been to and its white with what looks like blue paint splattered on it. It’s definitely my coolest looking record so try and find that one. (Not sure if there are any different ones but I imagine black) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-29 23:28:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As to you they rock! Have you seen them live?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Seen these guys 3 times and my collection is growing! Check out Manchester Orchestra (rock not classical lol) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-29 23:22:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-28 21:59:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-26 23:00:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 4-3

Wilson

10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-23 23:51:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How blatant were the misses? There are missed calls every game but were these worse than others? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-20 07:04:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whiny baby classic cupcake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-15 05:34:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Check out blackberry smoke! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-14 18:25:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Especially where you said they need to change to survive you are correct. But give them time! Only one album out. After Rush’s first album they were called the Canadian Led Zeppelin and look how they turned out. Rush def had Zep as an influence and it took them a while (and adding Neil Peart “oh yea that guy” lol) to really find their sound and become more themselves. That doesn’t man “Working Man” is a bad song tho ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-14 18:20:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every single musical act has a corporate “machine” behind it with the whole goal of making money. But these 19-21 year old kids have some real talent. AOTPA was a step in the right direction in terms of musical originality (more than “from the fires”) and I would like to see them depart more.

On the other hand, I do think they care about their music. There isn’t “the man” behind them telling them to copy Zep to appeal to older audiences etc. Thats tin foil hat shit. These are kids who are jamming out right now. So what if they sound like their influences. They just put out they’re first album. They’ve also been touring constantly for basically they’re whole career in the limelight. They need more time to discover their sound and depart from their influences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-14 17:56:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where our opinions differ is that they sound like Zep and you think its a bad thing but my point is why hate? Just don’t surround yourself with GVF or go on this sub to hate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-14 17:25:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sound like does not mean play the same songs. They do sound similar but that’s not a bad thing. They have original songs and lyrics. Even though they are obviously influenced by Zeppelin, they have different songs. So they aren’t a tribute band and there is a huge difference between the two that isn’t fully recognized atm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can anyone tell me where to get this hoodie/What it's called? Good win tonite! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-14 07:05:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-13 21:49:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously idk why its annoying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-13 17:07:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats really good actually. The last line “there are worse things you can sound like than Led Zeppelin”  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Are little depressions in records bad? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-13 07:13:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They look like little dips and they vary in size seem to be on songs that skip more on this record. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> All the hate its annoying </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-13 07:08:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People have their own opinions on music, always have, always will. People like different genres, styles, sounds etc. They also think others aren’t so good.

While this is obviously a valid point, all of the hate and absolute tearing into GVF has made it kind of annoying to read things about them/invest in content that is not put out by the band. Its toxic. Even on this sub, alot of people seem to think the album is 6/10 at best and basically a Zep b-side. Some are even straight up hating on the band. There needs to be more support for the band! People post positive things but all the comments are hate etc. Like seriously? This is the GVF subreddit!

Of course theres the BS reviews like pitchfork, but if you search up GVF anywhere you get people trying to destroy them. Bad review after bad review.

Do they sound like Zep? YES! Is that bad? NO! You can’t say they sound like Led Zeppelin and then turn around and call them bad.

Even though the songs may sound similar you can’t just say “cover band” because the songs are different! Since when did similar become the same.

In conclusion, sure you may not like GVF, so just listen to music you do like and bam problem solved. Don’t come on here and say they suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-13 06:49:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now just anthem of the peaceful army aaannd wait a minute...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-12 21:45:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We’re 6-3 come on! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-12 21:44:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Porsches are the best but I’d take the aston </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-09 03:46:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bruins suck but these😍 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-09 03:46:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shit is badass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Country pairs with Bohemia? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-08 22:54:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-08 06:17:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely shouldnt’ve been a misconduct, but bracing for a hit is different than lowering the shoulder after seeing him coming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-07 23:36:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 4-3 Ovi 5:30 1st period </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-07 16:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will we be able to listen not live on the radio? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-06 19:06:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whaaaat this is what I do right now! A group of friends and I won a volleyball tourney and won 7 free pizza coupons. We just use them all infinitely. Its a papa johns too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Forming Jerusalem as the Knights </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-05 22:47:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm in the middle of my campaign (taken Cyprus, 2 greek provinces, & Adana) and the Ottos are looking weak. Poland took some of Greece (weird i know). Do I wait for Ottos to go to war with Mamluks, or is there a way for me to directly go to war. I am allied with Venice, Poland, Ragusa, and Pope. What is the next step? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-05 21:22:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3-2, Carlson, 35 saves </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-05 14:48:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ll take it to a store and see 👍🏻 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-05 14:43:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What if I had the same album in a different record that played fine?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-05 14:39:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want them too! There’s a hippie store in my town lol but $30 is too much for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-05 14:36:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ll take it to one and ask them to play it. I bought it online from urban outfitters :/ never doing that again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-05 14:27:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It might have a few depressions in it. On the songs it skips but I need to look again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-05 14:22:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even if its the same album? I had another copy of this one that played just fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-05 14:06:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yess! This album is my fav atm but it skips on my favorite songs! Makes one of them unplayable. :/ Worst part is I got a new LP cause I gave my other one as a gift! :((( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-05 14:02:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have the lp60 and it plays all my other records fine. Just this one on a few songs so the record is definitely damaged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-05 14:01:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have an lp60 and i cleaned the record and it’s brand new. The turntable plays all my other records fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How to fix a skipping record? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-05 07:07:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Real newbie question here but i’ve seen a lot of mixed do’s and dont’s.

I have a new album that always skips in the same places.

Any way I can fix it or know what the reason is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone else’s vinyl skipping all over the place? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-03 03:56:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have the yellow one in particular but When the curtain falls and LLTB are literally unplayable and I just got the record! Does anyone know if its the record or not? And how to fix it if i can! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-02 01:46:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The scooters lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-02 00:10:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love Aachen and it's great to see some appreciation. Miss there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-02 00:08:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ubers will be v expensive too. Walk to a less in demand area, or hop on a bike share/bird. My friends and I after one of the Stanley cup watch parties took bike shares all the way to Rosslyn from Capital one and it actually was really fun! VAMOS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-31 20:46:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's amazing. God bless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-31 14:14:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats what i'm sayin

&#x200B; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-31 14:11:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> big oofs. I bet r/aww doesn't have many hockey bros.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 23:11:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The last point of number 3 literally sums up my opinions towards the situation. Masterfully said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 07:04:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Greta van Fleet comes alive! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone know where to download/listen to live versions they haven't released? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 06:59:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> like evil and others </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 06:38:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw yours on ebay. Is there a way to customize. I’m a newbie. Also i’m broke so idk :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 06:31:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This exactly! I just don’t understand.

First, why people are hating on the album/the band. Like seriously? How on earth can you not like this music if you care enough about rocknroll to listen. Sure they sound like Zeppelin. Why is that a BAD thing??? Sure they’re emulating classic rock style (clothes & overall vibe)  and sound. Again, Why is that a BAD thing??? Why should classic rock be left to the past. It rocks! Everyone loves it. The music made back then is still loved and enjoyed by every generation! Why should it be left for dead!

Second, listen to the freaking album more than once. Its not just zeppelin influence. Just cause Josh sounds like Plant (have amazing voices lol) doesn’t mean “boom zeppelin copy, cover band”. People who believe that really haven’t given them a chance and have let their biases take control of their opinions. They’ve really taken them at face value. GVF said “people ignore good music because it takes extra brain power to listen to”

Third, why do people come to this sub to hate and troll? Its actually maddening. Its all positive stuff thats posted. But the comment sections are an absolute war. Keep your hate to yourself! Just don’t listen to them then! Its that easy!


Its not really a peaceful army down here :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 06:14:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would that fit a large? Those are a little on the small side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Caps Jerseys for Sale? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-29 23:44:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looking for Stadium Series, Blue Screaming eagle, Capitol Building, and 2011 Winter classic

Size: L or XL

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-29 22:13:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [https://www.ebay.com/itm/Men-s-2017-18-Washington-Capitals-Brayden-Holtby-Stadium-Series-Jersey-XL-NWT/183494058008?hash=item2ab9192018:g:uSMAAOSwPR9byoKt:rk:4:pf:0](https://www.ebay.com/itm/Men-s-2017-18-Washington-Capitals-Brayden-Holtby-Stadium-Series-Jersey-XL-NWT/183494058008?hash=item2ab9192018:g:uSMAAOSwPR9byoKt:rk:4:pf:0)

[https://www.ebay.com/itm/Washington-Capitals-2011-Winter-Classic-Reebok-Edge-1-0-Jersey-50/123457936889?hash=item1cbeaa9df9:g:NboAAOSwkY9bgXzd:rk:1:pf:0](https://www.ebay.com/itm/Washington-Capitals-2011-Winter-Classic-Reebok-Edge-1-0-Jersey-50/123457936889?hash=item1cbeaa9df9:g:NboAAOSwkY9bgXzd:rk:1:pf:0)

[https://www.ebay.com/itm/Reebok-Washington-Capitals-Nicklas-Backstrom-2011-Winter-Classic-Jersey-XL-Mint/142965402294?hash=item214966eab6:g:GmEAAOSw-pNbuUIX:rk:5:pf:0](https://www.ebay.com/itm/Reebok-Washington-Capitals-Nicklas-Backstrom-2011-Winter-Classic-Jersey-XL-Mint/142965402294?hash=item214966eab6:g:GmEAAOSw-pNbuUIX:rk:5:pf:0)

[https://www.ebay.com/itm/2006-Alexander-Ovechkin-Washington-Capitals-Black-Jersey-Size-Mens-Large/323520933590?hash=item4b5359aed6:rk:1:pf:0](https://www.ebay.com/itm/2006-Alexander-Ovechkin-Washington-Capitals-Black-Jersey-Size-Mens-Large/323520933590?hash=item4b5359aed6:rk:1:pf:0)

[https://www.ebay.com/itm/2005-2006-NHL-CCM-WASHINGTON-CAPITALS-ALEXANDER-OVECHKIN-8-XL-TG-ROOKIE-Jersey/264012116422?hash=item3d785931c6:g:ZFQAAOSwa6Jb1pcv:rk:9:pf:0](https://www.ebay.com/itm/2005-2006-NHL-CCM-WASHINGTON-CAPITALS-ALEXANDER-OVECHKIN-8-XL-TG-ROOKIE-Jersey/264012116422?hash=item3d785931c6:g:ZFQAAOSwa6Jb1pcv:rk:9:pf:0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-29 15:59:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amen but still  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-29 15:59:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Considering how RG, Grossman and (sometimes) Cousins did we should definitely stand by alex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-29 14:04:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean we’re squeaking by but we’re still winning. I think based on the past few decades this is a good thing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-29 13:05:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> HAIL YEAH! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just a little something to brighten your Monday... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-29 13:00:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We're living in a world where the Skins are 5-2! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-28 18:05:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That was my most expensive one. My screaming eagle was $75 on depop. WC was $130. And ovi was a handmedown! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-28 17:59:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I bought mine a few years ago for that much :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 07:53:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We continue to use the best jersey in all of sports as an alternate... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does sock sizing just shoe size? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-27 07:49:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 22:34:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, its a good flair my guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 20:45:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> or some guy with a TV show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 20:26:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think they had some more of the kuzys in stock when I bought it. Goodluck tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 20:25:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh totally. Blank jerseys = suck and we arent suck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 20:24:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its sweet cause nobody knows about him but he actually won the vezina when playing for the caps!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 20:20:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sportssk.com They’re a legit seller on the sub! $130 is not bad at all for customized with the WC patch for that jersey. I see these all the time blank with no patch so Im feelin good :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 20:15:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probs too big for me. Any XLs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 20:09:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dannnnng ur so lucky! Its no Kolzig, but I got my Jim Carey (vezina winner I’ll have you know) after  they won the cup for $75 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 20:08:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can wear XL esp in adidas cause they run smaller right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 20:07:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ones I don’t have. But 2011 winter classic backstrom (but any player works) is at the top of my list. Plus SS, Capitol Building, and blue screaming eagle are all the ones i dont have.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 20:05:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tryna slide one my way ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 20:03:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Large but can do XL if need be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 20:03:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just got my Kuzy and Screaming eagle one this year. I’ve had Ovi and Oshie for a while. New patch on ovi makes it seem like I got a new one 🤗 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 20:02:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea I totally get that, but I’d rather buy the patch than a whole new jersey because the jerseys are pretty much the same from reebok to adidas. For me that’s a so what. Not looking to sell so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 19:57:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks man! Sounds like u got a sweet one too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 19:36:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can anyone help me out in getting them all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 19:30:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jim Carey #30 starter Screaming eagle, Oshie Reebok 3rd Jersey, Kuzy 2015 winter classic, Ovi is a reebok but I just put the final patch on it. I know could be Jersey Fowl but don’t really care cause the adidas and reeboks look the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Still a newbie, but this is turning into a nasty habit. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 19:29:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-26 14:34:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bad game. Boys gotta pick themselves up and move on. Shit happens on the road. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-25 01:11:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whyyyy did I buy the other one!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-24 22:00:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now do I buy this AND the yellow one... Have 3 vinyls... Am I that obsessed... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-24 16:35:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you’re looking to make one yourself, buy the plain white one and tyedye it yourself! It’d look sweet i bet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-23 22:46:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ryan Miller for sale? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-23 17:26:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OC is FUCKIN playin baby! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-23 08:50:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But i wish ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-23 08:49:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey man im poor :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-23 07:54:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whoops I screwed up

Size L or XL if fits small </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone selling Caps jerseys? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-23 07:50:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Winter classic 2011, Stadium Series, Capital Building, and Blue screaming eagle are the ones I need!  Preferably with players!

Size L or XL if fits small

Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-23 07:45:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it a large? Can you post a link? I can't seem to find it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-23 07:23:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you get the patch with the album? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-23 07:11:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Makin me think...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-23 07:09:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was really cool doing it. Just walking to that song looking at the trees was peaceful and got me HYPE for the album. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-23 07:07:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Let me know I'm lookin for one too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-23 07:06:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A really good singing voice from a really annoying talking voice. I think it might be his midwestern accent mixed with a speech problem or something. No evidence just what it sounds like to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-23 07:04:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've come to the conclusion that people can't/won't see past that Josh sounds like Plant. They sound similar but that sounds GOOD! I get kinda angry when people in r/listentothis say ledzepp lite etc. but haters gunna hate, we'll be top soon enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-22 21:51:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a fan. Although they should bring the og jerseys back (not just as an alternate). But I think they'll go this route if they decide to change em. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-22 20:11:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw one at my local barnes and noble though... check it out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-22 20:10:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I preordered it from merchbar! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In an age of darkness light appears... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-22 19:29:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-22 13:17:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WAZAAAAAAAAAAA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-22 07:55:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> and I know the way I wrote this made me sound like I'm not of our generation but as a college student I'm really happy our generation gets this too ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-22 07:53:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not  saying that rock can't evolve or that newer versions of rock aren't rock at all. I'm just happy if change is more towards GVF style. I agree with you totally as well. I'm into pretty much every kind of music out there except for pop and the closer rock gets to pop, the worse it gets imho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-22 07:43:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I bought it too hope it's awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-22 07:43:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also that would be sweeet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-22 07:42:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course the background music is led zeppelin. haters would eat this up if they found so shhhhhh... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A thank you to Greta Van Fleet </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-22 07:22:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The guys have rewritten the script for me. Being a huge fan of a lot of classic rock, GVF marks a breath of fresh air from the modern rock scene.

This may be a hot take for some, but most popular rock (21 Pilots is not rock I'm sorry) being released nowadays sounds like wannabe punk, metal, super alt mix and it just sounds cringy to me. Aside from some notable exceptions (for me Highly Suspect but I see this in them too) I just don't like it. I'm a huge fan of more riffs and melodic variety instead of just straight shred and scream. (Think Kaleo, Black Keys, Catfish & Bottlemen). I just hate that "Rock This" on spotify has GVF on the cover and is just ass the rest of the way. When I listen to GVF Pandora radio, Wolfmother and stuff that is much harder than I like comes up. There is no-one thats like GVF out there and I want that to change

I'm also into bands like Foo Fighters, Green Day, and RHCP but are they even considered modern anymore? I hear them on my local classic rock station all the time nowadays. I love these guys, but they're getting older and are becoming the new "classic rock" with huge acts like Zeppelin, Beatles, Stones, etc. being pushed even further back.

GVF are at the forefront of rock right now, and I hope the waves they are making will shake the rock world back to more classic sounds. I hope softer stuff that still rocks the house comes to the forefront in the near future.

I love the new album by the way, shit slaps.

TL;DR I don't like most rock out there and I hope GVF changes things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-22 01:39:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The jam at the end is soooooo good I love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-22 01:39:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> $20 dollar pin? Worth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-22 01:36:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's so sweet. Sorry to rub it in, but I love that I dropped $45 on this puppy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can someone ELI5 this dumpster fire to me? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-20 08:17:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven’t been keeping up recently but i’ve seen our string of bad results and now Hoeneß’ comments (although I agree Bernat is a bum, you can’t go out and say things like that). Things need to get together quick. The national team is in tatters too. C’mon guys!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-19 21:22:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everything they do is so planned! It shows they really care! AND their music SLAPS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-19 16:04:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why we keep lettin his bumass beat us?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-19 16:04:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Killin the game! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ready. Set. HYPETRAIN! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-19 06:09:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YESSSSS FINALLYYY!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-19 05:18:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dang it. Really want a GVF pin for my backpack. Would look sick :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-19 05:09:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How did you get the pin? I live in the US </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-18 22:37:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds so much like Rush </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-18 18:15:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Confirmed: song slaps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Niskyyy IN OT my DUDES and BABES!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-18 03:45:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck the Rangers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Seeing the boys over memorial day weekend and I’m so stoked! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-17 19:43:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The show in queens baby! I’m from DC so it’s a trip but it’ll be worth. A day in the city then seeing my favorite band!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-17 06:15:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're the One is really good but tbh I didn't like anthem or flower power as much as some of their other stuff. Of course that's just my taste, more a jam rock guy. Ideally I want a lot of jams and punch you in the face rock like Lover, Leaver and When the Curtain Falls. But a few songs like You're the One will spice it up and make it amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-17 06:11:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sweeeet! Jacket is so sick with the patch, wish I had bought one though. That and the pin and socks lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-17 06:10:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Only if they don't ruin the album. For how good the singles are I really hope so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 23:08:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-15 22:30:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Answers are too polarizing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I just signed up for the peaceful army list is it too late for stuff? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-12 20:01:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I realllly don’t wanna miss out! Of course if they haven’t said anything then nobody knows but if anyone does?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 22:02:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 21:38:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sweet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 20:23:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> PM me about the Ovi and maybe Ducks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 20:21:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kolzig still up?

&#x200B; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 19:30:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any player on the back? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 19:30:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you send me pics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 17:02:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I posted something and have looked around that sub too. Just lookin to see if anyone has one here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 16:41:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dang i have the reebok oshie one! I would love tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone selling Caps jerseys? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 15:55:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Preferably winter classic/stadium series (all years) or vintage ones. I'm a size L but can fit XL if needed. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 13:47:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pic and price? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 07:00:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I heard these run big. I'm definitely a large but if it runs small? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 06:50:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dang! Looking for one to wear not frame :) Got any others? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone selling Capitals jerseys? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-10 06:44:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Preferably winter classic/stadium series ones (all years) or vintage ones. If not can you point me to a site thats not gunna sell me fakes? I'm looking on Ebay and can't find legit ones. I'm a size L, but willing to wear XL if not huge. Thank You! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-08 19:34:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How does one assemble the wealth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Quit juuling for the first time today! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-01 06:05:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m scared but I really want this. I don’t want to be a slave anymore. I’m 18 and I don’t want to grow up and be addicted. If there’s any advice you can give me i’d greatly appreciate it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why is there so much hate on our boys? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 18:32:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's been so much positive coming out of the world towards Greta (tonight show etc.) and they're definitely the biggest up and coming rock band. With that though, there's so much hate and trolling "blah blah copying Zeppelin blah blah". Even though they do sound like Zeppelin, I definitely think it's not a carbon copy. There are a lot of differences in how Greta sounds. If you're as obsessed as I am, you can definitely hear a cleaner more melodious sound than the more start stop sound of Zeppelin (I.e Black Dog). I think people can't see past the fact that Josh sounds like Plant and they end it right there. People just gotta let go and let good music be played! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-26 18:19:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hear it but Josh has a more harsh voice imo. Also, even though I love Rush (probably one of my fav bands) I hope Greta doesn't go into more prog rock like Rush did. A few songs maybe, but our boys should stay the path.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 08:16:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its really good so far! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just heard When the curtains falls in NHL 19! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-24 21:18:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RECOGNITION! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are the dimensions of the side pockets of the Kanken classic? (looking for a water bottle that fits) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-23 22:33:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A story where God showed me a piece of his joy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-21 04:04:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I posted this in a comment but I felt the need to share this with the whole sub!

To provide some key context, this Summer I went on a mission trip in the Czech Republic. I was helping run a summer camp for middle schoolers in the town of Turnov (2 hours away from Prague). For the week we ran camp activities, taught english, and showed these kids who Jesus is for the first time. (Czech is one of the least religious countries in the world).

After the week of camp, my group went to Prague and explored a beautiful area of the city known as the castle (like the old walled in part of the city, not a single castle). I'll never forget this moment.

As we were exploring, the group stopped to sit by a statue as we came upon a view of the entire city. I was gravitated towards this and went to go look, even though my friends went to go sit. As I made my way towards the wall (where the view was), a poor street performer was singing "Hallelujah" and that struck me cause we were there on the mission because Czech is the least religious country in Europe. That was when it started.

As I walked across the square hearing that worship song, I started getting a feeling of pure joy. It got stronger and stronger the closer I got to the edge. It all came to a point when I put my hand on the wall of the castle overlooking the city. Internally, God showed me how much joy he can bring. I was in a beautiful place with all my beautiful friends. I had just spent a taxing week serving children in the name of him and he showed me all his joy at once. That is the only word to describe that feeling, he showed me all of his joy.

I felt overwhelmed with his power and just how good it felt to be in his presence. I just stood still feeling his joy. Tears almost came to my eyes. Whenever I feel down in my faith I just think back to this moment and I relearn just how good our Lord is.

Thank you for reading all of this! God bless you!

tl;dr God showed me all his joy when I was in Prague.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 07:35:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is my experience of a moment where the Lord really put his hand on me!

To provide some key context, this Summer I went on a mission trip in the Czech Republic. I was helping run a summer camp for middle schoolers in the town of Turnov (2 hours away from Prague). For the week we ran camp activities, taught english, and showed these kids who Jesus is for the first time. (Czech is one of the least religious countries in the world).

After the week of camp, my group went to Prague and explored a beautiful area of the city known as the castle (like the old walled in part of the city, not a single castle). I'll never forget this moment.

As we were exploring, the group stopped to sit by a statue as we came upon a [view](http://styledsnapshots.com/2018/01/travel-guide-prague.html/1-6-of-22) of the entire city. I was gravitated towards this and went to go look, even though my friends went to go sit. As I made my way towards the wall (where the view was), a poor street performer was singing "Hallelujah" and that struck me cause we were there on the mission because Czech is the least religious country in Europe. That was when it started.

As I walked across the square hearing that worship song this feeling of pure joy got stronger and stronger. It all came to a point when I put my hand on the wall of the castle overlooking the city. Internally, God showed me how much joy he can bring. I was in a beautiful place with all my beautiful friends. I had just spent a taxing week serving children in the name of him and he showed me all his joy at once. That is the only word to describe that feeling, he showed me all of his joy.

Just keep pushing and believing man! Know he loves you! He is our lighthouse!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-20 07:11:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey man.

I get these feelings sometimes too. Even in seasons of growing in my faith. Sometimes I have the bad thoughts that "this is all just BS". When I get these feelings though, I just say no this is what I believe. I focus on the things he has brought me and how he has changed my life.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-18 07:12:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beauty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-11 19:26:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you man! That was a great analysis. I think this team can go places! (although I think that every year). I do remind you that we probably have the worst management in the league but I will stay devoted just to have my heart broken!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-05 06:26:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Multipla is nice but its no Twingo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-05 06:14:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God bless you!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-05 05:47:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much for this! I can't tell you how much this means to me. So far I have been building said nest but sometimes I try to live without it finished. This is hard but I really want this. I'll do everything in my power to build that nest and not to have it fall out of the tree because of mistakes when we're young.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-05 05:21:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also, I didn't read you're comment thoroughly until now and I've realized that I've been going about it the wrong way. I need to really pour myself into Jesus to gain this self control. One of my thoughts about my faith is that I need to trust in he who will never fail me, because if I trust myself, I may succeed but I will eventually fail. Jesus will never fail. I have been holding this from God but I need to give it to him and continue to give it to him. Seriously thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-05 04:04:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats so true! I need to trust god more and trust myself. The more I overthink the harder it is. I gotta pray about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-05 04:03:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you and god bless you!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-05 04:02:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you man!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-05 02:32:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeaaa that is not what I want right now. Married in college is a bad look and I’m definitely not ready myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-05 02:31:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much. When I was writing this i thought of some people I could talk to on the phone to help me and confide in.  Our christian group will be getting started soon too so that will help with community and being focused on God!

Also thank you for not saying get married. We’re still fresh out of HS so thats a no thanks haha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-05 01:34:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If there’s a way that we can contain ourselves then I want to find it. Do you know of a verse about that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-05 01:27:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We’re 18 bro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-28 21:07:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate spiders but I love this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-28 05:33:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> abbey road ep i see you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-31 08:19:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks!

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How do I better put Christ first in my relationship. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-31 07:28:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So many things about christianity and being young clash. But I feel my girlfriend and I have been doing a pretty good job in putting the Lord first in our relationship. We go to church together when we can and have had discussions but it's not full on and It's so easy to get distracted!

Just looking for advice although I should pray about it haha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-31 07:00:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It will come. When you least expect it, where you least expect it. I was where you are for so long. The first step is accepting yourself. People will see that. If a couple adds up to two you need to add up to one. It's a tough time. I was desperate too (I think I have a few reddit posts about it lol). But someone will come along and it will happen so fast you'll forget all these feelings. Good luck! Sending good happy thoughts your way! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-30 21:36:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Screen seems to be shifted down and I can't click on buttons. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-28 23:18:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just re-downloaded EU4 on my new mac book but the screen seems to be shifted downwards. This also means that I need to cursor above the buttons (up on the computer screen) for me to press them.

I uninstalled and installed again but this didn't help.

Anyone else have this issue?

Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-19 04:30:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All it takes is an attitude change. Sure you may fall on your face, but if you just live confidently, its so much better. Tell yourself that you're good enough and that its ok to fail sometimes. You have to pick yourself up by the boot straps and keep on going. It's not going to happen overnight either. It takes work and practice and nobody is perfect. Just keep trying and you'll get there.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-13 04:13:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok thanks man. Will check. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Are there any stores in the DMV that sell vintage jerseys? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-13 03:27:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know there are a bunch of these kinds of stores that sell basketball jerseys but what about hockey?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-12 07:32:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m willing to pay about $120 and i’m a size L </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I’m looking for Caps ‘96-‘05 jerseys or Winter Classic jerseys both years. Size L, 50, or 52. The regret is real. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-11 08:36:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can anyone help? Really want an authentic. Way to many fouls on ebay and don’t wanna take a chance. Also prices sheesh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-11 08:26:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Caps still up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-11 08:23:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sweet
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone wanna sell me their 96-05 Caps jersey? Please thanks! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-11 08:06:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or point me in a direction to a store (in the DMV) or a website where I can buy legit jerseys. Also looking at winter classics. I’m regretting not buying those!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-05 07:05:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Giant corporations colluding to keep the current balance going?? Naaaaaa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Best hockey bar in DC? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-02 22:44:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-31 23:46:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get the quit while you’re on top bit. But wtf he could win 3 more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-30 03:45:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Civ and stardew get a vote for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-30 03:42:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> REP DC! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-29 23:54:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please make this happen and get rid of the dated “Redskins” writing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Who else thinks the Vegas show at the beginning is basically just disney on ice? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-29 02:34:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ITS GAME DAY YOU BEAUTIFUL FUCKERS! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-28 06:26:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-28 05:42:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like 1ish  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-28 03:33:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  ive only been smoking for a year and i’m 18. But i still want to do this. Ive seen too many stories on this sub and my family, I don’t want that to be me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-28 02:43:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m tryna do this too. Lets do it together. Lol I feel like a pussy on this sub talking about juul but its real too. If you wanna do this together lmk!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-26 06:16:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This one is amazing. I love and hate it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-24 23:23:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really like this! Seriously, go to the basketball courts and just shoot around or if you’re not into sports strike up a random conversation in the library or wherever. You can find friends in mysterious places. Also, there’s all kinds of clubs for just about every interest so just go to one of those. You don’t have to say anything at first but don’t have to be perfect! Even with just showing interest in things friends will come along. Donmt worry about it bro. You got this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> FUCK THE JACKETS! FUCK THE PENS! FUCK THE BOLTS! FUCK VEGAS! FUCK WE’RE IN THE CUP! FUCK THE PENS! ALL CAPS! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-24 12:42:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-23 02:28:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Basically they support the team that just won. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-23 02:26:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One of them said that home ice doesn’t matter until game 7. He’s talking about the Capitals here who have lost countless game 7s on home ice. THEY DONT KNOW SHIT WE DONT NEED THEM  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-21 06:00:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gosh idk I just related to this so hard. I just stayed out all night for the first time in soo long. I was with some people that I knew pretty well and others I knew none at all. By the end of it though I felt so close to all of them. It was just awesome. Wanted to share haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-21 05:08:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> CAN I GET A HELL YEA BROTHER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-21 00:24:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jeez from the title I totally thought I had found one of my friends from last night on here! PM me I stayed out till 5 too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-19 23:18:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Time. I know it sounds kinda cliché but I mean since you used the term “like” I assume it was never serious. To be honest there will be someone else to come along soon enough. I feel like i’ve been there too many times brother. But just wait it out and find someone else (that always helps). Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-19 23:15:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did like or do like? I just wanna know what I’m answering LOL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-19 23:12:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This series will be won or lost based on how many penalties we get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-19 23:00:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-18 03:03:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don’t you mean yanny? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-16 22:18:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A bunch of people at my school are and I’m like nooo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-16 20:50:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’d say  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> We lost 1 game to the "best" team in the Eastern conference. Big deal. RELAX. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-16 19:50:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-16 03:33:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right back at you! Go us!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-16 03:28:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go. For. It. I feel like i’m in the same situation just switch the genders (lol). I’m just gunna go for it. I have nothing to lose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-16 03:17:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like this a lot. Go you! Just go for it bro! You have nothing to lose! Even if you’re worried you’ll sound stupid its ok! Go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-16 03:09:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m a pro at this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-15 23:53:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its because people don’t want to seem racist and critics want to keep their jobs. The world we live in for better or worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-15 15:29:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope the same thing happens to me soon. You've motivated me :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-14 15:44:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude. Shit happens. R-E-L-A-X </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> UNLEASH THE MOTHERF*CKING FURY! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-14 15:42:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-12 07:20:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Future US army soldiers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-11 18:02:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At my high school we kind of had the same thing happen. This girl that not many people knew died and everyone of the "popular" girls acted like they cared so much and painted the rock and led things in her honor. Even though they never even talked to her and made her feel alienated. What proves that it was fake is that 2 weeks later everyone seemed to not care at all... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-11 17:57:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Buy slip on vans for sneakers and loafers for dress shoes and no one will ever know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-11 15:41:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol whats the alternative. I see that Rooney is a huge investment that is risky but come on guys. He could have a huge impact. Also, i’d rather have a packed stadium with huge fans and casuals than a half full one with just huge fans. Even if he doesn’t play well, DC will get the brand exposure and star power that this team has desperately needed for a long time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-09 20:38:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Classic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-09 15:42:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only thing that can stop this team right now is feeling like we've already won because we beat the Pens. Of course that energy can be used in the other way BY GOING OUT AND WINNING THAT BABY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-09 15:39:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hear you and holy crap it's annoying! But based on past playoff performances, this is what we want. We don't need no one to believe in us BABY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 15:19:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel you aren't the exception.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I AM SO FRICKIN PUMPED RIGHT NOW I LOVE THIS TEAM I LOVE THIS SUB! AMAZING! C! A! P! S! CAPS CAPS CAPS!!!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-08 04:05:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-05 15:22:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go Nats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> We got the win we needed. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-04 15:43:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They took game 1, we took game 3. Best of three. LETS GO BOYS!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 15:14:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean it all depends doesn't it? There's really religious people that aren't whack but all we hear about is the bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 15:12:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get that patent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 06:27:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  I have an automatic response to anyone that ever says anything creepy beside me at a urinal...
“You have one chance to shut the fuck up” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-03 05:07:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-02 23:14:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m not really an art guy but this is really captivating but extremely sad at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I have so much going for me but I still feel bad. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-02 05:37:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t know why but I’m sick of it. I’m going to college. I have so many amazing friends that care about me. I’m apart of so many things that bring me joy. Girls have always been a spot of bother, but things are looking up right now.

At the end of the day though, when I’m driving home alone I just feel it start to creep in. This unending feeling of being inadequate and alone. Despite that being untrue, I still think this all the time. This leads to having some very dark thoughts.

I just don’t understand it. I feel like there is something missing but, looking at my life, there really isn’t. I just want to be free from these doubts and get back to living my life.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-02 05:18:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its so hard to sleep more but at least try to get closer to 8 hours. Being a teenager doesn’t really help me but hey, cheers to team no sleep! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-02 05:07:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> E </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-02 05:04:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had to turn in my old phone :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is there a way to get back the photos from a certain phone back from icloud? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-02 04:54:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I recently got an iphone 8 and when I tried to sync my photos from my old phone from icloud, I got all of my family members photos as well (we share an apple ID). I want to know if there is a way to get just my photos (taken on my old device) back onto my phone without having all the rest of the photos that are backed up on our icloud. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm not really in the loop but I have a question. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-30 16:06:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Before Avicii's passing, he was set to release new EP's and a new album. Does anyone know if they'll release what he has if there is any? I feel like that would be awesome to do in his honor and many other artists have released after they died. Just wondering if he'll "live on" even further through new music. RIP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> GOD FUCKING DAMN IT BUT WE STILL GOT THIS </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-27 03:55:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-25 18:45:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’d say best porsche in the dmv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-25 15:56:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 100% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-25 15:11:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Best Porsche in Georgetown? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-25 14:33:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> THIS IS GREAT SIR! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-23 15:53:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Playoff wiz bitches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-23 15:51:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I DONT PLAY THAT SHIT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-23 15:50:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> THIS MY CITY BOIA I DON PLAY THAT SHI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-23 15:48:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know about you but I flex to the left constantly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-18 16:01:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh na </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-16 04:14:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit yes! People at the DMV do not care at all. They just need to check some boxes and move on (unfortunately a product of bureaucracy).

I took my grandpa to get his license renewed and the poor guy straight up tripped on a chair at the DMV (he has cataracts). He pretty much failed the test too but the lady kept saying. “I just need one more letter” on the visual test.

He’s gotten into multiple crashes so doesnt drive anymore. I have to drive him around lol. I enjoy the time with him though :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-13 15:50:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same shit. Different day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-13 15:35:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-12 18:03:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My b will fix this atrocity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I want to believe anything can happen! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-12 15:11:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> LET’S FUCKING GO! FULL CAPS BELIEF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-12 14:53:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Remember 2 years ago? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-12 14:38:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Favorite wiz mem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-03 20:57:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fortnite is tho! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I love these new flairs (I'm late I know) but it inspired me. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-03 15:51:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What if we had Arenas (prime or present) coming off the bench this season. Aside from having TSA level security in the locker room.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-01 16:23:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ve tried and I’ll keep trying. Thanks brotha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-23 14:56:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only fully armed squad in the Red Army. Edit: sorry for the sarcasm i guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-19 14:02:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Aral Sea is back and better than ever! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-16 14:35:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 20,000 admissions to college in my name... I'm gunna sell these </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-12 21:50:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, with the debt of the US government, you'd have some bargaining chips for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-06 20:51:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Triple A baby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> We have a heck of a team this year </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-06 20:34:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know this isn't the normal dialogue after 3 points turned into 1 in the 92nd minute vs. Orlando, but I believe we have a great (good) team!

Gone are the days of signing the Marcelo's, Nyarko's, and Sam's of the league. I respect these guys, they were workhorses, but it would be very naive to say they weren't well past their primes. Signing the players that aren't good enough for other teams in the league just isn't a good business model.

Our mid-season moves last year were what we needed, Arriola is our best player imo and Stieber is good as well. Now to go with Asad (a steal), Moreno, Ousted (perfect timing, starting keeper hits the market right when Billie leaves), Brillant, and others. We have some great pieces that are YOUNG and ready to go. All this with Acosta and Birnbaum... My only complaint is Mattocks, but hey, he's faster than Mullins.

I'm excited for the season for more than just Audi field! Vamos! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thoughts on this whole supporters situation. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-03-01 15:52:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is an absolute sham. This is literally the reverse of what should be happening to a fanbase at anytime, much more when we are about to get a new stadium!! This is a time of optimism for the club (finally signing players worth a damn and audi field) and it really is a shame to see the fanbase I love so divided by the actions of our own FO and leaders of the SE.
It was already sad to see the bouncing stands of RFK go but now United games possibly without Barra Brava and DU...
Many screaming eagles members (including myself) are outraged at this "partnership" and stand with BB and DU. I really hope the counterparts of this deal realize what outrage they've created and things change. We're all fans and should be treated as equals. Vamos United and fight modern football!

Edit: I do believe though that we all need to be UNITED in this effort. Through pushing our beliefs on the club but also supporting it wholeheartedly, being the bigger man. I’m still going to go to the games and stuff to support my club. But I am not happy with how things are being run. (Haven’t been for a while actually but this is the latest and greatest). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-28 04:21:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I also hate how colin cowherd is talking like he knows everything about this team when he never talks about them otherwise. Also trading John in the offseason??? WTF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-27 21:54:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amen brotha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-27 19:41:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope mine was actual talk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-27 19:41:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here. Exciting stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-27 19:41:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea I totally agree, those players are really coming into their own. We are doing great atm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-27 18:23:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh we have our own problems I know. Good 'ol teddie pisses me off more than anyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-27 18:20:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do the mainstreamers and bandwagons not like their order disturbed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-27 18:15:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Red with white, matches our color scheme best too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thoughts on all the speculation around, "are we better without Wall" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-27 18:12:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think we aren't, yet it's awesome to see us playing "better" without him. John was nursing his knee for pretty much the entire season before he went out to get his surgery, so that could be why his numbers were down this year. Also, without Wall's dominant presence on the offensive side of the ball, the Wiz need to move the ball more to win games. Hopefully when a full strength John comes back, he can just add to the everybody eats system that has been created in his absence. (He isn't too bad at dropping dimes himself).

tl;dr We aren't better without him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-27 18:01:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Been a wiz fan for all my life but new to the this sub and r/nba, why is there going to be a firestorm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-27 17:53:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or you're just a poor Nets fan... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-27 15:52:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thankuthanku </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-27 15:38:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How we can seem to beat the Celtics and Cavs, but not the Nets and Hornets. Oh yea and losing to the Jazz by 40. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone have a character chart? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-27 15:01:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [I feel like I have most of the characters and they're respective time "partners" down but if somebody has a chart that would be so helpful!] (/spoiler) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-27 14:38:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Check out Derbe Hamburg, they pretty much have the same thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-26 15:30:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was at the game and I was straight paranoid. 20 point leads are never safe with the Wiz. But also if the other team has that lead we seem to come back alot. Except when we lose to the Jazz by 40. I love the Wiz! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-15 14:52:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you hit that though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-15 07:14:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great big story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-14 07:18:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for letting me know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-14 02:54:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I signed up for the email alert but I don’t trust... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone know if the Wade vice jerseys will be restocked? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-13 16:28:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-12 18:27:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dark. A Netflix original from Germany. Makes stranger things look like  a kids show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-12 18:24:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Persian Boats. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Scaphism  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-12 15:46:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess I'm an outlier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-10 03:52:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does anyone know if/when they’ll restock? I want it sooo bad! They restocked the other players but the Wade would be the best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-09 15:34:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Use your fucking turn signal!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-07 03:59:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never cheat on my wife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-07 03:59:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It could be good if its “I have to talk to you” but thats 50/50 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-01 14:53:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Drums from In the Air Tonight by Phil Collins on repeat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-30 20:59:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats what season 2 is foorrr! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-30 19:52:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe I’m a hopeless romantic but I would’ve liked a little more of a love story involved between Jonas and Martha before he found out she was his aunt.  I know there was a backstory (last summer) and obvious romantic tension between them, but if more “happened” on screen and their affair went further, I would’ve felt more of the despair that Jonas feels in that moment.

Obviously not going THAT far cause you know incest and such... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-30 02:18:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was just saying how much I love the show and how I would hate to see what you linked happen... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-29 23:05:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No I totally got what you were saying! I guess my comment seemed like a response to said “slight” even though it wasn’t one :). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-29 17:36:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea I totally agree and your point about the storylines being unoriginal is right. But they gotta keep doing what they’re doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My thoughts on the second season. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-29 16:23:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [There are a lot of comments that aren't looking forward to the post apocalyptic future referenced when Jonas goes to (presumably) 2052. IMO, I don't really have a problem with a post apocalyptic future plot line, but I do agree that it MUST be done right. The creators cannot rush this second season as much as we all want it. This show was the best I have ever seen and I would be crushed if this turns into a "walking dead" type. I don't think this will happen but the creators need to put as much time and thought into the second season as they did the first.] (/spoiler)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-29 07:10:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you give a link? Not trying to pay 130€. Danke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-29 06:42:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just finished this show and I am stunned. I have never seen something as mindfucking yet absolutely amazing as this. Also I can speak some deutsch (I’m American) and with the subtitles I got the full original emotion displayed in the show. Definetly give it a try!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-25 19:57:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hawiian baby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-25 19:56:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love licorice too! That makes two of us out there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is something you enjoy that everyone else doesn't? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-25 18:30:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-24 15:47:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Crowder even stared him down. No class, or respect for your teammate. No wonder this team sucks atm. They are rotting from the inside.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-22 17:10:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you don't do something because of what might happen, then nothing ever happens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-22 17:09:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Porsche 911 turbo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 16:19:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How to get through Bleak Falls Barrow in Skyrim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-05 16:19:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most things about Skyrim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-01 20:56:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All out war... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-30 18:42:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hope it does too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-30 16:09:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate people like this. I really do feel you man. It's all fun and games until they're always busy. Find some people who will love you for who you are not just throw you under the bus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-30 15:58:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kickstart my Heart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-30 15:54:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Land before time on VHS was the move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-30 15:19:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was talking with the friend of my homecoming date last year and she wanted to see the poster I had made for my date! I being the idiot I am sent the picture of the poster to the positively wrong person. I sent the picture of my poster to my date I was going to ask the next day! My friend and I spammed her and told her to skip over the snapchat at all costs. She must've thought I was crazy but she still went with me, it turned out all good in the end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-20 21:54:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha i saw  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-20 20:59:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shit u right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-20 20:54:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> College application questions... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-17 03:11:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What goes well with adidas track pants? I have a few Polo RL shirts that go really well but i’m not sure what else does. Not really trying to go for the “slav” look but wondering goes well. Thanks for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What go well with adidas track pants? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-17 03:10:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What to wear adidas track pants with </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-17 02:25:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-13 16:02:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea I def see that. But Ze germans have a knack for losing to the Italians with the exception being Euro 2016 barely scraping by.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-13 15:35:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Germany is definitely hoping for a Sweden win...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-13 15:14:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When they reposted questions on /r/askreddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-03 16:18:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This has to be irony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-11-03 05:14:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It affects models 2012-15 mainly though if you have a 16 like me. Mine has had 0 problems thus far. Ford put the 16 in the memo they sent out but people I have talked to say they’ve seen it go up to 2015 not 16.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-30 19:46:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-30 02:17:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whose actually surprised lmao. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-26 17:49:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We built this city on roock and roolll!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-26 17:46:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One that takes a life, deserves to have their life taken. Plain and simple. Also rapists, fuck them too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-26 17:44:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being super loud and putting people down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-26 17:44:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 'roos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-26 17:43:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being abandoned by the one I love.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-26 17:41:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tell no-one. Move to Bahamas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-26 17:37:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Silence of the lambs is about a bunch of quiet baby sheep.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-26 17:34:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Skyrim. That horses can be witnesses to crimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-26 17:32:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-26 17:31:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Invest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-12 20:05:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That everyone in America would receive a free pony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-12 20:04:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do this near my nostrils so I sneeze.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-10 20:06:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But a lot of people still believed that the earth was flat because that is what the Catholic Church taught and much of what the Greeks discovered was forgotten.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-09 17:46:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But your hat is green though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-06 18:13:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably Land Before Time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-06 18:07:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apparently not my American Eagle khakis that ripped 2 days after I bought them. They fricken said "Built to Last" on the tag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-05 20:50:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> About 1 1/2 Chipotle burritos maximum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-05 20:50:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sooooooo many macbooks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-05 20:40:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to run around my house as a little kid in a circle, kitchen dining room, living room all day long. One day a drawer was left open, I have a small dent in my forehead to this day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-05 20:37:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having a law abiding citizen defend himself and others with a firearm of his own.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-05 20:30:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Always thought she was cute, but never considered her until I talked to her the first time. Now i'm asking her to the dance! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-05 20:25:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty good tired though. Literally every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-05 20:13:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That i'll do it tomorrow  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-05 20:05:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whenever I say stru-gul-ing like a drunk Joe Namath on Monday Night Football a while back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-05 20:03:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This would actually become a thing but locations would be reversed from the current definition of sanctuary city.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-05 06:22:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just go for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-05 05:12:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beggles! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-05 02:24:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would realize how to dress correctly. (13 to 17 is a big jump)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-02 23:48:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I rate super hard and I like Germany! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-02 23:47:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Button </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-26 05:18:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like the world is spinning out of my control in my academics, and I have the desire to get out of this rut, but I am so damn lazy I don’t do anything about it. Any motivational tips for a HS student?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-05 02:56:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty much useless nowadays my home phone number. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-03 03:51:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But I don't think in my corner of the USA ;). But could you elaborate why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-02 06:59:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will go nicely with my lederhosen!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-09-02 06:56:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wanna pet the mouse George! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-26 03:52:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> John Krasinski will always be Jim Halpert.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-24 22:50:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Defended 90's pop rock and having someone get 40+ down votes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-24 21:31:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I hold the door for somebody and they still proceed to hold it themselves, like wtf am I going to do close it on you?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-24 21:21:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Freebird - Lynyrd Skynyrd

3005 - Childish Gambino

Wonderwall - Oasis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-22 23:20:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ford dealer said 2016 model not a problem with the DCT but I got a letter saying I could be up for compensation, but no problems with the 2016 thus far. Just commenting on the look more 😉 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-22 22:17:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lamenting the purchase of my normal focus 😫 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-22 22:15:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Europe vs. America </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-20 16:42:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Classic Europe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-18 04:27:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This about Fournette or Gordon lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How do you think Leonard Fournette will do this season? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-18 04:17:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-17 16:13:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or brown </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-17 16:07:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This some Truman show type shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-12 11:15:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Mandela Effect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-07 18:21:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This can be read 4 different ways... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-04 14:48:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Baby Driver </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-04 14:46:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FIFA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-04 14:44:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Going through yellow lights. I always get scared that those cameras will get me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-29 12:41:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so sorry man. I would say definitely stay in SanFran and pursue your new career and just give this time. It will work out for the best, whether she wants you back or not! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nap time! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-29 12:13:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-23 05:27:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All those damn slogans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-23 05:14:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Semi-charmed Life by Third Eye Blind. This tune is about meth addiction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-22 21:53:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I. Hate. Pickles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-07-16 05:40:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Speed limits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-19 17:08:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes!! I get this sometimes and it really sucks! The first time it happened it hurt so bad that I got up out of bed to go get help. But when I put weight on it, the pain went away. Still felt a nagging pain for a day or two though...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-13 21:47:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The situation is like we are going to break up but still see how it goes when she gets back. So I won't have any strings attached like u said. But I just don't know how to feel about the situation if you get me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-13 05:44:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She is going away on vacation so I don't see her finding anybody over in Armenia that she could go steady with like we are now. But thanks for the advice appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-13 05:25:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1984 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:49:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was in your position for a while and I know how it feels.

You were talking about dating people from other schools and that is actually what I am doing right now! Ask some of your friends (or their girlfriends) if they know anybody and you might get lucky! I did!

Also, just let your guard down. Literally talk to girls the best way you know how and treat them with respect. I know my own damn self is the biggest thing in my way when it comes down to relationships and I always need to tell myself to chill out and just breathe.

Go for it bro! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:41:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Painfully close to adulthood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:39:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't tell anybody I don't trust.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:38:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seeing my Father with his mistress before he and my Mom got divorced. My Brother and I thought it would be a good idea to get him bagels for breakfast and take it to where he was living. The images still haunt me. I was 11.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:28:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Heathen!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What does it mean if a girl talks to me about her breakup? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:44:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So a little background here.

There is this girl that is my friend at school who just broke up with her ex-boyfriend and she is talking to me about it. We have already been friends before, but she only recently started to text me again and she talks about how she is with the breakup etc.

The reason I ask this is because this girl has always shown signs of liking me, even when she was with her BF, and she is showing more and more signs now. I was just wondering if she is just using me as a crutch for her hard time (I have helped her with her problems before) or is she looking for something more now that she is single.

Anything helps out! Thank You!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:33:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Blatant political messaging where it shouldn't be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-05-03 07:22:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One thing I have learned on this sub-reddit in particular is that there is hope. Do not give up on yourself. People always say "you don't know what you've got till it's gone". It's cliché, but i'm sure you are a big part in many people's lives, you may just not see it. I hope you heal and you are in my prayers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:00:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was a widely accepted opinion that Saddam had WMDs in 2003. Republicans and Democrats agreed. Now all people do is criticize it but people thought it was the right thing to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:34:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A subreddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:32:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Under Pressure; Logic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:28:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It depends on the owner's preference. In my house it is expected but I know plenty of people who do not care.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:11:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well the Caps had more fun!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:34:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Road trip with my extended family. I was alone in the way back of the SUV.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:45:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't talk about politics.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:55:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know. I have motivation to live just don't know what it is yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:27:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can't have one in the same? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:46:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Watch Food Inc. Very similar and exposes the food industry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:05:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sometimes it's this one tbh... Screw the rules! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:00:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a dude, but the first time I heard "Took a Pill in Ibiza" not remixed by Seeb, I had a good cry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:59:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shoot them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:58:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hitler launching "Operation Barbarossa" to invade the Soviets. Great for our world today, but a really big mistake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:56:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm with the guild... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:46:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm the exact same way! I think of it as I'm more independent from social situations, not scared.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:44:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think that no-one is either introvert or extrovert through and through. I think that situations and especially who you are around and your relationships to those people shape how you interact. People are so interesting. I want to be a psychologist :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:37:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bring a picnic I like it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:09:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "You can't start a fire without a spark" -Bruce Springsteen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:08:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey man, I know from past experience that if a girl says that "she wants to focus of school", she is not into you or just doesn't want to date. In my opinion it's an awful excuse that is like a "quick fix" and is like a middle finger right to the heart.

In my experience my crush always would tease with me like she liked me but would always back out when I started to get serious. It really sucked for me and I hope this is not the case for you. Good Luck Bro! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:59:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YEEEET </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:56:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fucked cause there's no-one. ._. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:22:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2 best teams going at it in the quarters! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:09:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For a lot of the departments, Trump is not cutting that much out of their funding. The numbers and percentages look scary and super high, but in the article there are charts that show spending is not being cut too much based on historical stats and are similar to many recent presidents.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-15 04:27:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck off Russia! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-13 07:02:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a republican... oh shit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:14:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How do Adidas NMD-R1's fit? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:44:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My shoe sizing is confusing, I am a 12 or 13. Normally a 12 fits me but it varies per brand. I just want to know how these shoes fit so I can get 12, 12.5, or 13 and have a good fit. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cool co-op country pairs? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:23:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My friend and I are looking for a good two countries to play as for a new co-op game. We are fresh off our pretty successful game as Hungary and Austria and we are looking for a new pair. Preferably in Europe but any suggestion works. Thanks!

Edit: Preferably big nations! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-05 20:02:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats good! I think the biggest thing with me is time management. I'm in HS still and playing Lacrosse takes up the time I spent before the spring just doing nothing. So it helps with my time management. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Athletes of Reddit, how does athletic participation link up with academic performance? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:56:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:52:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Teddy!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:21:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Clarks wallabies are nice for casual and fancy occasions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:24:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bless up for Spotify suggested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:47:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is really good! Even when you are not anxious it helps you be more aware and it's cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:44:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Breathe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:41:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Frosted tips... not really </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:36:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spoiler alert! The Water Diviner, its an Australian movie with Russell Crowe and it came out in US theaters like 3 years ago. Its a story about an Australian farmer whose 3 sons go off to fight for the British in WW1 (as Australia was still a colony). His sons fight and 2 die in the Battle of Gallipoli but the dad (Russell Crowe) goes to Turkey to then try and find them. It's an absolutely brutal movie with so much death and sadness and a lukewarm sorta happy ending. Also watching it in an empty theater with your own father adds to the emotion and sadness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:26:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Um... driving? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:13:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have 4 birthmarks, 3 on my arm and one right behind my ear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:42:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's totally fine! Especially if you wear a cool t-shirt under it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:41:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Too many...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-22 07:39:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would hope so if she calls 911 lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I [17M] have a friend [17M] who Is never serious. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-22 07:37:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey Reddit,

I know high school relationships and social life isn't that pressing but I'm asking this anyway. So I've [17M] had a friend [17M] for a very long time and he and I have been very good friends since middle school. I get the sense that even though we've talked and hung out countless times, we aren't truly that close. It's the kind of friendship that hasn't gone past the "first stage" if you will, even though we've been friends for years. We always joke around with each other and we make each other laugh a lot but we've never been serious, or ever opened up to each other. It has gotten to the point where, whenever I try to be "real" with him, he makes fun of me for it and almost shames me, and I don't think he realizes it.

A recent example of this comes in what seems to be a trivial form. I posted something meaningful about my life and feelings to my "finsta" (I know, trivial) and he straight up belittled me for it. It got to the point where he was making fun of how I explained how I felt in my post on a daily basis and I just snapped told him to shut up. As I said before I don't think he means too much harm but, it hurt my feelings. He's done this countless times where he tears me down for being "real" and I build myself up again. But the cycle continues. I've listened to a lot of my dear friends and others especially in my faith who have said to "get rid of the poisonous people in your life" and when people say that sort of thing to me, I can't help but think of this friend.

I'm not really considering breaking it off with this person, but I want to know what I can do to make this relationship more than what it is now. Any advice to get him to build on our foundation of friendship, and build a stronger, truer relationship.

Thanks for the advice!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cops of Reddit, how often do you speed? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-22 07:00:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:13:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Possibly gene editing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-11 18:51:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks a bunch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:39:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've seen #3 and #1.5 before! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-07 01:56:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alright itwould be awesome of you if you can tell me when you get them if they're real! I'd be grateful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:33:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks man! Never would've decided to go that deep! I'll be more careful from now on!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:07:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Both homo sapiens... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anywhere I can get Adidas Ultraboosts for cheaper? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-04 07:45:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-04 07:29:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wear this kinda stuff a lot and boots are a good spice up (like timbs) but also Clarks Wallabies are really nice with flannels, cause of the more dressy but also rugged look. (Preppy lumberjack? Lol) Thats what I wear with flannels a lot and it looks good! Also try chinos with flannels too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-04 07:24:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not sure what you're looking for like style wise but I'd say spend more on upper body (shirts, jackets, etc.) and shoes cause they are where more people focus on with your shirt being what people see and shoes being a "big deal" and spend less on pants cause they're just in between your torso and feet so just get something that matches multiple outfits (jeans, chinos adidas joggers etc.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-04 07:15:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uniqlo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-04 07:14:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ironically, The style nowadays is emanating the past decades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-04 07:09:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Athletic shorts when not working out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-04 07:08:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In what context? cause red with blue is really nice alot of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-04 07:04:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're nice but the color way looks like one of those jackets with the fuzzy inside and brown tan outside. I would go for a lighter color for stan smith's but overall 7/10! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-02-04 07:01:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me (aside from wallet killing prices) is non universal shoe sizing! I'm a tentative 12 or 13 and 12.5 rarely and I mean RARELY exists, so many times I'm either stuck with slightly too big shoes or need to break in smaller ones! It's a struggle!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:25:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a great story if there ever was one in EU4! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-31 06:44:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I'm a HS student do I don't work in an office but, one kid in my math class always takes out all of his pencils and holds them in his writing hand! He has up to 6 pencils at once in one hand!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:34:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thant makes alot of sense! Thanks alot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:57:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea I got u. I was just wondering about the neck u know how it always gets uneven?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:28:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow I just lost 30 pounds from how much u burned me! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How do you get a t-shirt to look good under a crew neck sweater? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:53:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:26:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> alot of times my recharge time is less
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:23:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And we are farting too much thus depleting our giant spacesuit
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Are you always in the friend zone if a girl calls you buddy? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:44:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So my crush calls me buddy a lot but in sort of a flirty way like "hey buddy!" Is it nothing? Cause I kinda feel weird because its like a "massive friend zone word". Any thoughts help! Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-26 03:57:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There was this one time where I was with an exchange student group and the mom of one of the girls on the trip was the chaperone, and the girl that was on the trip (lets call her Jane) would always call her mom "mother". Jane would always do this, not call her mom "mom" but "mother" so the rest of us, (being mostly teenage boys) in the exchange group decided to poke fun at her. I should probably mention that Jane is adopted and that is where my eternal shame stems from. So we all took turns teasing and mocking her and I don't really remember what I said leading up to it but it ended up with me mocking her fairly nerdy/factual voice and saying "birth giver". BIRTH GIVER! She's adopted! I knew this before I said it but I guess it was one of those adolescent moments of thoughtlessness. The whole room got quiet as everyone (yes, including me) realized my mistake. So let the eternal shame begin! I said I was sorry and it was just a minor blip in an otherwise great time, but I will certainly be ashamed for the rest of my days!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-24 06:58:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:01:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not worried just asking people's ideas. Thanks a bunch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-23 08:21:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The best things start out being uncomfortable. At least what I've experienced carpe diem! It'll be ok! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My interesting experience </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-01-23 08:18:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So this is going to come off as a tad strange but I had an experience a while back and I just decided "What the heck I'll ask Reddit". (By the way, this is my first post so don't be too hard on me!)

So I live in the DC area and as a teenager without a car I have used the Subway to get too and fro various locations with friends etc. So I was standing on the platform waiting for the train to arrive. As it roared past, right at the moment it reached where I was standing, I felt the strange urge to jump in front. I'm not suicidal, I've never seriously considered suicide, much less attempted it, but it was a really weird feeling. It was very much an out of body experience, and I think the feeling wasn't to commit suicide in particular, nor was it an "ooo what would happen" sort of experience if that makes any sense at all. It was somewhere in the middle and I felt very much out of my own control, with many fabrics of my being telling me, to jump in front of the train. Thankfully, I remained put and watched the train roll on by to it's eventual halt. I was shaken though, and I just thought about it the whole train ride and to this day, I think, "why in the world did I get the urge to jump?".

I've read some cool things on the phenomenon of how when people, say, stand on a high structure or building, get the strange urge to jump off. I don't want to say that my experience is the same exact thing but, I believe it to be similar. So I just wanted to ask, Has anyone experienced this same type of thing? Or even if you have any thoughts on it? What's it called? Anything helps! Thank You! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
