<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject48</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Too true 😭 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 17:30:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Too true 😭 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 17:29:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone like dogs? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 14:05:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone like dogs? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 12:45:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 19:41:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What kind of phone is better </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 18:56:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/jahg2s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 18:52:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Liked it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Which sign are you? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 18:42:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 22:12:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could you send me a link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 18:17:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’d like a few </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 00:12:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s only free if you buy a product first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 04:10:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For real.. me too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 09:05:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love you 🤣🤣🤣 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 01:47:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks 😊 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 00:10:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mobile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 00:10:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mobile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 23:58:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait I got a stupid question... how do you get that little trans icon and write stuff next to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 19:39:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is the second one still available? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 00:32:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you very much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 00:04:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have and I put a lot of thought before I do... I thought really hard and long and tried to imagine my life as a guy and it felt right to me... you should do what feels right to you :) hope this helps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How to deal with dysphoria when it gets really bad </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 00:01:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cw/Tw: mentions of self harm,dysphoria,depression,suicidal thoughts ETC.

I’m 15 and due to the whole virus going on there isn’t much I can do... I’m in a group home (lgbtq+) and have literally no way of really getting the help that I need as my worker does not really respond much... my mother is very sick (has been smoking for almost 40 years) and has really bad COPD and there is no way I can go out to visit to make sure she is okay... anyway back to the main story... about a month or two ago (I don’t know how or why) but I started to get really bad dysphoria about my chest and my lower half... I started Testosterone November 19th 2019 so I’m a little over 5 months on T... I noticed the big change that happens (down there) on T and at first I was really excited and happy but then all of a sudden I got into a really bad depression because I realized nothing was really there... I got so fed up to the point that I did both cut myself down there on purpose and clawed at it... as I said I’m 15 so there really is not any options for money making :( I’ve been trying to save up for a good packer... I used to have a really good one but due to my mom not being supportive in the past it got thrown away. Which is another thing... I really hate asking for stuff but if anyone has a packer or stp that they could give away could said people contact me?... I’m sorry for being all over the place but back to the story again. After it got cut it bled out a lot and idk it got bad for a little but is doing wayyy better. After I did that I had a sharp object in my hand and was feeling suicidal and just depressed af. I can’t really do anything I normally do at this point because of my dysphoria.. I can’t use the bathroom without getting physically sick or shower etc. my amazing girlfriend (who is also trans) always try’s to cheer me up by telling me it’s fine and she loves it. I been with her for about 8 months and I can say I love her proudly but lately this whole thing has been occupying my mind and I just don’t feel right... I’m sorry for the little story.. if anyone has advice could you please either DM me or just comment.. anything helps

Thank you so much for reading -Nick ❤️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-14 18:52:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is. I’ll have to check thanks though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-14 18:52:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone else having trouble with Sub-Q </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 08:05:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I find every week when I do my shot (on different sides) about an hour later it gets red, swollen, and really itchy sometimes Painful. I’m just asking if anyone else has or has had this problem and what to do about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-01 08:10:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s about time!🥳🏳️‍⚧️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-17 00:22:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> XD I'm Dying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
