<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject8</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 15:47:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> but lightsaber  is not as clumsy or random as a blaster; an elegant weapon for a more civilized age.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 10:54:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you very much, yes, although it cost a lot it has begun to be treated. At first I did not want because "he is not crazy" when he finally understood that having depression and "being crazy" has nothing to do with and he stopped behaving that way ... he has started to improve but this new facet of his has gets on my nerves
Hes 21 and i understand that it is a complex age and more when you have the problems that he has... but for many years fighting against this scourge and suffering it close to the family and now I find that my brother is one of them.

I really hope he come to understand that this twisted and victimizing mindset is getting him nowhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 10:42:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep shitty slut is the most aproximate translation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 01:49:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "...And go full stupid..."

Indeed man... indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 01:36:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  This week I discovered, to my horror, that my brother is an incel.  We are not very close but we speak once or twice a week, very basic conversations about politics or the situation in the world, as neutral as possible when we coincide visiting my mother. this week, while at my mother's house, I started browsing reddit and my brother, looking over my shoulder, saw a meme on "niceguys" a meme that horrified me but that he found "totally true and rightly" Right now I am totally in shock I dont understand how a person with higher education, not conservative political opinions in all other aspects of life, can, when comes to women, have opinions that are not only so absurd, also so far from the rest of his ideals.  Is true that he has depression, he dosesnt take care of himself, he has serious health problems and is overweight but I dont understand how he can blame women in general or anyone other than himself for his situation. I wish I could help him to put that attitude behind and I know I have to try to be pedagogical and understanding, but right now Im horrified to be honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 20:56:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But... but... Hal isnt the good guy? xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 14:57:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a surprise! I would never have imagined that that could happen.

Oh holy bearer of the saving penis, save all these poor "females" from their madness and delusion! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 14:53:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And didn't he offer to cure you of your confusion and disorder with his powerful, virile penis?

It would be surprising if didnt, its almost like a moral obligation for them, rescuers of confused women ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 14:48:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plot twist: In the middle of the season is discovered that the supposed "nice guy" who seemed to be the protagonist of our story is, in truth, a misogynist who considers that he has to pretend that he is a good person in order to void and use women as a toy who dont even consider human beings with whom you can talk or have a non-sexual relationship.

Then, when discovered, he isolates himself in his totally delusional illusion that he is a good person and becomes an even worse villain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 11:30:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think he is trying to say, without saying so, that he is that "dominant alpha male" and that any cheerful young lady can be honored to be noticed.

Not only is he repulsive in all his approach, but he knows deep down that is, he doesn't dare to say it clearly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Blair smile. Black cat, in spooktober, in tuesday thirteen.... and she smiles... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 15:58:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 16:39:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As soon as I slow down a bit I will bombard you with an absurd collection of experiences and curious facts about animals of all kinds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 18:10:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I came to say the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 21:42:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> indeed, my bad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 19:45:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is very nice to have something like that in the garden, I like winter but I find it a bit gray without these little friends running around everywhere.

How nice your lizard, that one is completely acclimated to humans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 18:28:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you very much, she lives at the door of my farm and over time she has lost a lot of fear when she sees me and that is why I have been able to get closer also, with the October sun they do not heat up at all and be more lethargic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My almost diary photo of a podarcis hispanica (female) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 14:48:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> reviewing my gallery I have found this old photo of a "eslizon" in my farm. Eslizón ibérico (Chalcides bedriagai) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 10:56:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 01:32:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a lovely place to lose yourself and think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 01:29:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kill it with fire!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 01:28:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow, your presentation is impressive, it gives the impression that you have a full and very complete life. I know what it is to not keep friends from the days of high school, university, etc ... on the one hand I do not regret it since I have nothing in common with those people but on the other hand you have that feeling that you are missing something.

I live very far away, in Spain and about baseball I know that you use a stick to hit a ball ... but hi! If you want to chat with someone about anything ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 01:21:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hoe dare you????
angry stupid "carro veloce" sounds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 00:56:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For a moment I have had flashbacks of my own terrible experiences ... I even seemed to hear "fortunate son" in the distance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 00:45:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure, he just wanted to save those poor Aryan women from progress and turn them into happy breeding machines for young and healthy Aryans ...

&#x200B;

The truth is that both Hitler and the one I describe shared, more or less, the same political ideas, it usually goes hand by hand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 23:55:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like your color scheme and yes the swords are awesome, great job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 23:51:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like to go look for my friends at the train or bus stations, or the airport with totally degrading and shameful banners, I think it is a very healthy way to show your friendship </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 23:49:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And still, he uses it better than 80% of the people on the streets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 23:49:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Si, es probable que te deriven al centro de salud mas cercano a tu casa pero si, llama a Sanitas que te darán la información, al ser asmática tienes todo el derecho del mundo (De un asmático a otra) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 23:37:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But don't stop now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 23:35:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I miss Leopold II, throwing feces on the table like a drunk monkey ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 23:33:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If she is very shy, try to make her feel comfortable with you, do not press, do not ask too much, try to be relaxed in the date, its not so important what you do or where than she notice that you are a calm person and if you are funny... that's it ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 23:31:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I could be wrong, of course, but it gives me the impression that when she asked for your number she saw you excited and realizing that you might have a romantic interest (and she didn't) it was better to put space in between.

Once again, I could be wrong but I'm afraid she doesn't want anything, I don't know, that's the feeling she gives me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 21:35:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> reminded me of a creature with a certain hygiene problem that swarmed my role-playing club years ago. He claimed to be the last feminist man in the world and defender of women and according to him "modern society forces women to fight against men, something for which they are not prepared. With how happy they are in their kitchens and homes" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 21:29:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> he is the messiah!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 21:27:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Si por supuesto, como dice el adagio:  "Discutir con idiotas es como jugar al ajedrez con una paloma; no importa lo que hagas, se paseara por el tablero, se cagara en todas partes y luego se creerá que ha ganado" no merece la pena porque además he descubierto que son inmunes a la lógica, la razón, la pedagogía... simplemente puedes intentar razonar pero con sus mentes simples solo les calan las consignas fáciles y el miedo visceral, lo que les regalan sus lideres. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> not mine but I think it fits here </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 21:21:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 20:09:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Muchas gracias pero vamos que tampoco me preocupa mucho porque es lo único que pueden hacer los troll fascistas sin la capacidad moral mental o intelectual de cualquier tipo para discutir solo pueden dar negativos.
pero si trolazo que se vea el trolazo que se lo lleva a ver si se cansan y se marchan... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 19:15:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Como diría su gran líder: Viva el vino!
Esa es la máxima de la política del PP, están brindado en la cubierta de primera clase mientras que el Titanic se hunde... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cheetara is tired of me taking pictures of her without warning </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 19:13:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 11:13:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pues ya lo tienes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 00:46:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Near my house is the gulpiyuri beach, in the north of spain, very similar to this mexican beach (look for photos "gulpiyuri") A few years ago it began to become famous and today, as soon as it is a little sun, it becomes an infected pit of crowded people, plastic and noise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Blair gets pretty to be the star of the spooky month! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 23:33:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 18:40:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow man, looks amazing, great idea! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 15:03:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Luckily was only detonating cetacean, for a moment I was afraid it was a gender reveal party and that we were all going to die </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 14:44:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too, me too ... the truth is that when I took her out of the shelter she was very shy but over time she is bringing out her true personality and she is very playful and "wilful?" (Como se dice traviesa?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> play with me hooman or I'll bite you with treachery </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 14:34:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Blair, nap in the fall sun </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 17:56:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 17:50:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very similar yes, they are species so close that I think I remember that I have read that, where their current distribution areas coincide in the south, they hybridize with some frequency. (south of Spain)

The colors of the siculus seem incredible to me, are very showy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 14:39:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please dont point to where the chair touched you ... we get the idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Podarcis hispanica, male (up) and female (down) both adult </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 14:11:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Podarcis hispanica (young male) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 21:59:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 17:07:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> me and a friend, in an old "half pipe" in the park of my city.

me: -the wood is raised and there is rusty metal, I don't like it, we better not use it ...

He: - I bet you don't have balls to do  (A que no hay cojones?\* in original spanish)

Me:  -whaaaaaaaaat?

So when i crash with a loose piece of wood, something that had to happen because of my stupidity ... i got thrown and "spike?" a huge rusty nail in my knee (used to be an adventurer ...) when i up and saw a lot of blood running down my leg i passed out ... woke up in the ER with a scar for life from my bad head </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> the beginning of autumn, Asturias, Spain </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 10:15:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 22:43:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was a shortened version of history, after seeing how things work here on their vacations they began to ask and investigate if the socialist system is better for the individual and, surprise, it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 15:50:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >Unrestricted capitalism, and unfair treatment based on power and income?

yesp a terribly and hypocritical meat grinder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 14:47:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My cousins, born and raised in the USA, really thought they lived in, I quote "the best country in the world" since they came to Europe on vacation five years ago ...  all they think about is "escape" and come live here. I am very sorry that what began as a dream of freedom and equality has ended up being ... whatever it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 14:03:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, first of all, even if something you say is true ... and what do you care? why is it your damn business? Please show me the credentials of guardian of morals and the compass of society and then I will admit that evidently, having been appointed by a higher entity as the guide of society, then, what you say will make sense but if not. .. seriously: how does it affect you or what does it matter to you?

As far as I know, people with hobbies, beliefs or ideas that may be clearly illusory for those outside of them, see believing in imaginary friends such as god, ghosts or bedroom visitors, are people who lead normal lives and current despite the fact that some of them can cause nightmares if you look at their FB (We all have a relative with the FB full of religious nonsense and, surely, political fundamentalism and hey ... they lead a normal life, more or less) In our society always, there has been a class composed in part of supposedly celibate men (I wouldnt bring a child near but each one...) who talk to imaginary friend and allow themselves the luxury of trying to be everyone's moral compass. .. and there are many people who listen to them and even respect them! and those people proselytize and pressure socially and politically ... but hey, the problem is some guys who want to have a 2D girlfriend/boyfriend of course … and let's not talk about those women cosplaying penguins who claim to be married to an imaginary being and all the evil they have done while also agreeing to be second-class citizens within their sect. There is not, nor can there be, any psychological study (serious of course) that indicates that nothing you say is true, there are studies on social adaptive needs and on the development of the person through the "obvious lie" that is not more than a phase of personality development and that HAS NOTHING BAD So living the fantasy that following a flag, some colors, a soccer team, baseball or whatever ... is normal, believing in god, allah, buddha, or the flying spaghetti monster is normal ...  What I no longer see as normal is getting into a reddit that doesn't interest you at all and rummaging through their comments just to argue with people who don't hurt anyone, I don't know ... that already seems a bit strange </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 00:59:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do not understand your need to enter a community with which you dont share anything just to bring to it the voice of your opinion, which no one has asked or wants.
Besides coming in just to argue and make people feel bad, you do it by insulting. Why? What do you gain from it? Is it your personal crusade? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 02:10:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True, the possibility of dying really makes skydiving less attractive.

The truth is that I could have chosen this one or the one who rides a bear or some other crazy person, but I think that today the orange one is by far the most dangerous and irrational

The bad thing is that according to the country and the leader, one day may not be enough to erase him, it depends on the powers that be interested in keeping him in his position. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 01:59:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I too if were to take control of a particular world leader, I would test to see if I could turn even more orange by wallowing in a bathtub of cheetos and then go skydiving, no parachute... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 01:31:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Let everyone hear who wants to hear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 00:05:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gracias majo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 23:57:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jajajaja pos bueno, pos fale, pos malegro xDDDDDD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 23:51:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Los desertores del arado odian a los de su propia clase porque les recuerdan lo que son y la traición que están cometiendo al defender al poderoso (que no la ley y menos la justicia) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 23:49:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Que se presente a las elecciones, obtenga una representacion democraticamente escogida y, entonces, que haga oposición, gobierne o lo que sea pertinente... entonces, no ahora, entonces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 23:41:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But it's part of the fun of reddit, aside from its community, which is generally fun and friendly ... this is the experience of American confusions and quirks ... and there's always one of those "karen-ish" situations.

&#x200B;

\*evil laughs in universal healthcare system </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 23:36:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does anyone know if its possible to load a blunderbuss with candy? it's for a friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 23:16:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The social and cultural influence of the church is still strong, although much less than before and, luckily, every day less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 22:55:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> waw, Well, hey, I was enlisted, I was deployed and now, years later, that I do airsoft... in my soul only burns the desire to run around and have fun with my friends, I don't know, it seems to me that here someone is a little bit " intense" man... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 22:32:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At this point in my life, closer to the end than to the start, the truth is that: if I can choose, I think I choose a good session of dungeons and dragons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 22:26:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No pasaran!
Madrid que bien resistes... (Although, in this times of Ayuso, I don't recognize this city) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 21:03:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good for you!

Hello, I'm very sorry to read what happened to you with those people. I am a convinced atheist with what it is difficult for me to understand, in part, some of the things but I fully understand that for you God is something important in your life.

Just a couple of points:

Religiosity, believing in God, does not imply having to accept, be, follow or obey a church, one thing is your relationship with God and another is a group of people, with writings and mandates created by people, who seek to control the other people's lives.

The other point is that whenever you find yourself between two options, one that DEMANDS you for something and the other, as in this case God and your personal life, that do not demand anything from you ... never give up, never give in to those who demand something of you . Choose god, choose your girlfriend and live your life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 19:09:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  I was a security guard at a gas station where a manager with an ego and absolute arrogance ruled like a small dictator (M verbally abused the employees, assigned them degrading tasks and also stole food,also he had eliminated the phones of his bosses from the contact list so that the workers couldnt bypass him and report) I didn't work for him, I did it for his direct boss and I reported these things since one of my tasks was to make sure if the rumors of his bad behavior were real, of course he didn't know anything about this point. One day, by chance in life, I had an argument with a "male Karen" in the parking and the man went to complain to the manager who then came to tell me in very bad ways and shouting. The truth is that: I greatly enjoyed that moment of "you can't say anything to me, I don't work for you” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 18:36:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am disappointed by the absence of illuminati and reptilians </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 18:24:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dizzy and wanting to bother </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 01:01:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Im not (racist, classist, sexist, homophobic) but...." "some of my best friends are (muslims, blacks, gays, foreigners) but...." And any other variant of these cheerful explanations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 19:33:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have felt very bad reading your story, right now we are fighting to get a friend out of a similar situation and this has hit me when I see her situation reflected in you.

You were young and he is a manipulative controller, from these conversations it is clear that he is still trying to maintain control over you and although you do not allow him that, being able to annoy you from time to time seems to be enough to maintain his illusion of control.

Do not blame yourself for being the victim of a professional predator like him, stay strong and eliminate this scourge from your life, if possible, with harsh legal measures, which is the only thing that human crap deserves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 21:35:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> After a very painful breakup and some terribly toxic friendships, I decided to do that, delete Facebook and leave only one Instagram account unrelated to my previous account and only for photos of landscapes, cats and warhammer ... and yes, it seems that my circle social has been reduced to just a dozen people and my D&D group but .. the peace of mind that I have achieved with this is not easy to explain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 21:30:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mac wants a flamethrower! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 20:49:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> great photo, i used to play airsoft in a very similar place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Another cepaea nemoralis in a rainy day.... and a sneaky helix aspersa at the bottom </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 20:34:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 13:16:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well... my name and surname only have 4 letters each so...

Fuck Fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 01:51:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One foggy night walking through the north of Madrid when looking up I thought "they really seem the headquarters of an evil megacorporation, cyberpunk style"

I have seen these towers in more photos on this reddit but not from this perspective, I hope you like them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Evil tower in Madrid </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 01:49:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 00:15:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I came to reddit by fortuity at a very delicate and hard time in my life and I was left for some acts of kindness and human decency that I havent seen elsewhere and that helped me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 23:42:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> actually it is almost impossible to understand some of the emperor's decisions regarding his "sons" sometimes he gives the impression that he seeks to "do everything wrong" on purpose, as with Magnus or Angron </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 22:46:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  It's not time to make a change
Just relax, take it easy
You're still young, that's your fault
There's so much you have to know (8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 21:18:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Asturias y Galicia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 15:20:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> for only $ 30 new sugar pump with free insulin dose as a gift! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 14:34:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lo mismo cuando descartemos a todos los negacionistas, a los que llevan la nariz fuera de la mascara, a los que creen que todo es una conspiración china etc... hasta sobran vacunas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 14:04:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe not, people may be tired of those old jokes ...

&#x200B;

Whispering in the shadows as fades into them: hydra dominatus ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 12:39:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am a Night lord, master of terror, veteran of the eternal war. I fear no man!

but this ... crazy motorcicle hun horde with their throat singing...

it scares me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 12:21:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Un buen himno para empezar el día, si señor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 01:03:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy demential batman noises. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 00:50:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you can only speak with Jojo references. Za warudo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 00:46:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know, I try to consult it with the pillow, but I always fall asleep before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 00:45:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >The Ordo Bathicus shall hath to reeducate such citizens on such matters of hygiene.

Give us a list of names and we will make each one a mask ... with the face of the next one on the list! and we will staple it!

Conrad style is the best style </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 00:36:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If me and my boys have been able to wear the mask on ten thousand years of eternal crusade against the false emperor, I think any imperial Karen can put it on for a while without anything happen ... although I have nothing against them joining the death guard if they wish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 00:29:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> in 1920 yes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 00:22:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh god, I have seen in my mind carts and chariots (drawn by horses like a army with poor supply systems) filled to the top with dakimakuras </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 00:06:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 23:54:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good for him rlly and He can be the only and unrepeatable "forever gopnik" and the truth is easy to him beat the survival record of that subculture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 21:00:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NoooOOOOoOOOO waaaamen are beings of light whose bodies only expel out glitter, rainbows and the smell of vanilla!!!

/S In case anyone doubted it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 20:49:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> His sentence is death! he don't deserve to be isekaed! Dont let any truck approach! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 19:11:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ExCuSe Me. ArE YOu OlD EnoUGh To Be / WoRk HERE? I WANT tO TaLk To YOUR MANAGER!

Poor man, I'm afraid hell spend his whole life in trouble with meddling Karens... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 19:03:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I collaborate with a shelter for abandoned animals and it is curious how many animals have gone through these "procedures" that come to us ... although it has a logical explanation: The "humans" who do this kind of thing are despicable and miserable and it is evident that they dont love their pets

Edit: gram </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 19:00:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When you try to camouflage yourself as weeabo and totally fail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 00:59:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ave dominux cake day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 00:58:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Currently with the ninth edition and its standards of morale and squads, a tactical use of the capabilities of the NL (-1 morale to the enemy in their checks) can work quite well, now, having said that and as they say, it is not a competitive army at high level (but yes, I have a crazy desire that the marines have two wounds already ... next month)
I don't like demons or their miniatures either, although I use slannesh daemonettes to complete my warband and I also use miniatures from "age of sigmar" (crypt infernal and other of the flesh eaters court vampires) to represent possessed and demon princes with a very NL theme.
Havocs
Warp talons
Chaos line marine (pistol B and sword)
This is the base around which I build the army depending on the situation and the battle, sometimes putting in demons or more artillery and machines (and a couple of knights of chaos if the points leave me)
but like i said, today it is not a high level competitive army but it is a fun army, the problem is that chaos is expected to use demons and infernal machines and the miniatures either dont fit with the NL or dont like to the players of the NL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 10:22:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Boss Baby, the movie. Soon in your cinema... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 10:18:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Estoy lamentando mas que nunca ser pobre y no poder darte el premio que te mereces! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 19:58:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well tonight I send my last excursion through the mountains of northern Spain to Byron, I love your idea, I think it's great and he's lucky to have a good friend like you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 14:55:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, that semi-thinking and racist ficus ... offends me on so many levels and in so many ways that I don't even know where to start </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 22:39:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I came to talk about leopold II but yes, all colonialism in general </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 22:38:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A person of extensive and exalted culture I can see here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 19:30:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Men, the world imagines that the Mediterranean are great lovers ... Im a shame for my race </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 17:10:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If the answer to the question depends on Ayuso, I can only tell you one thing ... potato </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 16:54:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i like the way you think!

Aunque atendiendo a tu nick lo mismo sobra usar ingles xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 15:55:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy lictor noises </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 15:52:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thnk you for your impious and festering words, are blessings to me!
Now I am working in a Khorne band and in my favorite, a night lords talon :D I think I have too much tendency to chaos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 13:54:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never before has my statement of "this is a Jojo reference" been more accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Unclean Squad finish at last! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 11:55:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 18:00:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hail to the Omnissiah? Magnus? Nice try heretic! xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 17:22:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Por supuesto que te dejo dudar faltaría más.. no sé si lo sabes pero tu afirmación dice mucho más de ti que de mí. 🙄 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 14:19:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no se porque, de esa escoria yo tampoco querria nada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 09:32:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look them in the eyes, smile confidently and watch ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 09:10:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All of the cannon catalogue or troma films catalogue... or any product from hong kong, i love B and Z series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 09:06:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It depends on how nervous the other person gets, the more nervous, the less likely they will pull out scissors, the more tense and competitive, the more likely they will pull out rock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 09:04:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its not an easy question, it depends a lot on whether one, two or all the parties involved are targeting you (in my experience, they were all targeting civilians, that's what civil wars have, excess of hatred) But in general my advice would be to get as much food, water and medical supplies as possible, hide and stay quiet and wait for a break in the front to flee to the nearest civilized zone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 08:54:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really expect that, daily exercises and rehab do a lot of I have to say.

Many of my friends dont understand why I make jokes about my pain, many times dark jokes, but it is as you say, not only do you fight against the pain, many times you also fight against ignorance and advice more or less well-intentioned but wrong and even stupid. At least in my case that tends to tire me even more than the pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 08:49:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh! What a beautiful and acrobatic  Jagdpanzer 38(t) (Sd.Kfz. 138/2) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rio Nalón, Trubia, Asturias </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 02:17:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 02:12:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Srry i live in spain, here i donate to "aldeas infantiles" (children village's- direct translation) In my work (a large multinational electric company) we also make toy donations but although EDP is present in the United States they only have the donation enabled for employees, im sorry I cannot help you more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 02:09:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If I told you ... I'm a degenerate weeabo, you can imagine... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 01:47:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Years ago I suffered episodes of narcolepsy, sometimes during these episodes I "dreamed" that I was doing the things I had to do but not actually doing them. One night I met up with friends to see a Cannon movie marathon, I was in charge of ordering the pizzas, three family size. To sum up, in the middle of an episode of narcolepsy I ended up ordering the pizzas three times, convinced that the previous times I had dreamed it, luckily we were able to cancel the last order, but not the previous two. In the end, I spent many days living eating cold pizza. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 01:38:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My grandmother told us stories of the black dog, a ghostly beast that loved the roads and whose vision was a sign of an early death.
Today I am a man of science, I do not believe in anything that I cannot see, but still ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 01:34:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  All right, you primitive screw-heads, listen up! See this? This... is my BOOMSTICK!  It's a twelve-gauge, double-barreled Remington. S-Mart's top of the line. You can find this in the sporting goods department. That's right, this sweet baby was made in Grand Rapids, Michigan. Retails for about $109.95. It's got a walnut stock, cobalt-blue steel, and a hair trigger. That's right... shop smart: shop *S*\-Mart... Ya got that?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 01:17:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> to unconditionally help some people who then always took my help for granted. When I couldn't help them anymore, I became the greatest villain in their eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 01:15:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Although i didnt celebrate that holiday, at Christmas I buy many toys and donate them anonymously, I have been doing it for years.

Edit: orthography </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 01:11:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the friendzone does not exist, what does exist is people who approach others with romantic interests but pretending to only seek friendship to be able to be close, stalking

If someone interests you romantically say it, if it is mutual great and if not, you have to be an adult, accept it and move on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 01:09:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Staying at a friend's house to sleep, listening to him wish his pillow good night ... and yes, his pillow was Asuna </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 01:04:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I give you the Latin version

To insult, Argentine

To swear, Mexican or Asturian (northern Spain) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 01:03:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Solitary man - Johnny Cash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 01:02:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in an area of Celtic tradition and quite a tradition of witchcraft, sometimes I find remains of rituals in the forests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 01:00:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 01:00:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My camera, any of them although I have a certain weakness for my old but reliable EOS500D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 00:57:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a glass half full of choccy milk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 00:55:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "my family and other animals" and in general all the books by Gerald Durrell, I read them as a child and they marked my entire career </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 00:54:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A challenging and or bratty attitude is extremely attractive to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 00:53:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry to read this, the truth is that I came to say the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 00:50:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the return of the soviet union! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 00:48:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My brother drives me crazy and arguing with him if a huge ball of cement was dry or not on a construction site near our house... to show that it was still wet, I jumped on it.

&#x200B;

I sank to my chest, I won the argument but ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 18:27:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No man, no... As I told you, read it again, we are proud of a comment, below the image, that says: "just give her a shower, german style" in obvious and dark humor reference to the Nazi death camps. That's why I tell you to read again because you have not understood.

In addition, if you read our comments you will see that it clearly states "as Spaniards we finally found something to be proud of" and its only that "death by words" and nothing else...

:s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 17:55:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a perfect example of terrible reading comprehension... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 16:30:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jajajaja ahora a mi se me va a hacer muy largo esperar al 28 por los emparejamientos! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 16:29:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Venga halloween te espera!!! xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 16:29:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Costumbre, mania, por no aguantar algun arranque tipo "Karen" de "Esto es reddit hablar en ingles!!" xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 15:39:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vale vale eso lo explica todo jajajaja lo que yo le decía esto de la pandemia hace que nos queramos apuntar a lo que sea!! Al menos a mí me pasa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 15:25:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jaja al menos tenemos eso seguro xD
La verdad es que me sorprende la cantidad de gente apuntada a catorce dias de cerrar el plazo, me parecen pocos pero bueno, a ver como evoluciona esto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 15:20:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo en un acceso de emocion me he metido al de halloween a ver que sale y si, creo que en r/spain seguro que sale mas gente porque aqui en un momento somos tres o cuatro... si es que lo de este año loco hace que nos apuntemos a un bombardeo yo creo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 15:12:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> El de truco o trato esta en la lista y se acercan las fechas, yo lo dejo caer xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 15:05:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 14:59:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me parece muy interesante, iba a apuntarme al navideño del año pasado pero me pillo en mudanza y una cosa y la otra... no sabia que habia tantos pero si, si formamos un grupo asi un poco majo yo voy de cabeza. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One of my old photos of larceta </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 01:28:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 16:53:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A la altura de Pintoria en la senda entre Trubia y las Caldas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Asturias, Spain </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 14:31:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 11:17:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yall got any more of that? Please? XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 11:02:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg now i can only see that Guy xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 22:40:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People have grown up being the center of the universe with rights but without duties and obligations, only whims and satisfactions. And social n, in general, feed that attitude. I believe that what is necessary here is that incivility behaviors and false news that create bubbles of mentally incompetent people be properly prosecuted and punished </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 22:12:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well rough century gives way a soft century and this gives way a entitled Karen aaaaaand here we go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 22:04:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can say the same for you, without a doubt the history of the twentieth century is very interesting but it is better not to go through it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 22:00:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, unfortunately, even if it is something that can be said with pride, in my city we put ourselves on the right side, against the fascists, but we lost the war and the consequences were ... devastating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 21:58:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's my retirement when work and the city overtake me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 21:55:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> &#x200B;

you're right, it's not that I worry too much but it's logical, thank you very much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 21:52:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks to you for commenting, I am going to take more photos of the industrial zone abandoned and reclaimed by nature so that you can see them, before the second world war, in our in-civil war, it was a prosperous, cultured and modern city of various Thousands of habitants, today it is a very beautiful place built on the remains of what is everywhere and only a few hundred live in the entire region </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 21:39:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, this is an industrial city from the mid-19th and early 20th centuries with an important weapons factory. Now there is nothing of that and they have converted it into a green area with canoes and nature trails, but there are still, more or less a kilometer north of this site, the old iron bridges for the railroad converted into walks for pedestrians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 21:37:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >Where I come from (Maine, USA) the old folks refer to the local blue heron as "shit pokes." I think because they love the mud flats where there tends to be a stench.

Years ago in the river we only had herons and some fish that we call "pixardos" but it has been a long time since cleaned the area and now there are trout, cormorants, otters ... a little of everything and the herons have multiplied </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 20:05:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nalon river, Asturias, North of Spain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [OC] Nalon river, Asturias, Spain. I hope you like it </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 19:40:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> pillar of an old railway bridge, today it is the island where the river herons nest. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 19:37:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Valle del Nalon </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 19:25:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 01:14:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have made me laugh, I didn't want to, it is not my proudest moment ... but you have made me laugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 23:09:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can see it in my mind, clear as day, singing through tears for the missed opportunity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 23:06:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My final... emerald... splash! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 22:40:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh? Are you approaching me?

Even though I'm Indonesian Chinese, do you approaching me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Asturias, Spain </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 13:49:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 16:10:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lol you dont know how much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 12:53:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Deeply disappointed that the best comment is not to: "furiously jerk off on a rooftop while howling at the moon"... naked of course </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 12:47:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I face these "masterminds" i always say the same thing: so if I hit you with a brick and you ask me to really stop, the only thing I have to do is hit harder until you shut up, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 12:43:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only thing that could improve the scene is someone on a heavy "communist" accent saying: "And if he dies, he dies" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Asturias, Spain </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 22:36:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 22:48:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Si claro, pero la gente tiende a tomarselo a una especie de competicion de ganar-perder y demostrar algo y por eso en vez de estar mirando como mejorar las cosas, al menos eso me parece a mi en este caso, se dedican a intentar demostrar algo, no se. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 21:05:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Si la idea es la leche, por suerte a nuestro jefe le gusta demasiado ir a esquiar y creo que esta de acuerdo con eso de quedarse en casa los lunes... aparte de que, efectivamente, es la reunion mas tonta del mundo, como no nos contemos el fin de semana y nos vayamos de pinchos no se me ocurre para que iba a servir salvo para perder el dia... pero es lo que tiene cuando los de RRHH quieren demostrar lo indispensables que son... y resulta que lo mismo no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 20:52:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uuuummmm no se que decirte, en mi oficina por ejemplo aunque somos un 80% de españoles tenemos una buena representacion de gente de toda europa y tambien de "locales" que hemos trabajado fuera y hemos adquirido otra cultura del trabajo.
Se nota mucha diferencia entre los que van a la oficina 9-11 horas diarias a calentar silla y apenas hacen nada pero tienen "mucha presencia" y los que vamos lo justo y necesario pero trabajamos.
Ya antes de la pandemia yo solia trabajar bastante desde casa y salvo algun pequeño accidente como abrir sesiones que solo podemos abrir en terminales de la oficina desde casa y que se volvieran locos los de seguridad informatica, la verdad es que siempre ha funcionado muy bien pero claro, no se hasta que punto es un caso aparte lo de ser una empresa internacional con estandares no tan rigidos como los tipicos del pais... no se si me explico. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 20:49:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Que no te extrañe pero nada de nada, yo estoy plenamente convencido y ademas el año pasado por casualidades, los de RRHH la fastidiaron mucho con las vacaciones y estan un poco en el "punto de mira" creo que intentan hacer "de mas" para demostrar que son valiosos.

Bueno, eso y la cultura que tenemos en este pais de que si no estas 12 horas sentado en la oficina en verdad no estas trabajando, aunque por suerte eso esta quedando atras junto con el "encargado lameculos" de toda la vida </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 19:41:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah si cosas ridículas de esas como querer hacer reuniones presenciales viernes y lunes (a ver de que narices íbamos a hablar en una reunión el lunes después de tener una el viernes) o videollamadas diarias de control se plantearon, mas por los de RRHH que creo que tienen miedo de perder su trabajo que otra cosa pero por suerte nuestros jefes han visto que el trabajo se hace y se hace bien. Salvo los chicos que llevan la microgestion de inversiones, que necesitan una conexión increíblemente potente, el resto seguimos en casa, al menos por ahora, crucemos dedos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 15:18:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Acabo de hacerla, espero que te sirva ya que yo llevo teletrabajando desde que empezó la pandemia y en mi empresa están encantados con esto del teletrabajo y yo también. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Monte naranco Asturias Spain </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 18:44:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 16:02:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> surprises me about the history is he didn't ask for training and aim to shoot insulin darts with a rifle ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 04:02:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jajaja si posiblemente causa esa sensación a mí alguna vez cuando alguien se ha despedido así sobre todo si yo tenía interés en conocer a esa persona me ha hecho pensar si he cometido algún error.
Y como buen asturiano soy muy chovinista así que te digo que si Asturias por algo lo llamamos el paraíso natural cuanto antes lo visites mejor (tengo muchas fotos aquí en reddit si quieres echar un vistazo?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 03:54:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactamente es que es una manera brusca de terminar una conversación sin dejar de ser relativamente educada pero dejando claro que realmente tampoco tienes interés en repetirla.
Como un punto intermedio entre ser grumpy y no querer insultar a nadie.
Yo ya te digo en la zona de Asturias y Galicia se usa relativamente a menudo pero en estos casos concretos, a mí no se me hace raro pero entiendo que no es algo habitual en otras zonas posiblemente </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 03:39:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mucho mejor jajajaja por desgracia mi ingles es demasiado técnico, cosas del trabajo, para ideas complejas me cuesta un poco mas.

A ver solo usaría encantado con alguien con quien, tras un encuentro cordial, tampoco tengo especial interés en volver a hablar o coincidir, como diciendo "ha sido un placer, pero si no se repite, no pasa nada"
Una manera de despedirse de un encuentro casual como por ejemplo con un amigo de un amigo o algo similar.
Sin embargo no lo usaría con alguien a quien si me gustaría conocer o a alguien que me inspire curiosidad o interés y por supuesto no lo usaría con un extranjero que seguramente no entendería esta compleja interacción social. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 03:23:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> may be by for areas? idk im from the north and here its said a lot but i also think it has certain connotations and idiomatic nuances (I have had to look for this word) because it has a connotation that i, for example, would never use with someone I really "encantado" meet.

I don't know if i explain myself :s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 02:37:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
In Spain "encantado" can be used as farewell but I have never heard it in my trips to South America (I am a Spanish native)

In Spain we use it for both things almost interchangeably, although as "farewell" it is quite informal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 01:54:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
Just with this answer, with the feeling that at least one person understands what is going through my head, you have helped me a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Poxi and the nurgletts, the unclean squad </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 01:49:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 01:25:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
It was something that always surprised me a lot of my ex-girlfriend's family, they get along! they love, talk and communicate! The first time I saw it I was very surprised since I thought that only happened on tv shows </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 01:19:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
Well, it reminded me of when in my adolescence I went into a bookstore to buy a number of X-Men and the saleswoman went crazy screaming that she did not sell pornography to children. The less people know, the more they think know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 01:14:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Behold!!!
my respectful, furry and unsolicited gifts of respect and love... and the lil carrot... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 01:07:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
Yes, you are not alone, sometimes without it coming from anywhere I have panic attacks in which I think that everyone is going to betray me, abandon me and put me aside.
 I try to control them and I tell myself that it is something that is only in my mind but unfortunately it happened to me (in a very "crazy" way) relatively recently and it is difficult to leave it behind.

I don't know if it will work for you, but what I have is a small group of "trustworthy" friends to whom I can send a message whenever and for whatever, its not good to depend on these external "stimuli" of calm but sometimes they are necessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 11:06:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my old job, the boss made a employee stand by the dumpster, making sure no homeless took out expired food that we had to throw away. The person who forced this was the manager, the same one who stole bread from the store and let the employees bear the loss in our salary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My father hit me when I was little for not being able to hit my brother </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 00:30:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
Hello, the truth is that I feel anxious and afraid (and guilty) to write about certain things and I tend to trivialize and hide them. I suppose some of you know how hard it is to write these lines.

English is not my first language, nor is my second, and I also write with the phone so please forgive my mistakes, also, I know that because of the way I write (I think it in my language and then i do the translation more or less direct) sometimes I sound strange, pedantic and weird, sorry for all that. Recently, my psychologist recommended that I begin to open up to people and tell the reasons why as an adult I am an extraordinarily reserved and suspicious person, as they say, sometimes is easier to talk to strangers so ... here I am reddit.

This happened a few years ago, the truth is that despite all the time that has passed and the continuous physical and verbal abuse, somehow I still feel bad when I remember the "bad" things that my father did, as if somehow way i was being disrespectful and betraying his memory. During a vacation, when I was little, seven or eight years old, my father, my mother, two of my mother's brothers, my little brother and I went on a trip to Portugal. It must be said that despite being a successful professional (director of a department in a big bank) my father, who couldnt go to university and study "job training" always felt belittled and neglected next to the family of my mother since all of them studied law (in truth, only he saw it that way, but that is what is insecure)  So he didnt enjoy the trip at all, spent everytime trying to impress my uncles, getting angry with the most stupid things and trying to pretend something that was not expected of him, nor was anyone asked of, of course the object of his fits of anger was us Usually the two of us, my brother and me. One of the days of the trip we went to eat at an "expensive" restaurant on the banks of the Duero, while at the restaurant my brother sat at one end of the table and I at the other, right next to my father, when the waiter we ordering food, the adults did their thing (fish, wine, those things) and the problem came when it was the turn of the little ones, since my brother, five at that time, only drank "fanta"
There was a very fun conversation between my brother, who insisted on only drinking fanta, the waiter who tried to make him understand that they only had "mirinda" which was almost the same and the rest of the family who was finding the situation very funny, we all were having a good time, from the waiter who joined the game quickly to my brother who was starting to enjoy being the center of attention ... everyone had a good time except my father of course, mad with the situation, feeling that my brother's behavior was somehow making a fool of him, he began to yell at my brother and demand that be quiet, that drink water and that not bother anymore, with that he only got my brother will be more involved in his behavior and that people will really start to look at him, not because of the child's behavior, for his own. Out of his mind, unable to reach my brother from where he was and totally maddened with shame, my father threw a monstrous slap with all his strenght... only it was direct to my face, which I didn't expect, nor did I know it was. passing by before ending up on the ground, scared, confused and in pain. Not being able to hit my brother, he decided that hitting me would be about as good.  I don't remember much of what happened next, I know that someone, I think one of my uncles, took me out of the restaurant and took me to eat an ice cream, I don't know what happened to the rest of the family but over the years I have found out that the waiter did not return to the table, another had to go to attend I suppose the man was horrified, my uncles never again went anywhere with my father and my mother had a "conversation" with him that made at least during two or three years he would not try to hit us again.


It is a short and somewhat silly story but it is a sample of the level of threat, aggression and fear with which we had to live our childhood, always hiding and lying for fear of doing or saying something that could upset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-22 00:44:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >Don’t see enough night lords, looks great


The problem is not seeing or not enough of them ... the problem is that you never see the one who kills you.

Ave dominus nox! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 18:07:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Y con mi hacha!!
Hay que averiguar quién es! Chico identifícate! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 17:02:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Por favor tenemos encontrar la manera de identificarlo para hacernos sus amigos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 01:51:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Si ya me fui también a goodanimemes pero con todo, lo de entrar todos los días a seguir con la guerra aunque sea con upvotes es algo... el tema es que a mi me pillaron por banda la primera oleada de "shadowbans" con lo majo que me había quedado el meme de ese día.... en fin...
A ver, Podemos es el resultado de una situación, una crisis económica y social terrible que no deja de crecer, ademas, ya ves toda la "guerra sucia" que les hacen y "a toda acción se opone...." vamos, lo típico de que a todo lo que les tiran encima, desde partidos prefabricados a juicios locos y absurdos, pues claro, es mentalidad de asedio y ellos se vienen arriba a veces con excesos de utopía, no se puede negar.
Capitalismo? Yo soy comunista, creo que el capitalismo es necesario y hasta natural, en verdad creo que la imagen "general" del comunismo esta muy difuminada y confundida, pero bueno, son matices ya sabes, lo principal es que los medios de producción tienen que ser de los que los usan, no de nadie mas... pero vamos que quitando eso, lo que produces lo tienes que vender, sino, no ganas pasta.


Y si, a ver, el sistema educativo y social son... en fin... entre que tenemos un trabajo importante ya desde los 50 por cambiar la percepción de la ciudadanía y aumentar su egoísmo y su incultura... y luego, por otro lado, todo lo que se deriva de esto (yo, yo, yo y solo yo, el resto nada, etc...) pues vivimos en una época donde la solidaridad o la sociedad no importan nada, ya ves que hoy por hoy hay gente que prefiere salir de fiesta aunque eso pueda matar a sus padres y abuelos! (Y conozco a una chica, auxiliar de enfermería que ademas trabaja cerca de una planta COVID que piensa así, no le importa nada lo que pase a amigos, vecinos y familiares, solo botellon y fiesta...) esta es la sociedad que han "diseñado" y esto es lo que tenemos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 00:52:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 00:37:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> El mensaje que te decía respecto a la radicalizacion de la gente:

[https://www.reddit.com/r/es/comments/iay4do/todavía\_estamos\_así/g1rv6bz?utm\_source=share&utm\_medium=web2x](https://www.reddit.com/r/es/comments/iay4do/todavía_estamos_así/g1rv6bz?utm_source=share&utm_medium=web2x) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 00:33:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Y contrastado! Y de todo... vamos esta a un derrame de OKdiario como poco xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 00:32:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mira a ver, que el mensaje lo pusiste hace diez horas, hace mas de 48 que archivaron esta causa, como todas, por falta de.... todo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 00:24:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo me fui de animemes pero sigo entrado todos los días a poner upvote en la guerra! No podemos permitir eso de ninguna manera.
Veamos podemos lleva un programa muy parecido al que llevaba el partido Socialista en los 80 vamos un partido social democrático que busca recuperar el poder del pueblo todo ese rollo muy bien lo veo bien pero me parece blanco yo diría que soy comunista bastante cerrado bastante de la línea dura.

Oye me encanta encontrar a un compañero de trinchera de animemes!

Edit: Perdon por no poner nada antes, me salto el mensaje y estaba jugando y dicte por no parar y deje temas fuera, pero vamos que si, las redes sociales, los medios "dinamicos" que permiten la interactuacion provocan efectos muy concretos, voy a poner doble post porque hable de esto hace unos pocos dias y es mejor enlazar. Perdona el caos del mensaje, es que casi me derriban xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 23:33:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Si y una cosa que se que no tengo que hacer... pero es tan difícil no hacerlo, es lo de no ser desdeñoso ni insultante, hay que ser pedagógico, tranquilo, claro y conciso porque de otra manera solo logras que se radicalicen mas y mas en su discurso ya que tu los desprecias pero los suyos los acogen y al final la sensación de grupo y de inclusión hace que se vuelvan mas radicales.

Por otro lado, ufff, entiendo lo que dices con los votos, el problema es que claro yo lo veo desde otro punto, quiero decir, para mi PSOE ni siquiera es izquierda y Podemos me queda a la derecha la verdad... pero si, a veces hay que votar a Kodos y escoger el mal menor o hacer presión con ello, el problema es que en España cuando haces eso no aprenden, en otros países puede, aquí... no, salen, dan una rueda de prensa diciendo que les ha llegado el mensaje, que comprenden lo que quieren sus votantes... y al día siguiente es lo mismo.

Por mi trabajo tengo que tratar con gente de toda Europa y, la verdad, a veces hablo con ellos y ni siquiera los de países con una tradición "política" parecida a la nuestra como puede ser Italia o Grecia parecen entender bien las cosas tan absurdas que nos pasan aquí. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 23:22:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> LOL my iron warriors they could say that of "iron out, iron in ... although mostly lead" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 23:01:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No te preocupes, la conversación se ha desvirtuado bastante.

El problema esta en que muchas veces cuando hablamos de fascismos, no van a querer razonar y cuando salen a la calle gritando sus consignas, eso mismo, en si, es una agresión contra todos los que piensan, sienten, etc... distinto.
Quiero decir, imagina que eres extranjero, homosexual, librepensador o cualquier otra cosa que esa gente odia... y te encuentras con eso y sientes miedo, sabes que si estuvieras solo, sin nadie cerca, etc... estabas acabado y eso es real.

No se puede consentir que según que ideologías se organicen para salir a la calle a hacer presión, después de todo, si ellos ganaran algo, unas elecciones de lo que fuera o el poder por el medio que fuera, perderíamos todos.

Y si, lo de moverlos a otra cosa y hacer que vean lo tonta de su ideología seria perfecto, pero mira como se aferran y como se cierran, este es un país de hoolligans aquí no importa nada mas que "que pierda el otro y que ganen los míos" aunque los tuyos te vayan a destrozar la vida si ganan (si, conozco gente en la salud publica y en la enseñanza que vota a PP o incluso a VOX xD) y cuando tratas con ese nivel de alienación lo único que queda es asegurarte de que al menos, no hagan daño a nadie mas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 22:43:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i can confirm, im the dinosaur who clap after all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 22:39:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vale... y esto que tiene que ver con lo que yo digo? A ver, no me entiendas mal, no me estoy poniendo en plan gato panza arriba es que, si alguien es racista, machista, clasista, lo que sea-ista pero sabe hablar, comportarse, no hace un proselitismo excluyente ni busca destruir la libertad del resto, solo tiene sus ideas y "es feliz con ellas" bueno, pues me da pena pero es su vida, que la viva como quiera.


En serio, tan difícil es de entender? Si alguien es irracional, fascista y quiere imponer sus ideas... ladrillo. No se, a mi mi vecino que es un señor muy facha no me ha hecho nada, a veces discutimos y a veces nos ayudamos y ya esta, es que no me parece tan difícil de entender, pero claro, el no intenta imponer su fascismo a todo el mundo.

Ser violento e intransigente con los violentos e intransigentes no es rebajarse a su nivel, es eliminar la amenaza. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 22:11:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bueno al parecer dijeron que iban a respetar la distancia de seguridad y que se iban a poner mascarillas que ahora se inventen historias pero engañaron a todo el mundo... que con todo, sabiendo con quién se la juegan tenían que haber colocado policía cerca aunque la verdad lo sentiría mucho por los pobres policías que tuvieran que tratar con esta gente.
Y sí por supuesto la gente cercana que no sabe lo tontos que son pues ahora tendrán que recibir una visita de los investigadores esos chándal rastreando para decirles "mira tal persona que tú creías que era normal no lo es y ahora tienes que hacerte la prueba por su culpa"
Se ven venir montones de dramas pequeños y tristes pero dramas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 22:02:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No les quites la ilusion!!! Dejalos que sean felices mientras pegan macarrones en un folio y juegan con plastilina a la espera de que alguien les enseñe el virus.

Na en serio, yo lo lamento por familiares y amigos, que ahora a saber lo que pasa por juntarse con estos esperpentos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 21:56:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tio, que son los que gritaban "Queremos ser normales, no subnormales" los esloganes son claros como el agua... pobrecitos xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 21:55:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Posiblemente porque estuvo cerca de alguien que dio positivo o algo de esto... la coña es que luego, pendiente de esta prueba, va a la manifestacion... yo no lo entiendo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 21:54:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pues nada queridos manifesters, ya estáis corriendo todos a haceros pruebas... y vuestros familiares y amigos que han permitido estos comportamientos de tarados... hala, saturar sistema sanitario y llorar!

Puf encima en Madrid, disfrutar lo votado.

Que pena siento, que lastima y transmito toda mi comprensión y solidaridad para el personal sanitario, de seguridad y limpieza que va a tener que lidiar con estos niños grandes y sus neuras y sobre todo, sus tonterías.
Espero de verdad que según vayan pasando por vicaria llorando por miedo al virus que no pueden ver, esos que quieren ser normales y los pobres solo llegan a sub... reciban la visita de la policía y les caiga encima lo que no esta escrito, por tontos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 21:09:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm usually a lurker who only gives upvotes ... but this time I had to come in to say that your conversion and paint job is awesome! And I am a chaotic devotee! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 20:49:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
mother and son </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rescued rabbits in the shelter ( there are many more to rescue... but work in progress) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 20:48:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anochecer en Asturias, entre Oviedo y San Claudio </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 20:43:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 20:29:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Madre mía, en serio podíais poneros de acuerdo para no repetir lo mismo todos, todo el tiempo... que uno tiene un tiempo limitado como para andar repitiéndose.
Claro que tiene que ser el ultimo recurso, pero vamos a ver en serio, se que no lo entendéis, que esto es un desvío mas del tema que es los fascistas pero a ver, vamos a volver a intentarlo por millonesima vez.
Es una paradoja, algo que suena contrario a la lógica mantenida y es que ante una irracional e ilógica, pero astuta, usurpación de la libertad de expresión para destruir esta misma, sin aceptar diálogos o lógicas, la única solución, la ultima y por desgracia la única, es la violencia cuando es necesaria.
Esas cosas de apariencia humana, que se llenan la boca hablando de cosas que no entienden (todos sus medios son libertad y democracia como nombre, ja!) no aceptan ni entienden, ni quieren dialogo! Y como el mismo Popper dice: "Ha de ser el ultimo recurso" muy bien, dime tu, como razonas con un tarado que ni habla, ni escucha, ni acepta, ni comprende, ni lee... solo quiere ganar como... como... ya lo sabes.

Es que es gracioso, tu propio enunciado lo dice "ultimo recurso" es que no se porque estoy escribiendo tanto la verdad.

Y como corolario, como le he dicho a tooooooodooooos los demás, claro, os digo "mirarlo en wikipedia" porque evidentemente quiero dejar un hueco evidente en mi lógica para que lo explotéis. Madre del amor hermoso. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 18:49:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jajajajajaja </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 18:46:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pues como decía, me alegro de que hayas leído toda su obra y muchas otras mas... ahora prueba a volver a leerla, con la mente abierta y la comprensión lectora que da la edad y la experiencia a ver si así... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 18:44:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jajajaja, me encanta que quieras usar mis argumentos contra mi, gracias, se que soy bueno pero imitarme no va a mejorar tu discurso.

No, no es reducionista, solo estoy hablando de la temática fascista.
No, no la contradice, solo estoy hablando de la paradoja causada por el fascismo.
Quien sabe, lo mismo solo lo he mirado en wikipedia... y aun así, tendría razón... quien sabe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 18:42:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True colooooors (8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 18:41:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, una vez mas, no estas entendiendo nada de nada.
Primero, leete de verdad la paradoja y la teoria, porque veo que la has visto con unas gafas un poco... manchadas.
Segundo, la exposicion de unas ideas que quieren acabar con la libertad de la gente es una agresion, se que ahora quieres hablar de proporcionalidad pero si ahora, hoy, se deja salir a esta escoria a la calle gritando y no se les para, mañana iran a Bilbao a golpear a gente y obligarles a cantar el cara al sol y pasado sera aun peor... anda venga, coge, lee, vuelve a empezar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 18:38:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pues temo que deberías volver a leer.

Entiendes lo que significa paradoja? A ver, lo voy a intentar una ultima vez.
Popper propone una idea utópica de un mundo tolerante y maravilloso, pero entonces, cuando le enfrentan a la realidad de la intolerancia sin medida y sin razón, la fascista, es cuando surge esa paradoja.

NO se puede ser TOLERANTE con los intolerantes.
NO tolerar a los intolerantes, te hace intolerante, es un uso lógico, apropiado y, por desgracia, necesario de la autodefensa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 18:36:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, expresar ciertas ideas que implican odio, por motivos raciales, sexuales, económicos, etc... es una agresión en si mismo y por lo tanto el fascista, por el mero echo de ser fascista, es una agresión con patas.

Repito, si crees que defenderte, usando la violencia si da lugar a ello, es lo mismo que agredir, entonces es que tienes un serio problema de comprensión </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 18:29:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A ver que acabas de aprender algo nuevo y lo repites cual lorito.
Popper dice que su teoría es ESA pero que hay paradoja en ella y es que en una sociedad con libertad ilimitada los intolerantes la usaran para acabar con la tolerancia, por ello su teoría es una utopía, porque a los fascistas hay que darles duro o perderos la libertad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 18:24:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, que sentido tiene decirte que lo busques en wikipedia si espero que no lo leas? Eres absurdo o es que no tienes ya nada mejor que decir?
Pretendes decirme que quiero desarmarte mientras te doy armas? Que clase de lógica es la tuya?

A ver, que ya no se como decirlo, los fascistas salen a la calle buscando imponer sus ideas a la fuerza, discriminando y odiando... no hay agresión en eso? En serio crees que las dos cosas son iguales? Agredir y defenderse de una agresión es lo mismo? Por favor eh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 18:19:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> En un principio iba a decir que si lo entiende pero que no lo quiere ver... pero después de leer sus  respuestas creo que tienes razón, no lo entiende. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 18:18:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Espera, espera, espera... me estas diciendo que los fascistas no usan la violencia? Apaga y vamonos.

A ver, ahora otra cosa, lo que te he puesto es la "paradoja" en la que explica el fallo del razonamiento de "todo blanco y negro" y el porque a veces, la teoría de la "no violencia" no encaja con la realidad...

En serio, que tu eres el que habla de la comprensión lectora de otros pero hijo... madre mía... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 18:11:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Si ambos te parecen igual de fascistas, entonces no se yo si puedes hablar de comprensión lectora o de comprensión en general... solo digo eh . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 18:09:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, no lo soy, pero tampoco voy a desviar la conversacion. Soy comunista, tu no sabes lo que es eso y yo no voy a perder tiempo explicandolo.

Aqui y ahora te hablo de la paradoja de Popper:  Menos conocida es la *paradoja de tolerancia*: La tolerancia ilimitada debe conducir a la desaparición de la tolerancia. Si extendemos la tolerancia ilimitada aun a aquellos que son intolerantes; si no nos hallamos preparados para defender una sociedad tolerante contra las tropelías de los intolerantes, el resultado será la destrucción de los tolerantes y, junto como ellos, de la tolerancia.

Mirala el wikipedia.

Y te digo una cosa: "Los comunistas también" No, una vez mas intentas ridiculizar y reducir al absurdo porque en tu interior sabes que la superioridad moral de la izquierda se pierde si nos rebajan al nivel de la derecha, pero es que eso no es cierto.

En fin, como decia, no me voy a salir del tema: No, a los fascistas ni agua. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 18:04:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, los fascistas se amparan en la libertad de nuestra sociedad para intentar destruirla, los antifascistas defienden esa libertad a como de lugar... evidentemente ellos pueden decir lo que quieran, pero es mentira.
Al fascismo se le combate, sin piedad ni medida, punto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 18:00:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, al combatir la intolerancia tienes que ser intolerante pero eso no te hace como ellos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 09:49:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I m caught in an absurd litigation with the Tax Oficce for my own stupidity. I owe them 1.37 euros and since the payment period has passed ( the debt is from 2017, part of the problem is that neither they or I realized it until now ) they dont help me fill out the documents, im not able to do it alone and im not going to pay a lawyer for that money so ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 09:41:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sic... it's tough to be a God </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 09:29:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are certain political movements that are learning all their doctrine from the O'Bannon school, which the friend and companion of the trump set in Italy to "train" the European far right and from those... these </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 23:21:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A ver hay muchos motivos para esto:
Partimos de un sistema educativo diseñado para crear "analfabetos funcionales" a ver, que si quieres estudiar, se puede, pero si estas a pasar los cursos obligatorios y solo leer el marca o los grupos de wassap... también, así sale una mayoría que apenas entienden como funciona el mundo.
Luego ideologos e ideologías muy simples, de odiar lo distinto, al que tiene otro color, al que piensa diferente, a lo que no entienden (y recordemos, solo leen el marca, no entienden nada) y claro, cuando aparece un voxcero....
Por ultimo, las redes sociales, FB, youtube, etc, generan contenidos que atraen la atención por ser controvertidos, raros, que provocan discusiones... y al mismo tiempo crean una burbuja alrededor del interfecto que termina pensando:
A) que el 95% piensan como el y los que no, es que están engañados y sectarizados
B) Que las ideas mas extravagantes, raras, locas, absurdas, etc... son las de la gente lista (como el) que no se dejan engañar y que saben mas que el resto (como el)
Resultado.... 1100 imbéciles gritando en plaza Colon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 21:47:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Es que es eso, yo los miro y es lo único que puedo ver, niños pequeños y muy malcriados que no entienden nada, que se dejan llevar por miedo atávicos y manipulaciones soeces y que solo saben llorar, llorar y patalear... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 21:35:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  [https://www.reddit.com/r/FuckYouKaren/comments/ias44m/but\_my\_freedom111/](https://www.reddit.com/r/FuckYouKaren/comments/ias44m/but_my_freedom111/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Peña del cuervo, Monte Naranco, Oviedo </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 19:19:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 14:19:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> she is, I took her out of a shelter where i collaborate and now she lives on my farm with her brothers and sisters is by far the most mischievous of them all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 14:06:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My pleasure, i take this photo testing the portrait lens of my camera.  [https://i.imgur.com/Wvl8dl4.jpg](https://i.imgur.com/Wvl8dl4.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 13:52:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shes a cross between a collie and a typical sheepdog from here in the north of Spain, it is not a regulated breed but there are many "like her" in this area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 13:44:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol, man... XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 13:44:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, she is... And a bit silly when she wants </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My backyard forest II (Asturias, Spain) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 13:10:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Nuka, exhausted after wallowing in the park </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 13:04:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 21:21:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/allisajojoreference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 20:49:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All is a Jojo reference! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 18:56:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hydra dominatus! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My backyard forest (Asturias, Spain) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 01:33:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 15:45:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
I see your bet and raise, if we have to fall in combat, well we fall

 [https://www.reddit.com/r/Animemes/comments/i7s2aw/my\_little\_lurker\_shitpost/](https://www.reddit.com/r/Animemes/comments/i7s2aw/my_little_lurker_shitpost/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My little lurker shitpost </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 15:43:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 15:30:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you a guild wars player? :o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 22:44:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "It is, of course, much easier to shout, abuse, and howl than to attempt to relate, to explain" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 21:30:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You see the distant flames
They bellow in the night
You fight in all our names
For what we know is right
And when you all get shot And cannot carry on
Though you die La Resistance lives on (8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 21:11:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
Here we dont want treacherous legions, poxwalkers, genestaler cult or any other xeno heresy! For the emperor! For the humanity! For the posterboys of Macragge! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 19:45:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Claramente el intermedio en la sexta si </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 18:06:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
Who has let out the guy from the Palestinian area that walks next to the orangutan? Why isn't one in the zoo and the other in a detention camp?

/s (surprise) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 15:52:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pero han cumplido con su misión en la vida xD

Yendo, con y 😊 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 14:51:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Esperemos que a las quesadillas les este yendo genial, se lo merecen! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 14:16:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
I'm so sorry you had to find an idiot of this size, OP, although I suspect that it will neither be the first nor the last unfortunately.
You can almost feel in the message how you go from being his dream "Astolfo" to being the object of dark guilt post-jerk off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 02:20:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  is very likely that the attacker has prepared a quiet place where to dispose of his victim, the most dangerous moment for him and therefore the one that gives you the most opportunities is when the attack occurs, before he can reduce you and take you to his lair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 22:20:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
Well, I can't speak for the whole world of course but at least where I live, after apostatizing you have to make sure they delete you from the parish file, only then do they really stop taking you into account in their calculations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 20:21:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Well, after all these years, I had never considered that possibility that you mention and now I feel a bit silly because sounds perfectly logical.   She could be a person from the neighborhood who is inadvertently stalking us and when we disappears from the area, she will elaborate a complex and strange story to get our new data. The thing is, it sounds very logical, very Ockham's razor.  LLD is a very clever girl (like a raptor) she lives many years in the big city and has acquired a sixth sense for weirdos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 17:39:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
The story is rare and if you think about it terrifying because of the absurdity and inexplicability of. For a long time it has had me worried and paranoid but it can also be taken with some humor and "nerdism"
 If in a few years I can finish my own podcast saying: "This is OP. If you are listening to this message, you are the Resistance." Will have been worth! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 17:30:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Well, if it turns out to be my daughter from the future who is here to stop Skynet and Bolivar Trask before they make a diabolical alliance that brings the end of humans and mutants ... it would not seem as strange as reality is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 03:20:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Well, on the one hand I am glad that my first impression was correct but I regret the presence of these snails as I work trying to stop invasive species, although in my case they are American ones that reach Europe.
Cepaea are beautiful snails, Im trying to identify a few unique phenotypes of the area where I live. Thank you very much for the information, it is an exciting topic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 03:07:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  I'm very sorry for what happened to you with the stalker situation, I hope it's over and everything is fine. For my part, the truth is that after that experience, so strange, I didnt know more about the strange woman but I admit that I became very suspicious and paranoid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 02:35:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
Thank you very much, at first glance I thought it was a cepaea nemoralis or hortensis but it cannot be because it is in the US ... by chance you will not know which specific species is it true? It would help me a lot to know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 02:24:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> let's go by parts as Jack the ripper would say
Humanism follows the precepts of man as the very center of the entire society and their well-being as the final goal. not seek individual well-being, since that would be something else more similar to anarcho-libertarianism or some madness of those, what it seeks is the well-being of the whole society, giving the individual as much freedom as possible.
Another thing, I have not said that in Islam women are oppressed, no more than in any other patriarchal religion of the time and whose precepts continue to apply, but come on, the same happens with women trapped in Catholicism, Protestantism or any other religion
In the next point you say "And even more so if they repress their desires" nobody, absolutely nobody, real or not, can tell another person to reject desires that can perfectly be freely reciprocated by another person (obviously things like pedophilia, necrophilia, zoophilia ... are left out because there can be no consent) but I repeat, no one, man or supposed god can judge some desires or reject them. It's totally unacceptable...
Indeed in another time racism was a common thing and slavery and many other things, it is also true that in its time and in many respects Islam was more modern and liberal than other doctrines ... but time has passed, the rest have evolved more or have disappeared
Once again, there is no subjective morality, morality defines society and society defines morality, absurd things, such as incest, are excluded and you do not need something like a god for that, for example in this case , that of incest, we are talking about serious health problems which, for the good of all, is not acceptable.
New problems and new challenges will always appear, who knows if in a few years transhumanism and cybernetic relationships or the lack of work due to the replacement of human workers by machines will not change the paradigm of everything we know ... but that The bridge will be crossed when we arrive and it certainly cannot be done by applying an outdated rule. Once again, I have no problem with everyone believing in whatever they want ... in their privacy, but proselytizing and applying mandatory rules, based only on beliefs, that cannot be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 00:35:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where did you take this photo?  it is to know a little more about the distribution of the species </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 00:28:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Well to start I have to discuss something about what is stated in your text and it is the use of objective and subjective. The objective is something inherent to the object, something that is true, antenthetic and real with the independence of the observer ... for that, God, in any of its forms, should be real, something that does not happen and it should be something universal, something that does not happens.
If we apply the rule that with a group of people believing in it, it goes from being subjective to objective, then humanism is as objective as Islam, Christianity or Hinduism to give examples.

Religious, conservative, reactionary beliefs do not want anything to change, however society evolves, I do not understand how ending outdated and corseted roles of gender, sexuality or beliefs can be bad for a society. I am not saying that you do not believe in the things you want to believe, as long as it is something individual and is not imposed on the collective. If someone, because they believe in their god, does not like gays, liberated women, people of another color or ethnicity ... well, I feel sorry for him, but it is not acceptable for a society to base their values on that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 23:48:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> With pleasure.
What you have said is that it is okay to oppress a person and their feelings just because of a belief. I have nothing against people believing in their favorite imaginary friend, but proselytizing is sick and criminal.
A society, whatever it is, cannot base its judgments and prejudices on religious motives, that is twisted and cruel, it forces you to think, be and believe in a specific way or be expelled from society, the human being is better than that.
Leaving aside the absurdity of continuing to base society on laws and totally absurd beliefs with more than 1440 years (or 2020, it does not matter which prophet you follow) What is sick is to pretend that the rest do it too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 23:32:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All is malicius and wrong men </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 23:29:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apostasy my friend, apostasy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 23:10:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
I have tried everything, investigated to see if was someone knew of my girlfriend, someone related, if it was a joke, if was someone from my past ... but I never found anything at all. The only option that comes "less creepy" is that it was a joke from someone, who did not know that I had moved and now does not dare to say anything because of the twisted situation. But although it is what I would like, I know it is not.


Now I don't think about it that much anymore, but for years this has stolen my sleep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Crazy strange lady looks for me in the middle of the night and lies about who she is </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 21:01:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi, I just discovered this community and I think this story might fit well because of how weird and creepy it is.  English is not my first language (nor my second) and I am on a phone with voice dictation .. sorry for everything

&#x200B;

A few years or so ago, I started working and moved from my parents' house to a small rental apartment with my girlfriend. The landlady, a charming woman, having two young people as rented went out of her way with us and the truth is that it was a very pleasant time we spent there.
After a couple of years the owner informed us that her daughter was returning from England (in my country working abroad is very common) and although she didnt want to, she asked us if we could move, we were sorry but it was understandable and as at that time we already had some money save, we decided to move to a larger house in the suburbs.
The weird thing comes now, a couple of weeks after moving, the landlady's daughter calls us very worried and tells us an incredible story. One day during the week, at two in the morning, someone began to knock on the door insistently, scared, she went out to see and found a young woman with a “strange” aspect with a huge dog who was asking for me insistently . "Hi, I'm OP's cousin, I need to talk to him" the Landslady's daughter (LLD) informed her that i no longer lived there and at first she didn't want to believe it and kept insisting, in the end when she saw that she didn't get anything and asked for my new address but LLD didnt see anything clear what was happening, she didnt want to tell her and when she saw that the woman did not leave, she threatened to call the police, that is when she left.  The point is that the description does not match any of my cousins and they werent, I already know. I do not know who that woman was, her description does not fit with anyone I know, we do not know what she wanted from me or how she knew so much information about me (She gave LLD a very detailed description of me) Thanks to my work, I have access to a lot of personal data, I have searched and I have gone crazy trying to imagine who it could be, what she wanted from me one day at dawn and why she lied about who she was ... and I have no idea, to today it still scares me to remember this strange story that remains unexplained. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 01:38:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Que gente mas tra...viesa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 21:38:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Hello, first of all, happy cake day! I am so sorry to read your story. I have saved your message to be able to read updates on the subject and I wanted to tell you that, if you are interested, study coming to Spain. There is a program of political refugees for reasons of sexual hatred and it is an open and liberal society in that sense. I have found this page that may interest you.

 [https://kifkif.info/en/](https://kifkif.info/en/)


Please stay safe and strong and if you need to talk ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 23:21:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
Wait a minute. Are you telling me that the average American can read? It is incredible, one day they are hitting a bone against a rock ... and the next day they are the same but some can read. where is the limit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 23:17:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
almost everyone looks good in a Hugo Boss suit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-26 20:16:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amazing shot! Internet is pleased! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 22:47:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bueno teniendo en cuenta que se supone que el idioma griego clásico tiene unos 4000 años de antigüedad más o menos y que el tal Matt elliott que por cierto no lo conocía hace música desde el 2000 más o menos creo que la palabra tiene su origen en antigüedad más bien 🤔 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 16:15:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me estrujó el corazón sirve para pena pero también para angustia básicamente creo que también valdría para decir lo que sientes antes de caer de una montaña rusa xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 16:44:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Service guarantees citizenship! Anything else os marxism!!!

/S un case someone hasnt seen space ship troopers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 19:12:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nazi rocket enginers use metric systen just say.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 15:56:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg death fetus in the beach! kojima tried to warn us of this world conspiracy and we did not believe him ... and now it is too late !!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 15:54:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol bueno tener un origen griego es relativamente común que una palabra se repita en varios idiomas pero desde luego es una casualidad muy interesante! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 15:50:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Petricor:  The smell of the land after the rain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 15:30:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah si, esta es la muerte de la archiconocida libertad de prensa española que hasta el dia de hoy se mantenia totalmente independiente y libre...

Adios periodismo objetivo, adios libertad de prensa, adios espantapajaros... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 15:29:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Si, que les gusten a Rallo y a la patronal es muy mala señal, tiene pinta de que vamos a pagar los de siempre y como siempre, de mas y perdiendo derechos... :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 10:18:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ya se verá cuando publiquen los detalles y hemos vendido nuestro alma otra vez o no como con los bancos... Pero bueno de momento sabemos que Casado estaba en contra y eso es muy buena señal para España y sobre todo para los españoles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 10:13:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the devil hides in the details
* maniacal villain laugh inserted here * </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 09:59:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> perhaps they are the superior race who orchestrated this conspiracy to wipe out our species and take control ... damn dolphins.

 The Simpsons Predicted It </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 09:56:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't be alone, this year there have been three times that happens to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 09:53:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The media doesnt say it, they deceive us about it, but there is a worldwide conspiracy to end the human race by encouraging people to go to the beach when they are pregnant. Abortions number in the millions every year.

/S because you never know who is reading </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 09:49:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anty-fetus grenade: cause 6d6 damage to any unborn who doesnt roll a cd20 reflex save roll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 02:01:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy cake day persona of culture! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 21:19:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Finish him!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 21:07:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
I am not going to say that this has escalated fast ... but it is like going from a kindergarten discussion to the Cuban missile crisis in five seconds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 20:17:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mirate esto:
 [https://rutasmisteriosas.es/reservar/madrid-misterioso/](https://rutasmisteriosas.es/reservar/madrid-misterioso/)
Son muy interesantes aunque no se como estaran ahora con el COVID </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 10:41:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  I'm glad to hear that you're fine now. Sometimes are hard to deal with guilt and regret.  There really is no reason to feel this way, but life is subjective and you have to be within the situation to understand the feelings it causes.
I'm working on my trust issues now and yes, things are going much better, thanks for asking! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 10:36:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 10:36:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds good, when I was working in England, I used to say words no longer in my language but in the local dialect of my region and some of them would stick to my coworkers because of how funny they found it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 09:56:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pero por estar estudiando o por demasiado anime? XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 04:10:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My father gift me a "toledo tizona" xD  He put his best intention into it but it is a tourist trap, a bad sword beyond what I can define ... but it is in my collection for being the gift of who it was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 03:27:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol, normally when I try to convey a "complex" idea I think of it in my native language and then pass it to English, sometimes it sounds a bit weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 02:01:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
Your story has shrunk my heart. A year or so ago I was ambushed by some supposed friends and since then I am extremely suspicious, your story has been almost claustrophobic to see me reflected in part. I hope that today all this has been left behind, I really do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 01:58:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
let the hunger games begin !!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 01:46:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont forget "the T.I.A"  (*Técnicos de Investigación Aeroterráquea*)
Aeroterran Research Technicians </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 01:31:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry pplo but im asturian, so the game ends here... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 01:11:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> US people say they won WWII... propaganda you know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 01:02:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
Of course we have it, but well, leaving that we talk about the case of Spain (and the dictionary boys) The point is that: Steve Bannon, on the right hand side of the US right, has set up his "university" in Italy to unite the entire European right wing in this and other stupid movements.  his goal is to weaken the European Union, but for now, these little steps (anti-masks, anti-vaccines, anti-immigration) are only parts of a larger plan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 00:00:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im in love with your new set up!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 23:49:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im not crying! You are crying!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 23:21:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well,  We import the worst ideas from abroad and keep in mind that some "political leaders" are buying the US right-wing speech ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 23:11:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love the "dramatic stand" that her has every time it enters ...  looks like a "telenovela" villain making her appearance.

"Yes world, Im here, Im Karen and I am going to make your life hell while the whole universe revolves around me" Stupid and entitled Karen ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 21:43:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Es gracioso, no le di importancia pero hace unos pocos días me pasó eso mismo solo que en inglés.

Bueno ya sabes ahora lo que toca es perseguir tus sueños </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 21:14:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 21:03:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The same thing happens to me, I am not deaf but I am "hard of hearing" and when I go shopping at the supermarket or I have to interact in places with a lot of noise and without being able to read lips I really have a hard time.  All in all, it is a small price for everyone's safety and health. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 15:34:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol I'm going to call my manager right now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 15:32:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> New creepy pasta! The Karenbot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 11:47:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol damn aromatic feninist slut!!!

/S for caution

I can understand that he hasn't read a book in years, obviously he can't read </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 02:18:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Por dar un golpe te refieres a recuperar la legalidad robada a tiros? Anda... que ya te vale </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 01:54:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pues mira, yo he vivido en Madrid hasta que he regresado a Asturias, te puedo decir que ambas ciudades estan entre las diez mas seguras de España, es mas... Gijon es la ciudad mas segura de España y Oviedo la tercera mas segura.
 [https://www.elmundo.es/espana/2019/05/14/5cda6cb6fc6c832a5b8b479e.html](https://www.elmundo.es/espana/2019/05/14/5cda6cb6fc6c832a5b8b479e.html)

Asi que no lo dudes, el unico problema aqui es el trabajo que hay poco, pero si eso lo tienes cubierto, ya estas tardando! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 01:47:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
Her original owners abandoned her because she was blind. They don't know what a loving, charming and funny creature they got lost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 18:16:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
in the north of spain we have the cepaea nemoralis and the hortensis, which differs only by the lip color. the truth is that they are wonderful snails I began to observe them while I was study biology  and now I try to make my farm a sanctuary for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 16:03:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wonder if Trump will continue to call It "china virus" when the new focus come from the us...
Like the bad named "spanish flu" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 15:57:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jajajajajajaja.... Aaah.... Jajajajjaja </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rayo and Nuka looking for attention </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 15:52:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Another cepaea nemoralis, Pink and with only one band </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 15:49:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 15:32:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
In one of my games the BGGE was a necromancer who controlled a skeleton of a megalodon among other things and lived on a ship. The players had to plan a great air assault...

This sounds like his son coming back for revenge... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 15:27:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
Ma'am, I'm going to shoot you sixteen times, but it's not murder, it's redistribution of lead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 21:25:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ahora una de indios y vaqueros anda... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 07:01:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But... But... You can message him for emotional ir financial support!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 06:58:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Heeeey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 21:03:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> El típico y tú más? Pero a ver el hecho es que yo estoy comparando simplemente estoy constatando </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 16:04:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
I didnt know that type of cake but yes, it seems one of those prepared in cinnamon roll style xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 14:29:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
This snail and the "sister" specie, cepaea hortensis, have a huge variety of bands in their different phenotypes.
Im going to link here some photos that I have of these snails

 [https://www.deviantart.com/kikeconk/art/Caracol-listado-III-611319172](https://www.deviantart.com/kikeconk/art/Caracol-listado-III-611319172)

 [https://www.deviantart.com/kikeconk/art/Caracol-610520652](https://www.deviantart.com/kikeconk/art/Caracol-610520652)

 [https://www.deviantart.com/kikeconk/art/Caracol-listado-II-604960182](https://www.deviantart.com/kikeconk/art/Caracol-listado-II-604960182)

 [https://www.deviantart.com/kikeconk/art/Caracol-listado-I-604959710](https://www.deviantart.com/kikeconk/art/Caracol-listado-I-604959710)

 [https://www.deviantart.com/kikeconk/art/Caracol-Snail-540441889](https://www.deviantart.com/kikeconk/art/Caracol-Snail-540441889)


all of these are cepaea nemoralis or cepaea hortensis, even the last one without any band. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 14:23:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  enter the comments just to looking for this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cepaea nemoralis </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 12:45:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 01:52:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Se pone las facho gafas de leer y pasa lo que pasa... XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 01:49:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ya estamos... Libertad de expresión dicen confunden informar con inventar su propia mitología desquiciada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 01:48:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cómo que el partido que viene a salvarnos a todos de las hordas comunistas feministas y judeomasonicas resulta ser un partido mentiroso traidor y ladrón que solo quiere lo peor para España? Jamás me lo hubiera imaginado. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 01:46:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> La novedad sería ver a alguien de derechas diciendo una verdad por una vez... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 13:35:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Qué personaje más desagradable la verdad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 23:27:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gálvez cries in spanish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 01:29:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
I was just discussing it with a friend a moment ago, I cant understand how people from that generation are behaving not as teenagers, but rather as spoiled children </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 22:00:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >Wow. Did they even look at what was in the boxes on your cart to see if it was something they want? Or were they just taking random boxes?

All random,  they just wanted my cart because it was more comfortable than the one they were using </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 21:58:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a metalhead brother I know that you are talking, on one occasion, waiting for a friend in the doorway of his house, a lady called her husband, her children and how many neighbors she found to get me out of there because I had the audacity to offer me to bring her shopping bags to the elevator while wearing a "satanic" shirt The crazy stories of southern Europe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Entitled Karen tries to stole my Shopping cart twice. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 21:45:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
I am writing on my phone, with voice dictation and English is not my first language, also, my reader insists on passing words to Spanish constantly, so please, a little understanding.

It's not that it's a great story, but it's the most recent one. A "Karen" tries to steal my shoppingcart at the IKEA, twice. Well, it's a simple story, today I went to buy some bookshelves and tables for my new house, nothing special, something simple. So I decided to approach at the IKEA at noon since I was thinking that at that time I would limit my contact with people who do not know how to put on the mask or who believe that using it is participating in a reptilian conspiracy. Come in, copy the codes of the furniture I was looking for, I took a low S-cart to load boxes and look for things, quick and easy. At this point, arriving at the checkout line, I received a call from my mother and there was a lot of noise at the point where I was, I just left my car against a wall and walked about five meters to answer the call. At this point and as I speak on the phone, I see a couple arrive, in their fifties, with a regular s-cart, much more uncomfortable than the one I took in the line of carts, they have their one loaded with things, they stop next to mine, they look around and since they think that nobody is looking at them, to my amazement, they start taking my things out of my cart and moving theirs ... I admit that I waited until they were almost finished to approach me and say to the man: -Hey! Please do not steal my cart man! - He, who was doing the operation before his wife's supervision, reacted quite badly, becoming defensive as if I was the one doing the wrong thing but after a couple of excuses, he proceeded to remove his things and return mines to the cart, although as I did so I saw his wife begin to heat up and speak very loudly and very quickly, I don't know what she was saying since I was still on the phone and, really, I didn't care.

At this point, I returned to my call and stopped paying attention to them, I broke eye contact for a few seconds and when I look again I see the woman, red rage, taking my cart at full speed with the clear intention of hiding it or at least making I have to go look for it somewhere far away just because of the rage that caused her to catch trying to steal it. her husband escaped the scene, between embarrassed and scared, she, when she was discovered by me, as I yelled at her to stop immediately, left the car looking around when she realized that everyone was looking at her and laughing and Without knowing what to do, he began to yell at me that the rules of the store say that the cart cannot be released at any time, to which I replied something that translated into English would be such that “The only thing that is tied to a car is a donkey like you " At this point, the woman, totally humiliated for having been discovered twice, threw one of the boxes from my car to the ground and then, taking off her mask, proceeded to cough over the entire content (three shelves) before fleeing the scene definitely already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 23:39:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jajajajajaja yo creo que si juntamos una comisión de "pulseritas arriba JjjjjjpaÑa" y los dejamos pensar sobre esto, no se, seis meses o así... lo mismo llegan a entender algún día lo irónico que es todo...

Pero no tengo mucha confianza en ello, con este acto tan maravilloso ya han demostrado la inteligencia superior que tienen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lua, old, blind but still playfull </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-27 10:52:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Le kiss </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-27 00:11:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rayo "lo tonto" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-26 23:53:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Asturias, north of spain </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-26 23:51:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 11:50:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> HoW DarE YoU tO SlEep WhILe hE iS hoRNy? You are a whoreslut!!!

I want to Talk with your manager!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Asturias </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 02:16:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sleeping Panthro </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 15:00:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-03 00:33:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> preventive racist attack. a new concept :s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 10:37:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jajja thnx quarantine is forcing me to do all the models that I had accumulated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 10:34:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> in these models most of the pieces snap perfectly. in some of them I have not used glue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 02:54:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, the only thing that differentiates them from a normal model is their funny appearance and easy assembly but its necessary to paint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> M4A1 chibi tonk... are being very long weeks and I am starting to run out of models </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-05 16:09:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 12:16:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol It is an incredibly common lizard in Spain. In my profile I have some more photos of this species. the problem they have for their captive breeding is that in winter they have to hibernate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 12:13:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry but the truth is that i doubt it's have a name in english.
But indont know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 12:08:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lagartija roquera in original spanish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Podarcis hispanica </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 15:41:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-16 23:52:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Muchas gracias. El Naranjo es un monte bajo pero toda su falda está llena de pequeños caminos y rincones como este, es un placer conocerlo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just the spot </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 17:08:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Trubia valley, Asturias, Spain </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 10:26:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Trubia valley, Asturias, Spain. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 10:23:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> (TTM) geraniun robertanium </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-22 21:22:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sleepy Blair </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-22 15:58:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "Las Campas" Oviedo, Spain </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-22 15:49:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Podarcis hispanica </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-22 15:41:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-20 21:37:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Without a doubt, this is the prettiest thing you can tell about a photo ... especially if her/him's like me a Skyrim fan

well this is Asturias according to our folklore in our rivers live dragons... I just say...

I think I'm going to put an ingurm gallery with some pictures I have of the valley </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My last photo... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-20 11:34:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-20 02:30:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you very much but all the credit goes to the river ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-19 18:46:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I searched the photos, stuning! I think that the trubia valley is like a tiny version of this buffalo river valley and I loved It! one more reason to know the states one day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-19 17:53:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure i can baby


/S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-19 16:45:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now i need to visit this valley!
I was born and raised here, how will you understand Im in love with my land .. and now you tell me that there is another place just as beautiful or more! I have to go and see </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> River, Fog and forest. Trubia, Spain </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-19 15:52:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Trubia valley, Spain </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-19 15:51:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wild panther </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-19 15:49:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I forgot to put my black cat in this Reddit. if she finds out, she will never forgive me </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-15 21:37:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My local forest 2 (Asturias, north of Spain) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-15 16:16:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My local forest 1 (Asturias, north of Spain) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-15 16:15:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Blair "one fang void" </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-15 16:13:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rayo say Hi (i use new macro lent) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-15 11:08:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-15 00:43:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just as someone wrote in imgur.
 When I wear pods, which is daily, is to avoid human contact as much as possible for my own reasons and I imagine that everyone does more or less the same whether male, female or selfconscious lettuce ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-14 07:04:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I'm un photography and I like to photograph trees and birds in parks. At least three times I was surrounded by police and having to explain that I do not take pictures of children, even once I was forced to delete a photograph because a hysterical mother thought she saw her son in a small spot that  in a corner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-14 00:03:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ciertamente pero...
r/emojipolice levanta las manos y suelta esos emojis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 15:31:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep, hes a little food thief </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Naranco, Oviedo... 2 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 14:50:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bicho is old but still playfull </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 14:48:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 14:46:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> he is the most affectionate cat in the shelter where I usually help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ken </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 14:44:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ken, the shelter cat </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 14:43:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Naranco, Oviedo. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-05 13:56:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I`m awake... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-05 13:48:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Panthro the "chubbyest" of all my cats </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-04 15:50:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 11:14:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the rules are always the same, it is the slang that changes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 11:11:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spain here, i cant understand too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 08:16:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Karen, your son masturbates with the fury of an ape in heat whether he has his laptop with him or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 08:02:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, I always thought that it is as simple as putting myself in the place of the other person. I have tried to do nothing that could bother me if I were in their situation. It is not that difficult but there are many people who have real problems with this, and i can understand It. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 03:09:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lua https://imgur.com/gallery/deiE5Fj

More photos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 02:59:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope you are!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 02:57:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is her face when I annoy her during one of her marathon naps in the sun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 02:55:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> many times I think that I am the lucky one, more than her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 02:54:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is a small flaw in your consideration. Black or brown people depending on their origin do not have privileges in society, quite the opposite. the logical thing would be that a man regardless of skin color or ethnicity will avoid causing unnecessary stress to a woman also regardless of skin color or ethnicity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 02:26:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry and you're absolutely right. Unfortunately I am working and I use voice dictation, and I am a bit of a mess then I forgot to check it and put sings. I'm sorry again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 02:19:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if someone bothers you that message that thinks that many women are assaulted and I don't speak only of rapes, harassment, unwanted compliments, verbal violence many times if I see myself in that circumstance of being on the street walking while a woman i aware that I am a big and bearded man, what else do I look like a Viking than someone civilized and then I take out my cell phone and pretend that I am calling someone and I stop to let her go away, a lot of people this seems silly but I don't want anyone to feel uncomfortable and much less for something that I can avoid so easily </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 02:09:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 02:01:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Snore like an old engine, shes delicate as a Soviet heavy tank ... but it's impossible not to love her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lua. Her first owners wanted she to fight, but she went blind and they ab4ndon3d her. Now she has spent all her life with me and I half of mine with her. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 01:55:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 01:06:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Eastern Europe we learn from children to impersonate Anglo-Saxons in order to do our job better as messengers of fear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 01:04:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know what bothers me more if the emojis or the dots. My emojipolice soul cries to see this.

 seriously what happens to this guy? Does a woman have to laugh like a fool of all him silly things and constantly tell him how smart and strong handsome he is to feel reinforced? He would have to talk to a therapist before it's too late </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-02 22:15:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ancient spanish yep
Aqueste comentario espero ayude a vuestra merced.

for most Spaniards it is difficult to understand too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-02 20:37:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spanish in Spain is quite different from that spoken in America. it's not that there is one that is better thanother but it is very different </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-31 22:09:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> and I have never met people of this type only with strong controlled and independent women not spoiled girls of machismo who want to be a beautiful object ... I guess it depends on the circles where you move </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-31 21:57:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We go with a small explanation for people with problems of understanding. This woman considers herself as a kind of award trophy that is the object of worship and that is what has been promoted by macho society. women as a trophy object to put next to men to improve their social presence, feminism defends equality and that implies that men do not have to be male types that hide their feelings and woman do not have to be a trophy to wait that everything is paid to her since we are all equal I do not know how it is possible that you do not understand it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-31 21:56:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We go with a small explanation for people with problems of understanding. This woman considers herself as a kind of award trophy that is the object of worship and that is what has been promoted by macho society. women as a trophy object to put next to men to improve their social presence, feminism defends equality and that implies that men do not have to be male types that hide their feelings and woman do not have to be a trophy to wait that everything is paid to her since we are all equal I do not know how it is possible that you do not understand it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-31 21:53:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have forgotten to warn that these sarcasm. because this is sarcasm right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-31 18:47:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SHUT UP KAREN!!!!
NOOOOOO KAREN NOOOOO!!!
If you want to prevent it, avoid places where there are many people such as fast food restaurants and avoid arguing with anyone so that their saliva drops with viruses dontt reach you! KaaaAren! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-31 08:47:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is BDSM and therefore the most important thing much more than any practice that is done is to speak, speak it all openly, honestly, ask everything and comment everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-31 08:40:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> starts well but then suddenly it goes crazy. in any case if it is a very Big dodged bullet because in his second message its seen that he will insist and insist... Like a old fashioned nice guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-31 08:29:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Por eso era importante enseñarles inglés para ver si así pueden comunicarse con otras personas.
Muchas gracias por la labor que has intentado hacer llevando un idioma humano a esas regiones! XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-30 23:47:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Puf esa gente habla peor que los chilenos no te digo más será cosa suya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-30 23:00:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Comelluvias? Joder soy de España y no lo he oído en mi vida </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-30 18:19:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have had the courage to reject something incomprehensible to any human being ... but to show you that I don't judge you and that I don't feel hurt either, I'm going to write 173 pages about the only important thing in this life: ME </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-30 18:09:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the problem is that, many men have a pressure on them to form a family, to keep their family and vive them a home, no show feelings, have succeed among women, succeed at work, compete and defeat the rest of men in things how (for example) to have the best car ... and all that all that image of the successful man the stoic and hard man is a product of the one imagine society and that is "machismo"
feminism does not fight only for women to have the same privileges as men, it also means that men can stop living trapped in that stereotype </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-30 16:19:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> north of Spain. I have it located in a very specific area and there are no more in the surroundings, I imagine its a local phenotype </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wild Sedum dasyphyllum in my grove </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-30 14:03:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-30 11:56:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/EmojiPolice please don't resist, let's make this easy and clean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-30 03:12:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Señor tiene usted mis dieses xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-30 03:00:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where I come from we call these "Friends" vultures or hyenas. I think the reason is clear. the message is strong and perfect but it may be true that the word predator is very big for these scavengers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-30 02:35:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> op sorry to tell you this but I'm afraid you've lost him. the only one, the authentic, the genuine, the nice Guy ... and you've let it go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 19:14:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> don't worry too much, you are doing well but it is true that this language can be a bit complicated because of that detail but everything else you master quite well is just practice and I am sure you will not have any problems </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 19:01:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nunca te acostarás sin saber algo más es parte de lo bonito de nuestro idioma qué es tan variado que nunca terminas de aprender. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 18:47:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uuuuummmm más bien sátira de la forma de hablar de los pijos, fresas o piquis en México? No estoy seguro de la palabra para definirlos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 16:07:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "más mejor" is something that young people in Spain sometimes use to reinforce a funny and a little stupid way of speaking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 16:02:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what are you trying to sumon from hell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 16:00:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's your name? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 15:24:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when you try to be a rebel teenager and you end up having to do with a lot of crazy people who are going to talk to you about international Zionism and that you are now one of their agents for world domination </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 10:09:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi, I'm the fedora man.

 I see that you havent deleted your account, you have not set fire to your house, you have not entered the witness protection program and you havent moved out of the country with what I suppose you have not rejected me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 09:47:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow very good use of the language just a few failures and what are the usual and logical in an Anglo-Saxon speaker. Youre very good in Spanish and don't let anyone tell you otherwise.

Yo sé que esto ocurre en todos clase

Yo sé que esto ocurre en todas las clases

El bueno parte de todo de este

La parte buena de todo esto

Es que cuando soy una maestra

Es que cuando sea maestra

Quiénes necesitan aprender una nueva idioma

Quiénes necesitan aprender un nuevo idioma

our bad habit of putting gender in all, I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Winter in the north of Spain </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 04:07:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 04:02:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your teacher was having a bad day and pay with you, which she should not have done. She is a bad teacher.

Anda y que te peten (get lost and get fucked) n case you need a phrase in colloquial Spanish to show her next time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 03:47:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol i miss my beautiful girlfriend, fat pig slut ... This is by far the nicest guy I've seen in a long time. Maybe it's not one, maybe it's three or four because it seems he has multiple personality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-28 15:03:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WoW "you're" i love Khalil too. love how he denigrates that racist scum with his totally calm answers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-28 12:52:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi shahdynasty!! Get Up anything exciting for the weekend?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-28 01:42:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can always tell her something of the kind: have you thought about asking yo the company for more people to help you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-28 01:39:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Man, I also usually hate human beings and their stupid lives and their inconsequential goals ... but even though you are going to have to listen to a lot of nonsense that you are not interested in but the trick is good and serves to pretend what you feel minimal empathy for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-27 17:30:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hablo de putas, la tacones. El mismo dicho pero más cafre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Im an agent infiltrated among the weeboos ... but I fear that my infiltration has been too deep now Im one of them </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-26 06:18:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-26 06:15:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Watch anime and hentai makes you a culture man.
but I'm sorry to tell you that I must arrest you for emojis crimes r/EmojiPolice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-25 23:21:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sad and long story here.

how many of you, I grew up in a house where it was necessary to constantly lie to avoid physical punishment and emotional manipulation, and not only that above all, my mother forced us to lie to everyone about all kinds of things, there came a time when the truth was so relative that it didnt exist directly.
during my childhood where also because of certain gestures of physical abuse and arbitrariness I ended up leaving my family. Unfortunately, even when I was an adult, I still had the skills learned and it took me a long time and a lot of effort to stop lying.
However, for many years I have felt that need to justify everything I say and feel that I lie even when I do not, I have had situations in which I have been involved in coincidences that have forced me to lie just to make it seem that I did not lie sounds crazy I know but situations in which the truth was so incredible that I preferred to ignore it.
the saddest part of all is that when I had left all this behind, a year or so ago, I had a problem with some very close friends and they decided to hurt me by accusing me of lying and having orchestrated a huge charade in the group.

Today I can say that thanks to a few very close people I have been able to keep my sanity but I have even doubted the things that I know are true and real in my life and there was a time when I no longer really knew who was the real thinks. Today I am still recovering but it has been very hard and really the scars that remain when you are a child may heal but they never end up going as I could see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-25 15:38:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Puedes poner una foto un enlace una imagen a esa paloma blanca que dices? Una paloma blanca es una paloma normal unas columbidae pero con una coloración específica no tiene nada especial. Las tórtolas son dove, incluso en Europa la tórtola común se llama turtledove.

A ver esta gente está intentando aprender un idioma si le vamos a hablar de la manera que tenemos de referirnos a cada cosa en un sitio concreto los vamos a volver locos porque nuestro idioma es una locura pero las tórtolas son un tipo de ave de la misma familia de las palomas pero de un género distinto no son palomas blancas a lo mejor en Chile lo son por un modismo local igual que cambian tantas palabras de una región a otra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 23:06:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> maybe because dictionaries use common language and normal people that since the mid-20th century he lives in the city and has not seen a bird in his life does not distinguish one from the other? As a country person as a biologist and as a native I can tell you that if you talk to anyone who lives outside the city or who has a minimum idea about birds in Spain will give you the perfect difference between both animals.
My advice is; look at some specialized publication </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 22:32:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No man. you are trying to take it to a technical field to confuse things I am not talking about genres, but if you prefer it that way and for clarity.
both animals belong to the columbidae family but Dove is streptopelia SP and pigeons columba SP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 21:52:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Las palomas y las tórtolas no son lo mismo... Anda que tenga que leer estas cosas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 21:51:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No.
Pigeons are palomas
Doves are tórtolas
If the person who explained it to you doesnt know the difference doesnt mean that it dosent exist. I usually try to do a minimal google search before speaking to avoid messing up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 05:14:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, let's see, if we did the translations well done the phrase would be: come try this milk, it's the bomb.
but if you make a direct translation:
-come and try this milk.  It's the milk
+the milk! is good milk!

Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 05:06:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its obviously a direct translation. "Im the milk" it really is, indeed, "Im the cum" but it is a wildcard word in Spanish just like "cojones"
but milk is still a feminine word and therefore although you are masculine it must be said "soy la leche" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-23 20:05:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Soy la leche", la leche es femenino.

Its a phrase made no matter your gender, it becomes feminine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-23 18:37:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Spain Spanish you can use "im the milk" to say that you are the best in something..  that you are the fucking master of something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-15 16:16:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nada un placer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-15 10:15:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the difference is that those manufactured in Spain under license use merlin engine, just like the bf 109 manufactured under license in Spain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-15 00:06:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> La bicha, la bisha, viene de una antigua expresión española "mentar a la bicha" qué significa atraer la mala suerte sobre ti al hablar de algo de mal agüero en especial de una serpiente (la bicha es una manera de referirse a las serpientes) en este caso estaría bien usado en femenino.

La bicha, la bisha, comes from an old Spanish expression "term? the bicha" what does it mean to cacht bad luck on you when talking about some bad omen especially snakes (la bicha is a way of referring snakes) in this case it would be well used in feminine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-14 22:42:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cuando quieras hablar ya sabes por aquí hay un montón de nosotros encantados de ello. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 18:53:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> look around confused "fuck, we are all Spaniards! nobody told me about this before born in Spain!" It's unfair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> give up scum you are surrounded. in original spanish </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-09 08:24:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-07 22:56:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am very happy to hear from you and discover that you have done so well.

I feel very honored to have been able to help in some way and it is really touching to discover that a few words to a person at a suitable time can work so much

Im really happy for you and you don't know how much this message means that is one of those things that gives you faith in people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-05 09:06:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know why you don't believe him. The same thing happened to me too and I don't even have daughters or friends ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-03 13:04:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Solo aclarar porque he visto algún comentario por ahí que lo hace dudar chiflados de derechas en este caso los hay en los dos lados no hay nadie cuerdo en este asunto </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-30 00:36:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shes too adorable for her own good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> why don't you let me sleep? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-30 00:34:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 11:56:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really hope it serves you and I'm glad I was helpful. The operation may vary slightly between different autonomous communities but they can basically guide you on the right track and start helping you now. request information about the social salary. Currently I do not work much with social services helping in what I can and I think this may be what is a first step out of the hole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 11:53:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The nukest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 11:52:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you have to think long term as a brilliant crime mind like me, Dr. Evil.
I would save them and demand from the governments of the world 10,000,000 dollars for not using them ... not even better! would require a billion dollars! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 07:36:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kind officer is adopted... this video just made my morning happy in a way that I didn't think was possible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 07:22:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry, I was reading your case and when I saw that you had a public health system, I looked for another message and saw that you had moved to Spain. I hope it doesn't bother you that inquired a little, I was curious.
Well the issue your neighborhood or town has to have a social service, in the town hall they can tell you where it is. These units have psychologists on duty that apart from being able to guide you to move faster through the system you can attend at first and in case of need like yours can make things much faster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 07:16:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>

Don't give this man negatives. It really could be a very good solution </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 07:03:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Op was looking for friends and found garbage ... I dont think there is anything wrong that she used the garbage to see if that serves to start a conversation with normal people who could be friends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 07:01:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> right now he is facing the mirror of his room repeating that same thing over and over again in looping. Srly with his pajamas of my little pony ir something like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 06:59:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy Pianola batman! he looks sooOo strong and soOo sure of himself .. its impossible that it be something like that !!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 06:54:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy fucking whore Christmas!! Oh men We are sure that it is only one person ... that there were not three or four at a time writing each their own conversation? Then there will be something that can be done I don't know with medication or electroshock? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 06:45:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The best plan in the world. if I tell the girls that they are fat and ugly many times, in the end to get my attention and affection, they will accept anything. and if they dont at least I will give way to all that hatred and that misogyny that I carry inside and in step will confirm the fact that I am a nice guy and all of them whores.....

BEST PLAN EVER
What could go wrong? I'm too smart

/S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 06:39:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you suggesting that this lovely and beautiful piece of dry shit is giving the victim of his harassment his own insecurities? :O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 06:33:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How high does your EP (entitled nice peopl it's even posible?) level have to be so that you react the way it does? There are many nice guys waiting for the slightest opposite response to explode but this seems hysterical at in less than 10 minutes drop all possible responses. Hes a unique specimen, I think should be captured and exposed in a cage or something like that.

Sofía, que no se te olvide que muchos tíos solo por el mero hecho de que seas tía si hablas con ellos es para darles sexo. Es una lógica... Especial pero muy en boga </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-26 11:10:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Heresy detected!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-26 08:47:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was the idea. I guess it goes without saying but I was being sarcastic and bringing ng rhetoric to the absurd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-26 08:12:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> perfectly combines the glorious magnificence and the most absolute decadence. I love it, disgusts me but I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-26 08:05:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know you but after seeing your Christmas tree I think you are a wonderful person </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-26 07:52:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mr. Brightside is... fabulous in ways that I didn't think could be possible

woman who lives, more or less, in my social sphere, it has come to me to know that right now you are in a state of singleness (more o less,  to my convenience) with what I imagine doing honor now basic kidness that I show towards all people of the opposite sex with the vague hope that look at me ... you will approach my house make an active contemplation of my penis right no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-26 04:24:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Indeed but the rommel thing was just going forward and backward without much sense along the coast in tourism plan ... and the thing about going for Baku oil was not a great idea as far as it looks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 23:59:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Deep are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 22:21:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the last time they could say they were moving forward somewhere ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 13:35:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  As long as he don't tell me "harder daddy" everything is going well ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 12:30:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I ask: then if I hit him with a bottle of wine on the head while I tell him how charming he is and how beautiful his smile os, even if he tells me "no" I shouldn't stop. right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 10:52:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So this means that what I have ... how metal is a real AK-47? and I here shooting stupid plastic balls! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 10:28:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unfortunately, life is complicated, if people have a mess in their head and do not know what they want to do because they have to solve it, you cannot read their mind or know what they really think. You do not know if s/he is being a sincere person or if is confused or if its a double game and sometimes it hurts but you must keep going with tour life and if that other person really has an interest to act with maturity and say things straight and to the face. and I know that it is not easy to do it because sometimes it is difficult to say what you feel but it is worse to expect to become illusions and then never to become a reality because there was never anything or because you missed the opportunity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 10:17:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can understand the confusion and even take it as a compliment but at the moment that it takes you by the arm that already happens to be an aggression . people are totally out of control and crazy I don't understand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 10:10:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pues qué quieres que te diga tú hiciste lo que tenías que hacer y ella te lo ha devuelto de la mejor forma posible. La verdad es que bonita historia de navidad.
espero que tenga el azúcar controlado y que tú disfrutes de esas maquetas me da un poco de envidia yo quiero un compresor como ese 👍 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 10:07:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All this sounds to me "Im too comfortable and Im very afraid to screw up so im going to let go of the pearls to see if anyone if the girls ends up confessing what she feels for me and I dont have to strain or worry" a strategy I suppose valid although a little conservative </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 10:03:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If a person tells you one thing but then acts in the opposite way, if his/her words and actions are contradictory in some sense then forget about it happens and follows the next one. to know what game he/she is playing with you or worse to know what strange mess has in his head and you don't want to be there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-24 16:49:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The parents are the bandits arround city... You are the mass murderer!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-24 16:32:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes, you are graduated xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-24 15:46:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> HoW DaRe YoU!!!! Girl you have to be bad to have a basic social interaction with someone of the opposite sex and not do it with the clear intention of giving sex later!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-24 09:57:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its the typical story that can be hard to believe until you have a dog and you take her for a walk and you cross with the crazy people what is on the street ... and I say it by terrible and bitter experience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-24 09:51:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> totally valid of course but lacking that color that we have in Spain when swearing 🙄 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-24 09:18:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As head of the development area of ​​my company, being five or six years younger than my colleagues and yet I look younger than I really am, I understand you perfectly. My boss has told me many times that maybe I should stop going to work in jeans and geeks t-shirts so that the new ones would not think that Im the scholar when they arrive but I find some guilty pleasure in seeing their faces when Someone tell them that kind of strange clueless hippie is their boss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-24 08:59:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mecagoenlahostiaputamierdajoder

basically that's my phrase when I'm under fire...
*intensifies insulting Spanish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-23 20:29:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you were right it's very nice i love it. For what you want to do I usually use a dry brush or even a sponge with very little diluted paint and I pass on the surfaces as if it were a dry brush. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-23 20:27:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, i had not thought about it... Until now, you see that I do it a lot to the little ones but I have a somua that paint as German captured, the story is that the first model came to me without the turret, I claimed and they sent me a complete new one and the old one, did you look at my profile, you will see that I turned it into a Warhammer vehicle and gave it some weathred look </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-23 13:47:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thnx i LOVE this tiny Chibi models, cheap, easy and flamboyants...
Maybe one secret santa could sent you some 🙄 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Meng models fans! M-5 Stuart and Kv-2. Piranha Tau, Sheman Jumbo and T-34/85 in background </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-23 13:42:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-23 04:45:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> :O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-23 04:42:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your kid will end up marching on Poland if he/she have one of these </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-23 04:40:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My pleasure Pal, easy and calma i know is dificult but on the end this has to go well is justice. and over time the desire to return to domination will return </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-23 01:19:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have been dom for many years. However, about a year ago and because of a very important personal loss, I simply find myself unable to do so again at least for now. I know it will come back that I will feel like it again and the strength to be it but these things are like that sometimes you pause, sometimes life pauses you. but it does not imply that nothing disappears only that its saved for another time

By the way find your story in general, jumping the sad details of it that I understand quite well for being also a child of that generation, touching not to say even romantic... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I've given myself a new housecoat this Christmas to let her sleep in the old one </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-23 01:08:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 22:39:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep the t run away xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 3 months ago i take care of 4 almost death anubias in a Lil forgotten tank... And this is today </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 19:57:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 17:31:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> right now, what I want is to send you a gift and give you a hug ... and then a punch in the face a certain piece of dry shit that someone gave the form of human being but forgot to put a brain. I know,  i know it is not very kind for these hollidays but it is what I feel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 17:21:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Viva Chile y no hagamos caso de las weas que ponen los gringos xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 12:21:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>

death is little punishment I believe that the only thing that can be done is to stab ver mother with scissors in front of her ... well, it's true, I think I'm talking a blessing but that's another story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 12:08:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's perfect yo go to wallmart and rollo out over the kart

Bliztkrieg shop motherfuc****!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 12:00:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ant-hem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 11:16:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BEST gif ever, well done pal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 11:13:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't realize that you had already put it on. You deserve a prize sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 11:11:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ph’nglui mglw nafh Cthulhu R’lyeh wgah’nagl fhtagn.

l’a k’nark Cthultu kyr’w qu’ra cylth drehm’n El-aL U’gnya] kraayn.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 11:05:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> we are two now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 10:53:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> is the new film:
 antz 2: red faction
 the worker ants are tired of the exploitation of bourgeois and soldiers and decide to take the anthill ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 08:03:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I asked how many crazy neigbo-karens this person had to meet to end up putting that sticker on his van </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 07:55:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A great job that this man does. However, what catches my attention is that the Nazis are able to draw a swastika correctly. I mean they are Nazis ... I am already surprised that they are able to walk and not shit on because mental effort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 07:42:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> an intelligent campaign cannot prevent people from getting drugs that is already proven not to work. Anyone can get legal or illegal drugs no matter so the best thing you can do is teach them to use. The war to stop the drug has long been lost. What happens is that many governments, especially one that builds walls, are interested in their political agenda to maintain this war ... but the important thing is the health of the people and this campaign i think it hits the right spot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 05:43:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Taking over poland with cuteness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 05:36:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its possible that this woman in the morning at home gets up and starts shouting that she wants to see herself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 05:21:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well i dom and feminist, are two things that are not at odds. A BDSM relationship is, above all; sincere.
your dom, all of them, first of all they have to know that if you are their sub it is because you want to be... dialogue much dialogue, set the limits very clearly, making a previous contract of domination may seem a bit old practice but that way you make sure that what you are receiving is a person and respects you but fulfills what you want what the degree is of domination you are looking for and need. look for a guy that is dominant but that does not have these preconditions, all you do is find a manipulator or even an abuser.
It may seem odd and contradictory but its not at all its perfectly possible to respect your gender, your identity, your person and at the same time be dom in the appropriate way but that said, it takes a sincere dialogue and a person who knows how to find and respect those limits. nobody said that being dom was easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 20:13:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Come yo Spain, soon we need volunters of the whole world to fight the fascist... One more time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 19:22:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
I don't usually write a lot but go through a situation similar to yours. My family had a branch of psychological abusers that were focus in me for being the most distant and different.
The few friends I had at that time were only close to me out of pure interest and betrayed me in a cruel and systematic way at the worst time and my mind was where you are now.


But the years passed, I found a flat, a hobby and friends first online and then in person who helped me to continue. Move, do not look back and although my English is not very good, if you need to speak here you have me, believe me I understand your situation very well and believe me, you can get ahead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 19:14:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Woooooo i need these so badly! Thanx for the link!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 19:11:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dont worry,  we all do a quick read sometime and sometimes that happens. What honors you is that you recognize that you made a mistake, I hope I and everyone were that mature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 19:05:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The decal come from a p-47 of "hobby Boss" brand. Is a very easy and great model 1/72.

Thnx i glad be usseful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 19:03:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just art.... Buuut some meng models come with pilot Cat or dog (japanese zero with a cat pilot a USA p-40 with dog pilot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 17:03:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Obviously yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 16:27:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can i buy five speedwagons? Pliiiiiiiis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hi guys, greetings from europe,. Im a bit classic, i know, but nothing like a old and reliable AK. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 16:14:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 16:08:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's very funny i look un the "decal box" and find one what say "Big ass Bird" originally It was from a  P-47 but i think will perfecto for this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 16:02:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thnx to you! Soon  in the near future, we will assemble a MENG model of a Sherman, i will be uploading photos but yes, MENG models are good, very good, friendly and cheap. (It seems they pay me to sell them) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 15:59:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thnx guys you are the best,  I hope he can soon have his own reddit account (it's a little young yet) and start meeting the good and constructive people here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 15:58:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, his mother leaves him a lot in my house while she attends to her buisnes and he is very interested in my "toy room" so I have looked for some models that we can do together, soon we will move on to the Hobbyboss 1/72 which are also very easy and so, little by little, go showing him the passion for this hobby. I'm glad to have something in common with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 15:53:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Furry reason?
 A long time ago, a friend of mine organized a role-playing game with characters that were anthropomorphic animals, the "anti-furry" activists threw themselves on him with a whole series of crazy accusations and insinuations that caused the girl leave the world of the rol-game completely. People have a great habit of being toxic and not accepting the rest.


Jajajaja MENG are chibi but not chubby (not at all at least) but Hasehawa are chibi and chubby  xD


Men, i take a look at your profile, anime (Especially girl und panzer), models, 3D anime figures... you have a friend here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 13:58:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >f course it’s turned to mEn BaD, rEsPeC wAmEn


I'm afraid you didn't understand anything. It may be my bad grammar. The message is that there are people, especially these types of guys, who use their appearance and size to intimidate smaller people.
It is a real problem and these types of people exist just like the "Karen" use screams and threats to achieve what they want.

Maybe... you are a nice guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 13:53:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Thank you very much, I know it is an unsolicited explanation but recently I suffered bully and this has caused me paranoia and anxiety, for a moment I was afraid that the bullies would have returned to "finish the job"
 In part I have returned strongly to one of my hobbies, modeling, just to combat this anxiety



I will tell my nephew what you have said, very kind, this is the first one who make and paint alone but with my supervision.


Well, eggplanes are very easy to assemble but they have a unique but great "but". Simple models of other brands such as "MENG" (In my profile you can see some tanks and planes of that brand) can be completely assembled without glue while these eggplans do need it.  They are very simple models to make but they have that "Japanese touch" that makes them a little more complex ... I would start with "MENG KIDS" models and after a couple of them I would go to chubby cute egg planes xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 12:43:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WTF? What happen here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My 6 y/o nephew first modelo, nota finish yet... But I'm getting a new family member for our sect... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 10:35:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 03:19:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol l say with THE VOICE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 01:43:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too, he is my baby yoda!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 01:36:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Muy brother dies, i cut myself, you BF have VIH and cheat you... Now come here and give me some sex...
it's a perfect plan i don't understand that it could go wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Intimidating Guy at supermarket </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 01:30:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a little story that does not fit at all in this /reddit but I think (maybe) it is the right place for the behavior of this person.

Im on tlf, english not muy first ir even second lenguaje tadatadatada...

today I was buying in the supermarket and when go to pay there is a fairly large line and the cashier call  another cashier to come and there will be another line.
For citizenship and common sense, people are expected to adapt to the new queue following the same order they had in the old one so that those who have been waiting the longest have been respected, its... logical
At the time of opening the new cash the people who have to pass are two young girls of about 15 years maybe, the cashier asks that please people respect the order and the girls are going to pay. at that time a guy, an adult man in his 40s comes out of the bottom of the línea and passes in front of them and puts the first hes trying to use his rather intimidating aspect (the typical look of one of those hooligans who spends the day at the bar screaming obscenities at women and talking about football) (soccer you know bit on the rest of the world this is football... A mess i know)
both girls and the cashier who is also quite young didnt know how to react and were intimidated by this guy but an older woman in my line did already call him a5ention for him behavior, he didnt seem to care but the action of the woman encouraged the rest of the line to tell him something...
at this point seeing that everyone had turned against him, the guy pouted and without saying anything picked up his things and left the line as if he had forgotten something and went to look for him. It may seem a bit silly story but here we can see the totally misogynist and macho behavior that many individuals have although our days and that always act as if women were second-class citizens and directly invisible. the guy knows perfectly well that hes intimidating for them and he uses it to get what he wants it has seemed really disgusting unfortunately its something that happens every day in many areas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-20 22:29:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have read many conversations but this is one of the most disturbed I have ever seen. his level of dissociation between what reality is and what he thinks is reality is incredible I think science should study </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-20 15:16:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If  offer yu to go with him to hilltop, don't doubt it seems to be a fairly safe place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-19 12:11:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guild wars pirate hideout st least it's look a lot. Amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-18 16:45:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You!!! Damn reds! Im triying yo take your towers xD
Green here :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-16 23:32:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand your story perfectly. I am an adult man who deals with his problems like any other person but sometimes especially when it comes to public administration and I find something really annoying oura of those situations in which every gets stuck due to the lack of some paper or a misunderstanding ... I am tempted to warn my mom may seem somewhat childish but i Hope that all the gods of all the pantheons protect the poor person who will have to stand between her and whatever she wants to get </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-16 00:14:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Europe here, you are right in all the union </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-16 00:11:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well first of all and you should not forget it is that you have not done anything wrong. practicing BDSM and the things you do in your privacy is something that only concerns you there is nothing illegal or immoral about it

As some people have already told you and he is absolutely right, many of the calls are surely to make sure that you are well, do not be afraid to take them and if someone wants to shout to judge you, remind him that you are the victim and that there is no place in your life if you are going to behave like this
The last place I don't know if this "dom" is simply stupid or evil. I do not know if this is a childish act on his part or if what is looking for is insulating from the people around you but whatever have done is a crime and itsa serious crime
.with a very high head and the security that you have not done anything wrong report st the authoritis and destroy him.

Sorry about my bad grammar and the strange structure of the sentences i think in spanish and then translate... This history make my blood boil...  If you need something just tell you are not alone in the community </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-15 23:55:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> don't doubt it you've been very brave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-15 20:54:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A todos nos gusta cazar a un "listo" pero no se puede ir por la vida pensando que todo el mundo lo es....  simplemente eso reddit está muy bien, hay gente maravillosa y algunas comunidades encantadoras pero luego hay cada individuo.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-15 20:27:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Si hay temas totalmente dedicados solo a cazar mentiras a cazar historias falsas etcétera y como tienen necesidad de hacerse notar en esos temas porque cree que así son mejores que el resto o yo qué sé pues están siempre pendientes y todo lo consideran falso hasta que se demuestre lo contrario... Como decía ni p*** caso </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-15 20:25:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maldito...  no Itachi 🙄🤣 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-15 15:43:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry men, only "pendejadas" you know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-15 15:35:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh? You're approaching me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-15 15:32:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No les hagas ni p*** caso a mí también me ha pasado alguna vez que llega alguno que decide que una historia es falsa porque le apetece o qué tienes ganas de conseguir ellos sus puntos imaginarios de Internet hundiendo a alguien en la miseria están siempre a la caza de cualquier historia que pueda acusar de falsa para ganar notoriedad tú pasa de ellos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-15 13:53:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Puto Itachi xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-15 02:18:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bueno lo primero de todo feliz cumpleaños. No sabes cómo me alegra poder poner un mensaje en mi idioma y no tener que pensar cómo hacerlo en inglés xD
Y si hay mucha gente realmente asquerosa en este mundo, lo veo en mis compañeros de trabajo ven a niñas que solo me pueden inspirar ternura y ellos las miran como si fueran trozos de carne es asqueroso..
Ánimo anda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-14 21:39:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolute 👍 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-14 16:36:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
I thought it was cute, I thought it was a tonge and that was enough. I regret that you do not consider it appropriate.

srry men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-14 15:37:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
I usually cause that effect, especially when I forget to shave before putting on my miniskirt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-14 15:34:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
Hes my wingman, always take care that in the end it goes well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-14 15:32:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
Well, because you haven't seen me in my sailor scout uniform ... that would change your mind.

At least it's a nice selfie, without my dog would have been /r SadCringe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-14 15:30:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
blemp derp cute yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-14 15:29:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >
Hes an expert in that and in the unseen kisses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-14 15:28:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
I'm lucky to have a very handsome little brother </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Trying to take a cute selfie... Aaaaand fail </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-14 13:52:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 01:01:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Man you deserve gold... But im poor... But you deserve
yyou know "casus belli" podcast? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Old Warrior, M4A3E2 Jumbo, italleri easy 1/72 modell almost finished </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 22:37:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-09 16:05:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, the same for judicial purposes and only in the workplace. in other aspects its different but I didnt want to waste time on detailed explanations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-08 19:09:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't understand... Is even possible be suspended for a date or a kiss?
it doesn't come to my mind that these rules may exist, it's just too strange </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My derpest dog, Rayo, love play in the dirt </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-08 15:01:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-07 23:12:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shut Up and take my coins!

P: This is the way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-07 16:36:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> considering the material with which you have done it the result is very good it really is.
I'm usually more of "blood for the god of blood" but I've been with a huge flu for a week so I appreciate Nurgle's blessing 👍 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-07 16:26:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Waw just... Waw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-07 14:28:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sir, I have perceived excessive use of emojis in your message. how is your first fault i will let you go with a warning but if this happens again... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-07 13:04:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thnks uuuummm about 3/4 hour more o less </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 1/72 easy model italleri. M4 Jumbo simple Paint for wargame </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-06 23:45:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-06 15:52:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cactus men </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Some old chaos marines (primardis at the bottom) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-06 00:36:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-05 22:41:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The pjs go to a easy quest... track the thing, hunt the thing, go back home ... but during the hunt they realize that the prints are something much bigger and more dangerous than they thought and that they go in circles as if what they are hunting in turn was hunting them ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-05 21:35:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A local nobleman is organizing a hunt. He needs you to capture fierce beasts, do it without damaging them and take them to his forests so that his guests can hunt them but without running too much danger either ... that they feel what danger but that they never get to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-05 12:43:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-05 09:52:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-05 09:51:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, what does gender matter if a person feels otherwise that their gender matters? why are there people who need to clarify these things? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-05 09:41:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im a dom and I have 3 subs that I usually play with and although I have been suggested to take this relationship to another level but always I have decided to keep it in the game and nothing else. I think it's something quite common and I don't think it's something weird or that nobody should judge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-05 09:36:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my country there are many people of that age who grew up in the dictatorship and belonged to what we could define as "the winning side" and are accustomed to being able to do these little things without anyone telling them anything. they have a sense of being above the law for small crimes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-05 09:15:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Finally find a belief that I want to believe in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-05 09:10:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why does the sexuality of others matter to people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-05 08:59:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In soviet russia tank Nerf you... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Entitled woman go to jail for a yogur </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-04 16:14:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
English is not my first language, I write on the phone etc ...
This happened a few years ago but I remembered today when reading the history of the police in the supermarket.
A few years ago I worked as a security guard to pay for my studies and was in a small neighborhood supermarket.
I dont know how it is in the United States or in the rest of the world but in Europe if you want to buy a yogurt you have to take the package of four, you cannot buy an individual one (except the big ones)
For some reason that I can't imagine, a Karen, in her fifties, arrives at the cash register only with two yogurts and the cashier, after much arguing with her, explains that no, that she can't take two, that she has to carry or all four or none.  Between screams, complaints and threats, after paralyzing the cash register, the woman says she will leave the yogurts and I, fearing a Karen-reaction, watched her from a distance.. well  whens he thought was alone in the yogurt aisle, she put the two she had in her hand in his bag with the clear intention of stealing them...
moment in which I appear.

Me: Madam, please leave the yogurts or buy the whole package.
Karen: What yogurts?
Me: Those in your bag, please return them or I will have to arrest you
Karen: You can't arrest me for some yogurts, jerk.
Me: Madam, some yogurts are only a theft (minor offense) but when you break the package you have turned it into a robbery (major offense) punishable by four years of jail, please i dont want to arrest you for some fucking yogurts


At this point she began to insult me ​​and shout inconsistencies that she had been shopping there for years and that she deserved those two yogurts and that I was little more or less than the result of the cross between a dry shit and a cheap whore (The woman had inventive insulting , I recognize)  With all the calm that I was able to gathe, i pick up my station and call for a police patrol, our supermarket has a strict policy of reporting all the thefts even if  are minor and when the patrol arrived and explained to them what was happening they were so surprised like myself because of the absurdity of the situation, that woman was going to face a criminal process for two yogurts of 50 cents each ...
She began to say that I had beaten her, i physically and verbally assaulted her and even that those yogurts were not her and that I had put them in her bag ...  Well, luckily we have cameras, in my workplace my word is worth more since it is considered that I have authority as a policeman only for these cases and we have multiple witnesses, before the police officers took her between screams and cries I could still explain that lying to the authorities was an aggravating factor for a possible conviction... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Blair just saw the last moth of the year </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-29 23:13:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-28 13:39:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For God's sake, can anyone help this poor man? I think he has suffered an attack and is convulsing on his keyboard

now seriously a very good picture of some vehicles that are usually less known </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-28 00:13:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep, my brother has told me that for Christmas he brings me one of those. an avenger I'll tell you how good Hasegawa eggs are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-27 17:57:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I buy these models in my usual model shop but if you dont live it in Spain you have it a bit complicated....
they are models of the brand "meng" is a Chinese brand that is beginning to have a lot of diffusion and I think they can be obtained online at a great price and the quality is very good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-27 17:33:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol. OMG Someone get that damn song out of my head!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A baby chinese J-20... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-27 15:33:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-26 16:41:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> at the moment the police are no longer paying attention to her because they knows that she is only looking for attention and it is likely that if she continues like this she will effectively end banner... I hope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-26 16:37:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Luckily my dog ​​is fine, she hasnt had another attack and it has been a few days and has improved. as for EK ... as far as I know she continues with her crusade against anyone who steps on her park </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-26 01:09:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She is so cute, real one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-26 01:05:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you ☺️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-26 01:01:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cant understand what i see in the photos are a bit strange angles and being so close to the image it is difficult to get a general idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-26 00:52:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is ... To small to read </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-24 13:25:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 17 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-24 10:49:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i think she have histrionic personality disorder or something like that :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-24 10:45:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I so sorry for your loss, dogs are pure unconditional love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-24 10:43:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> > Thank you very much and  im very sorry for your loss and that you had to go through this horrible experience.
>
>Right now shes snoring by my side xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-24 10:41:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
I'm so sorry for your loss.
I have always been present when the vet had to give the injection to put down some of the animals of my farm and the shelter in which i volunteer. No animal should go through that alone even if it hurts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-24 10:35:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
Thank you, I'm usually a very polite person and that's why it's hard for me to get rough with people but yes, I'm convinced I did well

i take this a few days ago: Aika de blop elder
 [https://imgur.com/a/9kjcLll](https://imgur.com/a/9kjcLll) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-24 00:19:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oooh i love the idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-23 23:48:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its not my first language either and sometimes I get confused. in any case the best light of tier 5 is undoubtedly the chafee and its canyon is scary ...

Medium i have T-34 in all versions and sherman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-23 23:45:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the feeling is terrible you feel helpless and thinking that maybe this is the last time ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-23 23:41:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  sorry friend, I don't know why I was convinced I had read light </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-23 23:40:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you're right in everything pal. I talked with some neighbors and they tell me that this woman dont take the presence of ppl with dogs in the park even though its a huge park and there is a specific area for animals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-23 23:30:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chafee! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Somua Chibi model rebuild as chaos missile Launcher (wh40k) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-23 23:22:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A karen makes me lose my temper during a stroke of my dog </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-23 23:19:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I write on the phone, English is not my first language, blah, blah...

Well, the story, sort, is that my dog ​​gives a stroke and while she is suffering, a stupid entitled Karen comes to complain and threaten me

I have a rather old dog, all her life she worked on my farm as a pest control and vigilant but now she is old and her job now is to take naps and receive cuddles.

A few months ago she suffered a stroke but is strong and shes recovering, unfortunately sometimes suffers small episodes, increasingly spaced in time and light but still...

today, after several days of rain, I went for a walk with her in the park, she loves to go play with other dogs and receive atention from people. Sadly, in the middle of the walk she suffered one of her attacks and for a minute he was convulsing and crying in my arms. During these attacks she suffers a lot of fear and stress and I try to calm her in my arms although I have to say that I also have a horrible bad time as anyone can imagine.

Well, it is at this moment, with her crying in my arms terrified and I also on the edge of crying, when a young mother leaves her children and cross the park (About forty meters more o less)

Starring: Me: Old and scared veteran. EK: well... she-

EK: Escume, Can you go somewhere else? Your dog is scaring my children. I bring them to the park to play and not to see a squeaky animal

ME: Es...CUS...MeE? Don't you see that my dog ​​is sick? she is having an stroke

EK: The only thing I see is an adult man crying for a dog that he should have killed a long time ago and an animal that could perfectly drive me crazy and attack my kids.

(My dog weighs like ten kilos (22 Lbs I think, I don't understand the usa measures) , she doesn't have teeth anymore and of course, there's the matter that she's practically blind)

ME: My dog ​​is not a danger, for gods sake are you not seeing that she is suffering an attack? You need calm and go and let me do the same as soon as I can.

At this point the woman began to shout inconsistencies repeating the same thing over and over again with annoying voice. This only served to make my dog more frightened and suffer even more and I, without being able to put her in some place and seeing myself overcome by the situation, I admit that I behave in a slightly ... rough way

ME: Do you want someone to stab you?

EK: W--- what???

ME: You heard me, go to fuck yourself or I swear to God, if you stay here and keep screaming, I'm going to be crazy

She ran away with her face completely red and sputtering, picked up her children and disappeared from the park.

A few minutes later a police patrol arrived, proximity police who work knowing the neighborhood and, in many cases, mediating in the neighborhood troubles.

Apparently they know this woman well enough "every week she calls once or twice to complain about someone" and after staying a while with me to check that my dog ​​was fine, they left convinced that the woman had exaggerated as she always does and recommending me If I see her again, request a restraining order or call them to take her away.

I admit that maybe I lost my temper, but that stupid Karen is one of the most annoying and unfriendly people I've ever crossed in my life ... even when I was on duty... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-22 21:26:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im in love xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-21 23:15:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And deadly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Chibi Chaos Tonk (Somua S35 modified) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-21 22:19:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Old lady street blep </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-20 14:39:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-20 14:38:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanx on my mind i mess the reddit 🙁 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Old lady street blep </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-20 12:51:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> It's time to get up yet? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-19 13:35:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-12 19:26:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pues ya subirás fotos a ver qué tal queda. yo te digo a mí me enamorado los aviones está marca primero y luego algunos de los tanques pero hice los de escala pequeña 1/72 porque bueno me interesaba para usarlos en un juego y porque eran todos soviéticos y yo soy un poco maniático con eso pero pude ver algunas maquetas 1/35 de esta marca y son todas muy buenas el trabajo es muy fino plástico muy bien inyectado </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-12 19:20:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pues este modelo en concreto no lo sé pero yo tengo varias maquetas de esta marca y son todas muy buenas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 13:01:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me parece el análisis más equivocado y trasnochado que he leído en mucho tiempo yo diría que sí que vox como partido se ha aprovechado desierto resentimiento hacia los catalanes generado por los medios de comunicación principalmente y por el PP que se ha terminado disparando en el pie al surgir un partido más fascista que ellos. Pero todo lo demás me suena a tontería pero gorda además permite que te lo diga </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Blake Wilson </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 12:51:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-09 13:22:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Full metal cry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Meng superdeformer kv-2 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-02 23:53:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 11:11:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are wntitled ppl on thse story but... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Four weeks later the anubias survive. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-25 22:02:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 20:45:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chonis... Tres generaciones de ellas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 20:43:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lovely... Damn cut onions ninjas strike again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 16:28:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think in spanish and then i traslate you know... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-21 16:21:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep Europe 👍 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-20 00:18:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These people dont think un the consecuences...
and of course they think they are much smarter than the rest and that they will always get away with it. They are the worst scum you can find </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 23:10:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep but soon he Will have to leave, pay veterinary expensas, he will not be able yo live nearby and then also face charges for animal abuse.

Un sorry for his daugther, she's a normal person and she had a lot of shame because her parents </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 20:58:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
Who, apart from the incel and the racists, have no more life than the internet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Old entitled poisoned dogs </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 20:49:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  English is not my first language, I write without supervision of a translator, etc, etc ...

First a little history. I live in a neighborhood on the outs of a beautiful northern city, our building is part of a complex of low buildings surrounded by large gardens. The neighbors take our pets for a walk in these gardens regularly, here they can play with each other without danger of being run over or having accidents.  And now the characters:  EOM: Entitled old man, we call it "EL PLANTAS (The plants)" Me: Of course ... NV: Friendly neighbor

During a meeting of the community of neighbors, EOM asked if it would be possible for him to be allowed to plant some flowers in the garden, as it was quite empty and nobody thought it was wrong to do, permission was given to him. He put some bushes of "gardenias" and some more flowers and then the problems began. First he started screaming and following the people who took their pets through the garden, saying that now that their flowers were there that there could be no pets area, then he began trying to forbid everyone from stepping on the grass, the guy intended to use as his private garden all the garden of the entire urbanization.

Obviously we ignored him and although it was usual to see him or his wife watching from the shadows what our dogs or children did, nobody paid attention. Then, one day, without warning, apear some sausages soaked in poison and others with pins inside, luckily the person who found it warning everyone and tragedies could be avoided. We informed the police and although we all knew that EOM had been him or at least we suspected, there was no evidence of that. three times more poison appeared in the garden without being able to hunt EOM doing it, the second time my dog ​​was poisoned and luckily we were able to save her but they were hard weeks of veterinarian and a very important expense.


Finally, one night when going down to walk “Luna” already recovered, i saw EOM in the shadows as always, I did not pay attention because Im head heated and I thought that if I got involved in an argument the thing could end badly . But half an hour later I left home I saw police car lights and a neighbor called me, NV, to inform me that they had hunted him with the poison and they took him away.  The affected neighbors denounced him, the community of neighbors denounced him and a request was presented to be expelled from the buildings, but of course, these things are slow and in the meantime he were monitored and it must be said that he gain a certain amount deserved bullyng....

The culmination of the matter comes the night that NV and I are in the garden, talking, we know that he or his wife spy us by the window but nobody pays attention. Just another neighbor joins us in the conversation and this neighbor is a national policeman, which is important for what happens next. A small explosion is heard in the EOM building and a few moments later he appears, totally out of his mind, running through the gardens saying that we have thrown a fire extinguisher against his door and that it has exploded causing damage and almost killing him and his wife. He directly accuses NV and me that we were coincidentally talking to a law enforcement officer so we started laughing at him and I don't know if because of the shame that his pathetic plan failed or my laughter, in a moment of madness , he threw on me to try to hit me with what EOM now also has a pending trial for attempted aggression, another for community property damage and his insurance refuses to pay him the repairs of his own home.

Sorry for the looooong story :S  I will be updating when I have more data
By the way, when going to present the complaints we have discovered that EOM has several pending accounts for trying to defraud the city council both, him and his wife faking falls in public transport or in state buildings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 12:32:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cesar and his  badly painted mustache are the real joker!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 12:29:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fucking stupid white ppl!! \*look at my own hand... oh wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 12:27:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
please, dear trump supporter who read that... do it. I love the irony that you will end up on the floor in a pool of your own blood. shot down by people with the flag you say love on their arm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 12:23:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  [https://imgflip.com/s/meme/Grandma-Finds-The-Internet.jpg](https://imgflip.com/s/meme/Grandma-Finds-The-Internet.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 12:19:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you say so... i know these riot bullies and their political agenda....

Keep sitting in your house. in Europe we dont agree with politicians who dont do their job use their dogs to impose fear and repression. i beat of these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 12:14:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
Your comment could not be more accurate sir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-19 11:14:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You punch cops, i upvote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 19:19:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great photo!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-10 23:55:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nazis against nazis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 22:25:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unpainted all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 20:37:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now i go to assemble a meng M3 that's going to be new ridiculous levels never seen before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 20:33:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep meng model 😁 are very good models and easy to assemble </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Almost finished strong kv-2 chibi soviet tonk </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-03 14:02:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 23:19:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ed... Ward </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 22:05:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol yep but i a strong Chibi soviet tank in two days im like new 😅 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Super deformer KV-2, work un progress </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 15:20:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 23:41:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because you are a socialist modern country. In Spain, conservatives control the media... they are very escared of the sucess of Portugal.

Only those who live nearby know there is more than towels, cork and "gallo de Barcelos" 😅 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 23:13:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahahaha. I go to porto at least one time every year. Eu posso dizer? Dezir? o mais básico tambem
It's sad but i speak better english than portuguese and i work for a portuguese company 🙄 EDP.
The spanish government is afraid that the spaniards will see the economic, social and political progress of our neighbors... So here Portugal don't seem to exist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 22:51:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The same to me with portugese. Lol.
In tourist cities like Porto its normal for everyone to speak a little spanish... But obviously this dont apply for a whole Portugal.
And the spaniards are todo lazy to speak other languages 😅
Besides the government has a certain interest in making us forget Portugal exist 🙁 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 20:58:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The spanish mask.. oh god 🤨🤨🤨 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 19:57:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! Laia sends kisses and bleps for all of you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 19:26:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure! In the península there are many crossbreed of podencos like she.

My great phrase un portugués (and of 95% of spaniards)

Desculpe, nao falo ben portugués. Fala español? 😟 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 18:52:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She's a very common type of dog here (Spain) is incredibly affectionate and intelligent I hope she can bring some intelligence to my other dog 🙄 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I went to the shelter looking for a friend for my dog ​​and I found was this "Bleph" I introduce you to Laia, she comes home. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 18:21:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I went to the shelter looking for a friend for my dog ​​and I found was this "Bleph" I introduce you to Laia, she comes home. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 18:20:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Edge of one Lil forest, Asturias, north of Spain. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 18:53:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 00:19:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when a stupid attacks your way of speaking, your spelling or your calligraphy you know he has nothing to take against you and can only cry 😁 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 23:00:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ￼ Aprende a pronunciar

It's stupid that the color of your skin can define anything in your life. Of course you have to remember this particular person is only reacting to what he has received all his life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One anda close teefie </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 12:35:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One anda close teefie </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 12:35:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 12:31:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm glad to see some pets so well cared for 😊 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 12:29:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stupid attention seekers like those who talk about Hitler or things like that. Just report only is the best </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 12:25:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Salmonellosis can be a serious disease in cats and the sliders are carriers of that disease ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TV os not foro Blair </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-19 14:33:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 18:33:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Europe os a Big deal too but... 🙁 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 17:35:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Usa... puffff it's Like baby showers. I can't understand this kind of absurd celebrations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 17:33:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a nursing aquarium that I have assembled with parts of the other aquariums. the others are a 45-liter breeding aquarium, a 130-liter Southeast Asian aquarium and a rare 60-liter other than what I'm going to dedicate... I Sony know yet. sorry for not putting it in gallons but I would have to calculate it and right now i hace a terrible headaxhe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 17:27:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But somewhere in the world is there something as absurd as a gender revelation party for a baby? I mean who does this nonsense? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 07:53:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 🤨 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One anda close teefie </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 13:28:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One anda close teefie </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 13:28:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 12:40:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pal you are not alone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Planorbis + anubia </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-17 00:38:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 13:08:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Next step, snails and one betta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 02:34:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A very tyni lamp 😅
in my grandmother's house there are some old lamps which are miniatures I guess it is something of some kind of old fashion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 02:22:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Table lamp stand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 02:18:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is pure cruelty and not only because the fish will end dying from the attack or the stress of it but also because the ammonia that constantly releases the turtle in the water will end up killing or making sick the rest of the fish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 02:15:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Insane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 02:14:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Espero que vayas a la cárcel cabrón y que allí alguien te acuchille.
----------
I hope you go to the jail fucking bastard and somebody stabs you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Small aquarium with anubias rescued from death through negligence. I hope get ahead </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 20:49:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Small aquarium with anubias rescued from death through negligence. I hope get ahead </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 20:48:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 20:13:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WoW... Just WoW... Ppl if the doctor prescribes pilla is a good idea to take... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 00:44:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ojalá lo haya matado </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-11 20:45:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cachopo! Mine name cachopo 3, the red one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Snail in anubias </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 23:02:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 10:56:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My pleasure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 10:45:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Green algae grow very fast when there is an excess of light. I recommend that you reduce the hours, leave it in seven or eight hours at most.
I would buy some snail that eats algar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 10:31:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how many hours of light a day do you put in the aquarium? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 16:05:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beautiful and Evil!!! XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Blair is EVIL!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 15:45:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Blair is EVIL!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 13:37:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 09:54:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's the perfect sight for one day a wizard come and ask you to carry a ring... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 06:48:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Puré happinest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Naranco, Asturias. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 16:01:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cepaea nemoralis </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 15:59:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 20:47:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First of all I am very sorry for your situation. In my aquarium, that works quite well are plants and snails, few fish and a lot of vegetation helps to avoid the formation of alga and that it is necessary to clean very little, sometimes its enough to "draw in"? the bottom and replenish the water... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Blair, a Lil Monster i found in the street a year ago... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 17:17:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 23:40:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WoW great job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 19:13:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ppsh and Tommy? 🧐 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 17:09:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My Spirit animal... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Twenty liter (5'8 gal) old aquarium with anubias and cladophoras left over the other aquarium. First day. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 15:01:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rayo may not be the smartest dog in the world, but he's pure LOVE... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 14:31:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Suspicious.... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 14:28:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Araña al agua </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 13:27:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Las Mazas </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 15:57:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Asturias, north of Spain </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 15:56:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Oviedo antiguo </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 12:23:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 19:01:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I LOVE Shibari and with one Hot model like her.... More </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Blair, a Lil Monster i found in the street a year ago... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-29 17:31:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Camino a San Claudio </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-29 12:34:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Campo San Francisco </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 12:30:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-27 11:38:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my head sounds "underwater march" un bucle 🙄 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-26 23:45:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SG? Omg... Pretty Big pristine eyes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 🔥 Monte naranco, Asturias </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 14:20:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Naranco, Asturias. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 14:13:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Moras en Asturias </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 14:06:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
