<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject30</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 23:42:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is a perfect comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 19:09:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thats a very weird selection of occupations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 14:27:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have fun at work tomorrow night I will is a </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 00:32:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The link would help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 22:11:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think theres an error. I tried to complete, and after the T/F section, it took me back to the previous page (the one about my confidence levels on COVID), then when i answered again and hit next, i ended up on a university page with an error code </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 04:21:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never thought of it this way, but you’re absolutely right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 13:18:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even though Columbus was Italian, and thought it was India? Oh and Vikings. Oh and millions of non-white people. Oh and the colonization of the West Indies was a brutal, genocidal campaign and should be remembered as such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 20:51:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That looks expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 20:01:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But then what do you do with them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 19:35:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a similar large amount of peppers from my garden, and don’t know what to do with them. What’s your plan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 19:20:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I enjoyed seeing these pictures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Went for a hike, this is all i came across. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 19:15:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 21:09:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the problem is your eating frozen foods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 14:13:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do what i can </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 14:07:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe a pin oak? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 01:33:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lynyrd Skynyrd is a tragic vestigial of the classic rock era, and this song is exhibit A. It is a heartfelt, and at times sardonic, condemnation of firearms for personal use. A great song, with social import and the standard southern rock guitars. However the band calling itself “Lynyrd Skynyrd” these days has quite a different view on things. In between waving the Stars and Bars and rolling out a decrepit Gary Rossington to finger a few licks before being relegated to the background, they release the track “God & Guns.” It plays exactly like the title implies: a spit in the face to the other fellows who recorded this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 18:38:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We all knew it would come to that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 17:38:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “Cal” makes sense as a written abbreviation, but I’ve never heard someone say it aloud like that. Perhaps “Cali,” but not “Cal.” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 13:39:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think they called it “broadcasting” back then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 13:38:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So... girls like Aryan Brotherhood members? Im gonna say thats probably not entirely accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 03:41:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We all know this is headed for Voodoo Child vs Voodoo Chile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 18:51:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Criminal that it didnt win </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 04:18:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whats your fav </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 04:23:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its not really ironic. He committed suicide partly over the guilt he derived from the picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 04:21:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ringo also did not write Yellow Submarine. Your inly two choices are “Dont pass me by” and “octupus’s garden” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 18:16:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are fish and chips a particular common takeout order in the UK? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 16:00:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely can’t be. Seems legit to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 13:41:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess the one ring is the 20th </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 13:32:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol no, that’s how they sold them. I smoked them that night and the next </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 13:31:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know, right?! They look awesome and I’m sure there’s no ulterior motives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 06:33:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is teenager-level “adults don’t get us” level of idiocy. There is actually a “side” here that ignores the very clear data supporting mask wearing and other social practices, that has directly influenced and created the situation we are in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 05:45:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, that’s a tabby cat. And the guy posting this video clearly didn’t respect the animal and forced it into a position where it scratched him. It’s not a big deal, animals do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 05:01:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love it, or tolerate it? Don’t confuse affection and submission for enjoyment. Cats that have been forced against their will to live indoors may be more likely to allow themselves to be picked up as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 04:54:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cats in general do not like being picked up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 04:50:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why would you pick it up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 04:24:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, thanks man! I did enjoy it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 04:22:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But isn’t it an ass in the pane? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 04:15:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s the most meta mushroom I’ve ever seen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 04:14:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Annatar 2020. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 03:33:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol, very true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 03:25:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So...

Would I rather be told something I have absolutely zero control over didn’t work out in my favor?

Or...

The person I have become through my own decisions, actions, thoughts, and attitudes is insufferable to the rest of my species and I’m overall a negative influence?

Yea, A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 03:20:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No buddy. It’s the other one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 02:45:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, compared to the purple box set, it’s so disappointing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Smoked this last year in Providenciales, Turks & Caicos. Not a big cigar guy, but I thought it was good. Is it? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 02:43:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 02:27:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea I couldn’t imagine that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 02:03:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do you think a disproportionate number of those who identify as transgender also claim their sexual preference as being other than heterosexual? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 02:01:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So you’re straight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 01:57:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea.... that’s called acting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can we all agree this is possibly the worst Hendrix release? I struggle to find just one track that makes it worthwhile from a listening standpoint. It is simply something to have for catalogue completion. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 01:55:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 01:36:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even if the point attempting to be made was correct, you’re comparing this to.... what exactly? The White House and GOP’s response? The one that made us a laughing stock around the globe? (Yes it’s a globe, in case you might also be a flat-earther). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 01:04:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m just going to give you a tip. It’s great that you worked so hard on these puzzles, but that doesn’t mean anything to the consumer. It isn’t an incentive at all to purchase them. Considering the NYT, like another commenter pointed out, is cheaper and provides drastically more puzzles, why would a consumer choose to pay more for yours? Trust me, I’m not knocking your work, it just seems from your replies that you think your estimation of your product is equal to what the consumers’ inevitably must be, and that’s not necessarily the case.

Bottom line: there are numerous alternatives to the NYT out there, many free, almost all cheaper than yours. You gotta have something special. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 16:28:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was this written by a 12 year old? Lol, “oooo I get to kiss lotsa people” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 14:16:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You lost it on #4. Extremely anti-Jesus practice right there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 02:24:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fucking died lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 00:21:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use apple cider vinegar when I’m going to make Korean BBQ wings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 00:20:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those aren’t all bluegills. Taking out that many young fish has a major effect on breeding populations, when you account for how many irresponsible anglers may be doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 00:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why would you keep/kill such small fish? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 00:11:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What’s your brine? I do 50/50 white vinegar water, 1/3 cup sea salt for every 3 lbs of wings, crushed pepper flakes, and white pepper for 4 hours.

Edit, my bad, didn’t see “pickle” lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 13:43:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Process? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 13:31:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a terrible meme because:

1. The dialogue doesn’t resemble in any way the source material, making it not irony, satire, surprise humor, or shock humor.
2. The point being made is so wildly inaccurate, and, truthfully, seems like it came from a teenager who saw it on Facebook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 03:04:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Songs For Groovy Children: The Fillmore East Concerts https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07Y97FMKC/ref=cm_sw_r_cp_api_i_o48DFbWYY3R6K </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 00:27:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Third show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Favorite Machine Gun version </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 20:57:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of the more mainstream releases...

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/j40m8n) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 04:39:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ever been to Oahu? Imagine that scene in the Matrix, where they show all the billions of humans being grown in pods in endless fields by the robots?

It’s exactly that, except pineapples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 02:46:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really thought the theme was great here! A true “ah-hah” moment, which is rare. However, some if the insanely obscure fill and proper nouns mean I’m starting October off with a streak-breaking loss. I truly hate crosswords that rely so extremely heavily on pure encyclopedic knowledge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 19:40:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There wasn’t agreement amongst the Fab Four that it even *should* have been released. It was originally recorded and conceived as Paul’s idea to “Get Back” to more classic rock’n’roll instead if the psychedelic-drenched products of the mid-60’s, and then morphed into part of a larger multimedia project as an accompanying album to a documentary style film. It got shelved as internal tensions between band members continued to mount. After a small break, they started work on Abbey Road amidst supposedly more amiable dispositions. That was recorded and produced with the intention of being the absolute final album, but Phil Spector later got his hands on the Let it Be tapes, and the chronologically last LP was issued. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 16:34:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m pretty sure that only eating cheese would have much quicker and more severe negative health consequences than only eating potatoes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 16:14:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea that makes zero sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 16:01:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea dude, I mean cmon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 15:45:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP is meta </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 15:44:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s absolutely fake and staged. There’s no reasoning into what the adults are doing, even if they’re just stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 15:38:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then read the Silmarillion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 15:38:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, the actual answer is that he was inspired to write it after the Cuban Missile Crisis, but the theme is of a culture or nation on the precipice of doom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 15:27:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What was your favorite thing about “The Lord of the Rings”? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 23:40:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “Illness”.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 23:36:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t think this post is implying this, but I always shake my head when I hear or see someone complaining that Gandalf’s plan to have hobbits take the ring was ridiculous or “unrealistic” (it’s a fantasy book btw). This is directly addressed in the book though. Any other option is explained clearly as foolhardy in “The Council of Elrond.” They couldn’t hope to beat Sauron in a war, couldn’t wield the Ring themselves, and couldn’t just hide it either. A seemingly desperate and doomed-to-fail idea like giving it to a halfling to destroy was really the only course of action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 02:27:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least you’re buying and cooking real ingredients instead of just microwaving/eating out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 21:02:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would say the left is probably some kind of salad tongs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 04:21:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 04:20:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Came here to ask the same thing. The head lamp and everything.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 04:20:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why’d you do it at night though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 04:15:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I had finished the puzzle, I found, to my surprise, that it had a very nice theme. Kind of feel jipped that it didn’t really come into play because if the ease of the other clues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 02:36:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anyone that can’t grocery shop themselves is either functioning at a very low cognitive level, or has been coddled their whole life and is essentially a child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cantillon: Brussels, Belgium </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 19:33:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 18:47:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I paid the insane WiFi fee on a cruise just to do the crossword... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 14:30:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Walden - Henry David Thoreau </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 13:28:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But 7 can be rooted as well, just like any number. Because the square root of 7 isn’t a whole number, doesn’t mean it can’t be rooted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 13:11:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any number can be squared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 13:09:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s a hippo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 12:57:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Taxi a former worker, abbr. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 12:56:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Typical slave master opinion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 04:41:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or CABARET for that matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 04:38:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t, but there’s a few hundred thousand south Asian slaves who do.

Or did, many died. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 23:12:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. You should read thought-provoking books, exercise, and communicate with human beings face to face as often as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 21:40:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Memory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 20:58:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never made brisket. Why the rest? You eat it cold? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 20:55:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m going to ask a really dumb question. Do you buy the pork cut like that, or do you cut them? In short, what the hell are burnt ends? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 20:26:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No it’s not. Dubai’s population growth has fallen from 8% to 1% annually in the past 5 years, and is on pace to be actual negative thus decade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 19:41:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol that’s a guy parasailing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 19:34:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’ll be very interesting to see it in another 20-30 years.... it’s already collapsing. Remember those “islands of the world”? Failed. Huge apartment/housing projects around the city stand empty or still unbuilt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 18:10:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think there’s probably better examples out there. “First lady,” with a 3-letter answer, in a crossword is always EVE. It’s on par with 4-letter “Stuffed cookie” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 14:59:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whenever I use paper towels, they always leave behind their own residue/tiny flakes of paper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I’m still not sure how to clean my pan, even after reading multiple tutorials. Most because none of them say what it’s supposed to be like after your done. Should it still feel “oily” afterwards? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 13:44:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 13:40:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So obi-wan just forgot about Leia’s existence? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 13:18:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol. It’s actually a pretty shite compilation too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 13:11:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only reason Pink Floyd vinyls, original are not, are priced high is because (typically college aged) young men drool over them. Except for some rare pressings, every album was so mass-produced they are the exact opposite of “rare” or even “uncommon.” DSotM should be $5.00 no matter where you go, even if it’s got the little poster inside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 12:59:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Welcome to the club. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 22:11:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t think you understand what fascism is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 21:55:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t know what a “Butcher” from “the Boys” is, but the answer is no. Not even the Valar could kill Morgoth, and we’re only able to expel him into the Void. He will return at the end of all days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 17:11:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You could’ve added “to squares” to play on the clunkiness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 16:37:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I tried to rationalize ANJOV being a way to mean “anchovies” for way too long. DIJON isn’t a “familiar” way to mean Dijon mustard. It’s just the actual name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 16:35:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 13:52:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do you feel like you’re not getting enough attention, and you do you pin your self-worth to the opinion of others? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 13:13:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Belgium is a great country to visit tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 13:03:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol it’s really not that complicated is it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 12:58:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why did the first and third from the left in the second row from the top have to be upside down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 03:15:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “I love democracy.” -Ki-Adi-Mundi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 03:14:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How the hell don’t you pick green? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 03:06:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not a Tribe fan, but had him on my fantasy team a couple years ago and he crushed it. I developed a bit of a soft spot for him since then, but from what I gather, his stuff has lost a bit of hits bite now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 03:03:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How’s Carrasco throwing tonight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 01:18:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s a quality beer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 01:15:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fucking lol’d </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 01:13:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The person driving that vehicle is not espousing any political ideas. They’re absorbing vacant, conflicting ideals that have been screamed at them from the pulpit, and now have convinced themselves of the existence of an alternate reality. They are insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 21:50:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So ~10 lbs of assorted raw meat... and two tubs of mayo.

Whatcha makin’? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 00:11:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I... don’t see any difference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 22:01:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea but I don’t remember it changing colors each year. Am I really that dumb? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Help! Rhododendrons and surrounding plants are turning color and losing leaves. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 18:41:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 04:20:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don’t forget Namdi! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 04:18:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy fuck dude that’s a nipple. I think you gotta call someone, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 04:01:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Forgot Samuel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 04:01:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not to be a hater, bc I love me some Sweet Baby Ray’s, but try one w/o corn syrup sometime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 03:59:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pointless when you can’t have a single good corner since.... Lito Shepherd? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 03:57:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you’re on to somethinh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 03:56:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What’s the reverse look like? And what’s the texture? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 03:55:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn’t that... the idea of soup? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 03:54:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe *pan*fish lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 03:54:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s a croaker and now I’m hungry. One of the best eating fish there is in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 03:50:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is 100% what it looks like. My only question is... is it human? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 03:47:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ve never smoked one before, but here’s how I grill mine:

* Score steak
* marinate 3 hours in glass or plastic bowl
-soy sauce
-honey
-rice vinegar
-garlic powder
-handful crushed red pepper flakes
-sliced scallions
-s&p

*grill each side over *very* hot grill 4-6 mins a side depending on thickness.

*rest 5 mins, slice against the grain in 1/2 inch strips </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 03:44:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That you must have met people who are so stupid, it’s a rational plausibility that there may be someone actually living on Earth who believes that picture is of a replica of something in a video game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 03:41:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Navy SEALS are *one* US military special forces, of which there are many.

And I checked, frogmen is a generic term for amphibious soldiering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 03:39:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m really sorry that your life experiences have led you to construct a world where it’s possible someone would believe that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 03:37:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I make this every 2-3 weeks. Absolutely delicious.


https://www.skinnytaste.com/orecchiette-pasta-with-chicken-sausage/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 03:34:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn’t “frogmen” a general term for amphibious special forces, regardless of allegiance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 03:31:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hell of a lot better than Atlanta Pop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 03:29:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 02:45:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Think that’s k32? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 02:43:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah that’s from Red Dead Online </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Which concert do you prefer? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 00:13:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Since we have decent recordings of both (audio and visual), I feel like you can make a fair decision. For me, it’s hands down Isle of Wight. Better set list, better band, better playing. I understand Woodstock has the “iconic” factor, but so does Isle of Wight, at least in relation to Hendrix. His return to England, closer to his death, and “God Save the Queen.” Plus it has an 18 minute Machine Gun.

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/iykgh1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 23:49:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A regretful one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 23:44:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A freshwater fish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 23:40:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about users posting content totally irrelevant to the sub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 20:32:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like Alaska, surrounding waters included, is worth a penny or two more than $37B </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 19:38:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. Looks great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 19:35:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well at 10:57, I feel pretty good now! Thanks again for the puzzles; they are definitely appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 19:34:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What was the weight, and how long did it take to smoke? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 19:32:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you see the top times? If so what was this puzzle’s? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 13:47:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy cake day bruh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 13:24:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> C </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 05:04:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Excellent, as always. >!EDGE!< was a real treat! (Or was it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 02:13:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s honestly such a quick read. My edition has some forward by Tolkien where he addresses some questions mailed to him by fans. One of the most common complaints he received was that the Lord of the Rings isn’t long enough. And  they are absolutely correct. I always end wishing there was more.

Obviously there is with so many other works, but nothing comes close to the LotR narrative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 00:21:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Delmarva peninsula being named “Niagara” feels a bit off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 00:19:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I, preferring to live dangerously, opt for the more robust 4 day rule. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Blues grail? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 00:00:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 22:41:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hadji Murad. Best novel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 22:36:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why does it have to be that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 17:05:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Recipe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 17:04:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How did you lose the tip of your pinky finger? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 16:40:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Imperial military did *just a tad* more than “blow up some ships” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 15:26:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Recipe/Process? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 04:22:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hendrix </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 04:17:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me neither </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 02:00:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, if you operate under the assumption that orcs are bred through sexual reproduction, it looks ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 01:57:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Structurally it’s probably fine, but you’ll regret it for simple aesthetic reasons. Go find a proper stand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 22:42:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can guarantee you that isn’t true. Alcohol is alcohol. If you consume the same amount, in the same time, you will be equally drunk. Drink 3 straight, full shots of 80 proof vodka in an hour, and drink 3 5% ABV 12 oz cans of beer in an hour, your BAC will be nearly identical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 22:38:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol “how do I start drinking beer?”

You just... drink it. If you want to try something good to start with, just search “top rated beers” in google and go from there. Or ask the cashier at you local bottle shop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 22:37:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beer... has alcohol in it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 19:56:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What continent is it in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 17:33:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I try that every time it’s a possibility </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 14:25:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “Aluminum” lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 13:35:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea I’m sure that’s what all these people are doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 13:27:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea... except the newspaper didn’t yell at you if you ignored it for too long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 04:49:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mate, that’s a 10 ft trailer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 04:47:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok... I’m guessing you’re ok with the tire being 2x the size of the woman as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 04:44:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who the fuck has a striped mattress? It’s clearly a child’s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 04:29:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m sure it is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 04:24:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, I can understand scale, as in the 5 ft long mattress the entire body is fitting on lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 04:23:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A whole 5 feet long! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 21:36:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow! That’s some really great forced perspective! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 16:02:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Y’know, just because a “liberal” doesn’t think a certain thing is good for society, doesn’t mean they are “offended.” I think that misconception stems from a lot of people projecting their own insecurities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What kind of falcon is this that showed up at my garden? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 15:25:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Homemade braised short ribs </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 15:05:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Homemade] braised short ribs </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 15:04:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 22:58:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I left my favorites in another comment, but I was just thinking the other day... the one thing I wish Jimi had done, is a Red House at the Fillmore with that band. Man, that would’ve been something... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 22:57:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wish he played it in all the shows! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 22:57:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The best recording of that song by far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 22:56:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Top 5:

1. Hear My Train a-Comin’ (1st show) Just so happens to be my favorite Hendrix recording
2. Machine Gun (4th show). Superior to BoG, the guitar is just... soaring
3. Bleeding Heart (1st show). So blues it hurts
4. Power of Soul (literally any of them). Probably the most underrated Hendrix song. The studio version on South Saturn Delta is also great
5. Stone Free (4th show) I mean come on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 22:52:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m working on a similar project </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Opinion on “Miami Pop Festival”... is it recommended? Sound quality/solos/crowd banter etc... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 19:43:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Want to know if the CD is worth the $11 on amazon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 22:57:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Perhaps literally! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 18:11:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NOTAHOPE really jarred me. “Not a chance” and “no hope” are what I think of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 18:10:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly the same problem area. Except I got ACTSON first which led to the rest. I was stuck between TREE and NEST, ARTI and ARTE, and ICON and IDOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 13:33:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It already did. It’s in the appendices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 03:12:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is actually kind of funy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 02:23:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The fact that you don’t seem to know much about snakeheads means you should definitely NOT get one. It will grow far too large for you to handle and feed, and you will take it to a local pond or river and let loose. This is very common in the US and is approaching an ecological disaster.

Be responsible and get something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 01:26:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you put it to good use, it wouldn’t have died in vain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 23:38:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought it was “Deli” at first, and now I think that’s a great dog name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 13:58:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Minor gripe on 22A... individuals (consumers) usually use cloud storage for music. Businesses (music stores) would usually use CDSTANDs, but who had one at home? Maybe a CD TOWER? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 13:55:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s a play on aide-de-camp. Since it’s “start(s)” it’s just plural. Neat clue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 13:54:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congrats! Thursday, because of the themes/rebus, are some people’s favorite day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 13:52:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You must’ve never read “War and Peace” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 03:44:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 25 years isn’t a break. It’s 1/3 of your life completely gone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 20:21:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This question is essentially: would you rather completely lose 25 years of your future, or have your past happen exactly the same, but you can’t remember 5 years of it.

Why would anyone pick the coma </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 18:58:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can we get the clues? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Help/ID on eye issue on Texas Cichlid? He’s had it on both for a couple years, otherwise healthy. Maybe just how his eye is? It looks a bit cloudy inside, and there’s almost like a whitish lens on the outside. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 17:52:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 13:14:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They were in Rhûn busy being sorcerer-kings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 13:13:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> George is dead too y’know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 13:11:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Idk it’s a little blurry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 13:01:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 04:35:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same thing here!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 04:31:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey I know it was tough, being up 17-0 and all, but it’s just one game. We’ll be *fine*. No need to protest and riot just yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 13:01:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Missed this one. This is way worse than my example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 13:00:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I *always* forget OREAD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 04:10:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 25D OHMY for “Goodness me!” felt like a misprint. It’d be like SPED for “went speedily”. Liked the theme though, nice and cutesy for a Tuesday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 16:30:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Poop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 13:41:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This guy thinks he’s a fucking genius doesn’t he. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 01:58:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol I guess it always feels like less in the heat of battle. Either way, those combined with Strzelcy and Polish Knights make for one of the absolute top Cav lineups in the gane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 00:51:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Swisher and the brands you can buy at the gas station are essentially large, milder cigarettes. The quality of tobacco is utter trash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 23:40:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just wish they had more ammo. I think they only get like 4 or 5 volleys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 23:39:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What crossbows do the Milanese have that Sicily/Venice/HRE do not? I do enjoy playing as Milan though, but mainly for their starting position and that you literally don’t need a single castle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 23:13:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ll explain why this meme is meaningless:

1. “1000x more” is just a number you pulled out of your ass. Obama would have had to golf every single day, while Bush only 3, for that to be true.

2. The main reason though is that this is just a projection of what Trumpites believe “liberal” thinking to be. In actuality, Obama was criticized heavily by the media for golfing, just as *every* President is.

3. Trump roasted Obama numerous times for golfing, said as president he would almost never golf, and has golfed over 3 times as often as Obama, frequently at his own courses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 21:31:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Poland has mounted crossbows on turn 1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 19:27:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vikings went from lovable underdogs to annoying pricks *real* quick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Catholic Factions Ranked Militarily </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 19:23:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. Poland
2. Sicily
3. England
4. HRE
5. Venice/Milan

Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 19:13:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gotta love Scott getting “something out of nothing”. Seems like he always fights for yards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 04:20:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you smoke it the entire time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 15:00:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those look awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I was having sex the other day, when all of a sudden my wife punched me right in the face. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 18:47:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Imagine my surprise, I didn’t even hear her come home! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 03:13:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fucking kek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 20:22:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn that’s so much better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 19:58:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those look really good. It’s hard to find socks that you can wear in both spring *and* fall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 14:08:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a communication tool. They were made so kings and lords could see each other and pass information from distant places. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 14:05:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Palantiri themselves, being made by Feanor, would not “corrupt” a user. If a being on the other side (I.e. Sauron) was evil, then it could manipulate you.

Likely all the Palantiri that were recovered were placed around the kingdom to be used again as they were in the second and very early third age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 01:55:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What model? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 00:17:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Junglemath, you’re the best, man. Please don’t ever change or leave this sub. I am not being sarcastic or “ironic.” I think you provide an alternate counterpoint to each day’s discussion. I doubt that I’m alone in saying that I look forward to your daily comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 00:12:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is seen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 21:50:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But if you don’t get the crossword your streak is ruined! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 21:50:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m in the exact same boat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Father just texted my brother and I this gem... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 20:03:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Which do you prefer? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 18:05:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m more of a crossword guy, but really enjoy the SpellingBee. (Still mad about “cope” though.

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/ipisxa) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 17:44:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What game you playing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 16:26:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a hard time rationalizing Disney’s products... The “Sequels” are so agonizingly terrible and clearly non-canon. Meanwhile, Mando and Rogue 1 are perfect, and fit in the universe. Even Solo makes sense. It’s hard to pick and choose, but that’s what they’ve made us do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 16:37:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol, no, it really isn’t. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 16:05:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just Franks Buffalo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> There once was a family, the Bigger’s. There was Mr. Bigger, Mrs. Bigger, and a son, baby Bigger. Which one was the largest? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 14:42:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The son, because he was a little Bigger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Smoked buffalo wings </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 13:28:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The best wings are... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 13:27:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/ioruo5) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 13:18:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi Spanish, I’m Dad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 13:00:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lime juice, chili powder, honey, soy sauce, cilantro, garlic marinade.


https://houseofyumm.com/grilled-shrimp-skewers/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 12:59:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So they would all fit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 12:58:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seems like a lot of us struggled in the SW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 04:12:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Little Seafood BBQ for Labor Day. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 02:23:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 20:55:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think we’ll get a lot of that. Probably should e included it instead of wings or the chicken/turkey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 20:53:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What’s your go-to process for burgers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Best thing you’ve smoked? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 20:48:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/iodewa) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 03:40:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Morris Arboretum >>>> Longwood Gardens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 12:47:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *smol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 12:39:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> $1k-$1.5k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 12:38:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you miss the part where I explicitly said “not my land”? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Any recommendations on a laptop that will support War of Rights? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 05:21:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Need to buy a laptop to game on (for reasons), and I really want to start playing this, so any advice would be appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 05:15:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ll count them out for you:

1. Indigenous peoples absolutely “erased” other cultures.
2. European descendants did not eradicate all native peoples either, so your first sentence is just silly.
3. I do not feel guilty for something I had absolutely nothing to do with. I do not live in the past. This is not my land, nor yours, nor the descendants of indigenous peoples’.
4. Distinguishing any individual as a member of an ethnic/cultural/racial group is backwards, antiquated, and frankly repulsive. Humanity will never proceed as long as people like you continue to dwell on absolutely insignificant differences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 03:47:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What the hell do you think indigenous tribes did to each other? It’s not about accepting that European-descendant settlers waged a campaign of forced relocation and extermination against the natives, it’s about accepting that that occurred between cultures throughout all of history and is occurring today.

Ignoring *that* fact is what is truly sad, and truly slows the progress of human society from an agitated grouping of differing peoples to a real community, where meaningless barriers such as skin color, ancestry, and ethnicity are erased. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 03:37:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “369 Billion Gallons of Water” lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 03:32:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pictured: my college apartment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 03:24:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This just pumped me up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 03:22:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least we won super bowl 52 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 03:22:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You sure about that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 03:19:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Humans should be illegal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 03:12:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “Yep” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 03:09:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was a big fan of Jafar (from Aladdin). Watching that movie now though, and how “rapey” he comes across as... makes me worry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 02:53:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why C(h)uckie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 02:41:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 12:15 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 02:41:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, it just makes that map factually inaccurate. If you give true “ownership” of land to previous dwellers, then you need to go back further into history and prehistory than what you’ve offered.

However, the ownership of land which precludes this map is non-existent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 02:21:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Humans should be culled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 02:18:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I said 6-4 Flyers so we’re right on pace!! 4 goal period for the good guys coming right up!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 02:17:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s too late. I can’t give up now. I predicted 6-4 Flyers so things are running smoothly in my eyes. 3 goal period for the good guys coming up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 02:13:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fun fact: the peoples on that map murdered, raped, and conquered someone else, and were just the most recent inhabitants when whitey showed up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 02:02:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unless the punchline is specifically a “swear” word, using terms like “fuck” and “shit” add nothing to a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 01:58:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Flyers will lose this game because I, a Flyers fan, am watching for the first time since game 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 22:25:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m glad I wasn’t alone.

And I have never heard that term for icebergs, but I had a feeling it had something to do with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 22:01:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea I kind of forgot about that while doing the puzzle. Kind of strange they would include her as an answer... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 21:58:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I spent about 20 minutes (not exaggerating) on 26D (Gilbert and Sullivan’s “glorious thing to be”). Not knowing that, as well as 26A (PAM Tillis), 51A (BERGS?? Still not sure what that means as to calves), and pretty shaky on 35A (TAGS for “plates,” and I still wasn’t positive) all really destroyed me in that section. I get so frustrated when it’s just one or two words, especially pop culture stuff, that take me forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 17:57:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ll never get over the idea that a portion of the country uses “coke” as a catch-all for any variety of non-alcoholic sweetened carbonated beverage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 12:41:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Small NIT to pick, but anyone else feel like DIETPOP for 25A should’ve had more of a clarifier? Given that “pop” is a regional term, perhaps include that in the clue? Not really complaining, as I did guess it on my first time through, but wanted to see what you all thought </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 12:38:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can absolutely guarantee you that with continued practice, every one of those answers will become, quite easily, very guessable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 12:31:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 12:29:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “Yuengling is the top-selling craft beer in the U.S. for the fifth year in a row. Pottsville's D.G. Yuengling & Son is once again top craft beer company in the United States by sales volume, according to newly released data from the Brewers Association, a nonprofit brewing industry trade group.” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 04:42:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The name needs work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 04:38:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Both are technically “craft” breweries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 02:24:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hands down the best American Domestic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 02:15:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oof... wait until OP hears about Operation Paperclip... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 20:32:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don’t you mean the functioning antique water pump you just purchased has a house out back? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 19:22:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nature is healing. #wearethevirus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 15:29:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But... why an Oreo? She’s still licking the chocolate bits. This is very irresponsible pet ownership. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 14:47:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unbelievable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 13:07:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Obviously? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 12:57:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Took me longer than it should have, because I started late at night when I was too tired, filled in most but couldn’t get the theme in ~10ish minutes. Gave up, just came back now and picked right up on the BOUNCEBACK trick (which I thought was actually pretty fresh and neat) but had to spend nearly 10 more minutes hunting down a 1-letter goof. Like others I had DALE instead of VALE, but I fixed that pretty quickly. For me I had ACEL for 1D (as in batteries) which destroyed my time.

I guess I should watch more Bond films? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 12:40:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That it’s embellished lol. Look at how much curve is in the video. He would have to be well beyond the ISS to see that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 03:40:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m not saying it’s of the same quality, just the exact same subject matter. Except Elvis though. This is better than Elvis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 03:14:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having never actually read anything about him, I pictured him as a 1930s Ivy League-Yacht Club sweater-wearin’ obviously white fellow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 03:13:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For some reason I thought that *was* Pele. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does the Mini difficulty increase throughout the week, ala the regular crossword? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 03:11:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They all seem about the same, including the “midi” Saturday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 03:08:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why no live for Nuenen? The tank fighting is pretty awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 00:27:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I heard you can catch carp on just about *anything* .... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 00:26:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My bad, I thought it was the lyrics that bothered you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 22:50:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would love to know what styles and performers of music you prefer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 22:49:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would you do the same if they listened to the Beatles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 22:48:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol at all the people bemoaning the blatant sexuality in modern pop music. Have you even *listened* to a single Western song in the past 70 years? Elvis? Sex. The Beatles? Sex. Jimi Hendrix? Sex. Motown R&B? Sex. Disco? Sex.

It’s literally what popular music has always been about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 20:58:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pure heaven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 20:55:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They’re all so great, but I’ve always been partial to Carentan. It feel so incredibly real and human. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Favorite Battle? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 20:51:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/ilcvua) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 20:14:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beforehand; however it forces you to complete the Hans Capon DLC before finishing the main story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This is the way </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 18:31:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 17:27:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> .... I’m sorry if you made this joke, but I really still don’t get it. What is a “bic dick” and how is it the same thing as a “little dick”? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 17:19:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ditto </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 16:48:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because he isn’t re-entering the atmosphere. The cameras are all using a fisheye type lens to give the effect of earth curvature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Awful </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 16:45:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 16:32:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That would be considered an eye shield. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 14:34:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get that BRENNERPASS isn’t exactly common knowledge, but AMENRA I remember learning about in 6th grade history. Also ZAS is relatively common slang, so I had no issues with that fill.

The theme was flimsy at best though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 14:31:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh god that’s terrible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 14:00:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “Our society’s tendency”

I think you meant all of human history’s tendency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 02:35:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s crazy that he’s really unknown today outside of certain, mostly reggae-fan, circles. How about the album with Jammy and Scientist? “First, Second, and Third Generation of Dub”. Prince Jammys “Second Generation” is one of my favorite dub tracks anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 02:21:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My stepfather-in-law is from Mahanoy City... he doesn’t go back much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 02:18:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love it. You ever listen to the King Tubby album, “Dangerous Dub”? A little later (‘81 I think), and it hit so freaking hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 02:08:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One of Tubby’s top efforts, if a little obscure. and obviously very “roots” heavy, the whole album’s dark tones pair great with the brightness of Tubby’s dubs. But honestly, what did you expect with Tubby and the Upsetters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 23:38:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s honestly very underwhelming in person. Having lived in the area, and visiting Centralia once or twice, I would advise against any special trip of over an hour’s drive just to see it. Despite the many pictures taken at flattering angles, it is very uncommon to see smoke billowing out of gaping fissures. Yes, some steam does seep out, and there’s the penetrating stench of sulphur in the air, but it’s more just a desolate clearing between two hills with a few dilapidated houses. The poorly-drawn graffiti all over the streets really shatters the eerieness, and it’s known locally mostly as a spot for teenagers to park, drink beer, and litter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 16:01:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anyone else feel like we’re seeing an unusual amount of MAITAI lately? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 13:25:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I freaking love mimosas so I enjoyed the inclusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 02:04:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just do the exact opposite of what I do, apparently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 04:09:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Process?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 03:41:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How many hours of actual smoke? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 03:13:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol I’m watching Band of Brothers and scrolling saw this meme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 01:13:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was in the same boat about 5 months ago (never smoked anything), then my wife bought me a Bradley electric smoker for birthday. I can honestly say that despite some obvious limitations, I’ve had a ton of fun using it and getting into smoking foods. Yes it uses bisquettes instead chips or pellets, but for a beginner, I find that makes it a lot easier to operate. It was around $225 I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 00:53:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Real question: what kind of mushrooms are these? I’ve never grown any, and it seems like a lot of the pictures people post here are of this type. Are they psilocybin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 19:09:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The next best thing is taking a break and coming back every few years or soZ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 13:05:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The whole first side of the second disc is incredible for me.

Once I Had a Woman, Bleeding Heart, Jelly 292

I honestly would probably say “Once I Had a Woman,” though. It’s some of the purest blues Hendrix ever recorded. “Hear My Train” gets a lot of praise, deservedly so, but I prefer the rendition he did the first set 12/31/69 at the Fillmore. That remains my absolute favorite Hendrix recording ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 13:01:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s a great track for sure! Do you know the differences/similarities to the Electric Ladyland version? Is it just a shortened version or a different take? I can never tell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 03:10:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing beats local! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 02:47:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol, it’s some weird bootleg. Has 6 or so live tracks from various releases. I forget exactly what, but I know about half of it is from Berkeley. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 02:42:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have to ask, what is your living situation? If you’re renting, then your landlord is committing a crime by not providing heat to the unit. If you own your own home, then maybe save some money instead of setting up an aquarium and get some heat. If you are underage and forced to go without heat by your providers, I would consider taking whatever actions might be available to you so you can find a better situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 02:31:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doesn’t your house/apartment/living space have heating? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 02:28:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s one book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 02:27:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you want to experience Lord of the Rings, then read the book.

If you want to watch a big-budget Hollywood action film interpretation, then pop in Peter Jackson’s trilogy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 02:25:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s really not. The pages go by extremely quickly. It’ll take you a couple weeks tops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 02:19:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WTF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 02:11:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RASSLE instead of WRASSLE is unforgivable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 00:33:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then you, sir, made a wise purchase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 00:15:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see you’re organizing your boyfriend’s library </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cherrywood Smoked Asian BBQ Wings </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 00:11:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cherrywood Smoked Asian BBQ Wings </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 00:10:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 23:58:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s honestly not terrible. What condition is it in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My Hendrix vinyls. “Blues” is probably my favorite. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 23:57:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 23:46:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What were they charging? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 19:19:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My last reply... I am *not* condoning any of the ALLIES actions, nor are they relevant to the discussion. Why you think the appropriate response to well-deserved criticism of the Germans in WW2 is pointing to the universal fact that winners write the history books, is beyond me. Suffering in POW camps does not atone for the Nazis’ and yes (very much so) the Wehrmacht’s sins. Finally, while it is true that many soldiers in the regular German army are free from blame, to take the position that they were mostly, or even largely, innocent is rubbish. Simply put, you have fallen for post-war Nazi propaganda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 18:58:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For the Colbert one: I laughed out load at >!OUI and SEMIHARD!< and I enjoyed it immensely more than most of this weeks NYT puzzles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 18:47:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m really not sure how you snowball my “Franz Halder wasn’t innocent” into your “the Allies weren’t princesses either,” but OK. I’ll just leave it at this: when your first, knee jerk response to a clear example of a war criminal is “not all the Nazis were bad!” you might want to take a hard look at yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 17:20:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 17:19:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my science </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 17:18:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I chortled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 17:12:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed on HIRES. However, it’s probably because Will Shortz still gets too confused by fax machines and modem cables to keep up with modern technology parlance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 17:10:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought TROOPS was pretty weak overall. Extremely rare to be used that way, imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 17:09:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! I’ve only recently been able to complete Saturday’s, after about a year of dedicated NYT solving. However, I must confess, that for a good 10 months, I rarely even attempted them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 17:05:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Franz Halder was definitely not one of those. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 17:05:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol Franz Halder was *not* just a Wehrmacht officer. He enacted the orders that allowed Soviet officers, soldiers, and civilians to be shot or otherwise summarily executed en masse without due cause. In other words: a war criminal.

Edit: I wanted to add that if you didn’t know who he was and his actions, you clearly know extremely, shockingly little about WW2 and the German command to be expounding lamentations about the public attitude towards it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 13:46:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You left out one of the most egregious oversights by the Allies, and US in particular - Franz Halder (chief of staff of the Wehrmacht) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 13:28:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least you’re sub-20! I just hit a PB with 31:31 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 04:36:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really disliked AHCHOO. It’s like they did it just to fit in the SAHL-DAHL thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 00:41:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Belgium? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 22:45:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doesn’t that literally make it *not* a black and white photo?

“Here, I’ve taken this black and white picture, and colored in all of the shapes. Now your brain perceives the images as red blue and green! Marvelous the tricks it plays!” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 17:59:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know how different it was. I was there. It isn’t very different than now. The biggest difference is your cell phone wasn’t as good. And I’m serious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 17:03:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 10 years isn’t far enough into the past to make it interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 13:04:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> PYRAMIDSCHEME FTW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 04:25:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I must say, I did hit my personal best on this one. That’s even with spending 5-10 minutes trying to figure out the TANEHISI area (I *always* forget the ISO clue). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 01:04:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn’t write the Quran. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 01:04:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m sorry dude. The Quran highlights several instances of Muhammad freeing his own slaves (often to make them one of his many wives/concubines) in an effort to show his benevolence. But he most certainly did hold many slaves, most of which died as slaves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 23:53:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ........ what are you talking about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 23:50:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All Muslims must follow Sunnah. Muhammad held hundreds if not thousands of slaves. Thus, Muslims must enforce slavery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 23:35:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do you believe slavery is a good thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 21:57:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interesting to see the SCAT discrepancy. I thought the published clue was ridiculous. I’m all for more risqué puzzles, but a slang for “feces” usually used in a pornographic manner, is kind of off-putting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 04:45:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> CACHINNATE?????????? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 03:58:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Didn’t say only hobbits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 03:39:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Ring bestows powers according to its user. Hobbits become invisible. Tom Bombadil is unaffected. A wraith would never put the ring on, as they are it’s slaves. They would only safeguard it back to Sauron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 03:34:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are Huorns in the “Fellowship of the Rings” too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 02:27:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What’s your process? My skin never gets like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is my ramp-up strategy a good plan? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 02:25:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 02:14:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What’s wrong with pumpkin juice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 23:08:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think we most definitely do want people who can’t hit a home run in an MLB park to practice until they are able to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 20:33:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I disagree. Definitely not impossible, just harder. Otherwise the first time it was used in a puzzle, no one ever would have solved it. Also, just because something is geared towards more experienced players, doesn’t make it necessarily “bad.” That’s like saying, “it’s not fair that Major League ballparks are so big, it’s too hard for me to hit a homerun.” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 13:55:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly that. As soon as you start to shit, just get up and abruptly leave whatever public setting you’re in. People will think it’s weird, but if it only happens 2x a year, it’s pretty easy to explain away. It’s not like the odor your shit *instantly* permeates the entire area you’re in; you have a chance if undetected escape.

On the other hand, you could literally never be able to relax at home, alone, for constant fear of shitting yourself and having to clean it up EVERY SINGLE DAY. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 13:52:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really think people are:

1. Discounting the positive aspects (such as you highlighted) to the giant bug world

And

2. Really ignoring how miserable it would be to be chilly *all the time*. There is nothing that ever makes it better, it is always there with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 12:32:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I vaguely feel like I’ve heard ALLWET in actual parlance, but at the same time I know it mostly from crosswords. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 04:17:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *MUCH* better than Tuesday imho. Nice unique theme that made you think a bit, even after you “got it.” And hardly any generic, bland fill, unlike the aforementioned Tuesday. 9:39.

I don’t know who Ken OLIN is though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 03:36:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that the guy from Stranger Things? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 02:26:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea but in this situation, you would not be warm. Ever. No matter what. You are constantly, uncomfortably chilly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 02:19:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s what I’m saying. And also, I meant ALWAYS chilly. Like, laying in bed under the covers, you’re chilly. At the beach? Too chilly to swim. Having sex? Chilly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 02:09:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well it sure beats Elijah Wood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 00:26:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just a little joke. Looks incredible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 00:23:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn’t it almost fall though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 00:17:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who the hell would poop themselves *every* day? If it’s in public, just excuse yourself twice a year, no matter when it is, and go home and clean up. If it’s a daily occurrence, it affects your whole rhythm. Are you just not going to bath/shower because you haven’t pooped yourself yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> WYR Live in world where there are a lot of massive 10 ft long/tall versions of regular insects free-roaming outside (and you look tasty) OR you are literally always chilly (like tshirt in 40 degree windy chilly) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 00:09:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/igm9wc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 23:50:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do you figure that first part implies all months with a unique date are cut? It’s just means that those specific dates are cut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 18:42:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well what do you expect when they use crappy Talmberg stone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 17:41:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alee is pretty egregious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 16:43:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 16:40:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did not know that was a subreddit. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 16:23:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pure gold </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Spelling Bee Gripe: why is “lede” not an acceptable word? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 16:17:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 13:24:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This puzzle was a “stackable cookie” away from simply being a prep course in classic crossword fill. EEL, AJAR, EPEE, AWL, SKYE, CEL, UTE, IMP, AIDE, ODE, ETNA all in one puzzle got a little boring.

When I read the first themed clue however, I took a pretty big gulp, as I don’t know as much Shakespeare as I should. But the rest of the puzzle was so easy I got almost all the crosses and filling in the 4 long answers was a cinch. Almost got a PB on this one.

I guess it isn’t bad for a Tuesday. I did like LEES and LEA (crossed by LEEDS) a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 03:56:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wife wanted me to throw away some old (but decent enough condition) pillows... I couldn’t because I imagined them thinking they were trash. Kept them “in case of company.” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 02:36:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It looks definitely not edible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The post below me (about LA Times difficulty) made me wonder... other than NYT app, where else can I get national puzzles on a daily basis? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 00:47:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 18:12:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you take it as a stand alone work of art, then they’re pretty decent for big-budget action/adventure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 18:02:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There’s plenty of adaptations that do an original work justice. Peter Jackson made too many unforgivable errors for his trilogy to be appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 17:58:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Peter Jackson movies slaughtered the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 3 year old Jimi Hendrix with his father Al - Seattle 1945 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 17:51:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 01:39:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *looks at user name

Seems legit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 14:55:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jimi despised the naked cover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 14:48:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s funny you say that the Experience was firing on all cylinders, because it’s the least “Experience” album of the three! Noel Redding only plays on 4-5 songs. Jimi or Billy Cox played bass on the majority of tracks. ELECTRIC LADYLAND is simply Hendrix putting forth a fully realized vision, his tribute to all the groupies he’s had sex with or tried to have sex with in his life.

EDIT: It also led to their original producer, Chandler, and Redding storming out because they didn’t like the “direction.” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 14:45:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The original 70’s version with the stuff recorded in England or the reissued one that actually has all its  tracks played in California? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 14:43:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of the 4 albums released, it absolutely has to be ELECTRIC LADYLAND. It is by far the most complete album, showcasing Hendrix’s primary attributes, fierce guitar-playing and evocative songwriting, more than any other. AXIS: BOLD AS LOVE is also a tidy little project, but just doesn’t have the impact of its successor. Meanwhile ARE YOU EXPERIENCED? is simply a collection of songs, albeit an incredible one. BAND OF GYPSYS is too top heavy to really be number one.

However, the absolute best Hendrix release, hands down, is the purple box set, THE JIMI HENDRIX EXPERIENCE. The 4 part collection has any and everything someone needs to listen to to appreciate Hendrix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What website do you use to find out when a certain word or phrase was used in NYT’s history? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 14:23:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 03:45:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> AMEN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 03:38:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 38:03 just above average. Got really stuck on SCARFACERESOURCES for some reason (I guess “scarce resources” doesn’t really roll off my tongue) and the surrounding areas.

Overall I thought the theme was fun enough, if a bit cutesy. I also enjoyed the overall lack of obscure pop culture. Except for MAHALIA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-22 17:59:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I heard that helps to make them more tender. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-22 16:44:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To clarify... if someone asked me point blank at 9:59 EST last night to name the leader of the Italian unification, I would’ve balked. But once you got a cross or 2, it should’ve popped right into your head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-22 16:40:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ve never heard that expression... guess I’ve learned something today! Now we’ll see what my wife does when I tell her she’s being too “flip”... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-22 16:20:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m surprised at the pushback on Garibaldi... thought that was a pretty well known name </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-22 16:18:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can someone explain 12D for me? I solved it through crosses, but I don’t see the connection. Flipper=Sassier?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-22 16:16:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think having the posts right at the time of the puzzle release. Very many, if not most, of the frequent posters here do the puzzle as soon as possible, and may wish to come here and engage in discussion.

I also really like the poll as is. Leave the “interesting” level to the comments, as it is so variable and subjective anyway. The poll is good for hard data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-22 00:58:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not having to black out your spoilers feels so liberating!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 16:56:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There’s one in every Cuman camp you come across. There’s one such camp on the road from Inn at the Glade to Talmberg, underneath a large rock formation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 16:18:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Still working on the whole west/southwest section... I’m not up on my Shakespeare, and I can’t seem to figure out 27D “Beat”... I have __HAU_TED which I feel are all correct

EDIT: Got it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 14:41:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m dying right now lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 13:43:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 13:43:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol you obviously can’t pick up sarcasm either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 13:42:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn’t say you were a fucking moron. Just that you look like one, and apparently act like one. Oh and I can absolutely guarantee you will regret, one day, getting that stupid tattoo that only an insecure child would think is cool or “extreme.” You obviously are only trying to shock people when they see it. And you’ve succeeded. Except the shock is at you, and at how immature and silly a person can be. Congratulations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 03:09:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What was the sound system like on Barbie Dance Club? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 02:48:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea because you look like a fucking moron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 02:27:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe because it’s a weird thing to ask people lol. Yea the spiral hurts your hand a little if you write like normal, everyone else just ignores it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 02:22:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How could anyone else *not* experience this? What hand configurations do you think people might have that would eliminate this problem? However, it’s not a big deal. Just live with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 23:15:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love democracy... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 21:07:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is my argument against the auto-thread. A large portion of the replies are usually in response to something in the OP.

My fear is an auto-thread would get fewer comments because how many people want to come and just say “I liked it, 5:32, fun theme” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 21:05:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I posted the NYT daily thread on Tuesday, and missed an important piece of the theme, while complaining in my post about it. I felt like it ruined that day’s thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 03:04:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lord of the Rings *is* the books. The movies are not Lord of the Rings. They are a cinematic interpretation of an existing work of art. Creatively, they are an entirely separate entity. If you want to enjoy Lord if the Rings, you have to read the Lord if the Rings. If you want to watch a movie, go watch a movie.

It’s really as simple as that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 02:59:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which is your favorite and why is it RotK? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 02:56:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How many times have you seen the movies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 16:59:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would purchase this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 16:24:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like I’m pretty close then. Difference is probably explained by dialect and fogged memory.

Is it worth a trip to visit my ancestral homeland? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 16:21:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My grandparents were Slovak, their parents having emigrated to the US around 1910, and could speak Slovak. Does “yitch” mean “to eat”? And “shedni sebba” mean “sit down” (sorry for the spelling, only heard it spoken) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 16:17:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also, what exactly is your reverse sear method? I’ve overcooked the meat the only 2 times I’ve tried it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 06:23:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try portrait mode, contrast and color editing, and a better angle. That’s what everyone else does!

Food looks delish though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 06:02:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn, I didn’t even notice the >!duplicate answer!< till I saw you point it out. I feel like that’s a pretty heavy violation on the part if the constructor/editor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 04:02:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An absolutely fabulous puzzle, errors and all. The clue about clowns and hula stuff should have been made plural to fit the answer. But this puzzle made me hope (perhaps in vain) that we get some more vulgarity in mainstream puzzles. Why? Because it’s FUN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 03:37:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Water, white vinegar, salt, white sugar, red pepper flakes, ground white pepper.

I forget the exact measurements, but it’s equal parts vinegar to water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 06:25:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hear My Train a-Comin’ live at the Fillmore East, first show 12/31/69. Available on numerous releases, most recently “Songs for Groovy Children.” I’ve listened to that 9 minute track hundreds of times, and I enjoy it even more each go-around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 06:17:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I SOMEHOW MISSED THE 53A CLUE EXPLICITLY STATING THE RELEVANCE OF THE THEME: IM A MORON </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 06:16:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow. I somehow missed entirely the relevance of that date. Now I feel like deleting the thread lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 06:14:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was on pace for about the same, until a couple snags, including the aforementioned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NYT Tuesday 8/18 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 05:12:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The theme was kind of out of the blue, unless I’m just not aware of something being topical this time of year. Also, really didn’t like 43D >!RUNSTO!< felt just weak. 12:28 but only because I thought it was >!abicus!< </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 00:57:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol, if you’re referring to the all-pineapple skewer, I assure you it was only because of poor proportioning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 19yo Tiger. The days of catching and eating full-grown rabbits have morphed into afternoons spent gazing out over his old hunting grounds. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 00:53:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> He’s a little long in the tooth (19yo), but here’s Tiger. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 00:50:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 22:59:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is also one of my favorite pictures of ptery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 22:57:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have never heard it called “hitting” practice before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 22:39:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Brine for 4 hours, then dry rub and 2 hours of smoke at 225, then baste with sauce and 15 more mins as hot as the smoker will get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kebabs! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 21:39:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Applewood Smoked Bourbon-BBQ Wings </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 21:36:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 20:32:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had >!ESPANO!< for some reason and it killed 2 extra minutes. 6:57 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 20:19:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m sure the animals appreciate it greatly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 19:01:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awesome work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 15:39:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bruh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 07:15:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lotta Zinc! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 06:05:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You say “progress,” yet you have 100% solve rate. That isn’t progress; that’s starting the app already an extremely accomplished solver. Or cheating and looking up answers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 04:06:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wasn’t complaining, its a meaningless Internet forum for Christ’s sake. I just meant he would get some good feedback there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 02:05:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try posting in r/gardening </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 01:56:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds straightforward enough. What kind of wood? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 01:50:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Been wanting to try my hand at one... what was your process, if you’d be so kind? It looks great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 00:10:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who tf is mcgregor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 23:10:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If an American were to take a vacation in Wales, where should they be sure to visit? And what time of year? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 15:33:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The cat is actually crying because he knows he’s the next ingredient </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 15:30:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bells is about $13 for a six pack here in PA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 15:28:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Excellent choice in beer btw. Bells Two-Hearted is possibly the best all-around IPA out there.

Oh and cool gator too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 15:24:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gotta love when Mother Nature gifts you a day of indoor relaxation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 20:30:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Worth it just for the theme. Lol’d when I figured it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 20:01:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 31:43, just about a minute over my Friday average... I actually gave up around 20 minutes because I was so lost on NW and SE, leaving most of it blank. Then of course I came back, guessed correctly on a few 3 letter downs and everything fell into place. One big snag was that I was *certain* it had to be >!GLASS!< for 46D for far too long. (As in >!raise a glass for a toast!<. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 17:58:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think they’re mushrooms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 13:30:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What kind of fish? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 03:50:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any fish in there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 03:45:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really enjoyed the theme. I got on a real roll once I got it, thought I was going to breeze through the puzzle, then just couldn’t get the NW. very frustrating, but a good puzzle. Mad at myself that I couldn’t figure it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 03:42:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God I’m glad I’m not alone at least </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What killed my cucumbers?? Started off perfectly healthy, then a few weeks ago the central leaves started to yellow, and now this. Please give me some feedback. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 23:45:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 19:35:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you read the songs you would know!

But for real. Without the songs, the setting isn’t complete. There’s a tone and obviously meaning to the words that help create the universe you’re peering into. Knowing the backstories and “lore” is vital to fully appreciating LotR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 19:31:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There’s almost no point if you don’t read the songs lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 15:37:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omfg I forgot all about Cathy. My local newspaper ran it when I was a kid, and even then I cringed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 15:36:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuckin classic Marlene </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 03:01:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, to be fair the >!Cleveland INDIANs!< are just a tad racist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 01:56:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Brine them for 4 hours first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 00:43:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Came here to say this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 21:41:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m also thinking the guy may be photoshopped in lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 21:23:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, I would tell and absolutely have told relatives that so-and-so have “died”. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 21:18:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lots of dogs would look huge if their head was a good 4 or 5 feet in front of a human head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 21:17:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In what sense is the word “dead” insensitive? It’s a standard English word, and not some slangy term like “croaked” or “bit the bullet”. And “pass away” is only said by those uncomfortable with the finality of death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 18:58:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guess I forgot about it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 13:39:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are way overthinking it my dude. It’s freaking Pokémon. There is literally nothing difficult, that’s the point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 13:38:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s a Pokémon game. They’re designed for 6-11 year olds. Nothing is difficult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 13:06:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea, but that’s what added about 4 minutes to my time, just that one clue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 13:05:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was actually a huge fan of the >!SUNRA!< clue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 04:55:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing like smoked nuts!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 04:52:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It fit so I was like, “it must be right” lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wednesday 8/11 NYT </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 04:30:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How’s everyone do? 13:38 here, just about average, however I spent ~4 minutes in the south, not understanding what they meant by >!spine. Also, I had never heard of the Ohio Players, but a clever enough theme for today, so I’ll take it. Still upset I had to erase STARSANDSTRIPES though...!< </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 16:09:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You used “exceed” twice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 16:47:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I meant to say “do” instead of being assumption with the “so.”

But, since you say you wish you had one, my follow-up question is, why do you support flag desecration? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 04:25:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fucking BAIT lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 23:48:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are honestly underestimating the male of our species. Trust me, I am one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 23:45:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can absolutely guarantee you that you are dead wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 23:12:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What temp? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 20:57:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So you own a “thin blue line” flag or sticker? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 18:26:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Except maybe Rise of Skywalker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 15:58:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Corroborating the leaf miners comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 15:55:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think nearly everybody does. And the reason? The shows are for KIDS. You’re a grown adult, that kind of entertainment doesn’t hold up after the initial nostalgia wears off because every single episode is exactly the same. And who cares? Go do something else besides watching cartoons like some college sophomore pothead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 00:43:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Loved this one. Excellent fill, >!UFOREPORTS and POTDISPENSARY!< my two favorites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 20:53:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Lover Man on South Saturn Delta is a great recording. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 20:53:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Bleeding Heart on 12/31/69 is among Jimi’s absolute best blues work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 20:52:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which song? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 20:51:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which Machine Gun though, first or second show? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 13:45:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Japanese Beetles! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 13:44:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m sad that Lover Man isn’t getting any, well, love. I always had a feeling that Jimi really liked playing it, considering it was never released and since the only way someone would have heard it was at a concert, I think he was also pretty proud of it. It’s a great little guitar tune. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 13:40:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Pass It On/Hey Baby on the Berkeley second show release is one of my all time favorites! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 13:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The recording from the first Fillmore show is one of the best guitar he’s ever played! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 13:38:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s the best version! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Whom do you prefer? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 06:10:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love them both!

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/i5sqei) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Favorite live song? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 06:06:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doesn’t have to be a specific recording, but of these concert staples, which is your favorite?

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/i5soic) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 06:04:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s a moot point whether he was “good” or not. The movie was just a hack-job sham so it’s entirely irrelevant as a depiction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 03:13:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This seems to be the solution </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 03:13:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe update your app? They added it a couple months ago. It’s right below the Daily Mini </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 16:22:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Meant to ask if anyone else is having this problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Issues with Spelling Bee in NYT app? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 16:21:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This happens daily... I won’t get the new puzzle until well into the morning, and it’s never the same time. The playable puzzle is still yesterdays, and when you tap “yesterday” for the list of words, it shows for that same puzzle. Kind of annoying, you’d think they would’ve fixed it by now.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 21:18:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “Not a Trump supporter but...” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 19:57:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don’t feel dumb. I once had a beautiful native brown in my left hand, the stringer in my right. I looked into those cold, reptilian-like eyes and felt a pang of morality. Told that trout that today was his lucky day and let him swim away. After that I couldn’t make another cast that morning, despite only being on the creek and hour or so.

I’ve taken many a-fish since then. Sometimes it’s just a thing that happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 18:19:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Keep in mind that the fish was likely in a state of complete shock, and the little awareness that they have was probably rendered to pure instinctual behavior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 18:05:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Welcome to Earth! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 17:42:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So that’s what you did with the apricots... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 02:57:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Always thought it was funny how he thought Star Wars was a bunch of teenaged nonsensical drivel, but sure loved those check$! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 02:50:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. Ducking. Way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 02:48:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Buddy tried to get him to play it more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 02:47:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s Noel... but what’s your definition of “playing?” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 02:25:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Always a good feeling! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 01:56:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What acid did you use and how long did it sit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 21:43:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn’t like how you had >!Ruled!< and >!Rule!<, but definitely some unique fill, and not too hard. Took about 10 mins! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 18:22:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s an ingredient in an >!EVERYTHINGBAGEL!< </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 17:37:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for asking and getting an answer on this Mini. I had forgotten that I had no idea what it was about and when I had it solved, I was just more confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 13:13:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does Shortz even look at the puzzles anymore, you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 05:27:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m still in shock over that clue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 04:25:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol, I was 21:08 yesterday, so this was much appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NYT Wednesday 8/5 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 04:20:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I liked it! 12:49, which is about average. Simple, grid-spanning theme that once figured out, made the whole puzzle fall right into place. Which, IMHO, is the point of a theme. Thought it was >!VERUKASALT!< for too long though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Homemade] Slow-cooker carnitas tostadas </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 03:59:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 02:53:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 02:19:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 01:50:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Welcome to the club brother. When there’s this much backlash over a freaking crossword puzzle, you know it was fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 16:42:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Perch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 15:00:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hungarian paprika (sweet & got), garlic & onion powder, cumin, cinnamon, brown sugar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 13:48:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was definitely crispy. However, I put ~225, because that was the average temp. It got above 250 at times, so maybe that was the difference. It also bribed for about 18 hours beforehand, but I don’t know if that matters for skin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First go at smoked pulled chicken. 4.3 lb, 4 hours at ~225. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 13:15:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 04:54:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The cross there was one of the worst parts. >!EDNA DAME!< who the hell has heard of her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NYT Tuesday 8/4 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 04:38:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Terrible. The insanely obscure pop culture, art, and history answers were simply ridiculous. I’m pissed at myself because I had to look one thing up to keep the streak alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 02:00:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 23:22:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very good! Bosch-esque. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What’s wrong with my cucumbers? Central leaves dying... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 19:33:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 18:58:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It sounds like you have a serious drinking habit, and likely a dependency. You should seek help in some fashion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 18:57:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ve driven drunk countless times, is it really that much of a rush? Especially if you “know what you’re doing,” it’s sort of just a casual drive with that little extra bit of caution/fear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 15:24:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >!OLMEC!< was definitely the highlight for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 14:55:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually thought it had some more difficult proper nouns and foreign language for a Monday. I didn’t really struggle but >!OLMEC, SAMOA, CABO, LANAI, MALI, MARDI, AGUA, and OTRO!< I thought could throw some beginners for a real loop. However, I enjoyed the puzzle, 6:30 (about average), and honestly >!OLMEC!< was a nice change of pace. I was worried it was going to be  >!INCAN!< lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 14:25:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But it’s not just a family photo, it’s a publicity op that was released by Trump for advertising. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 04:57:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The theme hints are in the answers, not in the clues lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 21:24:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Am I missing something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 21:10:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Enjoyed the theme, definitely an “ah-hah” moment when I got it.

But what is going on with the provocative clues/answers??? Lol, first we had HISANDHIS and LUSTS for “growing pulls” earlier this week and now >!PHONESEX!< lol. I love it!

Edit: 44:32, which is average for me for Sunday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 13:49:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You did a good job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 13:44:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, it quite actually is how it works. Humans’ brains aren’t finished developing at your age, so you can’t actually determine certain characteristics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 13:36:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then you’re not asexual, you’re just a confused teenager. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 13:10:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m guessing you never took a sexual education course, or have you just not gone to high school yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 13:07:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How self-conscious does he have to be, a fat load judging people’s food? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 13:03:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Always have to feed Mutt’s victims to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 12:47:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn’t see the cat, but can I say that photo would make for an outstanding jigsaw puzzle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 12:44:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should’ve just made 2 full paintings and presented them as one work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 12:37:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like this isn’t a random achievement, and that you purposefully broke a streak 101 days ago while making sure you had 1000 puzzles solved, and likely used hints to get 100%, just so you could take that screenshot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 12:34:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the clue was alluding to his documented fear of “the curse of the ninth,” and how he famously died after publishing his last symphony, which was titled his ninth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 16:50:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you missed the point of the clue... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 16:48:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do you have a 100% solve rate on 1000 puzzles, but only a 100 day streak? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 16:01:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> While he might not be your favorite, he’s definitely top 5 Sith Lords o.a.t. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 13:10:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is hilarious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 13:08:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m in Eastern time zone, and I can complete any day up till 11:59 PM and it counts towards my streak. I’ve tested it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 13:06:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You were right lol. I just got today’s! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 13:05:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My first Saturday I ever completed! 32:19 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 04:01:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you like girls with thick thighs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 23:20:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do you know you’re the first? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 14:52:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really enjoyed the clues, especially the >!”progressive” and racy ones like HISANDHIS and LUSTS!< thought they were a breath of fresh air. I did however set a PB, which I now have a 2 day streak of doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 13:57:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “Well then, let him go,” replied the lawyer, and his cheerful self-satisfied expression became sullen and spiteful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 23:54:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol no worries. Madder that I struggled with this one today. Guess the “Z” threw me off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 23:48:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any chance of the menu description? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 23:46:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is Boswords though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 23:45:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s better than 90 others! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How am I doing? Been at this since Jan of 2019, so about 19 months. Never solved a Saturday, but never cheat or look anything up ever. Only ask my wife for pop culture references once in a blue moon. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 23:41:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 23:36:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “Everyone” meaning you and the people that you’ve seen on this subreddit and elsewhere online who care enough to complain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 23:33:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God damn it. I thought you wrote that it *wasnt* accepted, and for some reason I had to test it. Now I got a Genius score I didn’t earn.

Not your fault obviously, just pissed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 14:38:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One puzzle doesn’t equate to an overall trend that the NYT is getting easier. It’s just a recency bias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 14:02:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe you just got better at solving? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 23:15:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, at 18 you are an adult. You are also a teenager. It’s not a matter of opinion lol. It’s like saying 100 is more than 1000. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 23:14:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “Teenager” is someone in their “teens”. As in, thirTEEN to nineTEEN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Beach at Dawn </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 21:38:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is Grey Poupon classic Dijon mustard top tier? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 21:31:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/i06zt1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 21:24:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Carson Wentz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The sunrise in the OBX, NC </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 18:34:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 23:23:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TRAIN WITH BERNARD

That is literally the answer. You just have to practice, not just for your in-game Henry, but for the Henry inside your mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 23:20:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “Main cellphone” lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 19:48:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you even want to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 00:21:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t understand the theme. How does it help you figure it out once you get 47D? I get that the circled letters are all >!in alphabetical order!< but what am I missing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 17:38:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “Not photoshopped” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 20:44:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 14:03:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do you have 5 leashes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 02:26:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this in a restaurant in the Outer Banks??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 17:15:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ve never seen a European pluralize “Euro” with an “s”. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 12:38:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes the famous beach nourishment... it really has essentially destroyed surf fishing. However last year I stayed in Duck, and it had been a little longer since the b.n. and I had some of the best success in a decade. We had normally stayed in Nags Head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 03:30:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Soooo WILD Steve!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 02:44:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What kind of territory does she have? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 02:14:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don’t need it! White wine vinegar and Dijon mustard FTW! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Maple smoked pork chops with some mayo-less potato salad </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 02:13:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Homemade] maple-smoked bone-in pork chop and mayonnaise-less potato salad. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 02:09:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 01:33:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 21:36:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OBX municipalities rely 100% on tourist revenue. Barring the Russians literally invading, or a zombie outbreak, they aren’t closing the beaches/towns. Even in the grip of a pandemic as serious as this, they will take every cent from you and I before they are forced to completely close. Even if the beaches are patrolled by SWAT teams, they won’t refund your rental. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> SHORE FISHING </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 21:33:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How has it been?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Lake NOCKAMIXON, Bucks County, PA </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 21:31:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would sincerely appreciate any tips/pointers relating to shore-fishing this beautiful lake. I’ve fished it twice from the shore, including the “fishing pier” with lures but no success. Help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Did you solve NYT SUNDAY 7/12 with no help? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 21:28:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/hq0cun) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 19:48:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cats bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 04:48:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only way to get better is to continually work at solving puzzles. A puzzle is only truly solved if all the squares are filled in using nothing but memory and reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 13:20:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Watch out for Cumans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 02:16:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Any* fish is better than *no* fish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 01:05:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cheated and had the app finish for me. I thought that bottom left was all I was missing, but I had a few errors elsewhere that I couldn’t find out. Ruined my damn streak too... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 00:48:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel really dumb. “Coinage” threw me off for some reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Help requested for today 7/10 Friday NYT </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 00:03:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 31D... I have >!NASCAR!< followed by 2 blanks, then ending in >!D!< Any tips or hints would be greatly appreciated... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-10 13:41:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait are you implying LotR doesn’t have a well-defined story? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-10 13:38:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Came here to make the same post. Phew! Glad it’s not me. I don’t think I could EKE out another day without doing the crossword! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-10 13:13:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s some boomer shit right there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 17:50:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As far as I know yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 17:25:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The area around >!hansom!< troubled me a bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 17:24:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also, can’t wait to take a >!hansom!< ride through Central Park </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 17:22:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you’re on to something here... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 17:22:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seems like a flimsy theme to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thursday 7/9 NYT Theme? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 16:53:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Am I missing something here? Other than all the circled boxes are filled in with >!circular-related!< words... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 18:07:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The hobbit films were ok fan fiction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 17:54:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can just imagine my late grandfather, an avid crossworder, coming across that clue... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 17:14:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate that clue so much for that very reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 13:47:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it’s pretty cool having a Sith Lord tattooed on your back actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 13:42:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The OREO got me lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 03:39:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is ULNA really “crosswordese” though? There’s really no other term for that specific bone, and it’s not an obscure or uncommon word. I know it’s a common answer though, so I definitely do appreciate the input!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 00:47:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope you have a good time. I’m taking a safari to hunt GNU in Africa for my vacation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 00:33:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you going to have a layover in EIRE? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 23:09:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The app actually doesn’t steal any information. It’s users willingly and voluntarily allow it access to all the data it collects when they install and agree to its terms. TikTok is a data collecting app with a video sharing function. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone add crosswordese words to their regular speaking vocabulary? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 22:46:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 21:45:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do the Mini>Spelling Bee>Daily Crossword. In that order. I find the first two get my mind rolling in the morning. I’ll usually come back to the Spelling Bee a couple times till I get “Amazing”. Haven’t hit “Genius” yet... >:[ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 18:30:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sleep on it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-06 17:29:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never grown yellow squash before, but I would assume the same holds true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-06 15:45:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. They lose flavor and tenderness if they get too big. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Oh yea, we all knew this one </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-05 05:12:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 14:15:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As does Death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 13:24:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ve been improving a lot recently on Fridays, but am almost exactly, down to the age, in the same position as you. I just roll my eyes and grown when there’s too many proper nouns. Same with foreign language bits. Although you should’ve seen me when I figured out what a rebus is... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 02:21:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s because it came from two separate warehouses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 00:52:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There’s two white shirts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Did Jimi ever record or even perform “Who Knows” except for the second and third shows of the Band of Gypsy performance at the Fillmore? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 00:44:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can’t find any. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 00:39:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wild black raspberries. Delicious and nutritious. Very common in Northeast US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 00:35:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You’ve just refuted your original point.

As for the mainstream being correct about games, I wholeheartedly disagree. Animal Crossing, CoD, Fortnight, Battlefield are all terrible products.

I thought the game sucked too for the record, but I enjoyed playing it. It’s not all about “ranking” and “scoring” things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 00:29:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So you’ve literally never enjoyed something the vast majority of human beings dislike? Or hated something the vast majority enjoy? God... your life must be fucking awful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 23:49:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why don’t you just cut it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 23:28:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m still stuck at Friday>Saturday. Been doing the daily’s on the app since about December of 2018, so about 19 months. I can do about 50% of Sunday’s, and rarely get stumped on anything before Thursday, but those damn Saturdays just kill me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 20:41:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 19:50:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea it really isn’t that hard, and I kill him immediately in playthroughs now. But my first try I had no idea what I was doing. I think the only armor I had on was a waffenrock and low level gambeson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 17:37:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always find that once the theme/rebus of Thursday’s is figured out, the rest has the difficulty of a Monday or Tuesday. Today’s (7/2) is a perfect example of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 16:47:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I find it very frustrating that I can almost always get through Thursday, about 50% of Friday’s, and a good deal of Sunday’s, but can literally never make any real headway on Saturdays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What day can you comfortably (>75% of the time) complete up to each week of the NYT crossword? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 16:21:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/hjxw1d) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 16:01:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmm I’ve never seen it in one before. Now I know! In case you’re curious, I solved the puzzle technically without cheating. I actually did have >!sera!< but my problem was on 72 across. I originally had >!oatey!<

Edit: thanks by the way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 14:12:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea but I quit the game and didn’t come back for almost a year bc I couldn’t figure out what I was doing wrong

Edit: I thought you meant your actual first time in the church, forgot about in the prologue in Skalitz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 14:11:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What the heck is >!sera!< </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 12:51:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having a tough time... my answer to 1 across seems off, but it fits perfectly with all the down clues in it. Any hints? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How little I knew... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 12:19:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 02:25:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Art rock ELO or disco ELO? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 02:33:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. Like a Rolling Stone - without it music today would have been very different

2. The Times They Are a-Changin’ - important protest song

3. Blowin’ in the Wind - same reason

4. Mr. Tambourine - best lyrics

5. Lay, Lady, Lay - best song on the list </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 02:39:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, if you talk to Kuno he sets off with the whole crew at once </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 02:11:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always forget about Monterey. I’ve heard some of it; how’s the sound quality? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Favorite/Best live albums? Looking for recommendations... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 01:19:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have:

The full Fillmore East boxset
Woodstock
Berkeley
Hendrix in the West
BBC Sessions (sort of live)
Atlanta Pop

What are some really good ones I’m missing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 15:54:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just sic Mutt on them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Stone died in the first mission. Does it matter?? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 04:55:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First playthrough with BoB, and the Stone died when we went to attack the raiders who attacked the first cabin by Samopesh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Idk why but this little map token made me chuckle </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 03:45:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 22:16:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They almost look like redbuds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 12:53:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s bc it is cheating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 12:51:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it worth playing Yakuza 0, rather than the newer release, Yakuza: Like a Dragon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 03:20:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe I slice it thicker! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 03:19:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really? I’ve done it for an hour before. Anything longer than that the squash does get soggy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 03:10:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Marinate in balsamic vinegar, olive oil, and minced garlic for 30 minutes, then put in grill basket and grill on both sides till slightly charred. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 16:47:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isle of Wight ‘70 he played one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Any idea what’s causing the yellowing/spotting on the bottom leaves of my tomatoes? Several different varieties, water every other day. ~8 hours full sun </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 13:30:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Any idea what’s causing the yellowing/spotting on the bottom leaves of my tomatoes? Several different varieties, water every other day. ~8 hours full sun </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 13:29:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 22:43:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I meant what’d you do with the snake. (I thought originally that was a lure in its mouth and it was hooked.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 22:40:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What’d you do?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 11:39:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 16:27:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My copy of Lord of the Rings has one that says “epic motion picture trilogy coming soon from new line cinema.” I think it’s kind of cool now lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 19:51:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because they’re not ripe yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 01:15:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Possibly the greatest fishing meme ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 14 fish total for Father’s Day with my dad, including this nice guy. 8 largemouth, 4 perch, and 2 (decent) bluegills. All released, but kicking myself I’m not eating the one big perch right now... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 01:11:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 01:08:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 23:59:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably because of the physical source tapes. It’s not like it’s some track floating around the internet. There’s a hard copy somewhere in Janie Hendrix’s mansion that was produced during a documentable recording session. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 23:56:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m very interested in the outcome of this. “Hey Joe” was Jimi’s first hit single, but “Purple Haze” is probably his most enduring track, at least in the ethereal consensus of popular opinion. He also played both routinely throughout his touring career, with some memorable performances linkable to each song. I personally prefer “Hey Joe,” as I think it’s a realer piece, while “Purple Haze” is more a product of the psychedelic scene’s influence.

But I love both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Pick one </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 23:35:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/hdf2kd) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 10:01:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely a genuine “aha” moment for me too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 09:57:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nobody knows what you’re talking about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> All the lasses in Bohemia, when a certain lad from Silver Skalitz rolls through their chambers: </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 21:02:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 13:47:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very fair opinion! The studio recordings are certainly well-produced, and still maintain the grit that was always palpable in Jimi’s music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 01:03:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is an excellent reply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 01:02:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Exactly* how I feel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 22:40:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It seems he liked playing in Scandinavia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 22:40:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No disagreement at all! Obviously the quality will be better with a polished studio product. However, I still prefer live Jimi. The raw, improvised feel of a Hendrix concert from introduction to encore is something so wonderfully unique, it can’t be topped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 20:53:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Henry’s come to see us! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 20:51:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s definitely a good lesson! You really kneaded it in the machine for a full hour? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 20:48:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any tips that you learned from attempt 1 to attempt 2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 20:08:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I usually stop right after I meet Ulrich. When he tells me he has some loose ends in Sasau to tie up, it’s a good place to focus on side quests and other things. I find it fits right into the story that way. I’m also doing bits and pieces all along the way if I find myself in certain locales. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Preference? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 19:46:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (Studio Jimi includes outtakes and “unreleased” material)

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/hbjfdp) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 19:45:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never heard either! Thanks for sharing, now I have something to go find! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 18:14:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They’re your rolls, ice ‘em however tf you want! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 18:12:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Excellent!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 18:11:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What kind of beans? Never tried growing them but I know they’re popular garden plants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 16:39:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any idea where I can get a hard copy of that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is your favorite recording of “Machine Gun”? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 15:57:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know everyone likes the Band of Gypsys LP version, but I prefer the one from the 4th show of the Fillmore concerts the most. Some other good choices are the Isle of Wight and Berkeley concerts. Wanna see if anyone has something I’ve never heard. There’s a lot to choose from! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 15:33:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dads cat does. But only with pieces of broken off notebook spiral... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 02:40:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And yet you chose this one ; ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 12:57:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You mean on the top right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 12:52:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m not seeing the infuriating part of this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 12:50:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s incredible that people actually fall for that account. I laugh every time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 12:28:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok, name one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 02:49:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whatever you do, please for the love of all dogs, do not buy a dog from any breeder whatsoever. Regardless of their “reputation,” there are thousands of perfect companions waiting for adoption just in your area. You’ll feel a much stronger bond to it as well. A life isn’t something to be bought and sold like a pair of pants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 02:45:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely all of this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 02:36:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 32 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 02:29:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No exaggeration, this should be a capital, executionable offense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 18:30:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Welcome to KCD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 18:28:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very happy that Billy is winning here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 18:28:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just listen to his music, it’s all there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 18:04:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh those will grow some nice fruits all right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 12:53:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 02:45:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Currituck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 02:19:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I made it just because I stumbled across this sub, and found it mildly amusing how much some people really cared about mustard. I didn’t realize how important it was! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 02:16:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why did you cut out the end?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 02:05:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those are some nice tomatoes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 19:31:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I should’ve combined spicy and brown and added honey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Pick a bassist. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 18:51:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/h9k1mb) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 18:50:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All recordings. The question is more which do you prefer in his overall catalogue. Phrase it this way: if Jimi suddenly appeared in front of you, which song would you want him to play? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 14:13:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I kind of meant stone ground as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In freshwater, which do you prefer to fish for the most? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 12:34:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/h9dr0i) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 12:27:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is why I prefer axes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 12:26:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol I debated as to what to put as the sixth option. I even tried to go back and switch it to fists, but reddit doesn’t let you change poll options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 05:43:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bro. I made this poll hoping to get some love for the axe. Shocked it has so few votes. It’s the best weapon imo!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 05:41:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You guys... really like mustard, huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 05:11:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Each option is supposed to be the “main” feel of the the mustard. All spicy mustards fall under spicy, if that’s your favorite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> You must pick one.. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 02:57:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/h95qxm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Suggestions on this little lemon tree? Got it from a gardening expo 4 months ago, believe it is a Meyer. Planted in standard “garden” bagged soil. Just had one flower bloom so I’m hopeful. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 00:25:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 00:22:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m on a HC play using axe and shield. Very rewarding combat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is your main weapon? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 00:16:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Averaged out over all your playthroughs if you have several

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/h930b0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Which do you prefer? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 00:12:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/h92ydc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My wife’s Lavender came in strong this year. Bumblebee as a bonus. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 23:51:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 04:36:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then find some new Jimi you haven’t heard before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 04:17:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jimi Hendrix. That’s all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 02:01:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Axis:_Bold_as_Love

Skip to Artwork and Packaging section </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 01:57:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea that’s exactly the point. Jimi had nothing to do with the cover. The label ignored his suggestion, just like they did later on Electric Ladyland when they used the nude women cover. He was disgusted and embarrassed by both covers, and said so numerous times in interviews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 01:10:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because it makes a mockery of an ancient image that is held deeply sacred by hundreds of millions of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 22:04:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ask Jimi, that’s how he felt about it. Probably something to do with using a culture’s most sacred and revered image for a measly pop music advertisement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 21:15:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s also racist as hell and Jimi despised it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 21:14:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you’re asking Jimi-approves releases, then my order is:

1. Band of Gypsys
2. Electric Ladyland
3. Are You Experienced?
4. Axis: Bold as Love

But if you’re asking my overall favorite Jimi Hendrix release? Then it has to be the Jimi Hendrix Experience purple box set. Too many incredible tracks to even mention.

For my favorite album-length release, it is without question the Blues compilation. Really showcases Jimi doing what he grew up listening to, and what all his music is based off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 01:57:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think they look literally nothing alike, except they have the same hair and eye color. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 01:49:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was wondering the same actually </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Are these onion seeds ready to pick off and store? Plant is from a kitchen onion that sprouted about 3 months ago. Also it i live in Mid-Atlantic US state. How do I keep the seeds for planting next year? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 01:48:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 21:20:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What’s the date on this puzzle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 19:24:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ahhh I gotcha. Not a bad idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 17:49:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You mean buy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rattay merchants not replenishing their groschen? [PS4] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 14:52:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Specifically the swordsmith and armourer. One is at 60g and the other ~250g, and both have been stuck there for several in-game days. I haven’t really looked at other merchants or towns, but obviously this is a problem, considering I probably have 50k worth of loot in my trunk and can’t sell it. Normally both would have 20k in groschen regularly at this point of a playthrough. Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 04:25:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The point is that he’s doing all of them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone else ever notice that Huntsman Nicholas complains about not being able to find the poachers, yet is selling a treasure map that LEADS RIGHT FUCKING TO THEM YOU IDIOT </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 03:18:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 02:22:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you hit a target it drastically increases XP. Whether that target is an enemy or part of a contest doesn’t matter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 02:13:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not just with Bernard, but make sure you learn at least ripostes. Practice everywhere! The entire point of the game is that you start off terrible at everything, like a 15th century son of a blacksmith would be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 01:11:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s called practice, young Hal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 01:05:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For the prologue, you play as actual Henry, all with full powered stats, just to give you a glimpse of what it’s like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 01:04:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a game I want to play </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 00:56:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Historically, Hans dies in 1419, so his death to a 17ish year old son of Henry could be a major plot point in the game.

Yes, it is kind of same-y to our current KCD, but I figure they have to complete the revenge plot somehow. And since building your Henry up to snuff is such a critical part of the game, I don’t see how they do that without it being a different character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 00:45:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Less often than I read the book! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 23:03:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My theory:

You play as Henry and Theresa’s son. Henry settled down, got inundated with his daily tasks as bailiff of Pribyslavitz, and never ventured out to finally track down Markvart von Aulitz. Something makes Henry remember his old vow (maybe a letter from Prague, or something about Radzig’s death), and before he can set out with his old friend Sir Hans on another adventure, catastrophe strikes. Theresa is killed, and Henry maimed trying to save her. With his dying words, he makes his young son swear that he will fulfill the family’s oath of revenge.

Well, young Henry Jr. has lived a... spoiled life. His mother doted on him, and father strove to give him an easier life than he had. Being the son of the village bailiff, he is conceited, vain, and overall a brat.

All skills are set to 0. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 02:36:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “Sushi” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 02:18:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s sorted alphabetically, but for some reason they switched from Great Britain to United Kingdom. They also use the native language spelling for Spain (España) and Croatia (Hrvatska) oddly enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 02:09:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see you are a fellow aristocrat. Well met. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 02:05:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that cottage cheese? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 01:46:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Psilocybin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 01:42:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You’re doing God’s work, my friend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My wife just said she “lost all her weeds” and is now upset. I do not play this game. What does that mean, why is it a bad thing, and what should I tell her to make it better? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 01:28:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Serious question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Will my PS4 version of KCD be backwards compatible on the PS5? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 20:41:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only info I could find was an old post here that people answered “yes” to the same question, but that was back in January. PlayStation is putting out that the “overwhelming majority” of games will be compatible, but since KCD is from a smaller studio, I was wondering if anyone had dug up more info in the last 6 months. Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 17:35:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bamboo is just about the hardiest plant out there, so you can plant it in soil or leave in water. I don’t think that ornamental variety grows very quickly though. Don’t plant outside though, most municipalities have laws against bamboo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 17:31:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s bamboo that was intentionally forced into growing in a spiral shape. Not really mistreated. People use them as decoration or in aquariums </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 15:56:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can’t skin hares? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 13:43:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have the hunting perk that allows to skin, but when I kill a hare, all I can get is meat. What am I doing wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 13:32:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If Gengar is a ghost, how can you bump into him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 01:57:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does it get enough sun? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 01:49:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you doing ok? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 23:27:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 23:24:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea I’m shocked that Sasau isn’t getting more votes. Has all the amenities of Rattay, the monestary for a unique feature, a scribe, and Johanka. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 19:23:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Excellent choice! Especially for when Theresa catching you coming back from the bathhouse... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 18:27:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not all Trump supporters are dumb. But they are all one (or more) of the following:

* misinformed
* uninformed
* racist
* anti-America
* misogynistic
* wealthy
* superstitious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 17:31:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Am I missing something with the charlatan? He only has a few small quests that don’t get you much, then fucks off to Ledetchko and doesn’t do anything. Everyone talks about him like he’s something special and I don’t get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 17:29:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I usually am a perfect chivalrous knight in Rattay, but a complete scoundrel in Sasau </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 17:28:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to think it was kind of shitty, but now I definitely feel the “backwoods” type charm it has. Plus it has Chumps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Favorite location in the game? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 16:53:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In general, to spend time in, to fight in, to loot in, the traders, the characters, the quests, the scenery, the overall feel. Any criteria really. Just want to see some opinions. Include the immediate vicinity as well (example, Peshek’s mill included in Rattay, monestary for Sasau, etc). If your favorite isn’t included, add it in the comments.

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/gzonig) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 16:49:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I definitely have that in all my Medieval II: Total War plays </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 12:57:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’d be interested in that squash recipe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 12:54:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gotta hit that chest in the tent in the back.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 04:31:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vicious, mean creatures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 20:29:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I go Ken, bc I find that Speech, Charisma, and Stealth are easier to build up/buff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 20:28:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So then you’re saying Trump failed and it’s right to hope for better results when he’s out of office? You can’t have both lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 18:45:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So in your opinion leaders are useless and can’t solve anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> They never get old, do they? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 18:34:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Henry, on his tour of Pribyslavitz with Marius the Locator </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 16:36:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 13:14:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly one of my favorite parts of the game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 13:11:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait what’s that big person thing in the middle of the map? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Burgher vs savage? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 13:10:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which perk do you choose? I always go with Savage, because most of your fighting is done in the woods.

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/gyaemm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 13:03:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The area we live in naturally has an acidic, clay soil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 13:01:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s a painting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 23:13:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never a bad time to get into, or back into, Dylan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 22:00:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You’ve got to be joking man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 21:34:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do another one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 21:06:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ahh, you’re a fan of assumptions I see. Well-met, my wayward idiot friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 20:45:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What did he do that “instigated?” He peaceably walked up a sidewalk while legally exercising a bill of rights amendment freedom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 19:46:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So... fighting against actual Nazis in pre-WW2 Germany is now a bad thing. Got it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 19:44:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn’t it the police’s responsibility to keep law-abiding citizens safe? Example: an elderly man exercising his constitutional right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 19:42:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “There is a point about Jews which occurs to me—you must not have too many of them. “

Winston Churchill, 1918 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 19:23:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You don’t want to. Its hardly a Jimi Hendrix album. They overdubbed nearly everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Pulled up next to this very good boy a while back. He wanted to say hi. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 17:45:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 16:19:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s only 4! But great tracks. Power of Soul is *the* most underrated Jimi song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 16:15:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very rarely. Just some old/dying branches once every few years. Overall great health. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 13:26:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. Hear My Train a-Comin’: Jimi was First and foremost a bluesman. Even Purple Haze has its roots in the blues. This song, even more so than Red House, showcases Jimi’s expertise in this music.

2. Machine Gun: In an era of protest and rioting (sound familiar?) this is Jimi’s most lasting manifesto of social commentary. Painful lyrics, soaring guitar, and numerous legendary performances, this is a must in any top list.

3. Little Wing: Simply just a beautiful song, that you can appreciate even more by hearing all the different versions. Jimi was hard and heavy, but this is always a breath of fresh air in his catalogue.

4. Purple Haze: Jimi’s springboard to stardom had definite staying power, and he knew it. This was always a concert staple, and those opening notes are as chilling today as they were in 67.

5. Freedom: At its core, just a great proto-funk song, but really signifies a direction Jimi was headed. Still loud, still heavy, but more groovy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Always been proud of my little backyard thicket. Whoever planted it knew what they were doing. Andromeda, rhodo, azaleas, cedar pine. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 12:43:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 05:06:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exact same thing happened to me on very first playthrough. Thought, “oh cool, a cave” and discovered the counterfeiters lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 02:28:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg never mind, his room is on the 2nd floor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can’t start “Next to Godliness.” Hans Capon is always just in his took in Pirkstein, with the door closed, regardless of the time of day, so I can’t start the quest. (PS4) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 02:27:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ve done it in other playthroughs, and I’m already chasing the German knight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 23:40:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s a great little paragraph man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 22:23:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why don’t you just skip it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 16:49:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice call, didn’t see that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 13:42:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What if I don’t recognize it, bc I’m too old? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 13:08:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interesting choice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 13:07:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t care at all about any kind of motor racing, or just anything automotive in general.

But I can feel the coolness in this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 12:34:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea, that’s why it’s not an option lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 02:47:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These people should be imprisoned, and force fed with a funnel, given tapeworms, and made to dance naked with music blaring at max volume. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 02:24:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m honestly not sure, I think it might just be a different graphic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 01:26:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They give you different results, but same chance of success. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 01:25:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Idk bro. I’m on PS4, and it runs fine. No bugs, no issues with gameplay, some slow graphics but nothing that comes close to ruining the experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 01:23:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same, and I’m on a fucking OG PS4. Yea some textures pop in slowly in Rattay (btw, lad, fancy a little wager on the tourney?), but other than that, clean as Henry’s conscience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 01:21:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You’re going way too slowly. Fluid, steady (not rapid) motion. What platform are you playing on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 01:20:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh this is gold </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Favorite Hendrix Album (that he approved and released). </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 01:04:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not the “best” the “most important” or whatever else. Just YOUR favorite. FYI and for the record: the JHE purple box set is the greatest Hendrix release ever.

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/gwsh73) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 00:58:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not many Hendrix memes out there lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 00:58:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cool guitar-playing, but wouldn’t call it one if Jimi’s “lesser known tracks.” It’s the title track of his most famous album! Now, if you said one of his most unique, I’d give you that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 00:51:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same, momentarily ruined my immersion on my first playthrough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-04 12:57:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the obvious answer is Watchtower, no?

Also: Bleeding Heart, Who Knows, Bold as Love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-04 02:12:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can’t really explain the gay element without major spoilers. Have you finished the main story? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 00:47:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just search “Kingdom come racist” in google </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 00:44:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can’t remember the next line sorry bro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 00:41:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When he died, the whole empire mourned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How does anyone believe this game is “racist” or “white supremacist” in any way? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 00:39:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. The Cumans aren’t painted as barbarian monsters at all. Henry even exclaims how much better and cleaner their camp is than the bandits’ in Nest of Vipers
2. The townspeople who claim the Cumans are monsters are shown to be ignorant idiots. There’s a whole side quest about it!
3. There simply weren’t people of ethnicity other than German/Czech/Polish/etc in that specific small area in that time. To include a character of African or Middle-Eastern descent just include one, in a game designed solely for historical accuracy is nonsense and backward-thinking, not progressive or inclusive.
4. If anyone thinks this game glorifies white-only society, and yearns for the “old days,” they’ve never played past the prologue. These people lived in literal shit! It’s the point of the game!

I despise racism and bigotry in all its manifestations, systemic or personal, but I also dislike false labels.

Idk, thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 00:30:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *ruled from Prague expanded* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Olena is fucking nuts. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-02 01:45:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-01 03:47:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No one ever said it better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 22:54:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every time I swing by to bang his niece, he’s gotta ask that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can we all just take 10 minutes and listen to Jimi play “Machine Gun,” then reflect on all the terrible things happening in the US this weekend? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 18:50:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 17:19:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This made me laugh like a maniac </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 17:15:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 17:12:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to be terrible at archery as well in KCD, but with everything else, it just took a little practice and now it’s an important part of my combat.

Also, I’ve never fired a bow in real life, and I thought they tried to make it “life-like.” Is it very different? Seems good to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 17:09:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How the hell do you get your lockpicking skill that high in the prologue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 17:07:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Possibly Jimi’s best lyrics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 17:03:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Weird, I was just thinking the other day how rain doesn’t change NPCs behavior. They just keep going about their day. I’m on PS4 with the latest update </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 17:02:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol of course! I prefer the JHE box set version on the second disc. All instrumental, and imo some of Jimi’s all time best guitar work. Leaves me blown away every single time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 16:59:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don’t fuck up the mass. Just follow The preaching of Jan Hus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 16:05:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also, there’s no need to take damage to win at Chumps. Just make sure you only shoot when the logs are closer to the riverbank, and that you finish first to get the extra points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 16:04:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, the archery contest at the encampment near Merjohed is so easy it’s basically cheating. It starts you off aimed dead center, just get the timing right and you’re hitting bullseyes every single time. Bet the max and you’re clearing 180 groschen (I might be wrong but it’s about that) every 2 minutes. So while not really “cheating” at a game, you’re kind of “cheating” at making money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 16:01:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wife’s visiting family. House to myself. I’m right at Questions and Answers in a HC playthrough. Gotta mow the lawn, smoke some chicken wings, then kill some Cumans all day long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 14:41:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Too high or too low?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 03:02:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To each their own! They’re all good! Not my personal favorite though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 00:02:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bought these a month ago on amazon. Great stuff! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 23:20:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s its own thing, and fits well on the album, but just isn’t Jimi’s main dig, so I don’t think it can be stacked up against the rest of his catalogue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 23:19:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What would be your first song? Mine would be hear my train from the first Fillmore show. Always been my favorite Hendrix recording.

Also, where is the tears of rage recording? I don’t know if I’ve heard it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 23:17:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol. You’re missing the fucking point of life dude. Existence is great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 22:01:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea peeing all over where little kids take pictures with their families is cool. Who even cares it’s the center of the US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 21:35:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I might move red house to #3 on my list. So many great recordings out there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 21:34:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I prefer Jam 292, but Pali Gap is great. Which recording do you like best? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 21:31:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Underrated!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 17:23:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wife and I want to plan a Europe trip next year, and Switzerland is on the list of contenders. We’ve been to Sweden, Denmark, Italy, and Belgium, but never seen the Alps. Any recommendations for cities, sights, activities, etc or just any tips at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 17:10:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Voodoo Chile is so great. The version on the “Blues” album is especially top notch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 17:09:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s some quality immersion right therr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 17:08:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a good list! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 16:32:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You don’t get it, do you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 16:32:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do it on HC for sure! Much better experience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 16:30:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only one I’ve heard is a live version on the JHE box set. A studio recording would be incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 16:29:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Foxey Lady is extremely underrated. I forgot about tbh, might have to add it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Argue about my top 10. FYI: not referencing individual performances, just the overall song in Jimi’s repertoire. (Except watchtower, that thing stands for itself, since he hardly played it live.) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 14:49:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 14:39:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My take is:

Original Experience had the best output, but it’s mostly due to Jimi. Mitchell is the *perfect* drummer for Jimi, but Redding just jars me.

The Cry of Love Tour band was the perfect combination for Jimi, and really allowed him to develop in a good direction.

Band of Gypsys is just it’s own thing, those sets were CRUNCHY. But Buddy Miles annoys the shit out of me on too many tracks with his wailing. Just drum, dude.

And the Woodstock band was shite. Watch the video and that dude banging on the bongos is literally nonexistent in the overall sound. Also, Jimi didn’t need a rhythm guitar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 14:34:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If Buddy would just shut up and drum, except for his songs, everything would’ve been better. The problem is Buddy was a frontman same as Jimi, and sometimes listening to those concerts it’s painfully clear to hear him vying for top billing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 14:30:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Btw, excellent technical skill, I couldn’t do that at all lol. Just messed up his details is all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 07:07:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whoever voted for the Woodstock band should be punished with listening to Fat Mattress for the rest of their lives </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Which is your favorite backing band Jimi played with? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 03:33:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/gt5m94) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 03:26:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Too heavy of a goatee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 02:43:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Always gets me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 01:46:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol, you still don’t realize that your dad was just messing with you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 00:16:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I play on PS4 original. The bugs are not that much of an issue. Maybe once in a while it’ll freeze when waking up, losing your progress, but just use more savior schnapps. The texture loading IS more of a problem though. You’ll see some pretty poor performance there, but it’s not constant and can be overlooked.

In short: don’t let a couple small bugs turn you away on what truly is a great, rewarding, and unique gaming experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 00:12:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always thought they should sell for more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 21:23:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Clinching is the best strategy vs shields for me. Or feints. But obviously ripostes always work. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 20:33:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For your immersion: pretty urgent. It feels weird delaying them.

For the mechanics of the game: not at all. You can do them whenever you feel like.

Edit: if you killed runt, you should be able to handle the knight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 20:32:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a great KCD meme. Well done 10/10 Cumans approve </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 20:25:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You know they planned to have 3 games, right? First was supposed to end after killing Runt, second where KCD actually does end, and the third with presumably killing Markvart. They compressed it into what we have due to numerous constraints.

Also, the glitches (other than texture loading) are really negligible now, so idk what you’re on about there.

As for the rest, it just sounds like you’re playing it wrong, my dude. No ones forcing you to cheese combat and many of the quests can end in numerous ways not linked at all to dialogue selection. Suggestion: play on HC with all negative perks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 20:19:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea what a loser </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 19:00:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m using an axe on this playthrough. Didn’t even use master strikes, but also had bane potion. I hit him 5-6 times across the chest and a couple in the head and he went down. 1-2 mins tops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> PS4 OG vs PS4 Pro? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 18:18:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know it’s best on a PC, but I don’t have a gaming computer right now. I was wondering if anyone knows how different this game plays on an original PS4 versus the Pro. I play on the original. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 18:14:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The answer is no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 18:14:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea I don’t know, Robard exclaims about how proud he is of you when you select the vanguard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 18:11:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think a well-landed arrow is one of the most satisfying parts of the game. That and destroying peasants at Farkle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 17:52:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interesting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 17:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Underrated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 16:59:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really wish they kept them accurate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 16:34:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hold the left analog with my index and thumb, and rotate it steadily and smoothly. It takes a bit to get the hang of, but eventually no more difficult than the Simplified setting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 16:33:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The worst is failing a haggle just because you wanted a few extra groschen, and now you’ve lost hundreds or thousands because of the reputation hit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 12:34:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea....  well my shitty phone picture has 682 upvotes right now, so your single downvote is utterly meaningless, peasant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 12:31:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is definitely up there! Best quest in the game imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 12:30:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> May God watch over you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 12:28:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I took it as Hanush was counting on that coin for something. Probably a debt to the bath wenches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 12:27:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s an all-timer for sure! Nice an early in the game too, really helps set the tone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 12:27:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s a great one too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 08:14:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How did you “accidentally” do it lol. It’s clearly marked DLC and it asks you 2x if you’re “sure” you want to proceed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 08:13:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You could just... play it at literally any point in the play through </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 08:10:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s actually much easier to just take a picture, with my phone, of my tv as the cutscene is playing then upload that. Takes approx. 5 seconds total. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 08:05:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Midnight from the South Saturn Delta compilation is pretty dammed heavy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 06:47:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I took a bunch lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 06:05:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When does he say that? I’m drawing a blank </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 06:04:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea tried to catch it at that point but I’m a second too early here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 06:02:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SAKRA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 05:48:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Best character by far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Probably the best facking line in the whole game </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 04:23:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 04:15:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always want to steal those goblets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just killed Runt on my first try on HC. Worried it would be a lot harder w/ the helmet... but I am PUMPED NOW </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 04:12:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 17:40:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the content I’m here for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 17:00:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I fully support extremely harsh penalties for both of these drivers. Since fatal accidents are caused everyday by this exact behavior, attempted manslaughter should be the charge, and a ten year suspension of license to begin after prison sentence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone else having this problem? PS4, game crashes when I sleep save. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 14:00:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haven’t narrowed it down to a specific location, but when I try to sleep save, the clock goes all the way to the right time, then screen goes black never to recover. If the sleepwalking perk is activated, it’ll display that, but just freeze and never come out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 13:51:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Keep it on your horse till it’s clean. Also if you just move towns it’s usually safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 13:50:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Should I... shouldn’t I.... no. I daren’t. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 12M 140 pounds fell down steps and hit his head on hardwood floors. Looking for prognosis or similar outcomes. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 08:37:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was knocked out, parents found him quickly (heard the noise). As they tended to him he had a seizure. Took him to ER, diagnosed bleeding on brain. Took him to CHOP (philly). Rediagnosed as only bruise on brain. Had CAT, MRI. Monitoring him now. Was awake/lucid, but on drugs now that made him seem “drunk.”

Prognosis?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> (Not me) 12 yo, fell down steps, hit his head hard on wood floors. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 08:33:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 03:10:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What now and arrows? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-27 02:56:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was bummed too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-27 02:39:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, you ride off the map and the play line is finished. You can go back to older saves though. And if you haven’t done the Hans Capon DLC, it forces you to before the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-27 02:25:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You must have never played Kingdom Come: Deliverance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-27 02:25:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God that’s incredible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-27 01:21:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don’t feel like looking it up, hopefully someone knows:

Are lunar mountains formed by plate tectonics ala Earth, or is there another force. I think the moon has a crust with mantle underneath, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-27 00:52:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Timmy vs Fritz would be a great brawl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-27 00:50:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fritz is legitimately mentally challenged, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-27 00:50:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not including Henry:

1. Sir Hanush of Leipa: fat alpha dog who gets shit done
2. Father Godwin: I mean cmon
3. Peshak: I just love how he talks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Props to Ota for marrying a half-wench </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-26 18:49:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 18:23:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! Should I use 4x4s for the posts or something smaller you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 18:21:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They don’t fit on the pallet. She got that with the idea that I would cut it and use as the base, but I don’t think it would look great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Help please! My wife wants me to build an enclosure, or at least platform for my trash bins, but I am not the best carpenter. If I have a blueprint or directions I reckon I can manage. Any ideas/suggestions? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 16:41:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 05:37:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey what’s your thoughts on Jimi Hendrix? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 05:33:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. Off-grid is a meaningless term. You’re some guy living in an expensive cabin binge watching Netflix on solar energy. Kudos, wish I was doing that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 05:29:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Considering municipal services (water, electric for sure) are provided by for-profit companies, and that broadband internet is a municipal service in several countries, what’s the difference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 05:26:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And you are the magician </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 05:22:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doesn’t that make you on-the-grid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 02:02:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I meant to reply to a comment that said the king was the highest ranked character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 23:51:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea, it’s part of the Wiman’s Lot DLC. You can get him as soon as you wake up in Rattay Mill.

Spoiler: he can attack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 23:49:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But which one?!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 23:45:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You get a dog named Mutt that follows you on your journey and helps you in several ways! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 23:41:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The dog mechanic by itself drastically changes how you can do a playthrough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 23:41:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hope you enjoy it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 23:18:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The DLCs alone are worth it. As for the bugs, I’m assuming you’re on console? I play on PS4 and there really aren’t any play-altering bugs that I see anymore, just some funky camera angles in dialogue and poor texture loading. What bugs specifically are you referencing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Every time </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 14:42:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Axe or Mace for Hardcore? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 23:09:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Second play through. First was Normal Difficulty, used Noble (short) sword pretty much the whole way through. No issues with combat at all. But for my first HC play, I want something other than a sword as my main. So should I go axe or mace? And what’s the best of each? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This glimpse has gotta be intentional, right Henry? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 04:10:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 01:51:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just the sleepwalking and helmet ones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Any suggestions for playing Hardcore mode? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 00:57:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Second play through, first was on Normal difficulty, and I didn’t have too much trouble with anything. I’m worried most about figuring out master strikes without the green shield, since I was never very good at the learned combos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 22:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I added that perk right before the last battle of the siege, and didn’t really test it out at all. So I ate about 4 potions, forget which ones, to buff my stats.

FF to jumping off the ladder onto the ramparts, and falling down, absolutely plastered with full wheel drunk, while Bernard and the boys clean up.

Good times Henry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 22:19:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s when I thought “holy shit this game is awesome” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 20:51:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait so once I finish the epilogue, it’s not just open-world free roam? No story spoilers please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Feels good </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 14:28:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 13:14:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 18:30:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Box set version FTW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 18:29:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hands down the worst a Machine Gun. Buddy’s singing is unbearable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 18:27:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. Hear my Train a-Comin
2. Machine Gun
3. All Along the Watchtower
4. Voodoo Child (Slight Return)
5. Power of Soul
6. Highway Chile
7. Red House
8. Little Wing
9. Bold as Love
10. Straight Ahead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 13:21:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m doing this. Thx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 00:09:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Should I quit my current (first) play-through on Regular difficulty and give my hand at Hardcore? It seems much more fun/immersive. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 23:47:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m currently at the siege at the end of the game, and have NOT done any of the DLC except get a dog. Would it be better to start from scratch playing the DLC as I go through? Also, which rebuffs should I pick? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 23:37:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She can handle a piece of meat for sure! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 23:35:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s not exactly a business as part of the program, but there are many ways to make $, and they operate essentially as a business because of the labor and materials required to profit. Potion-making, poaching, treasure hunting, armour/weapon trading, and others are all time-consuming activities that build relations with specific traders in the game. Stronger relations with individual merchants gives you better prices at which to sell your wares. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 21:36:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Realistic medieval combat w/ variety of weapons
-Horseback riding-Gamble at dice and tourneys-Get many different levels of drunk with varying effects-Pickpocket-Lock pick-Alchemy-Bed some comely wenches and a Lady or two-Have a pet dog-Hunt-Read books, literally-Build a village-Make your own business-Cook-Treasure hunt-Haggle with traders-Infiltrate enemy camps-Sleep-Ride around admiring the countryside-Help beggars-Kill *almost* anyone-Sway people with smooth talking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 20:40:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The fair Lady Stephanie had better win this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Who would you rather plunder? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 20:06:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed]

[View Poll](https://www.reddit.com/poll/gm6o7w) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 20:03:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Be sure to admire them for the buff boost! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hickory-smoked Pork Loin - to be used in sandwiches </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-17 23:10:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [homemade] hickory smoked pork loin. Sweet spice dry rub (nothing “hot”) after sitting 36 hours in citrus-herb brine. Using it for sandwiches. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-17 22:49:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hickory Smoked Pork Loin. Sweet spice dry rub, nothing hot, after sitting 36 hours in a citrus-herb brine. Using it as sandwich meat. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-17 22:47:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-17 15:23:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Armourer fixes all metal objects. Swords, shields, chain mail, helmets, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 21:47:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It makes sense that you can’t. These are animals that are at least a few years old, and have been raised to respond to one name that entire time. Changing it would be a futile chore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 17:43:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go back the save as close to the start of the raid and redo the whole thing. Make sure you don’t get hurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 17:23:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The main part is learning master strikes. Once you get that, even if you suck at everything else, you’ll luck into hitting some of those in real combat.

I also like to win clinches a lot to break their defense down and open them up for some devastating overhead blows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 17:12:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In case you didn’t get the memo yet... train with Bernard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 16:01:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.thechunkychef.com/bourbon-bbq-smoked-chicken-wings/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Applewood smoked whiskey BBQ wings </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 14:25:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 14:22:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yea. Delicious sustenance is for gays hurdur </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 01:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ve never bought anything from her. I have principles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 00:53:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And garlic to keep away evil spirits! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 00:52:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Roulls an’ pritzuls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bread! Fresh bread! Rolls and pretzels! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 17:07:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 13:40:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was just proud of hitting 14k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 03:24:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where do you find all your loot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 01:57:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How long does it take you to walk from Pirkstein to the armourer loaded up like that lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 01:44:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait how do you carry 800-1000 lbs of gear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 00:54:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s exactly when it happens to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Post top scores!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 00:53:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 00:50:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> PS4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Any one else get this issue? Happens with different traders, Henry doesn’t load, and you can’t move to “sell” or “check basket” this making the trade screen unusable. Any tips on avoiding it? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 00:16:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 00:13:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes that is where it comes from </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 23:21:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It really doesn’t. I was laughing like a Cuman just making it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 22:25:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I make no pretense of originality. I laugh at every KCD intro meme though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 22:13:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> KCD is so perfect for memes. And imo they’re all in good fun and don’t knock the game at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 22:12:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If I go back to an earlier save in the same play through, do some quests, then save that, does it erase my current save file (the one already at the siege of Talmberg)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can you finish the quests that you auto-fail once Talmberg is under siege? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 20:46:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First play through, PS4, specifically the Hare Hunt/Wolf’s in sheep’s clothing, and stealing from Lady Stephanie. They looked like fun quests and now I’m screwed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Better call Sigismund </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 19:41:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 18:29:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Had same issue in the monastery on og PS4. Mostly in the church </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 14:56:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually thought about it and definitely remembered getting caught looting the bailiffs house lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 03:50:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have 0 rep in Ledetchko but have never committed a crime there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 02:10:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was actually in the fratery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> All right which one of you wrote this? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 00:33:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 13:07:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You just have to get better dice and the agility perk. You become unbeatable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 13:01:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Already did that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 01:55:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s what I use! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sir Hans DLC not spawning? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 01:34:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just bought the DLC bundle on PS4, and all the other markers appear (women’s lot, BoB, etc), but there’s no market for sir Hans. I am currently at “If you can’t beat ‘em” in the main quest, and have completed the side quest where party with Sir Hans in the Rattay bathhouse.

Any help would be greatly appreciated. Thanks in advance, kind Henry’s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What’s everyone’s favorite dice? I never lose with 3 odd dice, 1 lucky die and 1 shrinking die. Also, how great is Farkle? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 17:45:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 17:04:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Very much! May the Lord watch over you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 23:43:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love side one, but side 2 has some of my least favorite Jimi tracks that everyone seems to love. Especially stepping stone lol.

But I couldn’t even try to fit it on a single album. There’s soooo much great stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 18:17:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Since it’s all new material I count it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 18:14:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you Experienced
Axis
Electric Ladyland
Band of Gypsys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Little project I’m working on... my version of Jimi’s 5th album. The abbreviations in () are the sources of each song. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 16:46:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 16:44:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If youve never listened to Band of Gypsys it’s hard to really rank the other stuff, especially Cry Of Love as you don’t really get a full sense of where he was coming from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 16:17:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just set it to Simplified. It’s easy as pie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 16:06:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or just set lock picking to “simplified” in settings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What’s everyone’s favorite dice? I use 3 odd dice, 1 shrinking die, and 1 lucky die. It’s impossible to lose. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 04:17:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> DLC Timing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 04:12:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m trying to avoid spoilers, but want to know when the right time to start any of the DLC is. I’m at Questions & Answers in the main story, and haven’t bought any DLC. Should I wait till endgame? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 03:37:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plus you get to bang the Lady Stephanie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 01:46:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s exactly how I did it and now I’m absolutely rolling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 00:44:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More like a sack of CHEESE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 00:43:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On PS4 as well and I have an issue with absolutely none of those things. The saving is simple; either sleep or take a SS, which are ridiculously easy to come by. The bandits always keep at each other unless you get too close. And i don’t even know what you’re talking about with Bernard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Killing Runt is a High </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 03:06:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Started playing about a year and a half ago. I kind of skirted through up to Nest of Vipers/Baptism of Fire. Well, got to Runt with about 50% health, pretty low stats, and no idea how to really fight. Rage quit the whole game after numerous deaths by his hand.

Just came back to it a few weeks ago. Did a bunch of the side quests, learned Master Strijes from Bernie, amassed ~15kG and quality armor, and just tried to face Runt again today.

Cracked that guys skull open with the Noble’s sword in about 30 seconds. I was so freaking pumped for the rest of the day and now I can’t wait to play the rest of the story and the DLC. This game truly shows patience and hard work really pays off.

Anyone else have similar stories? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
