<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject24</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 16:04:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my god. Thank you so much!

I hadn't even thought about half of what you said and I cam assure you it has been very helpful and I will put it to use as soon as I can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Advice to a new owner </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 20:05:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi! I'm thinking of adopting a kitten to help with my depression but my only experience with animals is with a couple of turtles and a bird. My mom had a couple of cats when she was younger but that was ages ago and I feel things have changed a lot since then.

What advice would you give a new owner? I live in a house with no backyard and no other animals. I worry about the cat biting or scratching the furniture and I have no clue where it's best to put the litter box.

Any advice you give is appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 00:21:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I felt pretty much like you and thought it was because of Hashimoto. I tried diets, exercice, all I could think of and I felt the same. Recently I spoke to my doctor about depression and I have been taking antidepressants. In 2/3 days I felt a lot better. I could get up in the mornings instantly, I didn't have brain fog and I felt less tired.
My guess is it depends on the person and you have to speak to your doctor about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 11:25:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hipothyroidism here with dizzyness 24/7, chronic fatigue, depression and brainfog. "You just need to go walk and be in the sun", "You don't have reasons to be sad", "You need to exercise more" (while already doing 1 hour daily despite the fatigue), "You wouldn't burn if you sunbathe everyday" (I'm nuclear white and burn for being 10 minutes in the sun).

That's my father, ladies and gentlemen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 11:22:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unfortunately not. She always says it has to be my period and leaves it at that. Never has wanted to test for anything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 02:32:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have lab test done every 6 months. If I show anemia in one my doctor will prescribe iron supplements. In the next lab work I am ok so they take them away. In the next one I have anemia again. This has happened for the last 6 years! Doesn't matter what I say to my doctor. It's not that difficult to come to the conclusion maybe I need a little less of the supplements but I need them in the log run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 11:20:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you always have aches and pains I would think there's something wrong with you! And that doesn't go away just because they test whatever your doctor  felt like that day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-27 10:36:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a professor in university that while explaining how urine works draw and put in the power point a little guy that looked like a kidney saying "keep your pee pale!"
I will never forget it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 20:03:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just started not eating grains, gluten and dairy less than a week ago but I really hope it does something to make me feel better. I think I will be quite strict now that I am starting and when (and if) I feel better maybe I will try too to reincorporate some things like you one at a time. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 11:34:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a rash like that a while a go but it lasted only 2 days and never came back so i think it was from something i touched, not levo. Maybe you're allergic to something new in your environment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 14:00:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I met a guy not long ago also through a game. We quickly started talking everyday because we had a lot in common. We both had depression and we both attempted suicide sometime before. He started telling me how he wanted us to be a couple and me to move to where he lives to be together even though we only had been talking like 2 or 3 weeks and every time I told him that I had a bad breakup and I was nowhere ready to be with anyone nor do I wanted. I talked to him like a friend who could understand what I went through and talk about our issues.
He started telling me I was the only reason he was still alive and finding out where I live (i still don't know how), what my parents names and jobs where and calling them his in laws. We lived like 5 or 6 hours away and I felt scared one day he would pop up in my door.
He kept saying I was the reason he was alive and I reached my limit. I couldn't be held responsible for someone else's live when I was struggling with mine so I blocked him and I don't know if he is alive or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 12:24:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for your comment and your concern. Unfortunately last week i had a lab work and I talked to my primary care physician just yesterday. All my results seem to be ok so they don't want to do a damn thing about me.
I have read that alimentation can greatly improve the condition so I want to try talking to a nutritionist to see if I can change anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 11:07:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have hypothyroidism and I'm always tired and feeling like shit. My father's favorite line is "you wouldn't be so tired if you exercised more". When I wake up I'm already tired and I force myself to do at lest 1 hour of exercise everyday (because frankly I couldn't do more if I tried). So his only conclusion is that I am lying and not doing exercise as I say or I am not doing enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 01:19:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She tried to expell me for being in the caffeteria instead of in her class. EVEN after I showed her a note from my doctor stating I went to see him that day because I was sick and EVEN after my parents showed up telling her I was sick and they took me to the doctor. I still don't know if she trully believed I could be in 2 places at the same time or if she just wanted to screw me over </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-04 10:37:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a 25 years old female and was diagnosed 3 years ago.
For me my symptoms come and go but since being diagnosed I feel pretty better than before. Whenever I start feeling dizzy and more tired I know I have to go to the doctor and change the dose. I haven't been able to lose weight but i haven't been gaining either. I have heard that keto is a great diet to lose the weight but i haven't tried it yet.
The tiredness will be better but it won't go away. The only way to not feel tired is force your body to move everyday even if you don't feel like it. After a cople of days you will feel less tired. Keep it up! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-03 16:10:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course NTA. Something similar happened to me. I had been with my boyfriend for 3 years and for the last year or so I had been pretty depressed. I wasn't taking antidepresants but I really should have and I was stubborn about it. Every time I mentioned being sad or not being ok he would say my problems were not important, I was making them bigger than they were and get over it. After many months of health problems the doctors realized what was wrong with me and put me in medication (it's not a mortal illness or nothing like that but I will be medicating all my life). I suppose this was something he couldn't tolerate or something just like your boyfriend and he told me he couldn't be with me anymore.

I felt pretty bad for a long time, but if I can give you an advice: It's not worth it to try making a relationship work if your parter doesn't respect you and that you sometimes need help to function normally. I can only recomend you to leave him. After a while you will see that it was for the best.

Best of lucks to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 17:41:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am in Spain too and I can tell you the parents are NOT following the mesures the government put. They are supposed to take maximum 3 kids with 1 adult (most parents go both and most families with more than 3 children take them all), they are supposed to go out only 1 hour a day (pretty difficult to control), they can only walk and maximum 1 km away from their house (and most of them are going to parks or big places where all the children and adults will be together and not separated from one another the minimum distance)

While I think that it could be done and not aggravate the situation if done well, it's obvious the government thought the parents would not be the useless self-centered idiots . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-25 20:26:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The chapter ends in page 111 and starts in 113... :(

Excuse me, I'm gonna cry in a corner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-04 19:36:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is truly my main reason tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-04 16:44:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just wow. The nerve of some people.

When I was a child I had a neighbour I was best friends with. She started going out with girls older than us and acting like them, mature and bitchy. One day I decided I no longer wanted to be friends  because I didn't know her anymore.

Well, her mom called my mom to basically say that I had mental problems because I didn't want to hang out with her and because of that I desperately needed a therapist :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-03 22:44:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tomorrow is my birthday... I was sad enough and now I am sad for me and sad for the cat! :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-03 22:32:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/MiniLadd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-01 22:17:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely NTA. If she doesn't understand how uncomfortable a bra can be to girls with big boobs is her problem, not yours. I alsa not wear a bra at home or while sleeping because I can't stand it and if anybody told me to put one I would say to them to not look if they don't like it. Their discomfort is not more important than yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 22:22:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That hit home :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 22:21:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope you can get out of that situation soon enough. Maybe try to tell your father he was right in wanting divorce. It's a shame your sister doesn't see your mother like the manipulative person she is but I hope she will one day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 22:15:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I will be doing the same in my birthday this april irl :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 21:58:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love that it sounds so much like a joke 707 would make </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 21:57:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We can cry in happiness together :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 19:11:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Untitled - Simple Plan](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZQ7oqmikZDQ) the music and lyrics are sad per se and everytime I have watched the videoclip I've cried </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 13:20:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am keeping a few fucked up secrets from everyone and I need someone to know them and understand me but everytime I have tried to tell someone they have betrayed me in the most horrible way and I feel like I can trust no one with my feelings. I need physical touch as well as emotional relief and nobody can give me any </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 22:19:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree totally! This moment could have been for teaching him to respects others and not to be scared of what people cannot control instead he just made a fool of himself and taught the child that he could get what he wanted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 22:13:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WTF lady! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 22:03:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would be the sister in this situation hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Entitled mother says that I need psychological help because I don't want to be friends with her daughter </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 21:04:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
