<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject15</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 06:42:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was able to get a better photo so I updated it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 06:38:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry my phone wouldn’t focus. Thanks for the info </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Salivary gland under tongue sore and red </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 06:35:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 21F 125lb 5’2” white
my salivary glands are beat red (see picture) and sore. I had some very mild soreness under my jaw last night. Is this a virus or something? I did have a headache yesterday. Could it be related to something I ate? I’d had something spicy recently when I noticed it but, it didn’t seem too spicy to me and I’ve had it many times before without issue. Just curious as to what’s up with this

https://imgur.com/a/Qki5e4p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 09:55:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is such a thing as being sex-repulsed asexual. I find sex disgusting and degrading as well. But for me it’s normal. If op also never finds herself wanting to have sex at all, with anyone, then this is a possibility for her too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 20:50:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You’re essentially supporting conversion therapy for asexual people. My girlfriend and I are both ace and we’re just fine, thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 20:48:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m not sure- it could seem that way to some asexual individuals. I am asexual and I can definitely see how it would feel degrading. But I don’t know about the violent portion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 20:45:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m asexual and feel this way about any sort of sex. Of course I can’t label your sexuality but it might be of interest to research this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 09:43:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Losing my ex fp still hurts really bad. I hate how I developed such strong emotions for someone who wasn’t capable of genuinely feeling them back.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 09:34:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NAD but I do get petechiae now and then rather easily due to a genetic condition and I can tell you mine have never looked like this. They have looked like bright red spots and are under the skin so you can’t feel them. They also don’t blanche when pressed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Help, going to be in withdrawal for upwards of a week </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 02:37:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I might not be able to get my psych prescription until October 1. It’s already my third night without it. I get really angry, like REALLY angry when I’m off my meds, so much that I can’t even describe it. I’m really really concerned. How do I get through this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 08:18:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m not gonna lie I cry on my birthdays thinking that I’m getting older. I do truly believe things tend to get worse as you grow older and I dread that so much. I’ve been like that since 12 or 13 as well, but now I can confidently say that I’m glad that I’m over 18. I don’t want to be more than 21 though but unfortunately that time is coming. I will feel very old this birthday. But somethings have happened recently that have given me some hope the future won’t be so bad even though I will be older </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 20:34:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 19:58:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I honestly find nails themselves to be gross and when they’re long and colored I just...
In other words I have no idea lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Help, I’m not functioning </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 22:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m in a situation that is really bad. I have no energy to clean and my room is a literal disaster. Like, really bad. And it’s full of boxes too, since I haven’t unpacked since I moved in March. I wear the same shirt literally for weeks at a time (including to sleep) because of the difficulty of doing a load of laundry. Even if I did do laundry I still wouldn’t change daily. I often struggle to even brush my teeth and hair. I never leave my room save to get food take my dog out use the bathroom and occasionally talk to my mom for a short while. I do go to see my girlfriend once a week as well but other than that I don’t leave the house. I get exhausted driving to see her and the whole time want to take a nap. Otherwise I spend basically all my time in my bed. Maybe this wouldn’t be that big of a deal if it lasted a little while but this has been going on (in fluctuating severity) for years. I feel I truly can’t work. I wonder if my therapist understands how bad it really is.  I am a failure and I hate this. I am not living. I’m 21 I should be enjoying my young adulthood. I just know if I get old I will look back on this and just feel so devastated. My mom will not help me clean my room or anything else... she might be willing to help me do some laundry but that’s it. I don’t know what to do anymore. I feel so frustrated because I so badly want to do things but I just can’t seem to. I know people probably look at me as a lazy piece of shit. I hate that. I hate me. What do I do??? I can’t live like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 04:11:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “Did you take your meds today?” In a condescending way 🙄 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 06:12:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a non-binary person who’s suspected to have PCOS, I’m sad to hear this is happening. I think honestly it’s a reflection of culture at large, which although becoming less transphobic, still retains some hate against LGBT+ individuals, especially among certain groups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sick of suffering </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 06:28:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m so so sick of this. Something always has to come along and remind me how painful life is and that it will never REALLY get better. I just can’t take it. Everyone would be better off without me anyway; I’m not a good partner, I’m not the best of friends, I’m kind of just a sucky person in general. I can’t make people happy in the way I want. I love my girl. Love is so painful. I could never get enough of her unless we spent every waking moment together and I feel like that’s not feasible. I will never be a good enough person. I hate this. My sister hates me, no one in my family accepts me for who I am, the only one who even talks to me is my mom. I wish I was dying or suffering physically I don’t deserve happiness.
I can’t do this anymore. I’m in so much mental pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 06:53:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me podcasts require too much attention. I like music because it is repetitive and emotional.

Just like me. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 16:46:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get petechiae when I scratch my leg. But I also have a connective tissue disorder and I don’t get nearly this many or this prominent of an amount of petechiae. Would be good to get some blood tests done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 16:40:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sometimes when you sit for long periods especially in certain positions you may get a bit of tingliness. That happens to me as well.
Unfortunately no. It’s an issue that comes and goes for me but it can be really problematic at times. My doctor recommended seeing a urologist if I felt it might be something elsebut I feel quite confident at this point that it is related to constipation because it comes and goes and so on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Friendship issues and ex fp </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 12:29:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Firstly let me explain that I knowingly allowed the distance to grow between my ex fp and I. I was experiencing so much pain in our relationship because I wanted to be her number one person and I never was. I wanted her to take me into her family like another friend of hers. But she never would. I envied that friend and felt hurt. I was desperate for her to love me. She said she did  but I know she didn’t feel as passionately as I did.
Now she didn’t talk to me much for a long time. I feel angry whenever I see her instagram posts of her on a trip living it up with her other friend :/ I finally just muted her because I couldn’t take it anymore.
She messaged me recently and I felt really mad. I didn’t want to reply but of course I did. I’m just angry she literally forgot about me. I wanted to say “oh so you remember me now?” But I didn’t. My ex therapist would have said it’s normal for relationships to fluctuate and to talk less then think about the person and want to see them again after awhile. But I don’t care I don’t believe in friendships that aren’t passionate. If they can’t be a constant presence in my life they are not worth being friends with.
This is probably why I only have one person I really consider a friend in real life. I have online friends and I consider them friends because I meet up with them in a game basically every day.
I don’t know I guess I’m just frustrated about it. Can you guys relate at all? Does this seem BPD-related to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 12:11:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She should be fired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 12:05:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NAD so I can’t say for sure, but I’m also 21 and have issues with urination. I was told by doctors it may be because of constipation pressing up against the area. Are you constipated? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 16:48:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Today I could not pee and after pooing it seems to still be an issue although I could get some out. I also think I might have blood in my urine. I’m going to see if anything improves by this afternoon and if not I’m going to call the doctor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 18:39:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, especially when I had an fp. It is one of the most painful things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 08:48:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do basically the same things you mention here.
Yeah I’ve mentioned it to a couple of them. It’s just i don’t feel like there’s anything they or I can do to change this feeling of desperation :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 01:40:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m sorry you deal with it too. I feel like I shouldn’t even talk to my friends anymore but I really do want to. It’s so frustrating :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Please help, I can’t stop “pushing and pulling” and testing my friends? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 14:18:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t know what’s wrong with me but I can’t seem to stop testing my friends’ love for me and pushing them away only to pull them closer shortly after. I hate myself for it. I have done this with past relationships (starting around high school). It often doesn’t appear until the relationship(s) have become deep and I am close with the individual(s) involved. I hate this. I say sorry for nothing and analyze their reaction. I act distant to see if they care and also because of regret for being too open with them. I desperately want them to show me they love me but at the same time feel very uncomfortable an discourage them from doing so. All the while asking if they’re angry and doubting that they love me. I am such a toxic person. I feel I should abandon friendships. Just stop speaking to them. After all why would they care? I’m just a nobody, insignificant in their lives in the long run. I don’t know why but I desperately want to be extremely important to them. I feel selfish for feeling this way but I really want to be the most important friend in a person’s/people’s lives, even though I have a girlfriend and I know I’m number one to her. I just get so jealous and standoffish towards their other friends that I don’t know. I know they say “act opposite to emotion” but personally I know I can’t live that way. It would literally kill me inside. I desperately need their love and affection. If I didn’t have it I know I would go to extreme measures. I would kill myself just to know that they would express their love for me after I was gone and that their hurt would show they care. It doesn’t matter if I’m there to see it. I don’t know how to bear this any longer. It’s ruining my wellbeing and my relationships and I fear it will eventually destroy my relationship with my girlfriend. For instance I already feel my perception of her being similar to the push and pull concept. I don’t act on it really, but sometimes I feel like I want to be single and that I should leave her and unhappy being in a relationship where as other times I feel overwhelming love for her and happiness with our relationship. I don’t get it. I’m confused. I need help. I can’t go on like this, it’s too painful. I want to hurt myself sometimes I get so mad at myself; I hate myself. Please tell me what I can do. I am seeing a therapist and on meds that keep me from being as emotionally unstable as I used to be but once I develop friendships what I’ve described happens all over again. Do I have to be friendless for the rest of my life and painfully lonely?!? Can I even maintain a relationship with my SO?? I’m depressed and I can’t handle this... what can I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 12:34:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It helps with my gender dysphoria and social anxiety so yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 12:53:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sad but true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 18:31:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I feel like that definitely could be related. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 18:27:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oof I feel like I’m saying this a lot on this sub
NADbut it really sounds like it might be a connective tissue disorder to me. I have one. Could be wrong though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 18:15:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NAD but I can relate to a lot of these symptoms. I have Ehlers Danlos Syndrome Hypermobility type. I hope you are able to find some help soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 17:52:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As far as dealing with it, physical therapy can be helpful. Pain medication. There is no cure. Supportive therapies, braces, and accommodations are what most people use to improve quality of life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 17:41:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was suspected that I had it for some time because my mother was diagnosed when I was very young. The first sign of it was hyper mobility (basically being really flexible, to the point that I sit in weird ways without even realizing that for most people that position would be impossible even though it’s comfortable to me). Later on (in my teen years) I developed the sensation of my joints slipping around in their sockets as I walked. It doesn’t hurt usually, just uncomfortable, it made me not want to walk. As time went on I began developing pain and noticed that my shoulders are constantly slipping in and out of their sockets (this has since been confirmed by my doctors). Other subluxations. The pain comes on suddenly usually and goes just as suddenly, although achiness sometimes goes unnoticed for me because it’s so typical. Sometimes my ankles will just lose their strength and collapse and I’ll fall. My balance is really bad; I never could ride a bike, and stationary bikes cause me a lot of knee pain because my joints are so weak my legs turn the wrong way. My skin is very “doughlike,” soft and stretchy. Severe Constipation and urinary issues as well. Weakness. I guess that’s a summary of everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 17:20:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As others are saying other symptoms would likely be present if this was the case but, I wanted to tell you as a person with hEDS I can do this as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 20:58:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not a doctor but, have you been scratching it a lot? If so, I’d say it looks like a mosquito bite. The more you scratch them, the bigger they get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Dysphoria (TW: mentions of self harm, suicide, sex related things) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 18:33:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am AFAB non-binary and asexual, and struggling with serious bottom dysphoria. I would like some words of advice about this.

It’s not just gender dysphoria- this is probably tmi but it’s also related to uncontrollable sexual feelings that I’m guessing are hormonal- but I have 0 sexual desire associated with them. I think maybe my brain is making me hyper aware of anything as well because of clinical OCD about it. Because of these two things I really want to remove everything involved. Graphic, but I keep thinking about cutting it out. Like I genuinely want it gone. It’s making me so miserable. I don’t know how to relieve this dysphoria. I need advice... idk what to do? It’s really upsetting to me. I genuinely wanna just remove it myself. Even though logically I know it would probably make me bleed out. I just don’t know how to get my mind off it and stop feeling so uncomfortable within my own body. Do you have any tips? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
