<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject57</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 22:18:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA. Be kind to your mother. You are not the center of the universe and no one at your school would care if they found out about your family's name theme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I've been using drugs to numb the pain and my actions have burned bridges with people I love </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 17:35:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 21:23:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jim from The Office. He's a coward, mean to Dwight, and let Pam give up on her dreams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 23:58:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think this is just to demonstrate the cost of the service versus ordering in pizza.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 20:44:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine is about the same age and 36lbs. She's very lean and lanky. Quick too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 00:41:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Found the incel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 00:32:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it possible you were misdiagnosed? My brother suffers from anxiety and was told he had ADHD. He was put on medication and it effected him horribly- jitters, panic attacks and a sick stomach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 23:50:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My ankles are double jointed! I can turn my feet almost completely backwards and have never sprained or rolled an ankle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 06:16:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now this is what I came for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> They're so pretty </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 06:11:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 00:58:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a trend? Gross. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 00:39:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chocolate and parmesan cheese </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 23:16:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pets! I was able to make friends with some of my neighbors through our dogs. I meet up with them almost every day at the park to chat and let our dogs play together. Even just saying hello to your neighbors can lead to a friendship </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 01:12:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Back pain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 01:08:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry OP, but it sounds like there's a reason they're limiting this. You may be a little too attached to your games. I think you should focus your energy into other interests. Do you like to read, draw, play music or sports? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 00:30:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. It sounds like your husband hasn't been doing even a fraction of the housework or child care. The fact that he gave up the third day and shoved the kids off on you, while you were already working, is disrespectful and mellow dramatic. I think you should seriously consider what you're gaining from this relationship OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 05:54:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You stand in a crowd and pretend like you can hear the guy on the megaphone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 05:35:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Link plss these are so cute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 00:00:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok, 5'6 and 144lbs is not chubby. You are right in the middle of a healthy BMI. Your mom sounds like she has some control issues, therapy would likely be helpful. I hope things get better OP. Remember that you are strong, your are worthy, and you are more than a number on a scale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 00:08:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a very energetic dog. My grandmother is afraid of dogs. Whenever I see my grandmother, I make sure my dog is either leashed or kenneled so she doesn't have to worry. This should just be common courtesy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 21:22:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. Even small purchases. My mother once screamed at me because I had spent $20 to buy breakfast for my boyfriend and I. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 04:35:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lil heavy on the face tune </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 22:55:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Says who? Pretty sure there's a long history of people doing crazy things to get out of the draft.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 22:44:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're assuming it's not an issue already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 00:27:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA. You're a grown man and should be working just like your girlfriend is. Staying up late to chat on Discord is in no way even remotely as important as your girlfriend's career. YIKES. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 22:00:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Linzertorte on Christmas eve </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 21:59:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any of the Naruto openings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Telling someone they're perfect is not a compliment </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 04:16:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Telling someone they're perfect puts unnecessary pressure on them and reduces them to a 2-Dimensional being. Humans are flawed and it shouldn't be seen as a bad thing. Flaws are what make people interesting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-26 15:49:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It gets better! I had many meltdowns when my girl was little. It gets exponentially easier after they're a year old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-26 15:47:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mom treats my brother and I horribly, then buys is expensive gifts as an apology. It's infuriating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-26 03:43:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-26 03:34:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the best handwriting I've ever seen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-26 01:46:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those little toes peaking out of the sleeves got me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 06:26:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can fit an ungodly amount of groceries neatly into one bag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 22:27:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ignore her and report her to HR for being a bitch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 08:14:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being constantly unsure of your own judgement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 07:25:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mom did this to me brother and I all the time. If we tried to actually leave she would block us and often got violent. Now as an adult, she tried to pull the equivalent "you shouldn't come visit anymore" so I went to leave and it replayed just as it did when I was a teen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 06:40:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What if we just didn't force people to risk their lives in war? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 06:36:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Public speaking is the most valuable skill to have in the work place. It sucks, but is entirely necessary.

I have an anxiety disorder and loathed my public speaking courses in college, but now I'm grateful I had them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 06:28:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can see Sulu being gay since George Takei is indeed gay, and the cast of the original Trek fought for him to keep his role after producers found out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 06:23:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agree. Orange is the best flavor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 23:16:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/raisedbynarcissists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 18:57:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What type of foods are you eating? High fiber, high protein should keep you satisfied. It's a good idea to load up on high mass, low cal foods like brocolli, raw spinach, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 07:13:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That my dog loves me too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 15:33:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooh, yah that makes it more difficult lmao. I wonder if you could send it to the apple store and have them pull the files. Either way, you're rocking it!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 15:05:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congrats, thats amazing!! Also, if you're wanting to get those pics off your phone, you should be able to connect your phone to a computer using a cable. Or at least that's what I've done with Androids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 06:49:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You may want to look for a weight lifting sub or something similar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 06:44:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait.. are you trying to lose or gain weight? From your description, you actually sound like you're underweight. You're young and active but really should be eating at least 1700 calories a day to be in a healthy range </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 06:36:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It sounds like you're going through a lot right now. I think you should talk to a therapist if you can, does your school offer any sort of counselor? The good news is you're still young and have plenty of future left. Begin your progress now so that you can be healthy and happy as you begin adulthood. You can do this!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 00:23:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can do this! Track your calories and try to get in exercise every day. It doesn't have to be anything extreme, even long walks are better than sitting on the couch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 00:19:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congrats!! That's amazing
One thing I never think about is bra size changing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 23:45:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's amazing how much more energy I have! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 22:10:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's most motivating for me is quantifiable data. Are you logging your calories, do you have a fitness tracker? You can do this, don't give up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 21:15:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you tried following along to yoga videos on YouTube? That's about all I did for the first month of quarantine. You don't really need any equipment if you have carpeted floors, but you'll probably want a yoga mat regardless. I just have a cheap one I got at Walmart for $5 and it's fine for casual at-home yoga </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Down 25lbs! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 21:04:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Down from 198 to 173. My goal weight is 155. For reference, I'm 5'7 and 23F.

As of July 2nd I'm officially down about 20lbs since January. It hasn't been the fastest process, but I feel like I'm achieving sustainable weight loss. I began by tracking my activity levels and setting personal goals to beat step records as recorded by my smart watch. Most of my exercise comes from hiking.

Once a week I take the dog for a long hike, it began as a 3 mile hike and has grown into a 6 miler. My goal is to complete a 12 mile hike to the peak of a well-known mountain by Autumn. Don't worry, the pup gets daily walks too, usually averaging about 2 miles in length. Before the pandemic hit I was kickboxing twice a week for an hour at a time.

Food wise, I haven't really cut anything out 100%. But I have made substantial changes. I eat far more veggies and lean proteins than I ever have in my life. I've also been tracking my calories and stay at 1600 or lower each day. On high-activity days I allow myself to go over this number while still maintaining a calorie deficit, as calculated by my smart watch and calorie tracker. For those curious- I have Garmin Connect synced to My Fitness Pal.

Overall, I'm feeling really great! I know 20lbs shies in comparison to some of the other stories here, but I honestly didn't think I'd ever be able to lose weight.

I wish all of you health, happiness, and success! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-10 06:24:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! I think adoption is great, but I've often found that agencies are pretty biased. I had a specific breed in mind and found a rescue agency for that specific breed. They wouldn't even let me an adopt a dog because I didn't have a yard. And even if I did, they required a fully fenced yard which is hard to come by in the city </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-10 06:17:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Basic home repair, cooking, and growing food </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-10 06:05:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some advice, if you continue this hide your face and charge more money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-10 05:46:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it possible he needs more mental stimulation? Have you tried getting him puzzle toys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 01:37:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Old school RuneScape... This will take a while </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 21:34:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A winter favorite is ham cooked in sauerkraut. Throw some cloves, bay leaves and celery seed in there too.. delicious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 21:33:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beets! I love beets. Especially pickled beets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 04:18:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please don't do this. There was a time when the $5 stashed in my glove box was about all the money I had for food </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Love those freckles </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 04:16:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hiking is her favorite weekend activity </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 22:11:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 23:03:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It'll turn out okay, whether her dad ever shapes up or not. Kids are able to adapt really well. It's obviously not the best situation, but you should be proud of your daughter for seeing things so clearly.

My dad was the same way through my childhood and teen years. We didn't rebuild our relationship until I was in college. Things are better with my dad now, and I forgive him for not being there. My mom raised my brother and I on her own, she gave us everything she could've. Because of her I was a very happy teen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 06:00:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You sold her things dude. YTA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 00:31:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not a customer, but at my work we had to ban a DoorDash driver for being aggressive towards female staff. He'd yell, swear, and do everything he could to seem physically threatening. He kept coming back and was eventually dragged out and charged by the police. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-15 03:20:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As if Mystery isn't a top selling genre </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-12 23:47:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See I get that! Sometimes I feel like people are more caught up in making sure their character is decked in full virtual Gucci than anything else.

Then again, I also made a space Invaders hat so maybe I'm a little hypocritical </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-12 02:00:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> His toes will be missed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-12 01:10:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been smoking pretty regularly recently, and started very light about 3 years ago (I'm 23). If I smoke too much I mostly get sleepy. Earlier this week I smoked too much and ended up going to bed at 9pm to cuddle my dog. I

It makes me appreciate nature more. I like to have a little and take my dog on a walk. It helps me feel beautiful. It helps me embrace my imperfections.

However, sometimes I also get very anxious. I feel better smoking at home or at a friend's place then I do at a party or bar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-12 00:54:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ESH and you both need to stop using each other as therapists. Get professional help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-12 00:39:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. You were treated unfairly and your mom knows it. Good for you for standing up for yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 17:45:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm hoping you just buy your sons a box of condoms each to hide in their sock drawer or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 17:42:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good point. I don't think I want to bring this ass hole back into my life over a couple hundred bucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 01:39:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got a recipe today from a regular balloon! I don't think I did anything differently, the game code just has not been kind to me lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-04 17:56:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! I'm so frustrated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-04 17:49:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you visit another island with a nook miles ticket you can use your shovel to dig up different types of flowers then replant them back at your island. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-04 17:43:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I install every update when I receive the notification-  So I have the actual blossoms, but no recipes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-04 17:42:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can redeem nook miles for a nook miles ticket at the ATM looking machine. Take the ticket to the airport and you'll be able to travel to a randomly generated island. For a shovel I believe you get the recipe once Blather's comes to your island, after you bring 15 specimens to Tom Nook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-04 17:40:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I play this game for at least a few hours ever day (yay quarantine!) and I still haven't found a single sakura blossom recipe- from jars, balloons, or villagers. Is it totally random? Am I missing something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 21:25:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the most naive, privileged thing I've ever heard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-22 17:58:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He needs to get off drugs and eat some protein </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-22 17:54:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's satire bub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-14 21:16:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol said the stay at home yoga instructor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-13 03:44:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So fuzzy!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-13 03:11:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a big oof </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 19:45:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's super pretty and safe! The building pictured is the library, I took many naps in their armchairs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 16:24:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Westminster in Utah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 14:12:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I graduated from the college pictured! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> It's my Silly Girl's 1st Birthday Today!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-20 03:13:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I downloaded MeetMe for all of 30 minutes and deeply regret it. (Yes that's his censored penis) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 23:41:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-11 04:12:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! Its probably for the best, I need to figure out who I am without a boyfriend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My girl has a knack for drama </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-04 19:12:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-24 04:57:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is actually really cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> On Saturday nights we watch The Office </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-24 04:51:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This dog toy that looks like a sex toy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-10 03:08:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> An evening walk with my pup </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 05:37:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 05:03:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably made by a now 30 yr old scene kid from 2009 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-14 05:01:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look I'm not risking chafed titties </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My Brittany pointed for the first time! At the neighbors cat </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-13 02:28:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My girl after a long day of play </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-01 05:38:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Got caught in a storm while hiking this morning </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 04:32:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Peaceful stream in Yellowstone National Park </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 21:45:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-23 05:49:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's good you feel remorse for your actions and are taking steps to improve. However, my cliched advice is "if you love something let it go." You may want this relationship back more than anything, but it will never be the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This trailer hauling two other trailers </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-21 02:40:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My groggy puppy after her spay surgery last weekend </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 04:32:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
