<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject55</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 03:40:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry I wasn't clear - it was removed about 2 months ago, and I followed aftercare instructions with no dry socket. That's why I'm weirded out by the suction feeling still, since it has been a while. I can't afford a dental visit at the moment, unfortunately, so I really appreciate you taking the time to give advice and ease my anxiety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 03:20:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much for the response!

Is the random suction feeling normal or could it have something to do with the sinus? When it happens it feels like it is affecting the tooth by the socket, kind of like the tooth is loose, but it is not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 2 months after tooth removal - still having strange sensation </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 02:48:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had my top left rear molar removed on 8/10. The dentist said there was an extra, small, deformed root that left behind a small piece. He didn't continue trying to remove because it was close to the sinus. Healing seemed fairly normal, but took much longer than I remember from a previous removal. There is still a fairly distinct depression in the gum and it seems like there is a sort of suction feeling that occurs by the remaining molar when I swallow a certain way or poke around with tongue. The remaining molar does not seem loose. There is no pain, but it is a strange feeling.

Would this possibly be because of the remaining root piece?
Is this something I should be concerned about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 17:18:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the read suggestions! The link you shared has so much information I can relate to. I wish I could afford therapy, but Dr. Google has at least helped me with a few coping strategies.

I was pawned off by the parental units onto a WWII/Korean War veteran with his own mental health issues, so toxic parenting is definitely a way to phrase it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sleepy teef </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 22:47:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How 2020 has us all feeling </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 22:45:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Snowberry clearwing, "Hummingbird" moth </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 22:34:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 18:52:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This term - "rat lickers" - is honestly a poor insult to use without context for the anti-maskers. I was about to get riled up because I assumed it tied into people blaming Asians for this virus. Instead, I looked at post history and realized it is a term being used for those who won't mask. I can support the sentiment and even like calling the anti-maskers plague rats, but using it this way makes it seem to have a different context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 18:19:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so sorry for your loss. Please, remember that grief has no rules. It is perfectly acceptable to feel completely overwhelmed and awful and broken. I can't imagine how your personal mental health is contributing to your pain, but that is also acceptable and not your fault!
The woman who raised me, who I considered to be my mom, passed away April 2, 2012. It has been eight years and sometimes the loss still hits me like a tidal wave. To offer some hope, though, the pain is not as big or constant as it was at first. I also struggle with various mental health issues and was absolutely not okay for a long time after, but it does get better. A month is a very short time to give yourself to heal. If you would like to talk, please feel free to reach out. I probably don't have much good advice, but I have plenty of time to listen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 17:48:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't have any advice for you, but as a 29F as well, I just wanted to let you know you aren't alone. I have absolutely no interest in hobbies or what most people consider entertaining. Absolutely lost in life. My mind is not blank when speaking with people but the interactions feel wholly fake since I tend to present a different persona based on what I think that person could be interested in. I honestly don't even know who "I" am. I have college credits, enough for a degree, but couldn't stick with anything long enough to actually build a career. I have children that are the only bright part of my life but I simultaneously feel like I don't deserve them because they are beautiful and I am a train wreck. If I could convince myself that anyone else would care enough for them, I would remove myself from their lives so I don't end up passing my emotional damage along.

I'm sorry you are experiencing problems like this. I really hope TalkSpace helps you work through the self-doubt! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 16:38:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi! I am not a doctor, but have been prescribed the 800 mg ibuprofen on a few occasions. Have you taken ibuprofen or hydrocodone before this?

Taking your medicines normally shouldn't be causing chest and throat pain, but normal side effects do include some stomach upset, like you described with drinking water, especially if your stomach was empty.
Hydrocodone, especially if you accidentally took too much, can also cause respiratory problems that could explain the chest pain.

If I remember correctly, the ibuprofen should only be taken every 12 hours however, so please be careful with how often you are medicating. I thought writing it down when I took medicine or setting an alarm for your next dose really helped keep up with the right times.

I would strongly suggest calling your doctor or going to urgent care if the chest pain and shortness of breath continue, just in case it is heart or lung related.

I hope you feel better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Pets for days (or karma) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 04:44:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cute cats for karma </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 04:36:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 21:29:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://nwarkansasonline.secondstreetapp.com/Confederate-Statue-Removal-Poll/questions

Right now this poll says 60+% think removal was a mistake. I just can't believe that is accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 03:18:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My husband and I have had the same problem with data and MMS since we switched over almost 3 months ago. We also had issues with regular texts until we resolved that, on our own, by switching the sims into each others phone. Somehow that worked and we just traded phones.
I've tried everything I've seen suggested as far as the data and mms go. Sometimes switching APN and turning airplane mode off and on works for a little while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 01:33:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not a doctor, but have had a couple surgeries and been prescribed pain meds. Just take it as you need for the pain, but no more than every 4 hours. Also from experience, don't stick it out too long and wait until you are in bad pain to take the medicine. It takes a bit to kick in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 2010 Dodge Charger - give up or attempt repair? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 23:19:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi!

We have a 2010 Dodge Charger SXT, V6, auto transmission, 117,095 miles. It has had a couple of electrical issues in the 7 years we have had it (cigarette lighter shorted and almost caught fire, passenger seat belt exploded, and fuse box has melted in a couple spots).

It no longer starts at all. Nothing even tries. My husband said he had started it at work on his break and it had sort of hiccuped while running. When he tried to start it after that, it would attempt to start and not turn over. It was smoking from somewhere unidentified under the hood - nothing caught fire but everything felt hot.

Towed for diagnostics and the mechanic shop says the fuse box is fried and they can't even run the diagnostics. Dodge says they don't manufacture one of the parts needed (husband wasn't clear if it was the fuse box itself or the wiring, but told me if it was that specifically it would be like trying to repair a human nervous system?).

Our local Dodge dealership said they could look at it and see if they could repair, but I don't want to throw more money at it if it's a lost cause. Any advice is hugely appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Found kitten - how long should I quarantine from my cats? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 19:43:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kitten, Unaltered male (I think), approximately 8 weeks, orange tabby, <2 pounds

I found a kitten in a storm drain last night. I waited about an hour to make sure there was no sign of any other kittens or momma cat, but it got dark and the forecast called for rain so I bribed him out with wet food and brought him home.

I'm guessing this kitten is around 8 weeks, maybe less.  He ate wet food with no problem, has greenish eyes instead of blue,  and a mouth of tiny teeth, but I'm pretty sure he is less than 2 pounds.

He is eating and drinking fine, but has brownish discharge coming from his nose and one eye is irritated (no discharge yet, but he is blinking and squinting it some).
I cleaned his nose and eye, and will be watching for any increased signs of a respiratory infection.

My two questions:

How long should I keep him separated from my other cats to ensure he won't pass any illness or disease to them?


Is there anything else I can do at home to help his cold?

[Kitten](http://imgur.com/gallery/2G3lHEK) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 06:15:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not positive exactly what they have, but Horsebarn has a lot of exercise bars. It's right off the bike trail close to Northwest Hospital and Krispy Kreme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 20:24:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do schools actually have nurse's offices with a nurse?
Yes, but don't expect medical care. They mainly dispense prescription medications a student would need, keep those medicines, epi-pens, care plans, etc. in a safe place, and determine whether to send a student home sick.

How prominent is bullying and how likely is someone to be bullied?
It varies how much the school administrators will allow and how severely they punish bullying. Some schools have no/low tolerance policies, and some seem not to acknowledge the problem. I was also homeschooled through 8th grade and entered public school for high school. It was a bit of a culture shock because I was fairly sheltered, but was lucky to be at a school where most people either ignored me or were relatively nice. Now, as an adult with children in school, the bullying I have witnessed and heard about tends to be more verbal than physical.

Are lockers stacked?
Unless they have changed it in the last decade, they are often stacked and line busy hallways. Lockers are inconvenient in general, but so is toting around 70 pounds of textbooks.

Do teachers not let students use the bathrooms?
Bad teachers do this. Most teachers will only limit if they feel like a student is doing something other than actually using the restroom.

How challenging would it be for a girl during their period?
This is where communication with your parents, the school nurse, and your teachers will be vital. If you are comfortable explaining yourself, let the nurse and your teachers know your situation. You would not be able to keep pain medicine yourself, and, in most cases, might even get in trouble for having it with you at school. Your parents should be able to give some medicine to the nurse, but will have to provide written permission for her to give it to you. At my children's  school, there is a section in the yearly paperwork that asks if permission to give over the counter medicines like acetaminophen (Tylenol) or anti-itch cream. You would need to go to the nurse and get medicine when you need it at school. As far as absences, that may vary from state to state, but in our district a student can only miss 9 days a semester.


What is with gym class and would it really be mandatory?
Physical Education is mandatory. Medical exemptions are about the only way to get out of physical activity. I don't remember the class being too awful, and it was only once a week. There is a shared locker room for changing, but usually some privacy, like a shower curtain or bathroom stall, is available if you are uncomfortable. Uniforms or required attire would be up to your school/teacher. When I was in school, we just needed a t-shirt and gym shorts. Showering should be entirely up to you.

How is homework assigned?
This is also something that will vary depending on your school and teacher.

How much physical violence is there?
Again, this varies from school to school. My answer about bullying applies here, too. Some schools won't tolerate it to the point both the aggressor and victim are punished when an altercation occurs. Some schools act like it isn't happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ongoing symptoms, maybe autoimmune related? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 01:54:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 28 F, 5' 1", 155 lbs, white, previous asthma diagnosis (no attacks since adulthood), anemia, and generalized anxiety. Taking iron when I remember. Previous tobacco, alcohol, and cannabis use in my late teens.

Symptoms have been occurring off and on since adolescence.  Newest symptom being that I have been having seemingly random breakouts of small hives all over my body following an emergency c-section in mid November. The hives have occured almost daily, both at home and at other locations and have appeared basically everywhere but my head, hands, and feet. They don't last long - usually it has cleared up within 30 minutes.

I have also been having increasing joint pain and "looseness." I'm not sure how else to describe it, as it feels like the affected joints are almost wobbly and are distinctly creaky in their sockets. It first started with my right shoulder at 16 or 17.The pain varies in location and severity, but is mainly in both shoulders, both wrists/thumb joint, both knees, right hip, and, weirdly, right big toe. My wrists and thumbs will randomly be severely painful when gripping. This is pretty new and flare ups last hours to at most 2 days.

Sometimes even a small bump/poke, like going to scratch an itch, makes my shoulders feel like a tiny hot coal is burrowing into the muscle, but the pain passes within just a minute or so. This also happens in my calves and thighs, but less frequently. I also have chronic back pain, but attribute that to two accidents when I was younger that caused damage (potential but never confirmed L1 wedge fracture and an angry vertebra right between my shoulders, if relevant).

Additionally, I seem to struggle with regulating body temperature. I get overheated very easily and sweat profusely, but also get shivering cold when in a cool environment. This comes with fun, frequent night sweats.

My mom has anticardiolipid syndrome that contributed to a stroke at age 39. I believe I was tested for that at 18 while pregnant with my oldest child due to her stroke and diagnosis. I do not remember being given results and no other doctors since have mentioned it, but I basically only go to the doctor when I am very ill or pregnant.

Any ideas on what this might be or what type of doctor I might want to start with are greatly appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 18:29:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We ported over on the 10th, so it has been a little over a week. Walmart accounts no longer work.
I cleared the text cache - no luck.

Everything works normally on both phones when we swap, but my sim in my phone just won't give me texts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 02:19:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Samsung S9+ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 22:47:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! I did see that there is an outage currently, but this has unfortunately been going on for a few days now, so I'm not sure it is related. I only attempted trouble shooting today, so hopefully it will work once everything is back up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Unable to receive texts </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 22:16:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Edited to note:
Problem is still occurring after outage.
My husband has an S9, also newly activated on Mint, and has been having basically the opposite problem intermittently. It works more often than not. Texts will always come in, but occassionally struggle going out.
Weirdly, we swapped sim cards, and all of my messages came flooding in on his phone. When we  switched back, texts stopped coming in again.

Hi! New Mint Mobile user here! Samsung Galaxy S9+ I ported my old number from Walmart Family Mobile. I'm having a problem with my incoming text messages. I can make calls, send texts, use wifi, and data, but for some reason no texts make it through to me. I contacted support and have tried both the Ultra and T-mobile LTE APN settings. I also saw another post about trying airplane mode. Nothing has helped. Any other tips? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 02:05:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Insane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 01:52:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It seems like signatures can still be collected, just not being actively done by this group anymore.

https://arkansansforcannabisreform.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 00:53:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://arkansansforcannabisreform.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-27 23:49:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This plant has appeared in my overgrown back yard. Any ideas what is is? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-27 20:50:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> http://imgur.com/WUITG3c

http://imgur.com/XJ1KRl3

http://imgur.com/855nSC8

6 to 8 feet tall after approximately 1-2 months of growth.
It just began flowering (mid to late July). Tiny, white flowers in groups.
Plant zone seems to be on the line of 6b/7a, minimum temp with wind chills are around -10° to -20° F and max temp around 110° F
I can't tell if it prefers sun or shade, as it has appeared all over my yard. It definitely is growing taller where it is along the fence line and edges of concrete.

Thanks for your help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
