<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject6</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 09:18:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In summer, I would go with Barcelona. Seville is a hell, temperatures in summer are insane. Madrid is hot too, but not that much. Barcelona is also hot, but it has a milder climate with the sea close to it.

Climate apart, Madrid and Barcelona are both cosmopolitan cities with plenty of museums and cultural things to do. I've been living in Madrid for many years and I love it. Seville is a smaller and less cosmopolitan city, but big enough to have cultural activities going on. It is also, in my opinion, the most beautiful city of those three. It has one of the biggest  (the third I think) historical center of Europe. Plenty of monuments and sites to explore, it is just gorgeous. But again, I wouldn't go in the summer as temperatures are usually over 40°C.

Anyway, I think you would love any of them and each one has its advantages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 17:27:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jjajajajajajjajajaja

Pues buen rollo, los 2€ pa un pintxo cuando se independice Euskadi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 17:17:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ya buscaremos otra forma de que alguno no esté contento y haya peleas. Yo he llegado ya a tal punto que lo único que quiero es que haya algo de unión y buen rollo entre españoles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 14:21:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ¿Por favor podemos dejar de usar este foro para discutir sobre política? Se supone que es un lugar de unión para los españoles de Reddit, no para dividir y polarizar el país. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 16:36:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 12:31:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mastodonte. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 23:06:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Castellanomanchego para la comunidad, manchego para la zona de La Mancha. A veces se usa manchego incorrectamente para toda la comunidad, lo cual es incorrecto pues La Mancha es solo la zona central de la misma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 15:24:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 09:09:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Give that chunk in Italy to the Papacy please. Just for aesthetics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 08:07:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're amazing, my mum went to Italy with her school and discovered them. Simple and delicious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 20:12:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Europe should be a pivot between Eurasia and America to prevent a cold war and polarization. Being in an alliance with the USA will only make us the battlefield of a cold war again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 17:53:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You forgot Bavarian soviet republic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 15:13:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We live in a society... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 21:43:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure, but that is not a bad thing (once he/she has enough knowledge of the language). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 21:22:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aquí no hay quien viva is a must. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 18:05:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Philippines, the best Latin American nation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 17:33:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Avilés is very close to the sea too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 08:47:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mum speaks English and Spanish. My dad could speak Spanish, Italian and Latin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 15:50:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's so cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 15:45:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it supposed to be arabic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 10:57:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Segovia and Cuenca are two amazing cities close to Madrid that you can visit in a day and nobody mentioned. Albarracín is also truly beautiful, but it is harder to reach without a car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 23:07:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The best thing you can do is to own only counties and baronies in your duchies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 23:01:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Perfectionism is just another way of procrastinating. Perfect is the enemy of good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 22:50:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Usaría el condicional, pero tampoco sé ahora mismo explicarte por qué. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 21:09:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> HOI classic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 20:48:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does he need also a SIM card appart from the phone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 19:55:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vehicle mobility data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 16:50:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hecho! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 11:26:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope they will change it eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 11:13:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, if you didn't hold so many kingdom titles, you could reduce the number of vassals. Just give some kingdom away and grant them their de jure vassals yo reduce that number. It is not unavoidable at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 09:31:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God works in mysterious way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 09:29:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate how Hagia Sophia is disabled as Catholic or Apostolic, as Constantinople is not a Holy site. Every Christian will be amazed by having such a church, even the Ottomans did. It makes no sense to me that it is disabled when controlled by another Christian different than Orthodox controls Constantinople. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 10:19:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, totally. Same language, similar culture, but totally different realities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 09:58:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How is your relationship with Brazilians? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 09:37:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you make an effort with the language, it is pretty easy to meet locals and friends. If you only speak English, things will be harder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 09:29:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try paper map mod, I heard it improves the performance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Natural language processing applied to mobility </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 19:51:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello everybody!

I am going to start a master in natural language processing, and I have the opportunity to do an internship in a company that analyses mobility data, but we are struggling to find a common topic. Do you know about some examples that applies natural language processing to mobility data?

Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 16:12:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is actually cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 15:29:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will probably try to create a dwarf dinasty, it seems much funnier than continue playing that game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 14:10:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When did you formed the Roman Empire? I totally losed my interest when I formed it, as I was too powerful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 13:47:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol I never noticed, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 13:15:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe their universities are not that good without the foreign students... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 13:14:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is something related to the 1.1? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 15:38:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am not the one posting misleading information on the internet to get attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 15:36:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Catalan nationalism in a nutshell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 15:33:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Butthurt spaniards that dismantle your made up story you mean? Cry me a river </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 15:30:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In this case, it is not excuse an excuse at all. The whole Pujol family is involved in an enormous corruption scandal.

And the three last presidents that where inhabilited were because they broke several laws, as proclaiming the independence unilaterally. I agree this is also a political problem and cannot be solved judicially, but Spain is not by any means a fascist and arbitrary state as some people show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 14:47:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol Pujol is in prison for enormous corruption charges. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 15:20:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sevilla is such a wonderful and beautiful city. This picture does not show it at all, it just look like an average city, when it is clearly not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 14:35:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got Syria, Crusader Syria and Catholic Syria, all of them Ortodox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 13:59:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Masterpiece </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 11:00:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lukashenko gang </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 09:06:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aquí no hay quien viva, the best comedy ever made in Spain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 08:50:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks man! I'm feeling better every day thankfully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 08:49:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It can only be investigated after 1200, I don't have it yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 23:31:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Many times a week, normall for dinner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 22:36:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I took it before I decided to form the Empire lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 20:50:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As I am quarantining myself due to having coronavirus, I've been playing a little bit more than usual. I founded the Roman Empire 1235 starting as Philip Capet of France, swearing fealty to the HRE and then using the Meritocracy perk to become emperor. Once emperor, I spammed the creation of titles for prestige to achieve the 10500 to remove the elective law of the empire. After that, I started conquering Catholic reigns and then some generations later, I married my son with a byzantine empress with a claim. After killing the Byzantine Emperor, its daughter became Empress so I could pressed my claim. Then, with my son inheriting the HRE and my daughter in law being Basilissa, my grandson inherited both empires. Then I just had to recover Italy and to do a Holy War to conquer Egypt and voila! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My first Roman Empire! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 20:50:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 09:33:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Switzerland takes lots of skilled and educated workers from the EU for free and they have free trade, banking cooperation and more advantages due to this treaty. Switzerland is built by immigrants and cooperation with the EU. Abandoning that would be more perjudicial to Switzerland than to anybody else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 20:19:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe the best, but also the toughest. I love leg day but damn boy, the next day is not so awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 08:56:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo creo que ese campo hay mucho trabajo, y de informática en general. Los sueldos sin embargo, no creo que lleguen a los 4000€ en mucho tiempo. Igualmente, con un sueldo de 2000-2500€ puedes vivir bien, la vivienda en esas dos ciudades es cara (700-800€ de alquiler mínimo para vivir solo, creo que Madrid es ligeramente más barata), pero el resto de gastos no son muy grandes.

Respecto al grado, Madrid y Cataluña son de las comunidades con las tasas universitarias más altas de España. Si no me equivoco, un año completo de grado estaría por en torno a 2000€ (un poco más en Cataluña y un poco menos en Madrid). Creo que este  es el precio para todos los ciudadanos de la UE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 22:18:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stalin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 22:04:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Con ese sueldo vives como Dios en cualquier lado de España, por eso ni te preocupes. Y una vez con buen trabajo, en España se vive muy bien (bueno, quizá ahora no tanto). Lo malo es que no hay buenos trabajos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 22:02:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you seen Extremadura's? It's similar but with a black stripe. Maybe you like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 16:17:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok so end the free trade with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 09:13:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been there this weekend. What a gorgeous city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 23:15:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The holy trinity: incest, poligamy and adultery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 22:04:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally unplayable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 14:37:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 09:24:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They only work if you do all in one sitting I heard :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 09:20:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does this allow achievements? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 09:16:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are mods that only use the paper map in the workshop. I never used them, but I saw other redditors saying that it improved the performance a lot. I hope it works!

Edit: I cannot English in the morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 18:49:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Based. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 14:32:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those horse are giraffes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 22:36:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 21:44:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Subjuntivo ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 17:43:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I made out with men and I didn't feel horny or anything. And I was drunk enough to see any woman attractive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 08:04:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry, I should not have said that. What I mean is that is much easier and natural to know new people in a group context and sharing activities that directly in a one-to-one approach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 22:38:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Knowing people in group activities? Through friends? Like a normal person? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 21:27:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I heard it from people from Mérida. Badajoz lies just at the border with Portugal, so I guess that's the reason (same with Vigo, I guess). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 20:54:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It means taking off as you say, but it is alzar el vuelo, not en vuelo. I would say it's only for birds, for planes we would say despegar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 20:53:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vitoria did, with a different grid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 20:50:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same for the people of Badajoz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 11:15:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You want big titties daughter-wives don't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 22:31:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Qué lástima. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 10:26:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Igual los demás no queremos una vida tan triste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 09:21:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just puked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 20:17:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same age as Messi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 15:15:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Around 0,60€ for a liter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 14:51:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is what I do but I use the same monitor for both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 13:55:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thankfully I use two different computers, it could be a disaster if I use my personal one to work... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 18:30:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Son holandeses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 15:58:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Finally. It took way too long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 17:57:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maths and Computer Science are very demanded right now. Other STEM degrees are also needed. Medicine or nursery have also good prospects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 22:37:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Siempre igual. La gente es muy progre con los negros pero por los gitanos nadie da un duro. Mucho Black Lives Matter (que está genial apoyar esa causa, no digo que no), pero cuando tenemos causas aquí en casa a nadie el importan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 22:35:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pero es más tema de xenofobia que de racismo, el problema racial de EEUU es muy profundo y de distinta índole. Yo creo que algo más parecido aquí sería el tratamiento que se les da a los gitanos, parte de España desde hace siglos, pero aun así apartados y despreciados por gran parte de la sociedad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 22:35:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pero es más tema de xenofobia que de racismo, el problema racial de EEUU es muy profundo y de distinta índole. Yo creo que algo más parecido aquí sería el tratamiento que se les da a los gitanos, parte de España desde hace siglos, pero aun así apartados y despreciados por gran parte de la sociedad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Flag of Kosovo if sea level rise by 2,659 meters </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 16:11:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> &#x200B;

https://preview.redd.it/zmlcrjtpaxm51.png?width=800&format=png&auto=webp&s=bd5b96ae2afe933c9804f0a38a8d8790dd0924c9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 14:11:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Qué pereza de gente de verdad, menuda obsesión con el color de piel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 12:31:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did my Erasmus there, such an amazing place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 00:31:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DeepL works amazingly good between Spanish and English and Spanish and French too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 21:29:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where do you live? I buy them in a local shop in Ciudad Real, they're working on an online shop but is not ready yet. So I guess it should be in other specialized coffee shops as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 14:32:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 20:57:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was in Germany doing my Erasmus that year. I've been from 2014 to 2017 and from september 2018 to 2020 lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 11:20:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been 5 years living there and not a single day it snowed and stayed on the ground. A couple of times snowed a little bit but that's all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 18:57:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Serrano ham. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 23:40:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Typical Habsburg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 19:21:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought I've seen it must you're right, it is not possible. But having a same sex lover is possible, right? I think that was what caused my confussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 19:06:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Much more epic name to be fair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 13:29:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We should remember that most Paradox games were far worse when released, and a lot of improvement will come. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 12:44:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gargantilla del Lozoya y Pinilla de Buitrago, with 44 letters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 12:39:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the main (and only) problem with this is inheritance. But with some adoption mechanic it could be perfectly valid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 12:02:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Another similar example could be [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Leopoldo\_O%27Donnell](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Leopoldo_O%27Donnell) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 11:52:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It depends on your religion and its views in homosexualism, but I am not totally sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 11:52:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is the option to have gay concubines is your character is homosexual or bisexual if I am not mistaken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 09:42:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Voy a cerrar ya la encuesta, muchísimas gracias a todos por las respuestas, sois la leche. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 12:47:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Joder y yo usando qBittorrent sin saberlo ¡Gracias! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 12:42:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No Instagram!... I mean No pasarán! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 12:40:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would say Iceland or Faroe Islands, due to the lack of trees and the style of the house. But it could be Norway too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Encuesta sobre teletrabajo y lugar de residencia </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 11:56:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Encuesta sobre teletrabajo y lugar de residencia </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 11:56:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Encuesta sobre teletrabajo y lugar de residencia </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 11:54:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ¡Hola a todos! Estoy haciendo un trabajo para la uni y me gustaría que me ayudaseis a recopilar datos rellenando esta simple encuesta. Lleva solamente 5 minutillos.

¡Muchísimas gracias!

[https://forms.gle/2g8tQcYCgVYt5G489](https://forms.gle/2g8tQcYCgVYt5G489) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 15:58:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kampana Tower, in Kotor, Montenegro.

Next time try to use the function that Google has to search using images, it is really helpfful! It is what I did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 09:14:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just fyi, Barça is only used with the football team, not the city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 20:45:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We weren't talking about public education, which it is pretty bad. Of course private schools are only for rich people. But you said that not even the fanciest school in Spain could teach a language properly, which is simply false. You just used that to bash the Spanish education system, which is legit, but totally out of context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 19:47:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course there are. I have friends that studied in a german school that were totally fluent in German. Also there are plenty of good private schools that teach other languages perfectly, like the Lycee Français of Madrid.

Why Spaniards are always trying to shame their country in public with false information? If you don't know what are you talking about, just don't say anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Flag of Poland but it is my burned arm </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 18:56:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 10:35:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bilbao tiene un área metropolitana de en torno a un millón de habitantes. Por lo tanto, es mucho más grande (a pesar de que el municipio en sí tenga una población similar) y con más vida y oportunidades laborales que Alicante. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 21:47:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly the same in Spain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 21:16:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, depending on who build it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 18:10:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a great idea! This subreddit never ceases to amaze me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 21:54:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same in Spain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 23:41:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Universidad de Castilla-La Mancha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 12:51:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RemindMe! 2 days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 12:50:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RemindMe! 2 days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why was French population density much higher than the rest of European countries, but then grew much slower? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 12:47:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-22 19:40:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Both are pretty nice places. I like Oviedo very very much, and Asturias is just a paradise. But Vitoria has a much better economy and I guess the quality of life is better. The Basque Country is one of the better places to live in Spain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-22 17:22:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sin faltar al respeto de nadie, menuda puta mierda de lista. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-22 02:36:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been skiing in Andorra a couple of times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 21:53:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Y ser gracioso. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 10:04:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is amazing how they punch above their weight in almost all aspects of life. That's why one may think they have more population (along with size) than they reallt have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 10:03:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sweden has roughly the same population as Portugal and is even bigger than Germany. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 09:37:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> En otros países y en otras regiones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 23:27:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Delaporte </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 14:31:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why in India and not in the UK? Isn't it safe enough? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 14:09:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 13:39:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course it was different from ISIS. Learn some real history instead of far-right propaganda. I am proud of Spanish heritage, which is mainly christian, roman and european, but that doesn't mean that the Caliphate was horrible and a dark era.

You simply told racist propaganda that is simply not true, and it has nothing to do with being proud of being a spaniard. At the time of the beginning Caliphate, the arab world was living a golden era and the christian Europe was in barbaric times. Then the things changed and christian Europe took advantage, but at the better time of the Caliphate, things were not like nowadays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 12:49:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A dark era is having a cultural splendor and having the biggest city in Western Europe, along with philosophers and scientists? Your racism is amazing. The situation of Morocco and Algeria noe has nothing to do with Spain in the Islam era. There was no liberation, simply a conquest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 09:55:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think is very important, if you use social media (that is okay, it doesn't need to be bad), to select carefully your feed and who you follow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 17:57:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The communist were crushed by the SPD in the 1919 revolution, so I guess that is an important fact to take into account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 21:49:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Piqué is going serious with Andorra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 21:43:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same as Dubai, luxury tourism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 16:15:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> EU can't even manage its own members as Poland or Hungary. Leave Erdogan for the next episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 23:55:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks a lot dude! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Working remotely to an EU country while living in Spain </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 20:46:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi everyone!

I got an offer to work for a Luxembourg company, but the law there forbids to hire workers living further than 150 km from the border, but there is the option of becoming a freelance (autónomo) in Spain and pay my taxes here. How should I do that? Should I pay the tasa de autónomo and the IRPF corresponding to my earnings? What about the IVA? How can I apply it? Is it different while working for companies in other EU countries?

Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 12:14:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In other parts of Spain they grow too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 12:24:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo soy de Ciudad Real y... Efectivamente no hay Corte Inglés, aunque siempre existen rumores de que se va a hacer uno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 10:15:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Be kind and good with all the people, not just me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 10:18:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interested too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 08:47:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is what I was thinking about, search after I start the MSc. My current internship finished in november, and the MSc starts in october. I would wait until january or so to see how the COVID situation evolves, and create some projects and advance with the MSc.

Thanks a lot for your answer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 22:40:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spain is way colder than the last few weeks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Getting a DS intership in COVID times </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 16:36:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi everyone!

I am a Physics BSc. from Spain. I am currently doing an internship in Madrid, in which my main task is to develop a python app to navigate a SQLite database. I have studied too some data science on my own, and I have enrolled in a online MSc. in NLP for the next semester.

The thing is I finish my internship in november and I could maybe get a job in my company. The problem with this is that the job I would do has nothing to do with what I am currently doing, but something much more related to engineering (as I work in a train manufactory company), which I don't like at all.

I am getting tired of Madrid, so I would like to try nee places. How hard is to get an internship in Data Science with my profile in these times? I speak fluently Spanish and English, and have an intermediate level of German. I don't care about the city, I just want to know if there are some options out there for someone like me.

Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 12:13:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I prefer winter tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 09:51:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay I just read the flair "To Anarchists". Now everything makes sense. Enjoy another failed, unprepared and spontaneous revolution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 19:50:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> La verdad es que no. Lo de la CIA era una forma (desafortunada) de hablar. Pero el hecho de que los medios occidentales inunden todo de información sobre un país del que nunca hablan justo cuando hay movimientos para derrocar a un líder poco favorable a occidente, pues da que pensar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 19:22:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literalmente está todo internet con propaganda. Huele a Euromaidan 2.0. Yo no me creo nada sobre las "revoluciones" patrocinadas por la CIA sobre países de los que nunca hablan salvo cuando les conviene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 14:05:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People are not organized, there is no working class conscience at all. It is, sadly, not time for a revolution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 13:36:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go for it! If it goes wrong, I am sure you will learn a lot and have a lot of fun. But I am sure you will nail it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 11:19:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even in that case, there are plenty of white latin americans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 12:34:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not only the monarchy was put back in power, but Alfonso XIII allowed (and encouraged) Primo de Rivera to take power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 12:32:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can I ask how tall are you? That kettlebell seems tiny  in your arms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 22:52:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The art is gorgeous! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 16:16:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And you can spread the virus everywhere and create a new focus. I cannot believe there are still people who do not recognize the risks of the virus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 13:10:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Desde luego, el sistema territorial español necesita reformas de algún tipo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 12:55:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lo sé, y agrava la situación de las dos Castillas más aun, concentrando prácticamente toda la economía de la Meseta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 12:49:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw one with red, white and yellow that was gorgeous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 12:37:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> También (no solo ni mucho menos) debido a que son pequeños paraísos fiscales dentro de España. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 12:34:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We have: "el hambre agudiza el ingenio". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 10:36:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Spanish Falange took the colours directly from anarcho-syndicalism. In the case of the nazis, it's because of the German Empire.

Edit: typo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 08:49:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And way cleaner too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 00:55:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They've been trying with Cuba for decades in their own backyard. They didn't even manage to kill Castro. Same with North Korea. The USA are powerful, but not omnipotent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 19:21:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Desde luego lo dejaron todo atado y bien atado. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 18:04:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would love to visit China, I want to go as soon as this situation finish! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 17:58:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for your tips!

And of course, reading stories you like is much better than forcing you to read something you don't feel like to read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 17:19:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where are you from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 17:04:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too, it is so hard to develop focus and perseverance these days. The only thing I can tell you is to not stop trying, and create favourable surrounding.

If you want to read for example, maybe take your book and go to a park or other place far from your phone or computer would help. I think adapting your enviroment to what you want to do and become is the best way to do it, as willpower can be trained but is limited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 17:01:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spain high speed network is very good (although a bit expensive). I am sure you would love Spain. I love travelling by train, it is so comfortable and nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 16:54:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ciudad Real, Spain. I didn't find a better photo but it reminds me of it.

https://images.app.goo.gl/RoH3UXuQs6sGjypQ9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 15:58:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reddit is centered around the US, and politics are everywhere. But this shouldn't be allowed as it is not really related with technology </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 14:54:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This looks like my city's station but with a chinese look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 14:36:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No sé, yo no lo tengo yo tan claro. Aunque sí es verdad que una victoria ahora de un sí a la monarquía en un referéndum acabaría totalmente con las opciones de república a corto-medio plazo.

Necesitamos una mayoría aplastante antes de ningún referéndum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 14:26:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Se necesita que el PSOE cambie su opinión respecto a la monarquía para que empezase a a ser viable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 14:24:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As we say in Spanish: "la paciencia es la madre de la ciencia" (Patience is science's mother). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 09:06:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same in Spain. Hispanic things I guess. But then they are open until 21:00 or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 00:39:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course, I don't even drive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 22:50:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 13:30:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same! I've been dreaming about making games for so long, and finally I decided to start. Good luck in this journey, your game looks very nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 10:32:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This. Galicia is one of the most conservative regions of Spain, but they have also a strong regional identity. Castilla-La Mancha has been always left-winged, but they are pro-monarchy mostly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 10:30:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The king in Spain represents somehow the democracy era (even he was appointed by Franco), and he "stopped" a coup d'etat in 1981. There is a state and private propaganda machine in his favour too. The only major party that opposes the monarchy is Podemos, and only mildly. The monarchy is a key figure in the post-Franco Spain, that is why people supports it.

And even with that support, he manages to have 60 percent of people against him. It is as easy as behave yourself to maintain the support. But these Borbon cannot simply behave as normal people. I'm glad all these things are happening so maybe we get rid of this family once for all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 10:22:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And Madrid one of the last. This map does not resemble the civil wars borders at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 22:59:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right now is not good due to the position of the dutch government and Mark Rutte in the recent EU meetings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 22:36:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ¿A qué saben las botas de un corrupto mujeriego? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 22:22:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like your own government does in the rest of the world and their own citizens? Like american companies do in all the world? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 13:07:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But a little bit is needed. We didn't have a civil war this century. That is not very Spanish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 13:24:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Laugh in Vatican </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 11:38:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is a good tool to achieve that goal, but you need more resources to really learn the language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 22:17:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This. I love good stories, but storyless open games are my favourite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 22:16:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My favourite games are those that are non linear and highly replayable, so you can spend as many hours as you like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 11:15:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Domingo (sunday) is also a Spanish name. Never heard other days of the week though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 11:07:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We have the same but in arabic and latin. Olive is oliva (latin) and aceituna (arabic). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 17:09:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a Spaniard, I can understand almost perfectly written Portuguese. Spoken Portuguese though, sounds like absolute gibberish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 14:38:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was growing way faster than the average. But of course, it has structural problema and the economic model is very fragile as we have seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 12:35:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spanish economy was doing great before Coronavirus, with some of the highest rates of GDP growth. But as our economy depends heavily on tourism, this have been an enormous hit.

I hope this makes our Spain to shift the economic model to a more robust and competitive one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 10:47:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo creo que Ciudadanos podría hacer algo similar a nivel nacional. Si recupera parte de los escaños que perdió y pacta a ambos lados según las propuestas, podría prácticamente dirigir la política del país, pues se volverían un actor indispensable. Sin embargo, han preferido una postura rancia y muy lejos de lo que dicen ser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 10:36:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pero eso es bastante común a todos los partidos, no creo que sea cosa de Ciudadanos solo.

En cualquier caso, yo creo que el estar de partido bisagra concede más poder del que va a tener nunca Ciudadanos si intenta desbancar al PP. Mira a los nacionalistas, con muchos menos escaños y son capaces de dirigir la política nacional dado que les necesitan para gobernar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 10:29:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ¿Y qué hay de malo en pactar con unos o con otros según convenga? Yo siempre he visto eso como una virtud, poder entenderse con gente con distintas ideologías para los temas comunes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 20:50:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ahora con la cuarentena está hasta arriba de aviones aparcados y en mantenimiento. Ojalá dure.

Como anécdota, tengo el orgullo de haber volado dos veces desde ese aeropuerto a Barcelona. ¡Y mi hermano hasta fue a Londres! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 14:05:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Spain it is like that at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 11:50:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Posting your own comments because you didn't get any upvotes is a bit sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 22:32:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True, and you never heard about those genocides comitted by the British, but always about every other one.

And also true, my bad, I thought it was the same in English. Is Americas in plural correct? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 22:24:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And Argentina and Uruguay genocides weren't comitted by the spaniards but the argentinians and uruguayans.

And America is the whole continent. The USA is the name of the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 14:48:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We gave up Cuba, Puerto Rico and Philippines in 1898, and Ecuatorial Guinea and Western Sahara in the 1970s, but these last two were not important.

The war of 1898 against the USA is know as the 'disaster of the 98' and it is a very important moment in Spanish history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 14:07:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've seen far-right Spaniards portraying the Spanish Empire as a fairy tale.

Btw, happy cake day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 13:23:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Colonization of America was brutal, but it was not a planned genocide as some claim, and it was mainly driven by greed. Many events of excessive cruelty by spanish settlers were condenmed by the authorities.

Colonial times were not a wonderful tale of diversity as other people say. I think our history (European in general, Iberian in particular) must be treated ruthlessly but with justice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 12:06:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The main genocide in America was the smallpox. That does not mean Spain didn't kill, slave and destroy, but it was never a genocide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 11:54:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Iberians did nothing wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 11:51:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And why not slaves? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 11:49:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you mean massive slave trade? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 11:48:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here and we are not small. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 10:52:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Madrid es de las comunidades que más se benefician del sistema autonómico. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 08:08:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is not fair to compare the nature of any country with Norway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 16:52:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Con esos, mano dura, estoy de acuerdo. Pero creo que hay problemas de vivienda mucho más serios como para estar todo el rato preocupados por los okupas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 15:43:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This. Politicians reflect how the people are. The spanish problems are much bigger than politics, they are deep inside Spain roots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 09:37:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Igual facilitar que la gente tenga viviendas dignas y asequibles es mejor opción. Luego se quejarán de que hay muchos indigentes también. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 19:10:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Party and naps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 15:23:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally agree, the merch selling would change the things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 15:18:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everybody participates in the system, so every worker that buys clothes is exploiting people by that logic.

I think they are exceptions as they are very rich workers, but not capitalists, same as sportsmen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-26 13:56:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Elon is more for for 69h a week for 4$/h </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-26 13:54:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahahaha overthrowing a elected leader, so funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-26 13:53:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Supports a coup in Bolivia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 19:26:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> El Oso y el Madroño, cerca del Retiro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 01:13:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depende de las zonas. La sierra de Cuenca y Guadalajara no es secarral. Sierra Andújar y Sierra Morena tampoco. También existen humedales, ríos... Pero si solo pasas por las autovías para ir a la playa, pues vas por lo más llano y rancio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 01:11:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Madrid siempre ha sido y será Castilla por mucho que reneguéis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 12:13:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, social distance in Finland is good enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 09:35:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only instance? Have you heard about the apartheid for example? There are thousand of cases of a minority oppressing the majority (for real, not lile this one) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 14:22:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't know Panathinaikos was from Bayern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 10:16:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depende de lo que entiendas por cultura española. Desde luego un segundo idioma siempre enriquece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 09:30:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mum is funcionaria and takes care of me very well. Check mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 09:22:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is not the best series but I think the idea is original, and that Spain is the center of the story and has an important role is refreshing. And the americans and companies don't mind people dying for cancer, that is a truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 08:51:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do you say that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 08:50:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I too disagree. La que se avecina is predictable and boring like TBB, but AQNHV is much much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 09:36:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cuts that came from the EU partially. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 20:57:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He is very attractive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 11:56:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here in Spain, and I guess everywhere as it not a pleasant job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 11:28:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree partially with that people mess other people lives. But saying the everyday life is disgusting... Maybe you are not confortable here, and I accept and understand that. When I was studying in Germany I also felt people didn't give a fuck about what you do or who you are. But there are plenty of good things of living in Spain that makes life here wonderful.

Every place has good and bad things, and no place is good for everybody. But I really like Spain and enjoy living here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 10:21:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe the building is very light. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 10:20:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol Spain is one of the safest countries of Europe, why do you say that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 18:42:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Es algo antiguo yo creo, nadie joven usa francés para referirse a una vulgar mamada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 17:36:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Una felación. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 11:52:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I make similar mistakes but the other way around when speaking English, even though I've been learning it for a very long time. Mistakes are part of the neverending process of learning! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 11:35:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the only way to learn! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My first walled city </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 17:44:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 08:48:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And it is a veryv slow train, I don't think is good idea to do Bilbao-Ferrol in one trip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 14:43:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think it's the reason in your case, but of course eating habits contribute a lot to acne. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 14:57:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Siempre he querido ir. Ya no. Gracias por ahorrarme dinero. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 10:46:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Encima de que de por sí no es muy agraciado, lo ves al lado de Pedro Sánchez y ya el pobre no tiene remedio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 09:33:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Spanish is very common to ignore them as most of the meanings can be understood by context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 09:23:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Un señor nos vio viendo fotos en Avilés y nos preguntó que si éramos turistas, nos dio recomendaciones para comer, nos dijo que tenía una casa en la Senda del Oso, que de dónde éramos... Un amor de hombre. Y como este, nos encontramos varios a lo largo del viaje.

Lo que me gusta es que es un 'patriotismo' positivo e inclusivo en lugar de lo contrario como se ve en otras partes con donde se sienten más suyos que españoles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 09:11:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Justo vengo de una semana de vacaciones de en Asturias, es gente muy orgullosa de lo suyo pero para bien. Mascarillas, tatuajes, pegatinas, todo con su bandera. Y mucha gente con la que hablabas te daba recomendaciones de sitios y lugares para que tú también disfrutases. Qué buena comunidad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 09:07:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pues a mí me parece que está bien guapa, aunque sea de una comunidad autónoma inventada y sin gracia (igual que la mía). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 19:49:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been playing for six years in Madrid. Not very popular but growing fast and it is moderately popular in some cities like Valladolid, and within the university students in Madrid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 16:58:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is free movement of people and capital between member states of the European Union. You can work anywhere in the EU too. So obtaining spanish nationality is not only a ticket to Spain, but also to the whole EU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 14:05:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People do not talk often about their wages, which I think is bad for workers. Knowing how much your colleagues or other people earn gives you the idea about how much should you earn, and if you are earning less than that, demanding it. This secretism makes employees earn less than they deserve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-27 11:19:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Basque Country is such a unique and wonderful place, both to visit and to live. I've only been once though, but I want to come back as soon as possible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-27 11:18:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love Ávila, it is so cute and cozy. But there is no much to there as many castillian cities next to Madrid, they are totally absorbed by the capital. And not only the city, the whole province of Ávila is something amazing, specially Gredos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-27 11:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Extremadura is truly gorgeous, and I think is overlooked even by Spaniards. It is one of the poorest regions of Spain, so a little bit more of tourism would be very nice to them.

Asturias on the other hand I think is very valuated by Spaniards, but not by foreigners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 16:00:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know, most tourists come to Spain because of the weather, and the North is not very sunny to be honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 15:36:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 15:30:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Val d'Aran :) why did you cancel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 14:52:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tony Soprano. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 12:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To the val d'Aran. Any recommendations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 12:34:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lucky man, I love your city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 12:33:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am going to the Pyrenees next week, I am so excited! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 10:21:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think there are many secrets left in Spain, but Asturias is an absolutely gorgeus place not so visited by foreigners. Outsanding nature, cheap and wonderful food and cider. And as you asked for a city, Oviedo is a place I really like.

Other small city not very visited by tourists that I love are Cáceres and Cuenca. I think Toledo, Ávila and Segovia receive a lot of tourists fron Madrid, but I love those too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 15:03:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why is always Spain is fragmented in this kind of map? Apart from Catalonia (nowadays not even Basque Country) there is no more independence movements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 12:08:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like in real life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 08:27:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The word for Flemish in Spanish is 'flamenco' (like the music genre). So you could imagine how disappointed I was when I discovered that Flanders it wasn't what I thought it was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 21:51:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Es Recoletos y lo que se ve de fondo es Colón. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 20:05:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hice una foto muy parecida la última vez que estuve en Asturias, allá por 2015. Es una estampa preciosa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 17:49:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> T H I C C </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 17:19:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo lo entiendo como comida de media mañana, entre desayuno y comida. Mi abuela, sin embargo, siempre usaba almuerzo como sinónimo de desayuno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 13:04:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know, but please do not become like those british people living in Alicante 20 years and not speaking a single word of Spanish.

I don't personally think guiri is an insult, it is just a stereotype about anglophone tourists and I would not use it with people really living here. It is not the same to be a expat than to be a permament tourist like those I described before.

So I don't think there is a reason to be offended. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 12:58:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Has anyone ever noticed that antifa drink water like the first fascists? the very people theyre trying to stop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 15:22:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totalmente de acuerdo, pero eso no hace que no haya derecha como veo a mucha gente decir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 15:16:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nadie lo sabe, no tiene sentido especular la verdad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 14:07:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sí, lo que quiero decir es que el PNV predomina en Euskadi por encima de PP y Vox. Pero sigue teniendo mucho voto a la derecha, solo que al PNV en lugar de a PP y Vox. Igual en Cataluña con Convergència. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 13:56:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Igual en Euskadi con el PNV . Son de derechas y nacionalistas, solo que vascos en lugar de españolistas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 10:48:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lot, both the armed forces and the police. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 08:22:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No es a esa gente a la que me refería con empresarios, pero llevas razón, que empresarios hay de muchos tipos, no solo ricos y casposos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 23:17:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pues porque la pasta la tienen los casposos por los favorcitos al régimen. Así es muy fácil emprender. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 15:45:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same but first the surname of the father. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 16:45:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But it has a legitimate celtic history, as half of Europe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 16:42:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also does France, England or half of Spain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 15:56:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go to bed earlier, there is no other way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 14:06:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spain's worklife is very stressful. Longer working hours (the mandatory rest for lunch in most companies makes the day way longer), low salaries, high unemployment and a bad work culture of just spending hours at work.

Outside work, Spain is amazing, but inside it, it is pretty bad. So I don't think GDP is only due to hard work and stress, there are plenty of factors that affects it way more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 13:08:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Public transport is very good and it is walkable due to its density (for short distances, as is a big city). Biking structure is almost non-existent though, and there is still a lot of cars traffic. Also frequency in the metro is worse every year. There is plenty of room for improvement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 14:05:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is a 52-page report from McKinsey called the future of work in Europe if you want to understand the map better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 21:07:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 11:01:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here, drank a lot in the past, but that shit is over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 16:01:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lo es. Mucha diferencia hay entre los dichos y los hechos. Ahora ni siquiera dice estas cosas, como para hacerlas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 09:06:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trotsky tried to do it during years until he had... some... accident... while... climbing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 21:08:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A friend calls Mediavida 'the Spanish Reddit'. I don't know much about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 08:28:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Estaba pensando que no está tan bien. Hasta que me he visto fielmente representado. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 08:24:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was once in the mountains of Alicante with a friend and it is wonderful. Tourists should go inland more often, Spain has much more to offer than beaches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 21:45:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try to do it, it's worth it. You will appreciate much more and healtiher food. And you will also taste junk food much more intensely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 20:14:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't like it before, you just need to get use to it. Junk food has a very strong flavour that modifies your feelings. Try to left junk food (specially excess of sugar and salt), and real food will start to taste better and better.

EDIT: By feeling I mean the feel of flavour in your mouth (taste?) that I don't know the name for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 11:32:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I miss my Erasmus in Freiburg so much. You just hit me in my most deep feels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 10:18:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, plenty of raw food is tasty and very healthy, and it does not even need to be prepared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 10:16:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eso pasa por dejar las cosas a medias en la Transición. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 10:08:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Quieren repetir lo que hicieron en el 36. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 10:06:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 27 million soviet citizens were killed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 09:54:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They use the WWII for justifying everythin Churchill did, but at the same time Stalin was the worst monster ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 08:09:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, Stalin contributed even more to defeat the nazis and he is usually portrayed as a total monster. But all of the horrible crimes of the British Empire are always ignored.

But I agree with you, spraying racist is oversimplify. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 23:12:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He starved millions in Bengal. That is a little bit more than being racist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 23:12:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, not every national hero commited a genocide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 23:11:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A hero of Bengal and the millions he starved too I guess. Fuck Churchill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> They: Who is your favourite football player, Ronaldo or Messi? Me, an intellectual: </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 09:50:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> &#x200B;

https://preview.redd.it/42a52p5cs1351.jpg?width=960&format=pjpg&auto=webp&s=eda6e25a14ef177d70330d21d224f98d9b01da4a </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-04 17:24:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the explanation to all of you guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-04 17:19:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But it is still a 6-lane road next to the beach, which is surprising to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-04 12:11:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I meant in Spain hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-04 10:41:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn, it seems to me that California's urbanism is even worse than the standard US urbanism, am I right or it is just ignorance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-04 10:40:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Urbanism in California seems to be a nightmare even for US standards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-04 10:39:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Madrid there are also highways through the city, but maybe not that straight through. But I've never seen one directly at the beach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-04 08:42:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amazing, but I really hate the idea of a highway next to the beach. Is this normal in the US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 13:54:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nada se me ha ido la pinza perdona. Llevas toda la razón. Igualmente no es que el gobierno oculte datos, sino que el INE hace una estimación de todas las fuentes mientras que el gobierno solo cuenta las muertes directas de los datos que le llegan a sanidad. Son cosas distintas en cualquier caso.

Aunque sabiendo esto, pues sí que deberían utilizar por lo menos ambos datos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 13:19:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Porque esos son los muertos totales durante la pandemia, los del gobierno son los muertos causados por la COVID. Números diferentes para datos diferentes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 11:12:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Henry VIII. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 10:28:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More like iRaq </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 10:13:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Recent and past I would say. The USA has a very high criminal record of invading countries and bombing civilians. I think this is why most people around Europe has a low opinion on the US.

Apart from international politics, I don't like the american culture and mentality. I think it is too individualistic and competitive (generalizing), and also very self-centered and egocentric.

Nevertheless, all the americans I've met being in Germany during my Erasmus were really nice people, I still talk to some of them very often, so maybe this is only the image of the country that reached me, as I've never been there.

But this is my opinion, maybe he/she has different reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 08:04:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Real equality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-02 22:26:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mi novia volvió de mi casa a la suya en tren cruzando media península cuando ambas provincias estaban en fase 0 y no hubo ningún problema.

Creo además que puedes volver a tu domicilio legalmente, pero aunque no diría que no hay ningún problema </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-02 13:30:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> England density population is one of the highest in the world. Castile's population density is low, but it is not almost without population.

If we compare to Mongolia, with 3 million inhabitants in 1.564 million km², now it seems that Castile has an enourmous population density.

My point is that it is not almost empty. It still has a low population density, definitively not empty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-02 13:17:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, both Castillas have 5 million inhabitants. It is not nearly without population, only some areas are very sparsely populated. But population is condensed in very dense nuclei, which makes a lot of the land empty.

Spanish cities, towns and villages are much much denser than the rest of europe, so that may be also a reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-02 12:28:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It would have been nice to be peaceful when bombing and destroying Lybia. Empty words in the mouth of a war criminal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-02 09:14:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totalmente de acuerdo. Twitter es una red llena de crispación y odio de la que no sale nada bueno. Desde que lo dejé mi salud mental mejoró enormemente. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 20:15:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My bad, I thought it was more abrupt. Anway, way more people die from air pollution every year than has died from nuclear accidents. I know that nuclear energy is not perfect, but is a better complement to renewables than fossil fuels. I can understand the fear, but it needs to be rationalized. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 14:55:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Let's see what happens with die Grüne the next elections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 14:06:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They are antinuclear, and for compensating the lack or nuclear power plants abruptly closed after the Fukushina disaster, they generate most of its energy out of coal, as renewables cannot sustain the demand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 22:43:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think so, but it is better that way, or it would be too light and hot half of the year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 19:08:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No idea, I guess because internal market good prices fluctuate a lot between countries. But I don't really know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Why restrict plants to your home? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 18:52:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-30 18:50:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It does not suggest that. Read about what this means. India has 1300 million inhabitants, Germany 80. Russia also has the double of population than Germany and half of the GDP. So they would be half as rich as the germans.

The GDP PPP is an adjustment to the prices of each country, but in this case is for the whole country.

GDP per cápita is when you measure the average GDP for person, which is better to compare the quality of life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 15:11:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> America and Western propaganda is the best one because their own citizens think it is not propaganda. They (we) actually think everybody is brainwashed but themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 09:59:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 09:19:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It looks amazing, I want to know it too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 21:55:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Al mismo tiempo* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 14:08:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember an article form a British newspaper asking why are spaniards healthier. I wonder why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-27 16:12:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Theatrus Orbis Terrarum I would say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 18:16:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a weird spelling for UK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 18:04:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mitsubishi Pajero is here called montero. Pajero means wanker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-21 17:30:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Muchísima crispación. Yo intento evadirme de todo en estos momentos para mantener la salud mental. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-21 17:03:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I'll try first as a duke, and if I cannot do it, I'll try the emperor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-21 14:16:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-21 13:42:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it better to do it as a byzantine vassal, the emperor or some italian? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-21 11:37:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which would be a good tactic to create Hellenism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-21 07:23:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Como gane Casado nos esperan tiempos duros también. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 22:20:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> La verdad es que no se podía no querer a ese hombre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 22:02:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Si hiciésemos un artículo por cada vez que Rajoy metía la pata, se cae el Internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 18:21:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Subiria al Getafe a bueno y al Atleti a élite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 16:16:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 12:30:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate people being late too, it shows lack of respect. Why should I waste my "chill" time waiting for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 08:39:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mostly wine and cheese. Half of the region are grapw crops for making wine, and the other half is for sheep.

I will investigate about the mines because now I am curious and never thought about it. I only know a mercury mine in Almadén (a very big one, now closed) and a coal mine in Puertollano.

Probably there were some silver mines but are closed some time ago. I will check as soon as I finish working, and if I find it, I'll tell you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 08:28:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We have now in La Mancha our modern don Quixote, also very thin but with a longer spear: Jordi El Niño Polla. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 08:26:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know about any gold mine over here, so if there was one back then, it is not used today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 08:24:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And Jordi el niño polla. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 14:38:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is a Netflix documentary (maybe only in Spain) called "100 días de soledad" ("One hundred days of solitude") about a guy that goes a 100 to a cabin in the mountains of the north of Spain, with no contact with anybody and the only technology being their cameras.

It is very good and very beautiful to see, I recommend if it is available outside Spain. It is also available in YouTube I think, but maybe there are no subtitles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 08:16:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The colours of the USA flag are really amazing, and I think in the real design do not look as good as here or in other redesigns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 14:45:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me encanta el que graba para acusar a los demás como si el mismo no estuviese allí. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 14:24:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 11:07:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And you should too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-17 16:16:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure, the problem are the regulations. The lack of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-17 15:24:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I usually don't see arabic script as text because I am not used to it. So every time I see it I find it amazing. I think it is the most beautiful script. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-17 15:15:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I cannot buy a house here either and I have to pay half of my salary in rent. Fuck this supposed freedom, it is only freedom if you have money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-17 15:13:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We are not talking about America and their prison labour or those assasinated by the police. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-17 12:50:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Como les jode estar perdiendo dinero a los ricos. Están deseando de que los trabajadores salgan a morir para comprarse otro yate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 17:10:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It seems also a much better game so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 15:10:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Paradox games offer thousands of hours of game and are being updated during 10 years. I think is a fair price to pay to have that many DLCs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 15:08:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is even worse. With a lot of cheap DLCs you can at least choose what you want.

Anyway, the DLCs are really annoying, but they are offering very complex games with a lot of replayability (does this word exist?). You can always have the DLCs in sales and with a little bit of delay and it is not that expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 23:23:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, neither are the rest of Spanish regions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 19:08:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 10:06:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also do other teams and had much lower success. Money is an obvious factor here, but not the only one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 08:42:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Papel Alval (aluminium paper), Kleenex (tissues) or pan Bimbo (loaf bread). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 18:11:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Singapore be like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 16:31:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And why would be they here if they're not supposed to enjoy it? It makes no sense at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 16:29:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> En mi insituto era igual, una celebración sin más y luego a beber. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 22:05:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Recuerdo haber mirado esto hace tiempo. Creo que si facturas menos del SMI o algo así no tienes que hacerte autónomo. Así que si son pocos trabajillos no sería problema.

Y las cooperativas freelance están un poco en el limbo de la legalidad según entendido, con lo cual no creo que sea recomendable.

Todo esto lo miré en Google hace tiempo, no me hagas demasiado caso porque no tengo mucha idea, pero espero que te ayude un poco. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My girlfriend gave my mum a plant as a present and they were both so happy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 09:24:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 14:57:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having played in Spanish made me to think about if the German translation would not be perfect. I will try that mod everybody suggested me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 14:37:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I decided to not duel again, nor command battles. A long reign equals stability and it is better than any combat bonus that you can obtain from your character. Maybe in some certain situation, but almost never. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 14:29:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same happened with me in Lisboa. I love Portugal but is really dirty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 13:23:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks a lot!

I always play in English both because it is easier to look on the internet and because the Spanish translation is not the best, so I guess translation aren't very good in general.

I will try a relaxed and tall game as a HRE duchy or something to start learning vocabulary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 10:27:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know the vocabulary is not the most useful or easy. The thing is that I will be playing anyway, so I want to learn something from it. Most of the English I learned is because I was exposed to it all my life in games, series, movies, internet... So I want to do the same with German, try to introduce it in my daily life somehow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 10:24:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, that is something I was looking for! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 10:23:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for your answer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 10:22:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks a lot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How good is the German translation? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 09:46:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hallo zusammen!

I am studying German (level B1/B2) and I would like to play the game in German in order to learn something while playing (and why not, play some German nation for more flavour). My concerns are that  tried the Spanish translation and it is not very good, there are many mistakes and weird things, so I always play in English. I would like to know if the same happens when playing German, or otherwise the translation is better.

Is the German translation good? If you played more Paradox games, are those German translations good?

Danke schön! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 17:51:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That sounds really nice! My brother lives in Trondheim, but due to the high prices of the food, we didn't really went to good restaurants and try traditional cuisine the times I visited him.

I'll tell him to take me to a traditional restaurant next time I go up there! Thanks a lot for your recommendation! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 17:30:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where are you from? Some dishes or places that you would recommend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 16:50:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know, I was just trying to trigger those barbarians from the north. There are some good dishes in those countries. It's the lack of variety and food culture that I find bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 16:33:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, northern european food is horrible, I agree with him in that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 16:23:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> USA and UK are managing this epidenic catastrophically, and the anglo pride is one of the causes of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 14:28:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Left upper is gorgeous. The others are also nice, but not as good as the first one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 14:13:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I prefer to play on Ironman because I prefer some roleplaying and realism than blobbing non-stop. It also helps me to think actions before doing them, instead of "what if" after saving my game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 12:11:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally understandable. Can you annex us, please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 22:25:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Estar hecho un roble" ("to be an oak"? Idk how to translate it) or "estar como una rosa" ("to be like a rose") are two typical expressions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 15:35:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The portuguese people don't deserve this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 14:44:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pues lo que debería hacer cualquier partido en esta situación. Es una situación muy excepcional y de la colaboración depende salvar muchas vidas, no es momento de politiqueo. Ya habrá tiempo para discutir después. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 22:54:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow Prague is way richer than I thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 18:12:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just puked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 11:06:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know now why in Finland people drink that much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 11:03:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do the mountains play a role in it too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 10:56:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It seems. I alsways forget how north the south of Finland is. I anyway thought it was a little bit warmer. My brother lives in Trondheim, Norway, and the climate seems milder there, not usually under -10 and almost no wind, as it is inside a fjord. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 10:38:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you usually get -20C at the coast or is something rare? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 10:36:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, in central Spain the sun is up from 8:30-18:30. Cold in the early mornings (some celsius degrees below zero), but once the sun is up, the temperature is way more comfortable (some days there are 20 degrees between the highest and the lowest temperature of the day).

So I cannot complain, apart for the early morning, things are nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-07 11:45:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lot. My lower back is killing me after a couple of months of quarantine. Recently they allowed in my country to do sports outside and I am feeling better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-07 11:24:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I liked it until you told they are protestant... Digusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 08:37:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I am from a country know by its beaches and the nearest one I have is about 4 hours by car. At least in Austria you have more rivers, lakes and mountain. Here, in the middle of nowhere, we don't have that, only 40 degrees in summer :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-05 23:14:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try to give it a positive spin. If you see other people in love, you can find somebody one day, it is not a reason to be envious, but to be hopeful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-05 14:56:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agriculture and construction workers mainly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-04 22:05:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would say that it would be easy to find a work as a teacher. People value native speakers a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-04 17:01:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> De momento no hay nada seguro, pero he oído que como muy pronto finales de junio, y se plantea incluso septiembre (ojalá).

Me he acostumbrado al teletrabajo y ya no quiero volver. Además que no entiendo la necesidad de volver ya la gente que perfectamente puede teletrabajar. Es poner en peligro la recuperación sin ninguna necesidad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-04 14:56:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would say some examples could be Germans as coconuts, and Spaniards as peaches. People usually are so nice here, but they too often have no commitment with relationships. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-04 10:01:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that in Argüelles by any chance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-04 09:15:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are many different kinds of jotas with their own characteristics. The Aragonese jota is the most famous one though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-03 10:13:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You also develop diabetes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-03 10:12:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/ShitAmericansSay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-01 16:39:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see you are a man of culture as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-01 16:09:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Our king is big and has military training. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-01 10:46:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A, that means to. "E", that means "and" before a word that starts with "i". And "U", that means "or" before a word that starts with "o". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-01 00:06:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm fine with that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 20:47:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Menuda pasada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 19:44:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No es enchufe, es conocer gente. No quiero decir que a cualquier inútil lo contraten por ser "amigo de". Pero si hay dos personas capacitadas para un puesto, a quien contratan es a quien conocen.

Puedes ser todo lo bueno que quieras que si no te conoce nadie te vas a comer los mocos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 16:02:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That custom nation has francoist vibes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 13:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Necesitas contactos o la educación no vale de nada.  Vale mucho más conocer al que maneja al percal que saber cómo manejarlo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 13:31:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Teniendo padres millonarios. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 09:34:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just having 200-300€ to help me to pay may rent will be a bless from the sky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 08:26:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks to God I have the NSFW filter on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 20:59:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is awesome and it is very spanish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 17:12:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you still feel the same when showering?

Do you sometimes take hot showers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 10:55:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SUUUUUUUUUUUU! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 08:57:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, if they speak English, they're clearly American!

I mean, how can he be from Vietnam if he is not speaking Chinese? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 15:46:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amazing map and amazing run. Congrats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 09:39:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is not the colour, but the culture. But it is racism anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 09:10:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't get why everybody hates Ronaldo. He is very proud, but he is also a very hardworking and kind person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 22:37:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lybia was doing good, then shit happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 22:05:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 15:03:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course: lolololololololo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 15:02:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aunque nos aceche el dolor y la muerte
Contra el enemico nos llama el deber </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 15:02:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 12:26:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Los de los asturianos si que me parece un orgullo sano y ejemplar, sin politiqueos raros ni nacionalismos (salvo residuales). Un saludo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 12:24:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is a weird thing. It is not anecdotal, I think that happens a lot. But I do think there is patriotism but covered by some kind of complex, a different one in each side of the political spectrum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 10:44:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aquí no hay quien viva should be on top. What a classic series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 10:43:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How can such a bad show as Elite have 100%? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 08:54:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is associated with being right-wing (except if the football team is playing). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 08:46:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And most of the D.R. Congo lives in a very small area in the west. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-26 15:21:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I has a Greek guide when I visited Greece with my HS and I thought he was Spanish the first three days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-26 15:20:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally true. It is amazing how well romanians speaks spanish, and how well they integrate in Spain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-26 08:24:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Understandable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-25 16:44:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Spain there is usually an hour or more for having lunch in the middle of the day, so people usually eat with their teammates in a restaurant or at the cantine. This leads to a longer worktime though, which is something that I really hate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-25 13:47:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Resident Evil 4. But characters speak with a weird argentinianish accent and it has nothing to do with Spain. But well, you pay with pesetas so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is the role of food in your country? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-25 13:46:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here in Spain food is a very important element in both culture and social life. Meal times are sacred and almost everybody eat with more people. Gastronomy is also very important in our culture.

But when I was doing my Erasmus in Germany or when I visit my brother in Norway, I feel like people just eat because they have to. They eat walking, alone, even at a university lecture. People don't seem to care that much.

How is it in your country? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 21:07:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The working life of Norway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 09:47:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bernie Sanders is not refering as the same socialism as Lenin. Socialism is the previous phase of communism, what the USSR did, what is commonly known as communism.

Bernie Sanders uses socialism to refer to social democracy, not the same.

Please, use better arguments than this stupid name fallacy, and investigate a little bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 09:16:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here I would say it is seen as less poor Sub-saharan country with white people (way more than reality). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 14:41:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing. I've been drinking 2-3 times a week during my university (and a lot), and I learned I had no self-control once I start drinking, so I stopped completely.

I've never felt better, I am so happy with that decision. I've been sober for 8 months now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 12:28:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This misinformation won't go anywhere. After this crisis, China would have achieved its hegemony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 12:21:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now we have a historical oportunity to improve the world. We have to use it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 08:14:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same story, you are not alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 22:09:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He is american with italian heritage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 18:58:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, that is not medieval. But it is amazing anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 15:38:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, it is way cheaper than I thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 15:32:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How much can be a gun like that? I am not fron the US so I don't have any idea about how much a gun can be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 15:21:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo espero que después de esta crisis aprendamos algo y el mundo cambie a mejor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 15:07:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nunca trabajó menos que hoy en día, pero con el enorme aumento de la producción podríamos trabajar menos aun en vez de hacer cada vez más ricos a unos pocos que siguen engordando sus ganancias, y los trabajadores tenemos cada vez menos poder adquisitivo y trabajamos lo mismo que hace 100 años, mientras la mitad del sueldo se va en alquiler.

Ya se está viendo lo útil que es una economía orientada al servicio y a inflar números vacíos cuando los países más avanzados del mundo tienen su sistema sanitario colapsado y no tienen capacidad de fabricar mascarillas, en lugar de orientarla al bienestar y cosas útiles y tangibles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 14:55:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ya pero como bien se ha dicho, aumentar la producción y el PIB puede ser cualquier cosa: armamento, alcohol, tabaco o servicios financieros... Dime tú cómo aumentar eso mejora la vida de la gente. Además que un crecimiento por encima de nuestras posibilidades destruye el planeta y contamina nuestro aire. Trabajar más para aumentar la producción hace que tengamos menos tiempo libre para pasar con la familia o para nosotros mismos.

No estoy diciendo que un aumento de la producción no sea bueno, sino que debería ser un medio para mejorar nuestras vidas y no un fin en sí mismo que se deba alcanzar a cualquier precio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 13:09:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this true? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 13:00:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No he dicho que no se haya mejorado la vida, sino que ahora mismo la economía está orientada a maximizar producción y beneficio, en lugar de a mejorar la vida de las personas y ser sostenible. Claro que ha habido mejora, una cosa no quita la otra. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 12:36:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Precisamente ese es el problema. La gestión que damos al tiempo, los recursos y medios. Todos estos están destinados a producir sin fin, haciendo de la producción un fin en vez de un medio para mejorar nuestra vida. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 10:12:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I disagree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 09:42:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This makes me unconfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 09:40:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And Laos is Bolivia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-20 18:11:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In a socialist state, the people is armed through a red army, so there is no reason for arming civilians.

In a communist state, there is no need to arm the people, as all the world is communist and the reactionary forces had been defeated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-20 14:47:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very nice job!

I want to add something. San Francisco is the spanish name of Saint Francis. San Priesco doesn't mean anything, as Priesco is not a spanish name or something. I don't to criticize you, I just feel annoying how americans create fictional spanish names that doesn't make any sense at all. Other typical things are names that does not have their correct gramatical genders.

Sorry for my rant, your work is amazing. I can't wait to have a new computer so I can play the game properly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-20 14:39:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amazing how Iceland has a 5th of its population on Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-20 14:26:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mostly Spanish, but I do use English in some programs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-20 10:49:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yes, comedy gold... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-20 09:59:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Brazilian Portuguese is easier to understand. But Portuguese from Portugal is a phonetic nightmare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-20 09:35:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm Spanish and post in Spanish and read the r/Portugal with no problem. Understanding our neighbours when talking... That's a pretty different thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 21:16:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Warm milk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 20:12:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you'd never seen porn, I think that wouldn't very problematic. But if you were a porn user before, it probably reminding you of it and reproducing what you used to watch. So I would avoid it too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 13:32:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did my Erasmus in Freiburg, Germany. I was surprised about how many people were barefoot in the summer in every place, even went to do exams barefoot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 10:52:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably because in Spanish americans are called 'estadounidenses' (also 'americanos').

I understand them, it is not nice that one country uses the name of the whole continent only for themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 10:49:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a surprise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-17 12:59:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, Mariano Rajoy has sort of humoristic quotes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-17 10:53:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can relate. Now I can pronounce it if I try, but when I am speaking normally, my spanish accent comes back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-17 10:39:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What if a leftist for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-17 10:19:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This, the problem is only at the beginning of a word. In the middle of a word is perfectly fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-17 09:49:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 'Within their means'. I know some people in northern Europe only want the south to drink and go to the beach, and if we had another economic model that would be impossible.

The problem we have with the EU is that forces us to be in lower value places of the value chain, while some core countries concentrate all the industry and high value sectors of the economy. We produce cheap food and offer cheap holidays resort, and we have to buy your expensive high technology products in the commob market. That is the whole point of the European Union. Some countries gain market gor their products, forcing the periphery to dismantle their industry, becoming richer and richer while calling us lazy. We have to live 'within our means' while you all gain the profits out of this abusive organization called the European Union.

I am tired of this rethoric that northerner works so hard so they deserve whatever they have, but a global pandemic hitting us is our fault. Some people think they deserv all while the rest deserve nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-17 09:41:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's unnatural to us to pronounce the liquid 'S' (I think that its name?. We pronounce it as 'Espain', we need a vowel before it hahahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-17 09:09:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jorge Javier Vázquez, vanguard of the worker class, the spanish Lenin. You guys live in a parallel world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-17 09:02:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, the difference is Italy and Spain are in the middle of a pandemic and the EU is ignoring them. If you can't count on the EU in this situation, when can you?

Same with the 2008 crisis, when the EU troika acted more as a mafia than any other thing. If in times of crisis we are getting nothing but insults, what do you expect? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-17 08:40:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Something that we can pronounce properly. That initial S is a pain in the ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 20:33:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Geographically speaking* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 18:39:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What happened to the under 8s? They ate them as communists do with children?

Fuck off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 13:11:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being ambidextrous is actually related with problems at learning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 13:06:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Antena3 awfully left winged lmao. None of them are leftwinged, maybe TVE and LaSexta a little bit socialdemocrat.

Come back to the 50's, fascist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 10:29:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, by Phillip II iirc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 08:22:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do you have your fridge next to your monitors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-15 19:47:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fruit and vegetables from Spain vary widely in quality. You can find very nice and very bad products. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-15 17:16:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Salud" is also what you say instead of "cheers" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 12:39:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spain is very far from flat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-13 16:06:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I read as I would read it if it were spanish: noompee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-13 15:12:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> New Zealand's English is pretty hard for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-13 10:49:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What I do is shower as I always do but with cold water. For me it's the best and most natural way of doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-12 17:26:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Muito obrigado!

Espero que en Portugal no se llegue nunca a como estamos en España. Un abrazo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-12 16:02:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you cook the omelette before eating it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-12 15:45:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Si no recuerdo mal el estado de emergencia se declaró más o menos a la vez, y la situación de Portugal era mucho mejor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-12 15:07:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> En Portugal se pusieron medidas cuando las cosas estaban mucho mejor que en España. Esa prevención hace que estéis mucho mejor. Aquí fuimos demasiado lentos... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-12 13:37:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you prefer omelette with onion, you don't like omelettes, you like onion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-11 22:09:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure. But I just can't stand people here idolizing drugs as if they were wonderful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-11 13:45:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gracias a eso, España es uno de los países donde más anda la gente, porque todo está más cerca. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-11 13:44:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo entiendo portugués escrito. Hablado ya es más difícil jajaja </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-11 11:02:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> El interior español está muy desierto, pero las ciudades españolas son muy compactas, con lo cual parece que está más desierto de lo que ya está.

Hablo en español porque yo os entiendo sin saber portugués, espero que al revés también. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 13:20:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, that could be. I don't know how GPA works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 12:22:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Qué buena pinta, ¡que aproveche! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 12:20:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Barcelona is pretty nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 12:08:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally agree. I hate those absurd stereotypes. I am from Ciudad Real and things are not much better here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 11:48:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's all advantages! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 11:43:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think in the Netherlands there are plenty of degees in English so you won't have to learn dutch right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 22:15:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And Andalucia has big cities, tourism and everybody knows it.

Ceuta and Melilla aren't paradises either. A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 18:58:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, that is what US is doing with China. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 18:47:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Once we are in a socialist state, the army is a proletarian army so the people are actually armed. There is no need of people having guns in their homes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 18:17:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Putting their efforts to keeping the throne instead of doing what's good for the region is literally corruption. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 18:06:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would say Extremadura is worse and more abandoned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 18:05:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unemployment, poverty and corruption mainly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 14:18:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 13:32:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Están buenas con cebolla (si te gusta) pero saben solo a cebolla. Para mí la gracia de la tortilla es que sepa a huevo, y para eso tiene que ser sin cebolla y con el huevo poco cuajado.

Pero para gustos los colores. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 12:41:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are both mutually intelligible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 12:20:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Habits are hard to build. The things is that you are aware of it and trying to change it, you're on the right path. The wisdom path is lifelong, you never reach your destiny, the destiny is the path itself.

Don't blame yourself too much when you make mistakes, think about it and try to improve. That is the stoicism, the neverending path of becoming a better and wiser person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 11:19:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rugby player here. American football hits are much more brutal and dangerous, that's why they use those armours. They call it football because it was born as a football code, and it is the main code there. Same happens with australian football.

They enjoy their football, you enjoy your football, stop being such a child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 10:23:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. I like both, but I think you can taste more the flavour without onion. With onion everything tastes like onion (which is nice also). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 10:22:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jamón with tomato and olive oil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 09:48:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice advertising of your book. Caffeine have very good effects for longevity and cognition, and does not harm sleep is used correctly. It has many drawbacks and does not affect every person in the same way, but it is very healthy.

Stop advertising here, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-08 15:18:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did, you can find some things "affordable". But I have no money anyway so hahahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-08 14:48:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was already dreaming with a house in the Alps. What a pity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-08 14:46:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Almost free, or swiss almost free? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-08 13:43:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me suena a chino: "it sounds like chinese". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-08 10:10:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Welcome to the internet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-08 08:18:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Portuguese and Catalan are two of my favourite latin languages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-07 15:43:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People already mentioned Serranía Celtibérica.

I want to add that there is a county in Extremadura called 'Siberia extremeña'. That county and many in that area are very remote (crossing between the provinces of Badajoz, Ciudad Real and Córdoba) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-07 15:33:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Burgundy cross. That flag is so strong and beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-07 09:52:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Spain that wouldn't be the case, as they are not monetary independent and cannot create money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 21:26:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Portugal is just long Galicia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 21:15:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't say anything about forbid. I was just saying how dangerous they can be. But somebody is a bit sensible about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 18:58:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hedonist capitalist propaganda that promotes drugs you mean? Heroin and cocaine have good doses? Most drugs are harmul and can really mess up with your dopamine receptors (and the rest of the body).

We can discuss drug by drug who can have positive effects and are more or less safe. But in general, drugs are really not a toy and can be very harmful.

Look testimonies of lots of people destroyed by heroin. And who can control dosage with drugs that are terribly addictive and mess with your dopamine receptors and you brain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 18:07:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree with you. Of course material conditions are the most important factor in this, but drugs do take an important part. I am not attacking people who consume druga, but those in this sub who talk about drugs as if they were wonderful and good for people. Drugs are pure crap, even if they are not the main problem of the working class, they are a big one.

But I agree with you in all what you said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 17:41:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally agree. What a sub filled with children that think drugs are the left. Drugs are counter revolutionary and very dangerous. Look how they used heroin to destroy worker movements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 17:38:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Drugs harm the body and mind even with moderation, and are a degradant and burgeois way of recreation. A lot of them create physical addiction, really harm your body and your brain. They destroy your dopamine receptors. Humans had raped and killed since we could walk, is that good? Look for a better argument.

And remember how heroin was used to destroy worker movements in the 80/90 destroying a full generation and killing thousand of people? Destroying families, communities, neighbourhoods? Oh but you are addicted and don't accept it. What a selfish and counterrevolutionary attitude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 10:07:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry, did you feel personally insulted? It must be hard to accept that drugs are one of the biggest enemies of the working class while being an addict. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 09:45:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Again, I don't think so (if you didn't experienced heart problems or something). The water won't be that cold with that ambient temperature. For example, in Scandinavia is very common to go into a sauna and then to swim in a frozen lake. I think is totally safe for a healthy person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 09:30:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I, personally, don't any troubles to sleep afterwards. It doesn't excite me too much, just gives me clear mind and body.

Every person is a world, so I would try it some friday or weekend so you won't have any trouble if you doesn't sleep as early as usual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 09:22:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Drugs destroy communities, people and families. Making them legal will solve trafficking problems, but not the problems related to consume. Alcohol was legal in the USSR and they had a really serious problem of alcoholism. Drugs are burgeois, say no to drugs. Stay clean, stay healthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 09:06:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, that is true, but I don't think it makes it communist or accidentally. A lot of people just think billionaires have to pay a lot of taxes and that's it, nothing radical there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 08:50:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good morning everyone!

Is it worth it to do a MSc in Data Science? I finished a BSc in Physics and I am currently doing an internship  that is not really related with the field (I am more of a python developer, and I will do some reliabilty engineering in the future, but I don't really like it and I want to try DS).

I have done some courses on Coursera about Data Science (Applied Data Science in Python from the University of Michigan), but I have no formal education on the matter. I know it isn't enough for a job, but I could get some internship in the field and then find a job. Is it worth it to do first a MSc, or is it better to just look for an internship? In the first case, which masters in Europe are good in the topic?

Thanks a lot guys! Have a good day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-05 18:34:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You don't need to compare to anybody, that denotes a complex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-05 15:13:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why is ACCIDENTALY communist? Can we please upload content related to this sub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-05 10:06:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, not my case. If you drink it only in the morning and have a good sleep schedule, I don't see the problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-05 00:38:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why not both? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-03 13:23:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But in capitalist democracy, you can buy leaders' intentions with lot of money, so is as good as billionaires intentions, that are usually not alligned at all with most of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-02 17:23:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Size is very important in performance, to be fair. But if you only want to have fun and do your best, it doesn't matter your size, you just have to find your place on the field.

On the other hand, if you would like to become professional or something, you need to have a good size or an outstanding technique and mind for rugby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-02 12:27:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Costa del Sol, with some kind of Marbella city full of mafia, rich people and corrupt politicians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-01 14:55:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I totally agree. Much easier to read than Meditations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-01 10:42:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-01 10:41:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mostly, yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 21:15:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Around 900€/m I think. Enough in small cities, not in Madrid or Barcelona. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 21:11:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most spaniards don't recognize the subtle differences in some sounds in English. They think they pronounce it correctly but they don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 16:21:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Extreme measures have to be taken due to those people that don't know how to behave properly. But this will pass soon, stay healthy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 14:42:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We cannot go outside except for basic needs (Spain). Thank you four your tips! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 13:34:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where can you hang then on a flat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 10:11:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-29 22:15:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Toasts with crushed tomato and olive oil, and a coffee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-29 22:14:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love the first one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-29 19:33:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is my favourite one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-29 11:06:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But Ferdinand VII had a massive dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 20:35:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jøë </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 16:42:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is a student city. It has one of the oldest universities of Spain, a big share of its population are students and it has a great atmosphere and is fairly cheap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 13:09:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gracias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 08:37:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Salamanca is an amazing city for students, I am sure you will love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 00:01:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Things only can go better then, stay healthy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 00:00:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I napped way more while I was in the university, so don't worry about that. But working full time makes it very hard. Where are you thinking to study? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 21:12:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are some good things too, we have to enjoy them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 20:40:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are illiterate people everywhere, just ignore those ignorants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 20:26:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Many many people in Spain think that. It's so annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 20:24:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish we had more siestas. Today I took one because I am working remotely and that shit feels good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 20:23:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That the weather is always good and everything is sun and beach. Spain landscapes and climate vary a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 14:20:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The state? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 21:09:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love that elegant finishing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 15:18:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would say just: "uso mi celular/móvil/teléfono veinte minutos al día". I would use "al" instead of "cada", but both are correct.

And the "por" sounds really weird to me (from Spain), but I don't know if that's something normal in Latin America, or just an anglicism.

EDIT: I read it again, do you mean using the phone (apps, surfing...) or talking on the phone? In the second case, I would say, "hablo por teléfono veinte minutos al día". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 15:08:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was funny the first time, but not anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 14:51:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not the best time to post this, but it is good to know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 13:34:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Prince Charles tests positive for COVID-19 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 11:58:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 11:37:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tough reality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 11:37:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He maybe just want to have fun and he doesn't need to prove anything to anybody? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 19:55:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am sure you wouldn't be half as rich if your country wasn't a tax haven in the middle of Europe. But who knows, maybe I am wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 17:49:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Switzerland wouldn be nothing without the rest of Europe's money in their banks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 15:43:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And why is Scotland there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 15:19:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A slim fit T-shirt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 07:51:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Neuken in de keuken </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 18:11:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seneca </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 14:46:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But it is tasty as hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 14:45:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same, olive oil is wonderful, but it doesn't fit every dish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 14:44:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Almost always. Sometimes I use butter or other oils if it fits the dish I am cooking better than olive oil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 13:48:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure, what I meant is that is not an optimal fitness, because is also emphasized in mental toughness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 13:24:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same in Spain, English speaking countries and culture are referred to as anglo-saxons for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 08:25:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ciudad Real as a capital is worth the bordergore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 08:23:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know in the US, but I have a friend who is in the Spanish Army and the training, apart from conditioning, seems to be focused in mental toughness more than fitness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-22 17:50:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Norway is the country with more tests per 100,000 inhabitants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-21 13:56:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A kettlebell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-21 13:39:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just normal french amateur rugby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-20 21:01:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where are you from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-20 19:48:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The whole concept of hospital CEO is really disturbing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-20 13:09:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not if they are not deformed. And 15 weeks for what? Being with your son must be boring, working is much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-20 08:05:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-19 22:37:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Always talking, never doing. Fuck off Mr. Musk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-19 09:00:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am Soanish. Even though English tourists are specially problematic, I think is a tourist attitude in general, specially when visiting "poorer" countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-19 08:46:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True, specially the -ing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 20:22:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Something like that I think. With the germans is everything finished in "en". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 20:05:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In spanish is very typical to mock it finishing spanish words in "tion". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 19:12:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't know what was that. It is amazing, but right now there are no subscriptions available. I will try the free version for the moment, if it is good, I will subscribe when I can. Thanks a lot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 15:41:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, once he passes it (and maybe you), you won't catch it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 15:39:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stay safe! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 15:34:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish I had bought it one before the quarantine (I'm spanish and we are on lockdown). But as soon as it is finished, with the money I would save not going out, I will buy a gaming PC for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 15:30:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks!

This is really awesome. I need a better computer to play this game, it always get slow when the population grows a little bit :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 15:17:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You did that with mods or can be actually done in vanilla? It is awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 13:53:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same in Europe. People never learn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 11:43:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He also renounced to his private inheritance. Well, isn't the crown itself a private inheritance? He could renounce to it too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 10:08:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it can create a situation where the revolution could be possible, but the working class is not organized enough. Maybe we see some protests and revolts that improves our lifes a bit. But I don't see plausible a socialist revolution with no strong communist parties or organizations. Let's see and try to make our movement grow these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 18:11:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beautiful, but misleading. It doesn't show very high density cities. For example, it seems like Madrid has less population than Porto, and this far to be true.

As a criticism, I think you should use another method that shows better the real population.

Anyway, it is pleasing to see :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 15:40:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 12:39:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought something similar (but I'm spanish), but love keeps me at home. Thanks for sharing your experience, I really apreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 12:14:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would do exactly the same if I were you. More time is better than more money. How is it to be a freelance there? Was it easy? Do you work previously in a company? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 12:10:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You must be rich there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How to create a SQLCipher for PyQt5? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 11:28:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am having some troubles in order to build a SQLCipher driver for PyQt5. I checked some ways of building a Qt SQLCipher driver plugin, but I am fairly new to this world and I only know Python, so I don't understand it nor understand how to make it work for PyQt5 without using plugins. I also saw that I building a driver as a class is possible, but I don't have any idea of how to build this driver. I have some disconnected information about drivers, Qt and PyQt5, but I just can't figure out how to put it all together. I also tried to investigate how the other SQL drivers are built in PyQt5, but I only found some wraps around C++ that I don't understand.

Anybody can help me to build a SQLCipher that I can use in PyQt5, as a Python class or any other different ways? I am having so many problems to understand all the tutorials I found, it's being a nightmare.

My OS is Windows 10 64 bits.

Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 09:14:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rivera is nobody right now, which I am very pleased. Casado is another guy that I don't really know how he got to the presidency of the first party of the opposition. Didn't they really have nobody better? And Arrimadas is awful too. Apart from ideologies, politicians in Spain, but mostly on the right, are really awful and incompetent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 09:00:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Abascal is such an idiot I never considered him an important politician. Then I remember he has 50 deputies in the Congress... These are strange and hard times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 08:51:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure, I was talking about Urkullu and Torra who complained about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 08:40:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure, I don't want to say that you must forget about that. But for the moment, both Catalonia and Euskadi are part of Spain, and a unique and strong government for all the country is needed and better than anything else. When everything passes, the normal political life will come back. But right now, we need unity of ALL of the state as some of you call it (:P). Stay safe, we will fight again as usual soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 08:09:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think southern Europeans are behaving much better this time than those from the north. Maybe we are not that lazy and incompetent after all, and there are some prejudices against us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 08:06:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some people are still more concerned about their self-government rights that about the virus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 08:04:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here in Spain everybody thinks that Spain's different and we do nothing good and so on. But this time I think we are behaving more or less (with some exceptions, but watching Swiss, German and Dutch people acting the same way makes me think we are not that incompetent after all) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-16 18:52:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why every country thinks they are special and they won't face the same problem? Dude learn from the errors of others, this is serious. Every country should start implementing measures as soon as possible to save as many people as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-16 18:40:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry, can you make a list of animals that people can eat please? Animal eating gatekeeping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-16 18:38:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And the two last pandemics of flu originate by eating chicken and pork? This is just racist nonse. Who are you to judge which animals can or cannot been eaten? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-16 12:22:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Estaría bien aclarar eso, porque puede llevar a confusión a los que están aprendiendo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-16 12:21:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, not the only one to be fair. And you the chinese should remember it. Of course I am talking about the Opium wars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-15 10:36:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congratulations man, you look awesome. Keep going on! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-15 09:35:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ha sido la forma de formularlo que me ha resultado confusa. Pero igualmente, yo sin ningún contexto, entiendo que quedar es reunirse así de primeras. Luego depende del contexto y las preposiciones asociadas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-14 23:21:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo me he hecho un server con unos amigos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-14 23:16:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fun fact: porro means joint in spanish (the funny one) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-14 17:26:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am spanish and I never heard that use of "quedar". I heard as to agree with "en": "quedamos en vernos a las 4". But for sure, at least in Spain, quedar means also to meet: "Quedamos a las 4".

When it means to stay if when it is used in a reflexive way, "quedarse": "Me quedo en casa". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-14 14:58:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like Bernie too, but he is not omnipotent. Here in Europe we have most of the things he want to implement and things are tough anyway, it is not that easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-14 11:36:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure, but Sanders couldn't save the country from a pandemic, just control it better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-14 10:11:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, countries with better system like Norway or Denmark are infected with a lot of cases per million inhabitant. Of course Sanders policies would help, but he cannot stop the spread of the virus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-13 12:59:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Los casos ya bajan cada día y solo hay unos 10000 casos activos. Están ya prácticamente fuera. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-12 17:05:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A virus is not a tiny microbe lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-12 15:48:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But was he obsessed (even as a teenagee)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-12 12:53:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Y si se contagia media población y hay miles de muertes, entonces sí que se va a ir a la mierda la economía. Es una medida para controlarlo y que todo siga normal, en lugar de forzar la máquina por no perder dinero a corto plazo, y que a la larga sea todo muchísimo peor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 14:59:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice. Europe and the US are doomed since a lot of time, it is just a matter of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 13:11:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ya, pero la gente trabaja </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 20:24:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> La gente es mongola </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 14:49:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bieeeeeeen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 15:43:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He remembers me to Mariano Rajoy, ex spanish PM. He doesn't have dementia, but said many many incongruent things on TV and the Congress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 14:35:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> North-center. I would say Segovia and Ávila. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 09:42:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have no faith at all in Sanders, sure. I just think it can shift the political spectrum a bit to the left and to implement the basic policies that those we have in Europe. But for sure, he will always defend the USA oligarchy interests and its imperialism.

Keep fighting american comrades! Greetings from Spain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 22:58:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, you can get a job. Not so easy in Spain, Portugal or Greece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 22:55:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I would prefer being from Lichtenstein (no offense, is just they are filthy rich) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 22:53:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where are you from? Because in southern Europe, situation is very different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 12:33:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> El problema no es el miedo a contagiarse, tienen miedo de no poder disfrutar del viaje porque todo esté cerrado. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 12:19:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is there any subreddit about how the Bible or Christian religion in general is related to communism? I think using Bible quotes and so on could be effective to distribute leftist view into pious population. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 12:16:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The thing about this happens only in this country happens everywhere I think. It's amazing how evert country thinks they're very special. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 09:39:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dutch I think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 09:32:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pedro Sánchez, by far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 21:44:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sparkling water tastes like white noise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 21:37:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right now everything is normal and there are no restrictions. All is open and functioning normally. Cases are rising fast, so I cannot say it won't change in the future. But so far, everything is fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 12:46:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We spaniards are also like that. We all say bad things about Spain all the time, but us and only us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-06 08:06:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People should not use genocide so lightly. Not everything is a genocide, and this it is not a genocide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 14:34:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In most of Latin America, only "cómo se llama" is used. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-04 18:42:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rosalía? Enrique Iglesias? I don't really know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-04 18:41:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sadly, I would say Enrique Iglesias. Rosalía also maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-04 13:42:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/AskHistorians </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-04 09:35:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Qué pasada. Tengo que ir a Cantabria de una vez. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-04 08:29:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ¿Dónde es? Qué envidia me das ahora mismo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 22:07:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's the first sentence of the USSR anthem (I don't understand anything but I know how it sounds hahahaha) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 21:33:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A small percentage, much smaller than in Nazi Germany. People were much poorer back then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 20:11:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The people who died weren't those who trade slaves. What you said is simply horrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-01 20:29:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is there other kind of labour? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-01 17:22:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't forget Gibraltar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-01 12:50:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. I have some preferences of course but I think every country has something worth visiting/experiencing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-28 20:57:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-28 07:42:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think there is no best city, just a lot of good cities. Some cities from Spain I would recommend are Segovia, Toledo and Albarracín.

Of course, there are much more, and probably better by some standars, but those are three I like a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-27 21:50:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Extremadura and any of the two Castiles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-27 14:16:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am so jealous rn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-27 14:16:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Madrid, 45 minutes combining walk+bus in the morning and walk+metro in the afternoon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 21:04:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 😢 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 16:48:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish he was Stalin tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 12:37:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you mean Libya flag? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 11:55:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To the glorious DPRK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 11:45:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pol Pot american version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 09:01:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not as much as people think. The Church and religion is very powerful due to historical reasons, but people are not very religious in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-25 20:49:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally agree. Last weekend I saw a femenine spanish first division match, and was way more enjoyable than the men's matches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-25 20:44:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sometimes these things just don't work out. It is not anyone's fault. You had great moments together and you will feel great again soon, these sad times will pass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-25 17:50:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It kept Franco in power just to oppose communism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-25 16:36:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eating carbohydrates before sleeping can reduce the cortisol and stress related to exercise, and making you sleep easier. A little bit of carbohydrates are good for sleeping in general, but mostly in this case.

Also reducing your body and room temperature before sleeping induces sleep. Have a coldish-warm shower can help to reduce your body temperature (not too cold though, that could stress your body and make a reaction). And try to open the windows of your room before sleeping to to reduce the room temperature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-24 21:20:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mercadona is a God here. The true spanish religion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-24 13:49:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bed is only for sleeping, no movies allowed. Not even sex.
ONLY SLEEP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 19:11:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How broadly is belarussian used in Belarus btw? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 19:07:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too! It is a treasure we have here in Spain, I would love to learn it if I had the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 18:55:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very broadly in all the regions with a regional languages. I am very proud of how Spain manages and protects minority languages comparing to other european countries (althought it could always be better) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-22 21:28:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't doing anything else. I hate adult life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-22 20:21:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My two favourites nuts together. I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-22 20:19:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Intermittent fasting makes losing weight fairly easy, at least for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 20:30:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rugby player here! I wish rugby would be more popular within the working class. Here in Spain, at least in Madrid, is mainly played by rich people. But its popularity is growing very fast, and it is reaching more workers, so I hope things would change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 09:47:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being focus on the food in order to enjoy it more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-20 19:00:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't watch TV or series or whatever while eating. Just eat. Enjoy the food. Chew as many times as possible. Make some small pauses.

In general, do it slow and conciously, with no distractions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-20 17:31:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And the rest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-20 15:17:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow the colonialist US government says that something that is against their interest is bad for economy. That only means that is bad for US oligarchy, not to South Africans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-20 08:14:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Burgundy Cross of the Spanish Empire. Damn, that flag was gorgeous.

Also, the banner of Castile and Leon (currenrly the flag of the region) is lovely too.

I don't like todays flag, to be honest. That big yellow stripe in the middle, and the non-centered coat lf arms on it. Maybe it could be nice without the CoA, but I don't really like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-19 18:27:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not in Champions League </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-19 10:52:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 22:30:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Son datos objetivos de mayor númeeo de referencias en Wikipedia. Son las que son y punto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 22:16:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He deserves it.

Edit: sarcasm omg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 15:45:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I try to do the most out of my life too, but don't talk as the current state of things is inevitable. Life CAN be different and system is fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 15:44:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everytime I complain about work, people are like: "yeah, like everybody, so don't complain". That's is exactly the problem, everybody is fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 15:42:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah be with your gf a couple of times a week  and play soccer on sundays while spending 50h in working+commuting (don't forget house duties). Life is truly amazing, how I couldn't see I had a couple of hours of spare time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 12:54:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 12:47:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Greece. An island if I could choose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 10:26:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is acceptance and adaptation to things you cannot change or control, but we can change society, just not immediately. Having a stoic focus on how to build a better society every day ignoring can we cannot directly control and focusing on working on what is under our control (afiliating to syndicate or party, build solidarity with our coworkers, creating class conscience) and having a good mood an hope instead of be angry every single day and doing nothing about it is a good focus on the problem.

You just have to value what's important and what's under your control, and do your part without wasting energy in things that you cannot change in the short term. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 09:43:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stoicism is a very good philisophy, but surely it can be used by the power to make us stop complaining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-17 22:00:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Genio y figura </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-17 21:54:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Designing realistic and enjoyable plans and activities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-17 17:33:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, 70+! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-17 15:08:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's pretty good, but I never used any other extensively to compare. And if you under 26 it is really cheap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-17 10:58:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. Faster or slower, you can reach every place in Madrid easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-17 08:01:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depending on how thick is the accent. Sometimes it is really hard to understand, but usually it is fine. Just  keep hearing and mimicking how native speakers talk, and you eventually would get a nice accent.

It is nice not to be ashamed with your accent, but I think it is important to try to reduce it as much as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-16 12:16:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or polla in Spain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-15 09:37:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cringe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-15 09:34:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We just want to live instead of be productive for our boss. I don't care at all if the productivity of the company raises. People like you are the reason we still work so many hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-15 01:44:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's THE SHOW from Spain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-14 18:12:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Es una lotería. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-14 15:32:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nevó bastante esa semana, pero se derritió bastante rápido. El sábado aun había mucha en cuanto subías un poco para la sierra, pero el domingo había muchísima menos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-14 08:56:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No sugar, YES MILK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-14 08:38:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unos sitios más que otros, pero la verdad es que en general está bonita. ¿De dónde eres, fellow manchego? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-14 06:58:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Del 25 de enero de este año. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Rascafría, Comunidad de Madrid </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 22:12:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 21:51:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What you never did a WC irl? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 21:07:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, you would say "adiós, me voy al gimnasio".

But if you are on your way to the gym and for example your mum asks you where are you, you would say: "estoy yendo al gimnasio". Do you understand the horizon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 19:40:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You would say "estoy yendo" if you are going to the gym in that exact moment. But if you mean that you're going to go in a near future, It would be "me voy" or "voy". The "-ing" tense in English has a broader meaning that in Spanish, so you have to be careful.

Don't hesitate in asking again until you understand it, because I feel I am not explaining it properly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 18:37:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Madrid here. Pretty good. Very very cheap por students (20€/month for a radio of more than a 100km, including parts of other provinces like Toledo and Guadalajara) and for old people (like 12€/month for Madrid city), but I think the general tariff is way more expensive (like 50€ for the city of Madrid), but I am not sure of the exact price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 18:34:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok I misunderstood the question, now I see it.

Well, "voy a comer" is "I'm going to eat".
But, with a place, "voy a casa" is "I go home". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 18:09:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> USSR for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 18:01:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I go to vs. I am going to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 14:27:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn your feet are gorgeous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 16:43:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It took me a couple of minutes figuring what was wrong with the map. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 10:03:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice post!

The only flaw I see is that you don't support your statements with sources, and that makes you lose credibility. Why should believe you instead of other people that writes the opposite? Internet is full of fake facts, so good sources are always good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 08:13:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So true. Spain is way wilder than Span, sure. But is way bigger and has around half the population. So obviously it has more space for wilderness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 21:31:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Envy. Spaniards prefer the others to have a worse life instead of improve theirs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 21:20:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In general, I think the USA are able to do the best and the worst in almost every aspect of life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 15:38:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Working 40h+/week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 14:04:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He is a millionaire. I think he probably consumes much more than many of us together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 08:27:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do something similar. I think about how I would manage a football team if I had one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 15:23:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is one guy that is always drunk and sleeping inside the Sol metro station, and doesn't seem able to speak properly, so I thought about him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 14:55:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! Have a good day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 10:04:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is nothing special and it is always crowded, specially before Christmas. Was he a homeless man? I think I know who you are talking  about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 09:21:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You were good before, but now you are awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 08:39:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 08:38:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally agree with you, but I think it is a must anyway. Madrid has many very beautiful places and people keep going to Sol, which is the place that I hate the most in all the city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 08:22:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do you say that? It is not best thing of Madrid but definitely is a really beautiful street with iconic buildings. It is more full of tourists than junkies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 08:20:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That we are lazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 08:20:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Terrorists jokes are a thing also in Spain with the Basque Country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 08:19:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't know I was romanian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 08:17:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just be careful when you use the balcony ok? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 08:15:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I heard people from the north of Spain saying that Africa starts in the Ebro, so I guess it is similar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 08:08:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a very widespread thought in Spain and I hate it. All the Romanians I know are really nice and hardworking  people.

But definitely, leaving food on a plate is way worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 17:58:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Something that helped me a lot to lose weight was reducing the number of meals. Once you are used to eat twice a day instead of five or so, it is much easier to eat less. Also, you can try to combine it with intermittent fasting (r/intermittentfasting).

And focus on quality of food, don't obsess with macronutrients or carbs. Eat "real" food, not processed junk. Eat plenty of fruits, vegetables, good meat, fish, eggs, nuts. Sleeping well and being hydrated (with water preferably) also helps a lot to reduce hunger, lose weight and gain muscle. Try to keep a bottle of water with you. If you think water is "boring" you can always drink infusions. Tea and black coffee can also help you to reduce hunger (if you try IF, they make your fasting period much easier)

And other people said, you can do a lot of things without a gym until you gain a little bit of confidence about your body. Being a teenager makes you usually very insecure yourself, it is pretty normal so don't worry too much about it, you'll eventually learn to don't give a fuck about what other people thinks.

 It is also very important to like the diet and the exercise you are doing, even if it is not optimal. The most important thing is to keep adherence to a healthy lifestyle, time will finally do it works if you build good habits. But that needs time, so don't worry if you fail sometimes or improve slower than you thought. Life is long and it is the long run what matters. Find healthy foods that you like, that keep you saciated. Find a sports that you love doing, find some friends to do it with them, which also helps you a lot to keep doing it.

As a personal recommendation, I have been playing rugby for a long time. I think it is a super inclusive sport, with great values and sportmanship, that also values very different types of bodies, specially big people being useful for the game.

I believe in you comrade, don't hesitate to ask me any question you may have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 08:55:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the worst chart I've ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-06 22:31:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Spain is like in Russia. My aunt sent me 5 of those daily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-06 13:01:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And Castilla-La Mancha or Extremadura? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-06 13:00:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Todo está mal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-04 21:18:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tía, but sometimes you can use tío as an expression, not necessarily to refering someone, like:
"Tío qué calor hace" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-04 09:14:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol soy idiota JAJAJAJAJAJAJAJA

A mí me sonaba raro pero digo puede ser no sé catalán. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-04 08:19:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If she chose you being much hotter than you, damn you must be amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-04 08:08:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or Spain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-04 07:13:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> El título es en portugués y es parte del meme original, aunque este mene vaya sobre el catalán. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> There are more Irish people living in the USA than in Ireland </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 08:30:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-02 11:55:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So we have to return half of Spain because it was conquered in the middle ages? What is the difference between Melilla and Granada for example then?

Melilla (Ceuta was stolen from the portuguese that is true, but the same applies afterwards) never had colonial institutions and was always managed as any other spanish city. Most of the muslim population that is living right now there are recent immigration. Just because is on the other coast of the Mediterranean doesn't mean things are different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-02 11:38:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ceuta and Melilla are no colonies. I am tired of this comparison. They are as spanish as the mainland. Conquered 500 yesrs ago, and never had a colonial status. So if Ceuta is a colony, so is Granada? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-01 23:54:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same in Madrid with some tropical birds. The local government is trying to remove them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-01 19:34:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having a tax haven in one of the poorest areas of Spain is not good either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-30 19:15:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same with boobs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 22:37:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahahaha well, probably this will happen. But I will try at least! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 15:26:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rail transport, and I work in a signalling division. Thanks a lot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 14:43:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually, I meant those kind of books instead of pure DS books. Some soft skills/domain books that can be useful to DS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 14:40:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I meant more things like big picture and soft skills, but useful to DS. Can you recommend something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 14:18:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's not true. Those things work. For example tobacco consumption is going down since restrictions and taxes were implemented, and more information about how nocive it can be given.

Also, drug comsumption is much higher there where people don't have any other entertainment or things to do. So providing alternatives is highly effective.

Can you proof that statement? Because it seems total nonsense to be honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 14:11:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I expressed myself bad. I wanted to say that we shouldn't aim to legalize more drugs, but to keep insisting in how these "soft drugs" can destroy lives, and providing entertainment alternatives and fight against mafias, limit where you can buy/consume alcohol and tobacco, limit advertising...

I agree with you that just prohibiting doesn't work, but being more permissive doesn't work either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 13:46:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe we should ask why don't we prohibite tobacco and alcohol instead of legalizing more drugs. There are no soft drugs, all of them are dangerous and can destroy lives and community.

EDIT: I expressed myself very badly. Check out below for an explanation (maybe you disagree anyways, but it is better explained) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 10:45:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The XIX century in Spain is total chaos. Tens of government changes, 6 different constitutions, tens of military coups... So we just simplify it a lot and choose the most important characteristics of each period. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Books to read while commuting </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 09:47:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello everyone!

I am currently a data science trainee who just started in this amazing world. I have a 45-60 minutes commute everyday that I usually spend reading (most of it). I am looking for some books to read on the way, that can teach me something useful but are "easy enough" to read on the bus/metro.

Thank you in advance!

EDIT: I didn't express myself correctly, I was refering mainly to books about soft skills, concepts and the big picture in general that can be useful to DS (as some of the answers pointed out).

EDIT 2: I cannot thank you enough guys! I didn't expect so many answers, I will take a look to all of them as soon as I have time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 08:37:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello everyone!

I am currently a data science trainee who just started in this amazing world. I have a 45-60 minutes commute everyday that I usually spend reading (most of it). I am looking for some books to read on the way, that can teach me something useful but are "easy enough" to read on the bus/metro.

Thank you in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-28 08:55:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure, but OP currently mentioned it in the post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-28 08:09:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You forgot a very important one: galician, spoken in Galicia and in some areas of León and Asturias. It is very similar to portuguese as they were the same language in the middle ages.

Also, there are some other minor and non official languages such as asturiano/astur-leonés and aranogese. Also in Melilla many people speak cherja, a bereber language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-27 20:09:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is my birthday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-27 11:07:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alcohol or alcohol hand sanitizer is what I found best for eliminating those smells. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-27 09:14:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Smoking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-25 17:23:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And Al-Andalus is part of the history of Spain. I would consider the Catholic Kings' reign as the birth of the modern spanish nation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-25 08:56:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All of them except from the Napoleon occupation I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 09:50:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is portuguese. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-23 18:41:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Candidates to the guillotine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-23 18:38:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This made me laugh in a rough day :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-23 16:04:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They also don't understand the meaning of friendly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-23 11:35:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was stating that the two cases were totally different, nothing else. Other than that, I am not saying that Spain is not guilty of other crimes. Of course it is.

The problem with Gibraltar is that is a tax haven in our own backyard, next to one of the poorest places of the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-23 10:57:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, my bad then. Maybe it is not the best argument to use. But I keep insisting that the other arguments are still valid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-23 10:44:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry, I misunderstood you. What I meant is that there are people living in every conquered city and that it is not a factor for considering it a colony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-23 09:49:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Islam came in the 8th century, but Morocco didn't exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-23 09:23:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, and there were people in Granada too. Why are they different? Conquests has happened all the time. But conquering a city doesn't make it a colony automatically. Why do these cities belong to Morocco when they has been spanish more time than Morocco exists, when they have never been colonies and why are they different from the conquered mainland Spain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-23 08:49:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That has nothing to do. Ceuta and Melilla are as spanish as the mainland. Being in another continent doesn't mean to be a colony. They were conquered almost at the same time as Granada, and since then, they never had a colony status in the country, but the same as any other spanish city.

On the other hand, Gibraltar is a tax haven, never had a normal status within the UK  and it is considered a colony by the UN.

Things are much more complex than you think.

EDIT 2: It seems that I was wrong with the foundation of Morocco. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-22 08:07:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are a very good and wise person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-21 09:33:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mostly while chatting, but can be used also in a casual conversation. If you want to sound more spanish, you can use "Vale". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-21 09:31:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As it should be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-19 21:22:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spanish China </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-19 16:13:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ole mi Españita </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-19 11:06:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> De-industralization due to the European Union. Our economic model is based on tourism and services. We became a party and vacation place for norther europeans at the same time we were losing almost all of our industry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-18 20:35:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Higher education is so good because they are very well funded and they bring talent from all over the world. They just have very good facilities and teachers because of money, so that brings good students in also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-18 00:50:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not having to work 41h a week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-13 17:29:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Caballo (horse) - heroin
Perico/farlopa (?) - cocaine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 19:34:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally agree with that. I think I don't understand the context fully as a european. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 19:26:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An anthem with no lyrics is absurd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 15:14:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me parece tan fascinante que no me puedo ni enfadar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 09:59:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Drunk people who likes to jump off of balconies and don't know that suncream exists. Also that they don't know how to eat properly.

Topics aside, most englishmen I know are really nice and funny people.

EDIT: Typos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-10 22:45:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Britain and France won both World Wars, so they wrote the history that treats them fairlier. British Empire did things in their colonies pretty similar to those did by the nazis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-10 10:11:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Andalusian accent varies a lot from west to east. Sevilla's accent has nothing to do with Granada's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-09 16:50:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My kind of playthrough. Just press play and wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-08 13:20:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This shouldn't depend of any company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-05 00:16:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> U r gay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-03 10:28:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am interested in working from Spain as remote (but being spanish), due to the low salaries here. Does everybody know which restrictions are there within the EU to work remote fron both EU and non-EU companies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-01 12:29:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same happened to me with alcohol. Stopped a couple of times, but somehow I started drinking again due to a self-imposed social pressure. Now I gained confidence and I don't care about what others may think. People sometimes call me boring or an old person for not drinking and going to sleep soon, but if you don't care, they finally accept your new lifestyle and nobody gives a fuck.

Good night, sleep well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-01 12:15:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I tried to do those same 3 habits (more or less) some time ago, and after failing many times (specially with alcohol), I am fit, sober and well rested. So don't worry if you fail one, two or many times, if you keep trying, you will eventually do it. I believe in you man, you can do it, and I can tell you that you'll feel amazingly after that, both phisically and mentally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-31 13:02:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do that and unite them with roundabouts. It gives a natural shape, at least a spanish one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-29 20:30:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cringe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-29 20:28:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why is this downvoted? Africa is big as fuck, there are plenty of countries and some of them are not  dangerous. It is not the same going to Somalia than to Ghana or Botswana. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 19:59:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is american football very popular there or it is just genetics? I know rubgy in Polynesia is the main sport, so it doesn't feel so weird that there are so many of them in rugby, but I have no clue about football there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 18:55:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Polynesian genetics are fucking amazing. Those guys are fast, big and strong. Rugby is full of them, I didn't know there were so many playing american football too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 00:19:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dutch Colombia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-24 13:46:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Spain people usually wait for the three wise men ("Los Reyes Magos") the night of the 5th of January. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-23 15:40:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You need movement during the day, not standing or sitting in the same position for that long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-19 10:59:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >when u also want to increase literacy, sometimes you know... you have to kill million people

r/shitvictorianssay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-17 17:32:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think most of the world is sadly like the US... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-17 08:31:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take a look at the Wim Hof method. I didn't try it personally, but I heard great things about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-15 21:33:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> $1,51 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-13 23:57:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, he was Spanish, then European. I wouldn't consider him Hispanic. But anyway those weird classifications about hispanic, asian, white etc. only make senses in the US. Race has nothing to do with culture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-12 10:26:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So nice! I will try to read it later and refresh my german, that looks really clean and neat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-09 19:43:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure, I am much wiser now, I could avoid tons of mistakes and have a much better life by the age I am now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-08 14:48:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They would save a lot of money both in salaries and cocaine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-07 11:15:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't know that gifs had sound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-06 15:26:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> GOMAD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-06 10:36:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which andalusian accent doesn't pronounce the R? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-05 18:38:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did when I was a teenager. As a young native spanish speaker, it was kind of dense to me, so I think it must be a hard reading for a non-native. But I am pretty sure that with patience, you could learn a lot from it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-01 18:56:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Roman: Ey Niko, wanna go bowling? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-01 17:10:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does he even play in Spain? I never heard him speaking Spanish... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-28 08:33:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is fucking amazing! A little bit of discipline and being concious about your well-being can do wonders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-21 07:47:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably the first one. Australia is massive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-19 17:47:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Que algo merece la pena. Por ejemplo: "te renta mazo ir al Campo del Moro", significa que merece la pena ir al Campo del Moro (y realmente merece la pena, es una preciosidad y es gratis :) ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-19 10:03:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A thing we do in Spain is simply black coffe (an espresso) with ice. Its cold and softer taste would fit perfectly to you in the summer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-12 12:38:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mucha fuerza a todos los latinoamericanos. Desde que EEUU se ha estado alejando poco a poco de Oriente Medio y Europa, ha centrado su política exterior en el Pacífico y América, por lo que os esperan tiempos duros. No os rindáis ante el imperio, tienen los días contados. Aguante desde España. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-12 08:27:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Qué malo Evo, dedicando la riqueza de Bolivia al bien común en lugar de dejar a su familia que se enriquezca >:( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 10:13:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very nice animation! Are the colonies of each state including on the graph or just the european population?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 09:55:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry for the delay, I was busy this weekend. Here you have: [https://github.com/amunozo/population-by-municipalities](https://github.com/amunozo/population-by-municipalities)

I will try to find data about more countries in Europe and create a much more richer map in the future, including some other aspects of population, so if you find something it would be good data if you share it with me :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 09:55:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry for the delay, I was busy this weekend. Here you have: [https://github.com/amunozo/population-by-municipalities](https://github.com/amunozo/population-by-municipalities)

I will try to find data about more countries in Europe and create a much more richer map in the future, including some other aspects of population, so if you find something it would be good data if you share it with me :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-10 09:15:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least is no the number 88. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-09 20:10:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, I've been busy these days, but I will share the script, and try to run the data also if I have time :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-09 08:58:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, I hate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-08 20:12:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He is doing exactly the opposite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-08 13:53:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-08 13:50:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is so innecesary that I really love it! Good job, this looks pretty nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-08 11:02:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whatever you prefer! It is an easy code, the only "problem" is to find the data, but that is easy too with enough patient and luck ;)

I just used a list of municipalities in Spain by population, latitude and longitude, and then did a scatter plot with the size asociated to the population. When I arrive home I will send you the code in a dm if you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 21:38:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I promise I will upload a better one with the Canary Islands on it hahahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 17:28:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will upload a map with Portugal data also in the future ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 17:27:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am really sorry about this, I will upload a new and better map including Canarias, I promise (I don't know when, tho). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 15:28:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Obrigado! I will look for it. At the moment I only found age related data in Spain for cities bigger than 50.000 inhabitants. I will continue trying :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 15:07:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you can find some data like the one I used (and with the average age also) in Portugal, I can add them to a map too. I think it would be easier for you to find (if you are portuguese as I am assuming) because looking for it in portuguese would be way easier. I will give you credit if I reupload it with the data from Portugal too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 12:54:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That data would be harder to get, but once with it, it should be nice to introduce a colormap relating to the average age of the municipality. I will try to find it, because that is actually a very cool idea! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Municipios españoles por población </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 12:27:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 12:16:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Made using Python's libraries pandas and matplotlib, population data from the INE (Instituto Nacional de Estadística) and latitude and longitude data from Google Maps.

EDIT: I forgot to add the Canary Islands because at first I wanted to omit them in order to manipulate the graph more easily. I think I would upload again the map but with the average age data that  u/xamavi proposed and with the Canary Islands.

EDIT 2: I uploaded the code and the data I used to a github (my first one so it is pretty basic hahahaha).  If you have any doubt or problem, ask me and I will text you as soon as possible :):

[https://github.com/amunozo/population-by-municipalities](https://github.com/amunozo/population-by-municipalities) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [OC] Municipalities in Spain by population </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 12:16:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 10:24:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Recuerdo estar 20 minutos solo en un restaurante en Alemania porque un amigo con el que fui a cenar no tenía dinero en efectivo y estuvo buscando un cajero mientras yo me quedaba ahí para que no pensasen que nos queríamos ir sin pagar. En España es cierto que en ciertos sitios se ponen un poco puntillosos, pero es mucho más fácil pagar con tarjeta que en Alemania. También es verdad que vivo en Madrid, pero en Ciudad Real, de donde soy originalmente, tampoco tengo muchos problemas.

Ahora, mi hermano vive en Noruega y no usa efectivo absolutamente nunca. He ido con mi madre ya unas 4 veces a visitarle y no hemos cambiado dinero ni una vez, siempre con tarjeta todo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 09:24:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just some vandalism that a worker will have to clean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 09:02:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Estuve un año de Erasmus en Alemania y me dio la sensación de que allí el efectivo era mucho más habitual. Muchos sitios no permitían pagar con tarjeta, y si lo hacían era con un mínimo (lo cual era una excusa para pedir un par de pintas más). Sin embargo, en España no suelo tener ningún problema para pagar con tarjeta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-05 11:51:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Finally some country concerned with climate change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-24 10:33:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Madrid makes problems even bigger, because it acts as a kind of black hole, atracting all people from the interior. There are more people in Madrid metro area than in Castilla-La Mancha and Castilla y León and Extremadura together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 15:36:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is not the topic. This is not the appropiate subreddit to discuss that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 15:24:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And anyway, it is content not related to this subreddit, so it shouldn't be here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 15:19:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't see Reddit protesting against all the injustices in the world. Just against China. Of course it is politics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 13:42:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice karma farming with things not related with the subreddit. I would be pretty sure that if I submit a post about the Ecuador protests, or something else not related to this subreddit, everybody will complain. Why isn't banned for ignoring the rules? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 10:53:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is irrelevant to this discussion. This is not the place to post political propaganda. I am sure that if the propaganda were about any other not so mainstream protests, everybody would agree with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 09:46:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is not related to the subreddit. Please submit your political propaganda to the appropiate subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 09:16:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chile, you gained some weight, you look amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 09:14:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's what she said.

Edit: shit, somebody said it before.

Great and clean setup, I love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 08:59:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totalmente de acuerdo. Los kurdos fueron la marioneta de los americanos, y en cuanto han dejado de ser útiles, les han dado la espalda. Lo mejor es la unidad de Siria frente al imperialismo que los mercenarios de EEUU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 18:56:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, but that wasn't true, I just wanted to point out that the things are not that easy.

Nice. But you better invest your time in other things. I will. It was a pleasure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 18:42:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You don't know what I do. You seem to be so busy commenting my posts though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 18:30:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When the youth unemployment goes down under 35% and the wages are enough to pay the rising prices of rent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 18:11:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> !!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 18:05:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here we have to take into account the bourgeoise as a revolutionary class back in the middle and modern ages. It is not only a term of profitability, but also the action of a revolutionary act. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 18:01:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Better than Joe's pussy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 17:15:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The same in the west. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 15:02:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 14:58:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, wikipedia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 14:33:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He didn't kill 70 million. Most of those deaths were fault of the insane trade embargo between 1950 and 1972, impossed by the USA because of China's intervention in the Korean War. Some policies introduced by Mao were not good, but it was a desperate situation that required desperated actions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 14:19:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi mum! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 14:08:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mao turned China from a medieval country to a world power. Of course I think he is a good person. An excellent one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 13:48:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They are helping African countries much more than french or british companies do. Their loans are fairer and they contribute to their economy. Without any coup d'etat as France in many african countries or the USA in Latin America. You are such a hypocrite, and you don't care about what your country do to african or latin american people. But poor uyghur jihadist. Start watching some other points of view away from western media.

And yes, I am a proud communist, it is not an insult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 13:45:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Freedom for what? I have to pay half of my salary for a room. And in Spain(my country), for example, many people had gone to jail because of tweets. Also some other people are on jail without any judgment, because of fake proofs for example. Of course you are free if you agree with the government, you are free aswell to do whatever you want in China without confronting the system. Maybe your western paradise is not such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 13:41:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They are not opressing muslims, it would be nice for you to read other thing different from western propaganda. They are fighting the jihadism promoted by the West, to prevent things like the ones that happen in Europe. The USA has a much larger prison population and treat them as cheap labour. But wow you call something concentration camp and sounds much scarier. Also they had to fight against multiple embargoes by the USA during the first years of the Cold War, the bombing of vital infrastructures by the ROC, suppoerted by the USA. But evertything is Mao's fault, sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 13:31:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The PRC saved 800 millions of people from poverty without invading any single country like the West do. It has it flaws, sure, but I truly respect them. Why are the westerners always messing with the rest of the world issues? You are afraid that your hegemony is going to an end, and cannot accept it. Hong Kong is China, stop colonialism once for all. Fuck the UK and fuck the USA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 15:13:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is a meme: https://knowyourmeme.com/memes/video-games-appeal-to-the-male-fantasy

And a non english Great Britain is a spanish male fantasy at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 11:37:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This why I hate videogames, they appeal to the male fantasy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 10:36:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I only listened to his voice in videos, since he passed away when I was 2. I wish I could have met him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 09:15:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Juche dab. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 15:47:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Esto tira mucho de topicazos la verdad. A los murcianos se les entiende mejor que a muchos otros. Depende más de lo cerrado del acento que del acento en sí diría yo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 10:22:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The thing is if you want to enjoy the life in society, you have to contribute to it. I agree with your statement in part, and that things should be different. But enjoying what hard work built without working yourself is nothing but being a parasite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 20:11:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nation and state are not synonyms though. It could be a stateless nation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 09:17:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Indiana, USA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 10:18:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-05 09:53:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is false. Ask the US and their block on China and how they try to destroy the revolution. The anticommunism in this subreddit is disgusting. Long live the PRC and the chairman Mao. Fuck British and American imperialism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 20:33:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Había un personaje (del Instituto Juan de Mariana si no recuerdo mal), que decía que el Imperio Romano cayó por culpa de implementar medidas socialistas. Esta gene vive en su mundo y en ningún momento le interesa la realidad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 09:39:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course they're able to pee, but they are not able to store the pee. They have to pee immediately after they drink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-04 08:46:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amazing, good job mate! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 21:51:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spanish Britain is the best thing that could have happened to humanity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 11:59:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ¡Buena iniciativa camarada! Aunque no me gusta el término izquierda, todo hay que decirlo :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-30 22:55:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, I hate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 18:07:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> El autónomo y el asalariado que trabaje en una empresa privada. Entre jornada partida y las horas extras no pagadas, la gente vuelve a su casa a las 8 de la tarde. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 18:06:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Los cojones 23 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 09:33:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow man, this is amazing! Hard work and patience can give wonderful results! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-27 18:03:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally agree, I hate how gym and fitness is related with these toxic men and chads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The flag of Wyoming in the style of Cyprus </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-26 23:12:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-26 10:23:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont think a fiction is a valid argument. Literally fiction can turn out however you want. I like Orwell, and I like his books, but you need real facts and arguments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-24 21:36:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So you are wasting your money in a football jersey from a capitalist team because Lenin is in it? I mean, you are free to spend your hard earned money in whatever you feel like. But this is simply merchandising, they are using Lenin to gain money and make profit out of him. You don't need to wear those to be a communkst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-24 17:49:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And both are fiction. Of course things can go however you like while you are writing fiction. Using them as an argument against socialism is childish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-24 11:37:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the face testicles would have if they had one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-23 11:55:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, he made you work 12 hours, I don't think that is a good boss tbh. Stop praising people who  makes workers work that much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-23 11:23:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it is even more badass when you realize they said that even thought they had no chance against Macedonia. It is easy to be a bad boy when you are dealing with somebody weaker than you, but you need some big balls to say that to a much stronger one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-23 10:43:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rich people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-21 11:58:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was visiting my brother who lives there, but I am from Spain, so I don't know. My brother told me trees and flowers would bloom in around two weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-19 11:50:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is there another way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Orkanger, Norway </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 18:38:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-16 13:15:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This pictures are amazing, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-14 14:48:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cities and villages are pretty dense compared to other countriews, outside of them it is almost empty. There is a concept idk how it is called but it is like inhabited population density that ilustrates the density of the places where people actually live, and it is pretty illustrative in this case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 20:00:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, that's though, but in the long run it is worth it, I can tell you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 15:01:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really love your handwriting. Good luck with that, you can (and will) do it :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-10 12:36:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like it worked before. There are books of theory out there, read them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-10 12:19:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First: the population in the USSR never stopped growing, even with the Holodomor. And then it grew and grew. Their calories intake per capita was higher than most of the West countries, so I don't think they were starving. The USSR also faced an enormous civil war and a drought that caused the famine, not he political system. The only "historian" that says that the Holodomor had so many victim like the propaganda says is Hearst, a fascist and anticommunist. All the rest of the data doesn't say that. Check the Dust Bowl also, a famine in the USA that american government made even worse. And Gulag population was much lower than the US prison population is nowadays. Also the political persecution in the USA was (and still is) very fierce, where communists were killed, couldn't get jobs and got incarcelated. So I think the communism worked better than the capitalism does today in most of the world. Do you have any fact to support what you are saying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-10 12:09:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You said that it was a humanitarian disaster althought you have no proof. Just propaganda. The USSR had a higher quality of life than the USA even with all the destruction they suffered in the war. They had works, houses, free healtchare (lmao), work/life balance (35h per week), retirement at 60 with full public pensions, free university (not like the USA crippling student debt), no homeless people, a much lower prison population than a supposed free country... The USA for example cannot provide any of those things for all their population, even thought they are the richer country in the world and had not suffer a major war or disaster in their entire history, even thought they are sacking the whole world and creating humanitarian disaster in all the countries they intervene (Lybia, Irak, Afghanistan...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-10 11:50:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It wasn't a humanitatian disaster. A humanitarian disaster is capitalism, and also an ecological one. But there is more anti-communist propaganda that trash there is in the sea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-10 10:14:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We need a communist revolution. Capitalism will never solve this problem, it is a system only interested in profit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-08 10:06:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alabama: 100 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-07 18:18:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everything that could go right, did go right\*

No France, no Ottomans, almost no England? It is SPAIN TIME. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-05 09:18:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Disgusting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 14:50:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very nice concept, it is the blue supposed to be different? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-04 14:49:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That blue is amazing, I never get tired of it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-03 10:07:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought the dates were wrong, then I realised I am european and everybody here is american. Impressive changes  in only 1 month btw! You look amazing :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 22:40:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mussolini intensifies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 17:34:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, that looks gorgeous! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 13:30:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That was somehow my concern. I suspected that it was not that sustainable/cheap as it may seems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 11:54:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry I didn't express myself correctly. I wanted to say that China is concerned about Uyghur extremism and separatism, not against the ethnicity itself. I didn't want to portray China as the bad guy here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 11:45:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Edit: my comment was a mess and not well expressed so nevermind and read the answer below. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 10:53:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would it be possible to have a whole neighbourhood like that? Because that would be amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 18:14:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Capitalism in a nutshell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 12:14:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahahahahahahahahaha I always turned off the sound effects, I find most of them a little bit annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-01 12:05:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I played back at home, my mum always asked me what music was that, because she loves it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-28 21:14:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Disgusting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-26 16:38:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cities: Skyline. You can play at your own path and every mistake has a solution. You just enjoy and create your city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-19 19:58:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/communism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-10 11:13:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow totally unexpected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-09 18:25:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just like North Korea, just build some nukes and insult the USA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-06 19:56:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-06 18:36:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is not related to socialism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-02 22:17:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mercadona masterrace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-01 13:47:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This plane is going to Estambul. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-28 20:21:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, and a GDP of 5 trillion I think. It is such an economic powerhouse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-28 18:17:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1 win, 127 million inhabitants and a lot of money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-23 13:13:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> North Korea can have many flaws, but I always admired how this country and its people is totally independent, how are they fighting against almost all the world, and how they are following their own way no matter what. It is really admirable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-23 12:48:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, this is gorgeous. Congrats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-20 18:42:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like good old MSN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-14 11:29:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think that an ancap society would try to desestabilize the socialist one, so no, I think if the socialist one wants to survive in the long run, must destroy them.

But in the hypothetical situation there is no interaction at all (which I think it is impossible in real life), yes, why not. It is not worth the risk trying to destroy another society that doesn't do anything to you. Let them live as they want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-12 12:17:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think thia is the most relatable meme ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-08 17:42:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> País de Sudamérica con más porcentaje de blancos junto con Uruguay, en fin... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-05 14:56:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amazing! If you send a letter with that handwriting to someone, that person would fall in love with you ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-05 14:39:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got banned 90 days for saying that USA backs Guaidó because Maduro is anti USA imperialism and they have oil. The mod told me I was reading RT and state disinformation only. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-05 10:35:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Asad rocky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-04 22:57:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oil, and opposition to the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-04 17:29:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He is not communist at all, every marxist should know that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-04 16:58:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why Peru is more culturally diverse than other countries of Latin America? I mean, apart from the indigenous, mixed and white comunities as other LA countries, they have a lot population with asian (mainly japanese) and african ancestry.  That country is amazing man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-04 11:12:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like pizza </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-01 10:49:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "North Africa and South-Saharan Africa", aka Africa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-29 22:06:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just like real life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-23 10:17:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unpopular opinion: Brexit is not that bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-22 15:43:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amazing! I love it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Elon🅱ated Muskrat </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-08 20:24:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My Heritage flag: Extremadura and Castilla-La Mancha (Spain) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-29 22:05:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> &#x200B;

https://preview.redd.it/crdsb8ip93j11.png?width=2400&format=png&auto=webp&s=300b7d18adf2a7d2ae5c1f445d4d3ac5b32f94f2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Turkey in the style of Greece </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-29 21:20:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> &#x200B;

https://preview.redd.it/qgc82lgn13j11.png?width=2700&format=png&auto=webp&s=676d049087bfcfb83c6e799c10e29ffaecfe88da </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Flag of the city of Seville, Spain </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-27 15:17:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Flag of Santa Cruz de los Cáñamos (Spain) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-20 19:31:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://preview.redd.it/sgc8i15o15b11.png?width=750&format=png&auto=webp&s=e5e4264b9ec4c618acc178fff454a83b58343fdb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Good german podcats? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-19 17:56:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hallo zusammen,

I would like to hear some podcats in german, but I don't know which one. I would like them to be podcasts made for native german speakers, not for learning the language. Some of my favourite topics are history, geography or politics (german or international), so if you know some podcasts about that, it would be nice to know them. Anyways, every suggestion about other topic is also accepted :)

Danke schön!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Best expansions to buy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-22 08:47:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello everybody,

I am thinkig in buying some expansion in the Steam Summer sales, but I don't know which one. I have "Res Publica", "Conquest of Paradise", "El Dorado", "Wealth of Nations", "Common Sense" and "Mare Nostrum". I was thinking about "Art of War", but I don't really know. Can you recommend me which ones are the best according to you? Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
