<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject75</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 03:07:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They have to be somewhat brown to be considered hazel. They remind me of dying plants. When a leaf transitions from green to brown. The shift in color can be tinged with light brown but still green OR nearly completely brown with some green still left. That's what the spectrum of hazel eyes is like. If it's a blue plant/flower that starts turning brown, it's not hazel.

Yellow-brown fit into the hazel category if they have some green. I love eyes like that. They look like amber glass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 02:34:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hazel is when eyes are light brown mixed with green. They can be mixed by having brown as the predominant color with a ring of green. They can also be reversed, predominantly green with a ring of brown.

[Brown](https://i0.wp.com/iloverelationship.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/09/brown-eyes.jpg) vs [hazel](https://i.pinimg.com/originals/d7/0e/88/d70e88479a5c0962e822d485747aae46.jpg).

It's like comparing the difference between light blue and gray eyes. Hard to describe, hard to agree on. There is a difference though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 19:34:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much. I've had the same issue with other habit apps so I'm really glad that this one might work :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 06:34:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm really glad you haven't felt overstimulation. It's not a fun feeling.

It's okay to feel awkward about not having the same experiences. Not having that symptom doesn't mean you're any less valid as someone on the spectrum.

I know what its like to be different from the people you're supposed to highly relate to. Like you said, it really is a spectrum. I'm personally in a weird spot too with symptoms. I didn't have issues with developmental skills growing up and have always been self-aware, almost too aware of how people are supposed to function socially. Unable to apply that to social situations, it's still very obvious that something is "off" about me irl.

We may be oddballs even in our oddball community but we still belong! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 06:24:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Money equals power in the mind of a businessman. They're right on some level- more money means no poverty, more healthcare options, more comfortable means of living. They're hopped up on accumulating as much material shit as they can afford because of the social status that comes with it.

They honestly think they're swimming in power and want you too as well. Working hard for their money and seeing results in shiny new things feels really good to them. If only they'd look up and realized that they're working their ass off to buy a new item that only serves the purpose to put money in another guy's pocket and think they're getting something out of it.

You've got the upper hand. Never let their preaching get to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 17:48:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Adut Akech :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 01:10:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm always on here referring people to DocumentingReality. It's a site that lets you get a few posts per month of morbid photos/videos in a bunch of different categories. None are usually without context, so you're not just seeing dead brown woman #273828 with her tits out like the shit you see on BestGore next to the porn ads.

There's still some tasteless stuff (as there is on any site of this nature) and the usual disgraces that gather on gore sites make appearances. They're easy to ignore though.

If you pay $25 one time you get the whole site instead of a few posts per month. I'm broke so I don't get that luxury :(
Great place, definitely check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 01:11:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This looks fantastic. Would you be able to list any CC you're using? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 00:18:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the best tattoo I've ever seen in my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 21:45:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so sorry that this happened to you. That artist needs to be fired immediately.
Don't go back- I question what they consider competent enough to etch permanent art onto skin.

There's plenty of things that people have mentioned in the replies here that would help it fade as much as possible before you either get a coverup from a professional who knows what they're doing or begin laser treatments.

You deserve every penny you paid back and you should get the word out that your artist fucked up that badly. That shop should be mortified right now. I hope you're well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 19:09:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm very sorry to tell you that even if you reach your "ideal", BDD will not go away. It's a mental illness that doesn't have much to do with your actual physical appearance. That's why it exaggerates flaws you perceive about yourself. No matter what you do, it will remain unattainable. The only way to work through BDD is through therapy. I wish it was easier, too. One day we will find peace and live within our bodies happily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 21:23:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Firstly, I'm really happy that you're planning on telling your parents. A lot of teens try to hide talking about it and avoid it as much as possible which always leads to things getting far more detrimental. Good on you, dude.

I would suggest writing some things down about your depression. The symptoms you have, what you learned while researching, and even write down the fears you have about telling your parents. Sometimes when I do something I'm anxious about my mind goes blank. A little cheat sheet helps a lot.  Make sure you inform them that you're not actively suicidal (if you aren't) at some point too. It's important that they know you're being safe.

If you have someone you can practice with and confide in first, that'd be great. I would tell a family member or friend you trust about your depression. That way you have someone cheering you on and someone they can talk to if they want to know more.

Parents can react negatively to hearing about their kids mental health problems. You need to prepare yourself for any reaction. They may be really sad that you're feeling this way and react emotionally, wanting to hug you. They could also be defensive and say something like, "Every teenager is depressed. You just have to get over it and pull up your boot straps". I don't know your parents, so I can't predict what they'll do.

No matter what, you're going to be alright. Stick to focusing on telling them. Treat their reaction after the fact if it's not a great initial outcome. Let the community here know how it goes if you feel comfortable doing that. We care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 06:25:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Another obviously fake post. Come on, guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 23:25:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> According to my mom (a huge Paula Abdul fan), Paula had been battling [an eating disorder](https://www.ornatopia.com/how-paula-abdul-won-her-battle-against-bulimia-and-encouraged-others-to-do-the-same/) and intermittently going through treatment at that time.

It's likely that to maintain her reputation and her sanity— because trust me, going public with an ED when you're in recovery is going to end in a relapse, she was directed to lie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 22:00:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can see why you're frustrated. Anyone would take on a cynical point of view in those circumstances. You being a realist isn't a negative trait in itself. It's helpful in some situations.

Make sure to keep yourself a little open to invite someone in. If you walk around thinking you'll never find someone, they might pass you up thinking you're not interested in them. Keep your head up and your eyes open.

I know someone who found their soulmate at 50. Didn't think it'd ever happen for them since everyone else in their life was getting married by their mid-twenties. You never know what life'll throw at you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 21:52:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's the other way around for me. Sugar relaxes me and makes me sleepy. As does caffeine. If I drink energy drinks I pass out in 10 minutes since it has both caffeine and way too much sugar. Great for insomnia, bad for my heart issues! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 21:44:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The right person simply hasn't come into your life yet. That shit's gonna happen when it's meant to happen. All the other people who've made you feel negative about relationships were possibly lessons showing you what traits you don't like in people.

I know you're going to get into a happy relationship in the future. Even if you don't believe it, some weirdo stranger on the internet does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 21:39:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I completely relate to you. I describe my brain as having three lanes of a highway, every thought is a speeding car. It's always rush hour in there.

I'm in therapy and on a slew of medications (Psychiatric meds for many things, not just my ASD symptoms) which helps a bit but is definitely not for everyone. There's no permanent cure but I do have some good news.

These racing thoughts usually start getting really bad when your brain is trying to tell you something. It can be a stress trigger that you're aware of. For example, some people are stressed because of the change that happened with the current pandemic. It can be something personal like a family, friend, or relationship issue. It can be due to previous trauma. Or it can be something you don't recognize. Your subconscious might have a "clog". A bunch of feelings that haven't been addressed. Your mind might be having a temper tantrum. This state of mind is not going to last forever. If you talk to yourself, maybe even write down the thoughts you're having, you can work through this. It's temporary. I believe in you, man. Even if you're not into therapy I do recommend talking to someone about this. Just to get all the thoughts out.

Someone mentioned weed already but I'm giving my two cents. I'm a stoner too but have issues with weed causing paranoia and anxiety and intensifying these overwhelming thoughts. The culprit is if I get Sativa and/or smoke too much. I choose to microdose only with Indica or a blend. Microdosing is taking such a small amount of a drug that it doesn't make you high in a typical sense. Just makes you feel buzzed, chilled, very clear-headed. I take one medium sized hit and I'll be good for hours. I have a low tolerance since I smoke such a tiny amount. It's perfect. I love being fully aware and not having the anxiety/paranoia/racing thoughts. It makes me feel "normal". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 21:23:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Communism (and politics in general). Criminology. Mortuary science. Film. Astrology. Music (mostly from the '40s to '90s).

A current fixation of mine is Dungeons & Dragons. Never played, not sure if it'd be my scene since it's reliant solely on social interaction but I'm really loving learning about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 08:36:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She looks so much like Megan thee Stallion in this photo. The wig reminds me of the Tina Snow album cover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 22:52:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holistic methods can be helpful for some people (usually effective for who *believe* they'll work in the first place) but when it comes to behavioral or psychological issues.. really? You're going to risk it and poke some needles in your kid instead of therapy? That's a damn shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Casual] Just A Little Morbid: A Survey (Everyone) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 07:45:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 01:19:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You deserve someone who doesn't bring you down for who you are. I'm sorry that she made you feel bad about yourself.

We can't control the brains we've been given and no one else lives our lives. You aren't immature. You're just a grown woman living life in a way your friend isn't used to seeing. Simple.
As long as you're not hurting anyone and are always trying to better yourself, you're doing adulthood right.

With that being said, daily living skills should continue to be worked on. We tend to have a delay in those. No shame in that. You're going to reach those goals and find yourself at ease with chores, cooking, etc. in time. You may not like them-- I know I hate them, but you'll tolerate them without avoidance.

Don't let someone's negative perception of your life impact how you feel about it. You love the things you do. I have similar habits with researching and staying up at night. I've perfected it through the years so I'm able to wake up earlier some days for appointments or family outings. Normal human activities and autistic night-owl tendencies can coexist!

Remember, nowhere in the world is there a list of guidelines that you need to meet to be an adult. There are societal norms but those don't equal success! There are "mature" adults who hate every second of their boring lives because they forced themselves to meet the expectations of what an adult should look/act like.

Also, your english is fantastic :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 17:37:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am so sorry that a therapist mistreated you like that. I've been in therapy for most of my life and I can say without a doubt that they're not all so callous.

When I scope out a therapist I've always used the site PsychologyToday because it has a filter to let you see therapists (near you, covered by your insurance) who are trained in helping with the disorder you click on. I refuse to go to therapy if they're not educated on how to handle my disability.

Give therapy another go if you're up to it. I know that a negative experience can make you lose hope but once you find a professional who finally *understands*... one of the most beautiful feelings in the world. Life-changing stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 04:44:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having enough willpower to accomplish a task would negate the dysfunction of 'executive dysfunction'. Doing so implies that there's a choice. People with this symptom don't get to opt to do something. It takes away our ability to do so the majority of the time.

That's why even things we absolutely love, like engaging with a special interest or talking to a friend, are avoided or ignored entirely without a socially acceptable or explicable reason.

The human brain is truly fascinating in the ways it likes to torture us, isn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 00:56:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When explaining it to people I usually use the glass barrier metaphor since it's easy to understand.

Executive dysfunction is like having a clear window in front of you. You see where you want to go (what task you have to complete), you know what direction to walk in (how to do it), everyone knows you're fully capable of getting there because the glass is invisible to their eye. But you physically can't. It's all blocked and takes much more effort than it does for anyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 00:42:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Day-long thunderstorms > sunny days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 06:18:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's something to be proud of as long as you're happy with it. If you do feel inclined to try something new or if you feel like you can't relate to others because you only want to watch animation, that would suggest that something may need to change and have a go at getting out of your comfort zone. But otherwise, lean into it. Watch everything animated you can get your hands on.

You may have heard about it already but I think Letterboxd would be appealing to you. It's a site for people who love film to build a platform and write reviews or just find new movies that you've never heard of before within genres you care about. They've got 25k animated films listed currently.

Animation doesn't really get on my radar that often but I really loved Paprika and Perfect Blue. Fantastic Planet too but it creeped me the fuck out at times. Something about the eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 06:01:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do become emotional. It makes me feel like a little ant underneath a big, black boot. I may not be aware of what's above me, but maybe there's something up there that's looking back at me and saying "Do they know they're that small?".

More along the lines of all-knowing aliens looking at how we operate rather than a Godly figure. Akin to how we feel when we watch bugs move in gravel. But I do get how my thoughts could be interpreted as a religious point of view. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 05:54:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here. I have "chipmunk cheeks". When I smile I look like I'm about start foraging for acorns. Try experimenting with different smirks instead of smiling in photos. Still feels foreign at first but hey, it's something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 05:47:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you have dyscalculia? It's what I'm diagnosed with. I may not be able to help you with math but I want you to know that you're not stupid. We just work differently. Sending positive energy your way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 05:42:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have these pretty regularly too. It's really hard to get through such intense emotions without freaking out. Especially when it's because of something as important as that. You're justified in reacting! Not dumb at all. All you need to focus on is working on what you'll do next time something worries you like this.

You sound like you have a lot of energy inside. While meditating helps me calm down, you might need something different to make sure your energy doesn't get wasted on the wrong thing. You've gotta push that angry energy out of the way first so you can focus on the solution. Gotta control that rage by letting it exist. Give it its moment.

We've got the classic option: PILLOWS. Scream into them. Put them on a bed and punch them. Favorite technique since it really does work. Just make sure you punch with your thumb outside your fist so you don't fuck up your hands. I have made that mistake not once, but twice.

Second option: Cold water. I use this one on a weekly basis. Just did it tonight. Best for if you don't want to make a noise or you're in public and know where a bathroom is. I turn my sink on to the absolute coldest it can get. Ice cold. Run my hands under the water. Make a fist, open close open close. When you decide its too cold, keep one hand under and turn it up as hot as you can handle. You can't do this for a long time but it helps me kind of "shock" myself into clearing my head. After I feel a little better I put water on my face. Not as cathartic as punching a pillow but not as calm as meditation.

Third option: Simplest one. Sometimes you just have to lay on the floor/bed and kick your feet. Yeah, like a kid. Who cares though. Kids do it because it works. I think more adults should utilize it. Maybe the world wouldn't be so infuriating if people would have a temper tantrum in the safety of their own home when they're pissed off.

Sorry this is so long. I'm known for how much I talk and giving advice too much. Hope you don't mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 05:14:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I watch her and support her on patreon! She's such a great resource for people who don't have the ability to seek information out through experiences with love interests, interaction with peers, or being too awkward to ask parents. Helped me work through some of the fears I have relating to sexuality in general.

Seriously one of the most important channels on YouTube. Damn them for not letting her channel grow because of their advertising bullshit / algorithm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 05:08:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't find it strange. We can't control what we're interested in. My special interests are communism and silent films, so I can sympathize with feeling like a weirdo for being into the things you love.

I would advise against geeking out about guns to people who don't already know you/trust you though. A lot of us tend to inform people about things they don't know much about because of how passionate we are. But as you can see by the current epidemic of mass shootings, it could definitely make some people concerned.
Stay safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 05:27:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was r/morbidreality, I believe. I'm a 2000s baby so I never got to see his work when he was still alive. Way too many talented people in Hollywood died in the 90s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 08:13:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Is [heavier white girl] like [heavier white girl] and [heavier black girl] like [heavier black girl]" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 07:58:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never seen a cat look flabbergasted before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 00:37:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Either OP is getting trolled or OP faked this conversation. There is no way someone could be this cliché and use every single catchphrase of MLMs/Beggars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 18:38:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, sure. I'm not surprised that a name has been used at some point in history. But it's still considered odd being used in this decade among Taylors and Michaels, y'know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 00:47:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> River / Rain (or in this case Raine) are normal names that've been around for a while. For example, the Phoenix family (River, Rain, and Joaquin went by Leaf for a bit). I wouldn't put them in the same category as Onyxander and Thelonious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 01:14:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The people in the comments here saying how these girls are trashy and have daddy issues. On a clearly staged joke video. Mindblowing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 18:11:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't forget to try r/crimescene and r/unresolvedmysteries too. The latter being my favorite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 17:17:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The funny thing is that [he considered himself pro-choice](https://qz.com/1623437/trump-shifted-from-pro-choice-to-pro-life-as-he-planned-a-presidential-run/) before 2015 and coincidentally changed his mind when he was running for president. Almost like he was pandering to the largely pro-life Republican party and doesn't have a single authentic bone in his body.

But what do I know. I'm just a silly little libtard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 18:37:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That dog looks british. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 22:48:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any parent who tries to "get rid of" autism clearly doesn't understand science that isn't learned from a post lodged between a wine meme and essential oil ad on facebook.

I believe everyone has the right to have a strong sense of spirituality/faith and should practice as they please. However, once it involves harming others emotionally, physically, or sexually... it's not faith anymore. It's a vehicle for abuse whether they're conscious of it or not.

I have learned to love my autism despite the challenges its made me overcome. I hope the children of parents like these will accept themselves too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 22:17:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been searching for a bit and have come up with absolutely nothing besides some (albeit tepid) images of [the fateful corkscrew](https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2217198/amp/Renato-Seabra-trial-Horrified-jurors-shown-bloody-corkscrew-male-model-used-sever-65-year-old-gay-lovers-testicles-sickening-hotel-slaying.html) and a bloody, destroyed wine glass shown to the jurors. It looks like whoever handled the photo-based evidence did a great job keeping it closed off from the public.

If anyone does eventually find something showing the scene, lmk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 08:18:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think I'll ever be able to wrap my head around her surgery choices but I appreciate her zaniness. She seems fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 06:31:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not weird at all in this community. I personally find myself looking back on u/jessicamshannon's [Abu Ghraib writeup](https://web.archive.org/web/20191013202412/https://imgur.com/a/C6mLO). It's a fantastic examination. All of her work is great, although for a lot of them you will have to use the Wayback Machine since Imgur decided to crack down on what she had posted.

Not sure if you've been looking at similar subs but r/serialkillers has some photos and content that'll blow you away if you sort by top posts all time. Those are less gore more substance usually. r/morbidreality is more like here in my experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 20:47:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Here's](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC5925757/) a really in-depth study on female autism in comparison to male autism. The study found that women not only have been proven to have less daily living skills but also that their masking skills are superior to males on the spectrum. Meaning that women with autism feel pressured in some way to hide these traits for the sake of others perception of them. Women have the same kind of autism. They just show it differently than Twitter Fuckhead would like them to. Because obviously he knows everything. Especially in regards to women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 23:09:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Brother*, but I'll take it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 22:27:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm fat but at least I'm not fat and racist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 03:28:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got my very first drastic haircut in years as of a few months ago. Cut off my long hair. Barbers/salons are really some of the worst places to be autistic in. You're completely right about them being overstimulating.

Lanza wore the same outfit over and over again. I believe it was an oversized pale blue polo and some kind of pants that weren't jeans. He was so scrawny that he looked like he was drowning in them.

I was just thinking, "At least I don't wear the same clothes all the time". Then I realized I wear the same pair of pants every time I go out. Damn. Obsessional behaviors suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 00:39:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Much like other mass shooters, there were so many instances where it was visible that he needed help and yet no one did anything.

He cut off his entire family near the end, becoming a recluse and only corresponding with his mother through email despite being inside of her home.

Multiple mental health professionals declared that he needed intensive therapies and medication in an effort to stabilize him and help him get on the road to a sustainable life. Everything was declined by him or his mother.
His father made his best effort to get involved with his life but Lanza refused and avoided him.

There is no sane way to rationalize pedophilia and most definitely no sane way to rationalize killing children. Talking about someone's mental health that could have been preventively treated doesn't mean excusing the deaths they caused.

There's nothing we can do about what Adam Lanza did. We have to focus on the potential future mass shooters. Talk to recluses, utilize therapies offered, make treatment more available, de-cringe talking about mental illness, and parents really have to monitor their kids better. I know his mother was physically ill and emotionally exhausted but God, she needed to intervene more when he was stonewalling her.

If you are experiencing the feeling that your fate is either killing others or killing yourself, there is no shame in seeking help. A reddit comment isn't going to change your mind, I know that. Dark thoughts aren't destiny. You don't have to succumb to them.

Long unnecessary multi-paragraphical rambling that no one is going to read over.
Also it sucks that Lanza was autistic. Majority of us on the spectrum don't have violent intent, just lots of social anxiety. And bad hair. I don't know why so many of us have bad hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 00:41:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've read a lot of fucked up cases regarding child abuse before. Too many. But this takes the cake as one of the most sadistic I've heard of. The lack of remorse and nonchalant attitude from the guardians that killed him gave me chills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 01:47:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I remember seeing the tapes of the hangings floating around online for a while. Maddeningly unsettling. Couldn't sleep for a week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 04:57:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This special breed of bigotry comes from the worst kind of voluntary ignorance. Seeing the world is changing around you in a way you don't like and choosing to make your kid as unprepared for it as possible.

You can shelter them all you want, the world is always going to be as diverse as it is. I pity her and I hope her kids will favor love over her outdated, paranoid worldview. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 02:05:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She believed that consuming too much yeast created issues with development. Gave me a book about it called [The Yeast Connection: A Medical Breakthrough](https://www.penguinrandomhouse.com/books/33760/the-yeast-connection-by-william-g-crook/). Says that it has ties to things like AIDS, suicide, and autism.
She believed that capitalist America "forces" bread into so many meals because it makes consumers more docile.
I'm a communist and all, but Jesus christ. It's fucking bread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 19:43:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a former therapist who always seemed timid about my transness. One day I said to her, "Ask me anything you want about it and I'll answer with no judgment".
I thought it would be like, "How did you know you were trans" or "What does dysphoria feel like".

But no, instead she asked, with a matter of fact tone and a neutral expression:
"Is it true Michelle Obama is a man?".

When I tell you I was taken aback, I mean I was genuinely speechless. My brain couldn't process the stupidity I just heard.
I told her that no, trans people aren't a hivemind and that people who believe that about her are usually ignorant right-wing conspiracy theorists. Not surprised, she was anti-vax and thought the government normalizes bread & fluoride to control our minds.

I switched therapists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How important is the material of the initial jewelry being implant grade? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 18:14:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So, I'm considering getting a slew of ear piercings in the upcoming future. I'm doing my research and I keep coming across mixed opinions on material.

Some piercers refuse to pierce with any other material to promote healing. Implant-grade is the only option.

Some say that piercings will heal just fine with sterling silver or steel as long as the person does proper aftercare.

In your opinion, which is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 22:11:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There may be different flags flying but abusing authority, hiding behind a badge, and killing civilians doesn't discriminate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 20:10:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Secret History by Donna Tartt. I'm rereading for the second time and I really love it. It does drag a little in the middle but the payoff is entirely worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 19:59:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, trans autism gang :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 19:56:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lot of people on the spectrum have [hypersexuality](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC5789215/)! You're definitely not alone in that.

I personally can't relate but I'm gay myself. I have no idea how I would begin navigate the dating world or eventually develop a sex life. Intimidating!

Have you considered adding that you're autistic in your bio on a dating app? You might be able to draw in someone who knows how to create an atmosphere that'll help you become more comfortable with them. Find someone with compassion and an open mind and get laid. You deserve it.

You may have them already but from what I know about treatment for hypersexuality is that there's plenty of self-love involved. Get yourself some sex toys if you can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 19:42:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I'm discussing something I can see in my mind I tend to look up where I'm "holding" it in the mental vision, like it's physically floating up there. As if my eyes are projectors and only I can see the hologram. It's not a hallucination, just a mental portrait.
We have similar brains.

I describe it to people and they look at me weird. My therapist has gotten used to it, thankfully. Former ones were seemingly made uncomfortable by it.

I know of a few other people who have this "power". I'd say we're lucky.
This may be odd, but may I ask what your astrological sign is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 19:34:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I watch the same things over and over and over and over and over and over. Film, television, videos. It's soothing. I like noting details and memorizing scenes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 19:32:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've done this before! Hallway smoke alarm wouldnt stop beeping and I lost my mind. A hallmark of the autism experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 19:25:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First off, you're not pathetic. You're a human being trying your best to function when you have a mental illness trying to stop you. You have social challenges on top of that.
This is the version of you that's incapacitated. Not at your best. So don't be too harsh on yourself at your current state.


I personally know the effects of how an unreasonable expectation from a young age can cripple you.
That doc saw your potential and overdramatized it in an attempt to inspire you to work harder. Their attempt had an adverse reaction. Instead, it made you crumble in the shadow of what others thought you were destined to be. Some prodigy or whatever. It's not your fault they chose a bad route to make you feel inspired.


Realistically, you're an intelligent person who has high potential. Just because you're not a savant or whatever doesn't mean you're useless. Plus, you're going through shit. Nothing pathetic about fighting a battle with yourself, man.


You're gonna be fine. It'll take time, you know that already. But you will get to a place where you don't feel like this. A place where your potential is reached with a reasonable outcome. You'll be able to put those skills to use and you'll feel great about it. Fuck social skills, there are a lot of people with challenges like ours and they end up successful regardless. We're important members of society. Just different.


I don't know if any of my longwinded little speech helped but I want you to know that I think you're gonna make it. You're going to be alright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 19:06:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not looking to date for a while but I'm so nervous for when I do.

I'm great with words. I've written erotica for years through fanfiction. While embarrassing to admit, it's given me a lot of useful hints about what exactly brings passion to light. It's a dance of subtle social exchanges.
A seemingly impossible feat for me.

How do people maneuver these things in practice? It's so intimidating. I doubt anyone could ever view me as sexy, I'll settle for adorable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 18:52:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just because we have to take a different path to get there doesn't mean we won't arrive at the same destination. Sure, there's roadblocks. Maybe it takes us a little longer than someone else. But we'll get there.

That's what I say to myself every single time I feel this way. My life isn't going the way I expected it to and that's fine. We're not tied to who we are or what capabilities we have today. Learning, growing, changing, accepting.

Being autistic doesn't ruin our lives, just gives us different challenges. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 01:45:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The rape & murder of a fifteen year old girl.
He made a false confession because he was extremely impressionable and easy to manipulate due to his disability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 03:43:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Inbreeding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 20:10:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm undecided if I want to be donated to science or become one with the earth when I die.
I think I'd be helpful scientifically because of all of the things I have 'wrong' with me. Fun to study.
But I'd also love to become the same flowers I loved as a kid (daffodils).
I wish there was a way to do both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 03:04:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Documentingreality's site only lets you have a few free posts on a 4-6 week basis before asking to pay a one time fee of $20 to keep it running. It's a huge place, completely worth it in my opinion. Photos, videos, discussions. I personally didn't feel comfortable there because of some of the users being blatant nazis or being outspoken about beating off to dead women. Maybe I'm just a pussy though.
Regardless, quality mortuary gore among other things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 00:12:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't right now but I'm very optimistic.
I'm 20, never kissed or anything yet. Sometimes it makes me sad but I would rather have a good experience later in life than a bad one at the age that I'm "supposed" to.

I'm going through a gender transition right now as well, so I'm not keen on putting myself out into the dating world until I feel right in my own body.

One day I'm going to find myself on first dates, probably meeting people through dating apps. Awkward moments, social blunders, bad times that make good stories, and rejections.
But eventually, I will find someone who I love that loves me back. We'll have good chemistry and he'll accept me for who I am (and I'll of course do the same to him). I'm looking forward to that time in my life :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 23:58:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 4 is the best number. Four has four letters. Four cut in half is 2.
Both 2x2 and 2 + 2 is four.
Two twos make up one four.. it's so whole. It's the purest number to me.

Least favorite numbers: 3, 5, and 7 and any numbers containing them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 23:48:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kale. It's one of the only vegetables I can handle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 00:50:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love you, Tom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 00:34:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The sound those made when they broke is enough justification to immediately knock one over the next time I see one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 06:38:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a premonition in January that she was going to die this year. I don't know if I believe in that sort of thing but maybe it'll manifest into reality if I say it enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 19:02:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I second this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 19:02:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A Shakespeare book I have that's 84 years old. It has 150gsm wove paper. Whoever owned it previously must have been a smoker. I found that smoke intensifies the signature "old book smell". It's beautiful.
Book sniffing gang. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 18:52:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've always done that. I was at the library almost every day as a kid and got in the habit of it. Different density, age, and type of paper have their own unique scents. It's intriguing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 15:58:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The egregiously incorrect anatomical leaps they'll take to make a "hurr durr used to be man haha funnie" joke. God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 21:49:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The world has made a lot of progress in trans rights in the last ten years. More social awareness, protective laws, acceptance, and medical coverage than ever before.

Even those who don't understand us can put judgment aside and remain civil.

Other times they don't.
When that happens, we end up with cases like Muhlaysia Booker, Rita Hester, Bailey Reeves, Marsha P Johnson, Chynal Lindsey, Paris Cameron, Johana Medina Leon, Kiki Fantroy, Zoe Spears, Bee Love Slater, Dana Martin, Nikki Kuhnhausen, Ellie Marie Washtock, Alexa Luciano Ruiz, Tracy Single, Claire Legato, Serena Angelique Velázquez, Jazzaline Ware, Ashanti Carmon, Selena Reyes-Hernandez, Denali Berries Stuckey, and Jordan Cofer.

I'm a trans man, the likelihood of me getting hate crimed is less compared to trans women. Every day, trans women (especially women of color) are in fear of being killed just for being themselves.

I hope for a world with more education, more compassion, less hate.
It's an obvious battle to come out and transition, but it shouldn't be a battle for our lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 17:32:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Double cheeked up on a Thursday afternoon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 20:12:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hair loss sounds like a difficult thing to go through. When I talk to someone experiencing it they seem so embarrassed. It helps if I show my little cowlick patch where I'm missing some hair. I've always had it.

I have hope that science will bring more accessible treatments and at-home solutions in the upcoming years. There's already shampoos with minoxidil in them that I saw at Target. It's going to get better and better as time goes on! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 20:03:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take biotin supplements if you don't already! They help speed up the "awkward stage" of growing your hair out and they make it really soft and shiny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 20:01:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you :) Yay for haircuts!! Just promise me that you'll think about it for a little while before booking the appointment. It's always good to let the idea breathe and see if you really want this big change a month from now. Whatever you choose, you can do this. I believe in you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 19:56:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! It's a great feeling to change things up. Whether that's someone growing long locks or cutting them off, it feels good to have a part of yourself that you intentionally altered. Especially after years of having the same thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 19:51:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 19:50:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hell yeah!! I'm glad you pushed yourself to play. Tennis seems fun but I'm too uncoordinated for it :( I'd probably hit myself in the face with the racket by accident, honestly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 14:30:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sensory problems. I hated how it felt when it was down. I liked how long hair looked on other people but since I only wore it in a bun it defeated its purpose of covering my face.

I think there's a lot of people who feel better with a long mane of hair. I just wasn't one of those people, unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I finally cut off my long hair!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 03:59:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been hiding behind my long hair for two years now, covering up my face as much as possible. I couldn't stand the feeling of it down, so I always wore it in a man bun. I hated it but refused to do anything about it because it was like a security blanket to me. It felt like it protected me. Mace in a back pocket, except mace doesn't clog your shower drain.

I've felt very stuck recently. I wrote a little list of things I wanted to do to change myself for the better. Getting a short haircut was at the top. My haircut guy is really nice and has accommodations to his salon for me, so that alleviated some stress.

I showed him the picture I chose and talked about it a little and he was able to execute it perfectly. When I saw myself I felt overjoyed.
I never like how my face looks but having nicer hair is giving me some previously undiscovered confidence.
The floor was covered in huge clumps of hair by the end of the appointment. I feel so much lighter and cleaner now that it's off of me.

I did it! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 03:34:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was feeling similar about it when I was actually subscribed to here and saw new posts on my feed that were usually very downbeat and bleak. It wasn't helping me mentally seeing those at times I really didn't need to.

When I stopped subscribing to here and specifically looked this sub up when I felt like it, I began to have a better time. The highly upvoted posts with more engagement usually aren't vent posts. And if they are, they're likely to have comments with positivity, telling someone that they're going to be okay, their way of dealing with said problem, etc. I liked seeing that. It changed my view on the sub completely. At its best, it's truly a supportive community. At its worst, as you said, it can be too negative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 00:23:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As an autistic faggot I feel very offended being grouped in with a spineless twink like Gigi.

We have dimension because we're people. Just because we have special interests doesn't mean we can't bother to educate ourselves and expand our world view.. we're not stupid. I think it's harmful to portray us as self-centered retards to make some drag queen seem less boring.

There is NO excuse to be apolitical in world where free education is at your fingertips. She simply didn't care to bother with learning about the oppression of marginalized people because she doesn't find it important enough. She lives in her little bubble with her same 2 jokes and lack of flavor until speaking out about politics will benefit her. Pathetic.

Blaming it on autism diagnosed in a youtube comments section.. truly gross. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 16:05:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jesus christ, delete this.
Black people are being murdered. This is not time for a fucking cop joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I spent 78 hours making Newcrest my meticulously detailed custom town.... and then it vanished. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-31 17:39:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know why EA hates me. I crafted those buildings and homes with so much pride and tenderness. I am on the verge of tears over a video game (I'm autistic so my reactions may be different than others).

I'm not looking for advice on how to resolve it, I've tried every possible way to locate the files and bring them back. They're just not there. I have to become at peace with that.

I have to face that I need to remake my town and save each lot to gallery just in case this happens again. If anyone else had this issue previously, I stand with you in solidarity. This shit sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 03:59:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a fellow gay autistic guy worried about dating in the future, this made me smile.
I'm really happy for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-22 10:33:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is now my life goal to check off each of these boxes. Consider this my new bucket list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-22 10:27:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whether she's under the influence or mentally ill, she still remained kind while impaired. That in itself is something to appreciate. There are far more stable and sober, yet mean people out there.

I hope this lady is having a nice day wherever she is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-21 05:24:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please become more educated about what the LGBT+ community has gone through and still experiences in current times. There are different types of oppression that exist in the world that coexist without invalidating each other.

[698,000 LGBTQ adults (ages 18-59) in the U.S. have received conversion therapy, including about 350,000 LGBTQ adults who received treatment as adolescents.](https://familyproject.sfsu.edu/sites/default/files/FAP_Family%20Acceptance_JCAPN.pdf?response_type=embed).

"[Family rejection on the basis of sexual orientation or gender identity can have extreme effects on LGBTQ youth. In one study, lesbian, gay and bisexual youth who reported higher levels of family rejection during adolescence were 8.4 times more likely to report having attempted suicide, 5.9 times more likely to report high levels of depression, 3.4 times more likely to use illegal drugs and 3.4 times more likely to report having engaged in unprotected sexual intercourse, compared to peers from families that reported no levels of family rejection. As a result of family rejection, discrimination, criminalization and a host of other factors, LGBTQ youth represent as much as 40% of the homeless youth population. Of that population, studies indicate that as many as 60% are likely to attempt suicide.](https://www.thetrevorproject.org/get-involved/trevor-advocacy/homelessness/)"

In 2019, [331 trans people had been killed for being out of the closet](https://www.forbes.com/sites/jamiewareham/2019/11/18/murdered-hanged-and-lynched-331-trans-people-killed-this-year/#593ea3852d48). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-21 05:10:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so jealous!! I feel like everyone who plays this franchise dreams of having all packs of their game. One day I'll get there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-21 05:07:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This looks so beautiful and cozy. I wanna fall asleep in there rn!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-21 04:21:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a gay autistic person, no.
Two entirely different things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-21 04:06:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, it's considered to be "higher-functioning". Generally, that's a label to show that we don't need as much support for independent living as others with disabilities do.

The majority of people like us won't need a caretaker in our adult lives. Though we may need therapy, support groups, routines, or other accommodations in our lives that will help us continue to function independently, it doesn't force us to rely on reminders to bathe or needing to be fed by the hand of someone else.

It has much less to do with our actual, individual functioning and more as an organizational tool in diagnosis and various therapeutic treatments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 23:53:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My cat squints one eye when he's angry! It's actually kind of cute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 05:06:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought the bald bastard was holding a gun up to his head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 20:52:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having so much filler (potentially surgery?) and still feeling the need to edit to look "better" somehow.

Women are put under such pressure to possess physically unobtainable perfection that even facial alterations aren't enough on their own. When does it end? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 20:45:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Considering how many things she doesn't edit on social media, I think this is easily forgiven.
I love her so much. Protect her at all costs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 20:15:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just turned 20 and have been having a similar crisis to yours. It's hard to grasp that reality didn't bend to meet the standard I set for myself as a kid.

Interruptions, setbacks, trauma happens that alters our timing to get to the goal. Doesn't mean its not salvageable. It'll happen. Just later, on its own time.

Unclench your jaw. Let yourself breathe. You are not stuck, you cannot be late to the future.

Those few sentences have been my mantra to help me cope with not meeting expectations I made when I wasn't as experienced with how life goes. Shit, I have way more to learn before I can handle some bigger aspirations. In due time, we'll get there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 20:07:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aspiring author. I've been told I was "gifted" in writing when I was a kid but now get worried that I won't live up to that standard. I still love writing, dislike the anxiety that comes with it.

I have a few ideas for novels in wildly different genres. Not sure what to start first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 20:03:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! [My cat who I've nicknamed, "Nasty"](https://imgur.com/gallery/l76HyZp) is one of my biggest reasons to get out of bed in the morning.

He learned odd habits from me, like having to follow my strict routines. We joke that he "caught my autism". Love that guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 19:53:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so sorry she does that to you :(
You should never feel embarrassed about what you love. She only does this because she's insecure about herself. In her mind, putting you down for being happy/excited makes her superior to you. It's entirely untrue and cruel to do to your child.

Relish in your SI in online communities as much as you can. Her weird complex can't get in your way there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 04:09:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Erratic, unusual behaviors + tics aren't uncommon for people on the spectrum. The recent influx in severity and frequency is concerning. Especially if there are slurs involved that could get him into trouble if he said it around the wrong person.

This could be:
- A reaction to trauma. Any abuse, physical injury, violence, natural disaster, loss, NDE, or crime witnessed/experienced.
- The beginning of a larger battle with mental health ahead. The symptoms you've stated apply to many disorders, but two that I'd especially like to note are [schizotypal personality disorder](https://www.health.harvard.edu/a_to_z/schizotypal-personality-disorder-a-to-z) and [schizophrenia](https://www.nimh.nih.gov/health/topics/schizophrenia/index.shtml). Schizophrenia commonly develops among males in late adolescence to mid-twenties. I am not in any way, shape, or form telling you that these are the most probable cause. I felt that it was reasonable to mention this as a possibility.
- New compulsive habit. Compulsive behaviors are extremely common within the autism spectrum. Completely manageable with therapy.

Now onto what you can do.
You need to make the time to show support for him. I don't know you, so maybe you two are best friends and spend a lot of time together. But in case you aren't, you have to know that this is the #1 way to help someone seek treatment. Building trust and showing care for someone abrasive, reclusive, or otherwise "weird" means they can feel seen and wanted.
No lecturing, preaching, anything. Just spend more time and get to a point where you can bring up therapy casually and it won't make him feel betrayed. Foundations of love means there's a cushion to fall back on if he strikes down the idea of treatment.

Therapy will be needed regardless of what's causing his behaviors. I know that he'll get there. It will take time. Thank you for asking for help, it shows you care about his wellbeing.

Note: Sorry if there are any spelling errors or weird phrasing, I'm a little sleepy while I type this out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 03:27:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does he have surgery on his hairline as well? It's a straight line now while before it looked normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How to treat T-induced chest acne? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 22:49:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've got sensitive skin that decided all of the hair I get from T must arrive enveloped in acne. Given how much I cherish my chest hair to relieve my dysphoria, I need to get this shit calmed down.

Did anyone else get chest acne w/ their hair too? How did you treat it?

On a skincare sub in regards to any body acne they said to cut out fragrance in shower gel. I'm willing to do that if it's the only option but having a masculine scent post-shower helps me not feel as bad afterwards :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 15:23:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Firstly, I need you to know that no one here is judging you or thinking you're overdramatic. Trust me, we understand.

You want someone to give you validation. You want confirmation that your behavior is altered because of a diagnosis. A sense of security, an explanation of why you interact with the world the way you do. This an entirely understandable feeling.

You are not a failure whatsoever. With or without a diagnosis, it is absolutely ridiculous to feel that you're a failure. Just because you don't find happiness in places that other people often do (parties, big social circle, etc) doesn't discredit your way of life.

I relate to the self doubting that comes from "Maybe I'm just lazy and everything is my fault". What I've learned through therapy is that I perform at 100% capacity every day. Sometimes 100% means I feel accomplished for brushing my teeth, other days it means doing every chore and go out of my comfort zone to socialize.

None of this is your fault. Any kind of executive dysfunction (Found in depression, anxiety, autism, ADD/ADHD) can result in living differently than others. Think of how many people there must be who love being alone with their dogs, sitting on their porch, going to functions alone, just chilling. There are so many people like you guys, you just don't know because none of you interact!! You're not alone in that way of living and it's a totally viable lifestyle.

You're smart. Well-spoken, engineer's mind. Preferring seclusion is a commonality among people like you. Tinkerers, creative types.
You seem wonderful and I feel it's important to tell you that I'm proud of you for reaching out and potentially giving you a diagnosis that would validate your experiences. Even if you're not on the spectrum, you are just as valid. Don't sweat it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 14:35:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right back at you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 22:21:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Self doubt manifests as a way to protect you. If you assume the worst, anything other than that exceeds expectations.

It's something to be worked on if you have any chance of talking to a therapist or confiding in someone who can remind you that you don't have to rely on that coping mechanism anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-04 19:23:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Welcome to the community :)

I feel like there are so many people out in the world who are deemed as "weird" by peers and in actuality just have undiagnosed autism. I'm not sure if that's your case, but it's the first thing that came to mind when you mentioned bullying.

I received a lot of that in school. Verbal and physical. It actually led me to going an alternative route academically and getting the hell out of there as fast as I could. When I graduated it felt like so much was taken off of my shoulders. High school is hell for people like us (most of the time).

I'm 20 now and I can say with certainty that things will change drastically in the next few years. Hell, even a year from now you might feel like a new person.

You've got a diagnosis which means your school will accommodate you if you ask them to. If people are assholes to you, you'll have extra defensive teachers who honestly protect students way more if they know they're autistic.

The loneliness is different for everybody, much like the spectrum itself. It's common among us, but we have different needs. For me, I'm lonely because I feel like I don't have as many friends as I should. I rationalize and understand that I will have more in the future, it's just not my time to meet them yet. So you may not experience loneliness as you continue to grow and change.

I have a therapist who I adore and now belong to a support group IRL for people with social anxiety. Things get much better.

You will see plenty of negative posts on this sub while browsing. That's people venting, don't let it make you paranoid that things never get better. Sometimes reading other people's venting drains me of hope. Don't make that mistake. Always look ahead.

I make the most longwinded posts and comments. I've got you beat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-04 19:04:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm the king of hating mouth sounds. Biggest sensory trigger for me.

I've never kissed anyone before, but I know that people have had some success in desensitization.

Basically, you have to find a physical sensory touch that you like (having a back massager on your neck, feeling of soft fabric, anything goes) and pair it with the sound of kissing.
I'd recommend doing this using a video of people kissing instead of your boyfriend giving his lips away as a therapeutic treatment. Do it over and over until all you can feel is the positive sense and the sound of kissing playing is no longer in focus. Repeat as long as you need to.

Theoretically, it should help lessen the intensity of the hatred of this sound. If it continues to be a problem, I think a therapist who works with people on the spectrum or even a hypnotherapist could help you much better than attempting anything solo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-04 18:54:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Social media is parasitic and competitive. These people posting photos of events might have had a shitty night at that same event but hype it up so others can see how fun their lifestyle is. It's smoke and mirrors to get others to like and envy you.

Once the camera takes the photo, that fun "smile for the camera" moment is over. They return to reality having mediocre times. Awkward silences in conversation over okay-ish dinners. They're probably wishing they were at home half of the time.

It's all fake. Don't stress about it.
Places like tiktok and tumblr are the only communities I like since they're tailored to things I want to see (+ people like us) and I don't have to engage with people I know outside of the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-04 18:07:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is really beautiful :) You're talented, OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-04 18:06:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm touch aversion extraordinaire.

Love to me is expressed through words, gift giving, and shared vulnerability.
I do fantasize about a life where someone could tuck a strand of hair behind my ear and be able to rest their head on my shoulder. I hope I have that experience. I crave that.

I'm so happy that you've found someone you click with. That must feel absolutely wonderful. Proud of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-04 17:54:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I put the brilliance either way high or low depending on the photo, highlights all the way down, turn back the contrast, sharpen, then use a secondary app to add grain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-04 17:51:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm more of a cat person since they match my temperament, but I do love a good dog.
In the future I plan on getting a borzoi. They're my favorite. Big lovable weirdos.

My problem is that dogs trigger HUGE sensory issues for me. Drinking water and licking their fur has made me have breakdowns many (many many many) times. I hate wet mouth sounds.

I wonder if I would fare better with a small dog?  I've only had big dogs. Small ones could be my cup of tea. Less tongue might equal less sound? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-04 17:42:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm well versed in politics, criminology (not just "I watched some true crime docs and Mindhunter & listened to LPOTL so I'm clearly an expert"-- actual criminology), and film. I have so much information racing through my head constantly. Buzzing.

Other than that, I've been an avid writer since childhood. I plan on starting my novel within this year. It's a life goal of mine to publish something.

Not sure if this counts, but I'm great with helping others. Tons of empathy and over a decade of therapy tools have made me into an amazing shoulder to cry on. People have told me that I've got a calming presence. For how brash I appear, I really am a teddy bear at my core. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-04 17:26:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Everyone interprets the world around them in different ways. We unintentionally interact based off of that perceived reality.

You see life through a lens of fiction. From a young age you most likely developed this viewpoint from consuming media and being strongly influenced by characters. When your brain saw a person you know had traits similar to a fictional character, a bridge was made between fiction and reality and they fused into one.

The only way this would be harmful is if it hurt yourself or others. You're in the clear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-04 17:11:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want you to know that you don't deserve all of this to be happening to you. The amount of change and loss you're experiencing would make anyone, spectrum or not, have a breakdown. I can relate to losing a friend.

Your reactions are cathartic because it's your mind's way of letting all of that energy out. It's trapped inside of your body. All of those pent up emotions.

I have PTSD and I manage my breakdowns by using a few things from my many years of intensive therapy:

- Journaling. Doesn't need to be written down if you don't want it to be. Take your phone, download a journaling app. Even your Notes app works (assuming you have an IPhone, hopefully there's an equivalent if you don't). Turn on voice to text and start talking. You don't need to re-read it. You don't need to keep it on paper for others to find. Rant, cry, scream, whisper. It's all private. It really has helped me so much in life. Please consider it.

- This is kind of obvious, but do you have any pillows you can use for punching, kicking, stomping, throwing? An old pillow designated to beat. Physical aggression is something we all are capable of. Our bodies and mind are connected, so we feel a release of stress when we're able to throw some punches in a way that won't get us in trouble.

- Relying on others isn't the best idea. It feels natural to want closeness and help from loved ones, but it can quickly turn into resentment when they fail to help (and in some instances, make things worse). Set boundaries. Hefty ones. In the case of your girlfriend, tell her exactly what she's doing to not help you right now. As calmly as you can muster. Tell her what she can do to help you more. Again, calmly.

- Find comfort. For me, that's turning on a bunch of fans, watching old movies, playing The Sims, taking naps while listening to audiobooks. I use an orange sheet made of a soft fabric and cocoon myself in it. Create a nest, a pit, an area for you to go relax in. Let yourself eat junk food if you crave it (limit it, of course). Listen to music you loved growing up. Go into a space where you feel nothing can touch you.

You're a grown man who is capable of surviving this. You are going to get this under control regardless of how its making you feel. These circumstances are traumatizing. These breakdowns are natural. You will heal from this pain. I'm not talking about healing through religion (although if that's your thing, utilize that tool of comfort). Healing yourself while knowing you have the support of anyone around you. That could be other friends or family or strangers on Reddit who have hope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-04 16:43:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're not alone in that boat.
[Translation for people who hate phrases: I'm telling this person that there are a lot of other people on the spectrum who don't like their photo taken]. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Aspies who have had sex, do/did your symptoms affect the experience? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-04 16:36:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been particularly curious about what its like to have sensory issues while sleeping with someone.
Along with that, our lack of communicative skills and inability to read nonverbal cues. How do you overcome these things that most people rely on to have good sex?

It's reported people on the spectrum have their first time later in life, but how old were you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-03 07:08:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You doin alright? Mental health and all that shit? Knew someone who would give herself random tattoos because she was having manic episodes. Stay safe, man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-03 06:55:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude, you're being too hard on yourself. I snooped on your post history and you definitely look male. You've got your dysphoria blinders on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-02 22:45:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I turned 20 not even a full month ago. My therapist who got really fast results on T is mid to almost late twenties I think. No one ever told me that starting later makes a difference in the pace of results. Damn.

I'm jealous of cis guys who are my age looking like they do, living their life as a dude without question. I compare my transition a lot to that standard even though I shouldn't. Puberty sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Any late bloomers? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-02 22:01:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are there any guys here who were "late bloomers" in their transition? I'm a couple months away from being 2 years on T and really struggling since my changes have been minuscule and I don't pass whatsoever. I need some hope that in the future this pain will all be worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-02 03:59:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What have they done exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 21:56:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this a fetish thing or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 20:42:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll get all of the boring important stuff out of the way: Do not go without a condom, even if you're on birth control. [You can order free condoms online or seek them out at a clinic if you don't want to buy them at the store](https://www.cosmopolitan.com/sex-love/a15842219/free-condoms/). Porn makes going without condoms look sexy. STIs and unwanted pregnancies are not sexy.

Sex is awkward to talk about for a lot of people. Even more for an aspie. Though there is no shame in talking about it, thinking about it, or having it.

There's a lot more prep to do than just, "Hey wanna fuck?", which doesn't bode well for the communication needed in bed. You guys have to be open and honest, ready to speak about what you want and don't want.

Ask him gently if he's alright with you asking him some sexual questions. If he says yes, you're good to go. Ask him what he's into. What kind of porn he likes. Fantasies he has. What he dislikes in porn. How he feels about sex before marriage (most don't care, but you never know someone's morals if you don't ask).
If you want, you can tell him what your answers are for the same questions.
This is a conversation of vulnerability and bonding. It's great preparation for transitioning into a sexual relationship instead of just a romantic one. Both partners feel heard.

Next, discuss what your first time would consist of. Some people are satisfied with just penetrative sex, others think head and penetration are both expected. Some people consider a handjob to be sex. Or mutual masturbation. Find everything out, get on the same page.

Then, set a date. When and where. It's important to make it a different day than when you first talk about it so there's time carved out to plan and prepare. Plus extra time to consider that you really do want to follow through. Getting tested is an optional but VERY much recommended. Feel secure in your choices.

Make sure the place you have sex is private, comfortable, and safe. A space where you can focus.

When you do have sex, listen to each other. Talk during it. Communication. Is. Key. If he looks nervous, talk about it. Ask each other how things feel. He cannot read social cues or facial expressions, you have to be verbal.

Remember: if at any time you or him decide that you don't want to continue- the other person needs to stop immediately and respect that decision. Doesn't matter if that's in the middle of the first convo or in the middle of sex. Make it abundantly clear.

Sorry this is so long, I'm a very thorough person. Aspie-ism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 20:08:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because people tend to infantilize individuals with any kind of disability or prevalent impairment, our sexualities often get tossed to the side and ignored.

But we do share that huge range of sexualities that NTs have. Although according to a 2017 study we have a [higher chance of hypersexuality and developing paraphilias](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC5789215/).

You're not at all alone in your heightened sense of attraction as an aspie teenager, its completely normal and healthy despite it not being talked about much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 19:43:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I completely agree. It's very hard to control a support community in general. We can see that from communities like incels/mgtow. A group unifying individuals and validating their feelings and experiences turned into a toxic, hateful cult (the term cult being used as an exaggeration to note on their hive-mind mentality, not its literal meaning).

Do I think this sub will turn into that? Most likely not- but it's possible that it could become more toxic than helpful.

When we express frustrations of NTs not understanding us or making us feel like trash, we need to make sure we take a step back and analyze our intentions and tone as we write posts and comments. Instead of validating someone solely through matching their disgruntled attitude in the moment- try truly supporting them. Make the interaction meaningful.

Example:

Post: My sister's friend saw me stimming and said I looked like a freak. I hate NTs so fucking much. I'm sick of their constant judgment.

Response #1 (Validating, unsupportive): What a bitch. NTs say they're openminded until an autistic person is around and suddenly they feel the need to talk shit about someone lmao

Response #2 (Validating, supportive): I'm sorry that happened to you. You're not a freak, man. If you can, you should tell your sister to talk to her friend about it. You have a good chance of getting an apology. People hate being called out when they've been a dick. Can possibly prevent her from doing the same thing to another aspie in the future too >:)

That's just my opinion on a way to improve the community and prevent bitter wallowings. Sorry for being longwinded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 00:31:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The symptom of house neglect in depression is very, very real. I've been there and it is rough to get out of. But you did it!! You're taking control back of not only your surroundings, but your life too.

I've never been on a hike before and I've always been jealous of people who go on them, so you've got me beat on accomplishments.
I am so proud of you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 00:27:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wooooo!! As someone who can't do anything handy, I'm amazed at your skills. You've got to be a wizard or something. Seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 00:25:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm so happy for you!! I know how difficult it is to climb out of those patterns and you're making a great leap into recovery.

I would recommend getting an app to track your progress during this time, whether its an app designed for EDs or just a private journal app. Write down those accomplishments along with any negative self-talk or steps "backward" (bad days/weeks or relapses are, as you know, a part of the process- don't fret about them).

Even though it's not an easy feat, you're gonna make it there. You are going to beat this and become your best self. I'm so proud of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 23:31:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got tested for the virus and my doc was much gentler than this. It's painful regardless, but his doc made it a special kind of brutal.

To anyone seeing this and saying they're not going to get tested because of how painful it looks:
Each swab has to be swirled for 10 seconds total. 20 seconds of your life can save you and others around you. Don't be stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-25 23:45:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Constantly. My brother and I are both on the spectrum and we both talk to ourselves often in ways that aren't "normal".

He talks out loud but I do it internally. My mom always told us to not interrupt him when he was doing it. He used it almost like therapy. Worked out problems through pretend confrontations.

My sessions talking to myself aren't for relaxation/therapeutic purposes. They're mostly entertainment. I get bored and go off into my headspace of new ideas, thoughts, stories. I have so many thoughts racing through my head all the time. So many unexplored concepts.

It's extremely common for autistic people. We're naturally creative. Whether that's engineerial or artistic, it depends on the individual. Either way we're all probably trapped in our heads in some form. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-25 07:44:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm glad you exist too.

We all fit in somewhere. Sometimes that's a place accessed through a screen, but it's just as valid as it would be if it was screenless.

The internet has always been my safe haven. I feel like an alien everywhere else.

I did find one place that I fit in that wasn't online. A support group for people with debilitating social anxiety. It was mostly people on the spectrum. I felt seen.

When you feel ready/have the resources/the world stops being crazy, hit google up to see if you've got any nearby. They're usually hosted in therapy/wellness centers.

I'm not into hugs, but I will give you a virtual hug because you seem really kind: [Hug]. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 23:01:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God, I miss this woman. Her plastic surgery matched her larger than life energy, so I don't consider her botched. It was just how she was meant to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 19:12:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They throw tantrums when a woman says, "Hey I really don't think it's smart for me to have this clump of cells form into a living, breathing human being" before she opts for a termination.

God forbid she doesn't carry that fetus to full term and give it a worse off life with the consequences of what made her get an abortion. Things like not being able to afford their basic needs, having a mental health problem that needs to be worked on before exposing them to an unstable environment, resentment for the child because it's the product of assault/abusive relationship, or being too focused on work/school to find time and not neglect them.

That doesn't make sense to them.

But a pandemic where they could put people in danger because they want to spread germs and walk around even though health officials and the head of the government in America they love so very much say not to? Suddenly choice matters. Fighting for having options and not have law dictate what you can and can't do for your body.

It's genuinely quite funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 03:10:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As an autistic person this makes me very sad :(

I can't blame his family for clinging onto hope during a (seemingly endless) drought of information. It's easier to hold onto the most positive "what if". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 09:46:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey that's the vibe I'm feeling right now :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-20 23:17:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've heard similar sentiments about CNN but haven't looked into them as of yet. It's difficult to separate genuine issues with major news outlets from the people who claim everything they dislike is fake.

I'll look into it since I'm curious. I edited it out of my original comment (for now). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-20 17:49:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty sure she just got a nose job and the rest is editing/filtering with those face altering apps. The photo quality, lighting, and skin smoothness changed drastically. I could be wrong though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-20 17:45:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn't it crazy how the same people who cry "FAKE NEWS" at information from reputable sources like TWP and NYT get their news from Facebook articles, unsourced blog posts, and YouTube conspiracy theory videos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 00:14:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jessica Lange x [Lady in the Radiator](https://images.app.goo.gl/HAFKuuQy2VE3YWcs5) lovechild. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-15 05:54:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Solved solved solved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-15 05:54:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my god, I think that's it! Thank you so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-12 00:08:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am terrible at video games. Unfathomably bad. I get overwhelmed by navigating maps and needing to look at the screen and push buttons at the same time.

The only game that I have loved and played since I was a little kid is The Sims franchise. I know everything about it. Experience with mods and custom content built up over the years and now it feels effortless to sit there for a few hours and just fuck around with new additions to my game. It gives me a chance to build characters and escape my life (which I really need in times like this). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-11 18:42:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a complex time right now.
Unprecedented, none of us know how to feel, cope, or act.
It is completely understandable for you to feel this way. Trapped or secluded are two extremes that we've faced before in life. Being somewhere in the middle is a new experience for us.

I think the best thing to help you out would be talking to the two people you're with about this. They're probably feeling the same way. Mildly claustrophobic from the monotony of quarantine and probably feeling just as worried as you are about their health and safety. Use this time to let everyone know how you feel and they'll reciprocate.

Is there anything you do to cope? A favorite hobby or activity will be your safe haven.
Creating a routine for this time specifically will help you out a lot. Allotted amounts of time with one person, another time with the other. Try to take as much control of this as you can.

Also, I like your username :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 22:16:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely true. I plan to remain in self isolation as long as I can to minimize my risk. Especially since I was just in a hospital building and erring on the side of caution that I could've picked up the virus from that location. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 20:22:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are totally correct. As excited as I am to test negative, there's always a chance of it popping up again. I'm continuing every previous precaution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 20:18:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True! I'm continuing taking my precautions every day regardless of results. My symptom journal will be updated for as long as this pandemic lasts to be extra sure I know what's happening with my body and if I need any more help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 20:12:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for not removing this post, I really appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 20:11:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry you got freaked out by my post :(
It is completely understandable that you're anxious about this pandemic.

With every little cough or ache people can panic, thinking that they've got it. All you can do is ground yourself in reality and remind yourself that you're taking every precaution. The risk for you catching it is wildly low. You're safe.

Something that's helping my friend is keeping a "covid journal". Just any notebook (or diary app) to write about how the events happening in the world are impacting your emotions. Write any symptom you have down and rationalize it into oblivion. Take control.

Thank you so much for your kind words. You seem lovely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> COVID TESTING UPDATE: RESULTS. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 16:06:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I made [this post](https://www.reddit.com/r/aspergers/comments/fy6bos/what_to_expect_if_getting_tested_for_covid19_a/?utm_source=share&utm_medium=ios_app&utm_name=iossmf) yesterday about the process of getting tested for coronavirus. I'm happy to report that in less than 24 hours my results have come back negative.

I checked the site (MyChart) to find that at 5:41am they had entered the results. This surprised me. They had said it'd take 3 to 5 days! Nonetheless, I'm pleased and grateful for not being sick.

I still have to deal with symptoms that are making me feel this way, but it's nothing that can scare me as much as possibly having the virus did.

Getting the testing done, albeit painful, was  so worth it. Now I know for sure that I'm going to be okay and that my family doesn't have to worry about getting sick from me. And I get to cuddle my cat as much as I want without getting anxious that he'll catch something from me :)

Thank you to everyone who commented nice things on my original post. It means so much to me that this community cares and is receptive to my attempt at being helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 15:56:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thankfully he's shown no symptoms! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 14:59:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy to help :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 14:57:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you very much for your kindness. I'm happy knowing I'm helpful to others during a time like this. I know how frustrating it is to search for information and have it give me a vague outline of what I'll go through. Details are soothing to the soul.

The breathlessness progressed like this:

DAY ONE: I began feeling more winded when I was walking around doing normal tasks. Breathing deeply left me with a dull ache in my chest. Not my heart, but my lungs. I brushed it off as anxiety attacks leaving my chest tight. It's a common symptom for me in regards to my mental health impacting my physical wellbeing.

DAY TWO: This is when I knew something was up. It was more intense when I went to lay down or stand up. Along with this, more body aching. A low grade fever joined the party in my body, solidifying my fear of COVID being a possible cause.

DAY THREE: Oh lord. There's almost nothing worse than waking up feeling how I did. Pure pressure and total inability to breathe deeply. When I tried to breathe deeply, my breath hitched. Breaths were shallow and painful. The pain is a tight, dry feeling. You know how sometimes our throats hurt when we wake up after a cold night? Similar pain, but located in the lungs. Intense.

DAY FOUR: Wonderful progress. Instead of continuing to get worse, I'm not struggling to breathe nearly as much (so far). My breaths are still more shallow than usual and the ache remains, but I don't mind since I'm feeling secure that it's going to test negative. It may be wishful thinking but I'm going to embrace it and hope the universe will give me good news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 14:36:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm glad that it was helpful to you :)
I love demystifying scary things for others. I know how much it would have comforted me if I read a post like mine before I went into testing. My anxiety was through the roof from how little I knew about what I was in for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 14:32:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 14:32:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Better than yesterday so far. Not sure how I'll be after I get out of bed, but right now there's less pressure inside my chest, letting me breathe deeper. Improvement! Most with the illness have their symptoms worsen daily, it's an extremely fast paced virus. I'm hopeful that I'll test negative and be informed I just have a nasty flu :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 14:27:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ♥️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 14:27:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem. Today I woke up feeling less strain on my lungs. Yesterday when I woke up it felt like someone was squeezing my lungs, so this is a definite improvement! Other symptoms from previous days are present but not worsened.

I'm optimistic that I might test negative :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 14:22:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't seen many people talk about the testing. That's why I found explaining the process valuable. Taking away that mystery puts us in control of our health!

I actually didn't make the post NSFW, I believe a mod did. Presumably because it could upset someone in the community who is already having trouble coping with the pandemic. Completely understandable if that's the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 09:25:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel you. My mom knew something was really wrong with me when I asked if she could take me to the hospital. Terrified of medical facilities gang.

I'm sending some positive energy your way. I sound like a hippie by saying that, but I mean it. Stay safe. Thank you for being kind to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 09:20:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much. I'm confident that I can handle this >:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 09:18:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been going by the paper they gave me. It reads, "In isolation please try to stay as far away as possible from both human and animal contact as a precaution against transmission".

I'm going to ask a family friend (a doctor who is working with patients of the virus) about it for a second opinion then. Thank you for letting me know.

I'll jump with joy if I can hold my cat without any worry tomorrow. God, I love that little guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 09:14:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It definitely sucks! Those 20 seconds of pain have a great payoff though. Nothing beats being informed about your health. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 09:10:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you very much. I'm planning on updating regardless of a negative or positive result. If its negative I'm going to be very happy.

I'll report how long it took the lab to process my swabs, how they informed me of it, and any other bits of information I'm given about non-COVID sicknesses floating around during this pandemic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 07:35:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm glad too! Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 07:35:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will be thrilled!! After a celebration of health, I'll have to schedule another appointment over the phone to see what my symptoms are from now that the virus is taken out of the list of possible causes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 07:30:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not at all. No gagging, nausea, anything of the sort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 07:26:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll try my very best :) Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 07:26:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I tend to be longwinded. I was worried people would be irritated by it. Thank you for being kind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 07:25:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you very much :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 07:25:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd recommend using any spare notebooks (or virtual ones) to track symptoms if they pop up. It aides with feeling in control of something as intangible as a sickness and helps doctors in the process.

Keep her feeling confident that she's doing well during this crisis. I know that when I feel like the whole world is a mess it brings me peace if anyone tells me I'm doing a good job with what life has dealt me.

Make sure to take care of yourself too. Caretakers and loved ones of people who wouldn't deal with illness well carry the weight of the world on their shoulders during this pandemic. You sacrifice a lot for the comfort and safety of your child and I want to thank you for that.

Every human being has strength inside them, including your daughter. Things are going to be okay no matter what. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 07:10:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Think about it this way: it's 20 seconds of your life that hurt. But that pain can supply you with results that can change/save your life altogether. Not only that, but testing helps you know if you're going to harm others by passing on an illness that they might not be able to fight off like you can.

If you develop worrying symptoms (which with the precautions of quarantining and necessary hand washing- the majority of people won't get it at all), you're in the hands of doctors who will make it as pain free and short as they can. It's so worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 07:03:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can with proper precautions like disposable gloves and keeping away from their face. But since I touch his face so often it's easier for me to love him from afar.

If you search the risk of giving it to domestic animals there's two distinct results: that its entirely transmittable to pets or zero risk. I'm only following what it says on my paperwork from the hospital since google results, even from reliable sources, don't feel solid enough for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 06:20:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely. When I get my results I'll make another post and if I'm positive, I'll do recovery updates throughout the process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> WHAT TO EXPECT IF GETTING TESTED FOR COVID-19: A TIMELINE OF MY EXPERIENCE. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 04:28:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> UPDATE: As of April 10th, my results have come back negative in less than 24 hours. I'm so happy right now. I'm going to continue every precaution regardless of my results just to be safe. [Here's my update post.](https://reddit.app.link/gl4atxpRz5)

I wanted to post how it went for me so on the off chance anyone else needs to be tested, there won't be as much fear of the unknown. That's one of my biggest issues, going into a new situation anxious because of not knowing what to expect.

I'm in the United States in the midwest. I don't know if other states have different procedures, so please look up info from your local hospital regarding testing.

I hope that everyone reading this is healthy and safe. If this helps anyone, I'm glad. If it doesn't apply to any of you, I'm glad too.

STEP ONE.

I realized that over the past few days I had been having some weird symptoms. Shortness of breath, a dry cough, shallow lungs, headache, fatigue. I'm a very anxious/paranoid person, so I brushed it off thinking that I was simply imagining it- that it was my anxiety. Until I got a fever and woke up feeling like something was sitting on my chest, I really couldn't breathe. Lungs hurt, throat hurt.

I made a phone appointment with a doctor. I hate talking on the phone but I had to.
She asked me about my symptoms and had me breathe as deep as I could while counting to see how deep my lungs would let me go. She said that she didn't like how it sounded and that she would like if I went to the hospital ER for a screening.

I was to call the hospital before arriving so they know I'm going to be there.

STEP TWO.

Once I called and told them I was coming, I was driven there. They weren't using the tent like I was told they would. That was due to weather.

They had me go inside in a separate room that they're using for screenings. I had to go without my mom, who usually helps me talk to doctors since I have a phobia of hospitals. It was explained to me that they didn't want anyone to catch it from the screening room. Extra safety precaution.

I was given a mask and sanitized my hands immediately.

I went over my symptoms, answered basic questions, and had my vitals taken by the nurse. This included taking my temperature, my blood pressure, and my heart rate.

The doctor came in and did the same thing the nurse had done. She asked more questions, mainly about how I might have been exposed to the virus.
I explained that I've only seen two people during this pandemic. I asked if I could have gotten it from a delivery person who didn't clean their hands and was told it was possible.

She told me that I do have to get tested at the main campus of the hospital downtown from where I live. That there's an uncomfortably large chance that I could have it.

I was told about how scheduling testing would work. I'd go home and receive a call to schedule a same-day appointment.

I went home at 2pm and got called at 2:30pm. The hospital called me up and I got an appointment for 4pm.

STEP THREE.

We followed the directions to go to the testing. It was located in a parking garage of the hospital. On arrival there was a plethora of signs.

The signs said "Please keep your windows closed, follow the signals of the workers around you". Everyone there had masks and hazmats on. Some police officers had yellow reflective vests. It felt weird, but not scary.

I called from the car to confirm my appointment with a doctor who we could see outside of our side window. She told us to move ahead in the line of cars and continue to follow the instructions on boards and signals of workers.

The line went faster than expected.
The final sign said to roll down the window of the person getting tested (mine was the passenger window) and turn the car off.

A doctor greeted me and asked me for my name, birthday, and my address to confirm that I was who I said I was.

She had two large cotton swabs with her. She said in a kind voice that she's going to have me put my head on the car headrest with my chin up.

I was told that she's going to go very far back through my nose to my throat and that the swabs inside will be swirled for 10 seconds. Both nostrils will be tested and it will be hard to not push her away.

I was handed tissues in case my nose ran afterward. I was nervous but comforted by how gentle she was being. My mom held my hand.

She put the first swab in and had a hard time finding the path. I have weird nostrils. After 4 seconds of the first swab she got in the right area. It was not pleasant. It did hurt pretty bad. It feels sharp and I imagined the swab touching my brain. In reality, it was just the back of my throat.

She told me I was doing good and started to count. I counted with her. At 10, she took the swab out. I took a deep breath and asked if I could take a drink of water before the second swab. She said of course, and I drank the water and centered myself.

The second nostril was much easier since I knew what to expect. The pain was present but I was able to relax more. I counted with her again and it was done.

The doctor told me she was proud of me and that I'll get my results in 3 to 5 days. They'll send them through email, over the phone, and on MyChart.

STEP FOUR.

For now I have to remain in isolation while waiting for the results. It's just me and my mom, so I'm okay.

This means I can't even cuddle with my therapy cat, but I can have him sit in the same room as me and pet him from afar with a back massager I have as long as I clean it every single time I touch it.

I had been brave all day with phone calls, solo doc appointments, and with the testing experience. On the drive home I finally cried for the first time during this whole ordeal when I read the part about not holding my cat.


If anyone has questions, feel free to ask me in the comments. Thank you for reading. I hope you're well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Struggling to get through season eight. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 01:49:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been watching this series with my mom every day for a few months. The seventh and eighth seasons have been god awful. Eighth being the worst. I really don't understand how they let this air.

Every storyline is ridiculous and the characters feel like caricatures of themselves from past seasons. I read all the spoilers because I truly don't care anymore. But I can't give up since I've spent months watching these people grow :(

Am I the only one who hated this one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 18:38:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 20, immunocompromised. Moderate risk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-08 04:58:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had health issues that caused mine to be super heavy and last almost two weeks per month, so I can 100% say I feel that pain. It's bullshit and I wish it had an off switch.

For now, best thing you can do is treat it clinically and minimally. For me that meant seeing it as another bodily function that I had to get through. Nothing more than that. Pretended like everyone else had it too.
I also would double up on both products, the super plus forms, wear them at the same time. Would only have to change the non pad one twice a day.

Also, bonus if you're extra dysphoric: Take products out of their boxes and put them in a plain container so you don't have to get misgendered via marketing when you go to grab one. Cramp meds can go in empty mens vitamin bottles too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-08 04:48:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That quote is genius, I've never heard that before. I wrote it down so I can repeat it to my therapist. I've had a pretty difficult journey in transitioning and I'm going to try my hardest to not be so harsh on myself about what I think I'm supposed to look like.

I'm trying to use this time in quarantine to work on my confidence. I think that's really what makes me find a guy attractive. Someone who even if they're shy, they're okay with themselves. I might never be conventionally attractive but I'll try to feel hot. I'll get there one day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-08 04:43:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ever since I was a kid I had that "Do I find this guy hot or do I just want to look like him" thing going on. It's still set in my brain to be that way and I really need to take action against it. You're completely right.

I journaled out a list of things I like about myself. It's only three for now and they're kind of goofy but I was able to do it. I'm happy about that.

Thank you for the support. It means a lot to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-08 04:37:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Both my group therapy and solo therapist are offering phone appointments. I've been avoiding them since I also have that same issue with phone calls, but amplified because I have sensory issues (ASD).

My therapist is a trans guy too so it definitely would help rn. I might try to give it a shot since the pros outweigh the cons. Thanks, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-07 23:29:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love astrology. It's a huge passion of mine.

With that being said, your birth chart does not dictate whether you have shitty behavior or not. Everyone is in control of their ability to not be a cunt who spreads misinformation to feel like a quirky outsider going against the grain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tips on how to not compare yourself to other guys? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-07 23:12:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see beautiful guys and my first instinct is to compare myself to them. Knowing I'll never be cis. It's even worse when its another trans guy who passes extremely well.

I wasn't very blessed when it comes to my timeline of transition. I don't pass visibly or audibly. I don't know if I ever will. Since I have all of this free time in quarantine (and no therapy for the same reason) I can't stop obsessing over how inadequate I feel.

It's rough and everyone keeps telling me to not compare myself to others. But how? It'd be helpful for someone to give me tips on how to stop. I'm willing to try anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-07 17:39:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why'd they do her dirty like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-03 03:35:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm going to go visit my Grandma.
I miss her so much and it makes me want to cry knowing I can't see her right now.
Shoutout to Linda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-31 07:40:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kitty cat :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-31 00:21:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely 100% relate. I still have massive issues with keeping up with dental hygiene due to depression, but I've found a few things that help with tooth brushing sensory-wise.

[This toothbrush called 'Radius'](https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07NP8XFV4/ref=cm_sw_r_cp_api_i_m7MGEbWHJ9HH4) is great. It's huge so you can get all areas of your mouth quickly. Makes the process shorter, so its better.

A toothpaste that doesn't taste like disgusting fake mint is actually for kids, but it makes a huge difference. [Here's that](https://www.walmart.com/ip/Aquafresh-Fluoride-Toothpaste-Kids-Cavity-Protection-Bubble-Mint-4-6-OZ/10453056). It barely tastes like anything at all and after your finished there's no aftertaste.

If its the texture of toothpaste that's bugging you, I've heard that Lush makes [different forms of it](https://www.lushusa.com/face/teeth/) in jelly and tablets. I've been wanting to try the tabs for so long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-31 00:07:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My medications cause me to have vivid dreams and be able to recount them when I wake up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 22:42:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm getting Dean vibes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 22:42:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll rephrase (I'm on the spectrum, sometimes I mess up what I'm trying to say because of my wording).

I was referring to the idea of being able to gender someone's writing. You mentioned programs that identify femininity or masculinity. Appealing to what a computer registers as your identity is a difficult and fruitless task that only harms how you feel about yourself.

I hope I'm being coherent. Sorry about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 22:36:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You sound eerily similar to me. I'm going to be on T for 2 years in June. If I don't try, my voice remains androgynous-ish, gets higher when I'm around women. Which is basically every day since I live with one. But around cis men it goes down.

I'll be real. It doesn't seem like everyone gets the voice drop naturally on T after only a year. I went on a higher dose and thought it'd make my voice drop faster. It didn't. I felt miserable until I asked the tough question: if it'll ever change.

My doc explained it as, "You're one and a half years on testosterone. Male puberty for one year. That's a fourteen year old boy. You are allowed to have the voice of a fourteen year old boy for now".

My voice is slowly dropping now because I've been using a pitch app to track it. It's a mixture of patience (I know how devastating it is to hear that it takes time. I'm sorry. It's unfair and I wish it was different) and working on it every day. That's what you've gotta do, man. Doing your part as your body takes time to go thru these changes is important.

We're gonna be alright. Our voices will drop and our dysphoria will lessen. You've got this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 22:26:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think its a good idea to force change when its unnecessary. If you're writing the way you always have, its male. You're male. If you started writing any other way, sure you'd allegedly seem even more masculine to other people, but you wouldn't be you anymore. Changing the way you speak to appeal to others isn't worth betraying authenticity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-29 23:11:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I survived trauma regarding mass homicide so this is extra fucking ridiculous and borderline offensive to me. Trivializing school shootings because some pasty boring ass drag queen got his feewings hurt while on a reality competition show. Fuck off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 17:01:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I told my mom that I'm not going to vote if that predatory alzheimer patient is my only blue choice, she lost her shit. Sorry, ma. I hate all rapist pigs equally, regardless of color. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 07:26:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think they're trying to say
"Woman stay inside = no meaning, no smart, no struggles, vapid" Vs. "Man stay inside = deep, intellectual, misunderstood, profound".

Because every shy woman is shallow and doesn't face the turmoil the average shy guy does I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 02:19:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a best friend who is also on the spectrum. We live across the country from each other but have known each other for nearing three years. We're inseparable. Talking to him is like speaking a secret language that only we know.

He doesn't have a supportive family, so my family steps in and gives him the love he needs. I can't even find words to describe how much I love him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 01:50:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Sims. It's been an on/off interest that I've had since I was nine and was using it as an escapist coping mechanism at the time.

It works great for stress management and fun making/using mods + custom content. Those can be a project that I look forward to for a whole week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 22:25:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YES. I'm constantly touching and cleaning mine. I even use a back massager on them, which when its pressed against ears it feels like heaven. Some people would find that overwhelming though.
Ear gang. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 17:49:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The envy I have right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 18:47:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Since sexuality/flirting has a lot to do with picking up on nonverbal communication, it's common to feel this way. We usually don't notice or reciprocate hidden signals.

I'll probably need my future partner to take me by the shoulders and say, "I AM ATTRACTED TO YOU" or I will never register it.

But there is help for this! I recommend watching [Sexplanations video on flirting](https://youtu.be/HWDGrUQr-60). She's a sexologist and has a lot of useful stuff that's helped me figure things out. Tons of resources for people who need things put in plain words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 18:33:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy birthday! I'm turning 20 next month and I'm hoping for a similar experience. I never liked going big on birthdays. Just a simple and pleasant day will suffice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 18:28:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's wonderful!!!! I'm so happy for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 18:25:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, frequently. The only way I stop obsessing over it is talking to someone else about what happened.

Usually they will make you feel better or add their own story of embarrassing moments. Aspie or not, we all cringe at our previous selves. Trust me, it helps so much to talk about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-21 21:01:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a little boy trapped in a cat body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-21 20:58:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 01:14:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please tell me this is a troll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-16 20:01:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not weird at all. You have a nurturing spirit. Maybe that's your calling in life. Taking care of children in a daycare, being a maternity ward hospital volunteer, or a teacher/teacher's aide. Don't let anyone put you down for having a passion. If they do, tell them that you're sorry they don't have as big of a heart as you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-16 19:58:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looking at your post history, I'm quite concerned :(

It seems like you've got a lot of negative habits trying to combat your symptoms. This includes your special interest with drugs turning into a reality of using recreationally.

I have no opinions on the average young adult's drug experimentation, but it is dangerous when it's paired with mental illness or disability.

Your obsession with suicide and self harm isn't healthy. You've had multiple suicide attempts along with many threats.

I want to ask you, are you okay today? Is there anything you need resources to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-16 19:46:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's awful of her. Wearing a corset seems to be a coping tool for you. You should be allowed to wear what makes you feel comfortable. Is there any way you could convince her to give it back? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-16 19:28:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> KING </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-16 19:27:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wore a corset for almost two years (I'm also a guy). It gave me a more severe, noticeable, and feminine figure. I regret it now.

I'd suggest wearing binders. They're thin, comfortable, and very tight.

Binders are often used by transgender men to flatten their chests for a male chest. But originally they were made for compression after surgery without being too bulky or uncomfortable.

I'd recommend [Underworks binders](https://www.underworks.com/men-compression-shirts) for you.

They're undetectable under clothes AND their compression is better than any other brand. Everyone can use them. They come in a good range of sizes as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-16 19:14:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seagulls are misunderstood. People think they're gross or annoying. I think they're wonderful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-16 19:12:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unfortunately. I have a heavy brow so I often look angry when I'm not.

When I'm "in my own world" aka zoning out, or anxious, I look like I'm scared. Very wide eyed.

Facial expressions are weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-13 16:49:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> .... Am I the only one who likes her new nose? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 16:44:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congrats on your top surgery! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-04 21:23:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tulsi - March 8th </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-04 21:22:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Elizabeth Warren - March 6th </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-04 06:02:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you :)
I came to the realization that I needed more help when I was reviewing how my mental health had been for the past year in late 2019. I had a therapist at the time that I was comfortable talking to but not making any positive progress with. I had a relapse and I was more isolated than ever.

I made the goal of saying goodbye to that therapist and finding someone more equipped to handle my issues. Found my current therapist who works at a big mental health facility. Very different from any therapist I've had before that were in smaller offices.

Through the process of paperwork I was told about the free groups and classes they offered. My gut told me that I needed to push myself to go even when my anxiety told me that I shouldn't. So I waited until I felt very safe and ready in my new solo therapy before I inquired about going to group.
It went so much better than I imagined :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-04 04:22:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My regular one-on-one therapist is at a mental health center, so he had told me about the programs they have there.

They definitely exist. If you Google outpatient mental health services in your area, you'll most likely find a place that has groups. I really hope you do because it went great for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm going to my first group therapy session today and I'm a little terrified. Wish me luck? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 19:01:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a group for social anxiety / social skills. I'm so worried that I'm going to be the most severe case (Haven't spoken to anyone besides family and docs/therapists for five years).

I have a tendency to avoid uncomfortable situations and when given the opportunity. All I do is run away, cancel plans, leave early.
I made it a goal for this year that I won't do that anymore.
I'm pushing myself to go to this thing. I have to get better and learn how to talk to people if I want things to change.

Wish me luck, guys.

UPDATE: It went so well! I wasn't able to talk right away but after I warmed up to everyone I was able to chime in. I felt like I fit in for the first time. No one was judging if I was better or worse than them and everyone had their own quirks.
Someone sat next to me and even shook my hand when he did. That was the best part for me. I rarely have human contact and I didn't expect to any time soon. He was comfortable enough to choose to shake my hand :)
We did mindfulness exercises and talked a lot about our experiences and interests. I learned about everyones lives and realized that some were very similar to mine. I don't feel as alone knowing that I'm validated for how I live.

I will be going to group and individual therapy every week from now on.
Thank you to everyone who was supportive and wished me the best! All of that positivity really meant a lot to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 18:30:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Controversial opinion here. She's still very pretty, even with the egregious amount of filler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are your stims? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-01 17:44:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine is cracking my joints. Mainly my neck, hands, and legs but sometimes my feet and my hips too. I have [hEDS](https://www.ehlers-danlos.com/2017-eds-classification-non-experts/hypermobile-ehlers-danlos-syndrome-clinical-description-natural-history/) so my body is bendy and crackable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 22:41:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Legitimate IQ tests can usually only be taken when they're mandated. For example, mine was done when I was getting a 504 plan in school. Online tests are worthless.

I'm sure you'd be able to find a way to take one locally. It most likely will cost you though. I can't imagine they're handing them out for free since someone will be either monitoring or dictating the test as you take it.

Truthfully, IQ doesn't mean shit. Mine was 141 yet I can't do basic math. It's not indicative of all intelligence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 22:31:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Welcome back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 22:16:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've smoked weed intermittently for a few years now. Small doses, never getting hardcore stoned.

There's a vast difference between the effects of indica vs sativa to me. Indica makes me normal. Temporarily cures my auditory sensory issues. I become friendly and talkative.

Sativa makes me nuts. Paranoid, racing thoughts, can't feel sensory input like touch and temperature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 22:07:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't have any social media besides here, a blog, and a film review site. None of which are attached to people from my past.

I would recommend everyone gets rid of negative content that invades their life and creates depression or anxiety. In a click of a button we can free ourselves from that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 22:05:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exceedingly common for us. It's a bad feeling. All-consuming irritation. For me it turns into aggression/rage where I (childishly) lash out at others. Thankfully I learned some coping skills to replace that behavior with.

Listening to audiobooks to take myself out of the moment, scribbling on a notepad harshly, loud music. All very helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 22:00:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only way to get this in order is to be direct with him. Bluntly tell him that you're interested and if he's not comfortable with you pursuing him that you'll stop. Follow through on this promise.

You don't want to make him uncomfortable by continuing when he doesn't want you to. He may have strong feelings for you but is too insecure to act on them. A possible relationship is daunting to us. We need some space to ruminate over it and become content with the idea of closeness.

Put your platonic relationship on the forefront, romantic inclinations on the back burner. Room to breathe makes everything better, safer, enjoyable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 21:49:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's called the autism spectrum for a reason. We all have symptoms, but none of us are identical in our issues, traits, capabilities, and behaviors.

There's no "right" way to be autistic. Professionals who are able to diagnose are aware of this. If they aren't diagnosing you fairly, you always have the option of getting a second opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-24 14:35:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being on the spectrum affects how we process information, how we react, how we behave. It's completely reasonable that you have an "abnormal" way of handling loss.

You may have a sudden wave of distress at some point. It can hit you out of nowhere. But if you don't, there's nothing wrong with that.

It's socially acceptable to pretend to be sadder than you are, so do that if you want to blend in during the funeral procedures.

I am very sorry that you lost someone you love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 16:47:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People are assholes, man. They'll always find a way to make you feel like shit.
They don't actually care about your weight. All they want to do is feel superior. Bullies find a way to pick on something they assume you're insecure about. You look completely healthy and normal. Nothing to worry about there.

I looked at your post history like I do with most people on this sub before I comment. You've got drawings on there that look fucking professional. Legit the cleanest lines I've ever seen. That's some shit that they can't make you feel bad about. You're extremely talented. Fifteen and able to make art like that? Jesus.

Ignore the cunts who put you down. I know its hard not to be affected by their bullshit. You've got this though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 16:27:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a cat who has epilepsy, this doesn't resemble what I've seen in his seizures. If it is one, it's definitely not grand mal/tonic clonic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-19 23:12:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My future is one of the few things in my life that I have control over, so I fantasize about what I want a lot.

A simple life. I've spent nearly twenty years in almost constant duress.

I'd like to move out into my own apartment and create an environment of comfort and stability. Lose weight and get healthier while cultivating my independence.
Once I'm ready I want to date and find "the one". There's a lid for every pot. Someone will fall for me as hard as I fall for them.
I'm going to adopt and probably be the softest, most passive father. My husband will have to be the stricter one.
Get a job from home, write books as a hobby or part time gig, raise a family. Die at 94. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-19 22:59:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I only wear oversized black clothing because I'm insecure about how I look and don't want to accentuate any of my features. It's easier for my colorblindness too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 00:02:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Something we all have to remember is that there are going to be lots of people in life or online that don't understand us. Even people who will go out of their way to be assholes to us because of our autism.

These people are not the majority anymore. Autism is talked about. There are accommodations made for us in schools and work environments. Representation on TV and in film. Programs in communities like support groups, social groups, and workshops. We're finally being seen and its taken a lot of time and patience to get to this point.

Antivaxxers have dug up completely disproven information and weaponized their own stupidity to bash what we go through (Simplified: They use our diagnosis as their "proof" that vaccines cause bad things to happen. This is completely false and doesn't have science to back the claim up).
This is their problem. Not ours.

They'll be shamed on public platforms by anyone who is brave enough to confront them and tell them to fuck off.

Don't sweat it. The people who call us retards are ironically more retarded than we'll ever be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-17 23:51:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your family members are assholes for pulling that "joke". That's downright humiliation and I'm sorry you had to experience it.

I don't know how sensory reliant you are. Like if you could instead write the sentences down instead of saying them with the same level of satisfaction. Though if you could try, that'd be great. It's definitely more socially acceptable to use that outlet.

If that's not working, I'd say try using some kind of stress toy or fidget toy. Handheld, preferably silent. Or if people around you don't mind I think pen clicking would help.

But at the end of the day, you're just doing what comes natural for you. Yes, it may be a distracting symptom, but why is their slight irritation/discomfort more important than you functioning how you were meant to? Your brain gives you these impulses for a reason. As long as you're keeping your hands to yourself, not saying insensitive or dangerous phrases, you're a grown adult who deserves to be able to repeat or move around when you need to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-17 23:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I grew up watching Monk. It was nice to see representation of a successful person who isn't neurotypical. Especially someone with a caretaker.

Autism and OCD have a lot of overlap in symptoms. On the show its stated that he just has OCD, but since he's fictional you can decide for yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-16 17:41:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 10:43:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've worked way too hard to anchor myself in this world to give it up now. I didn't plan to see sixteen years old, now I'm turning twenty in a couple of months.

I made myself available to accept the universe's fruit. I make the best of what I have and show gratitude for it every day. My small handful of family members who support me. My therapy cat who adores me. My closest friend who makes me feel like a whole person. My passion for art and film.

And most importantly,
Because I want to live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 04:03:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That hasn't been the case for me but it is a possibility. Thank you for mentioning that.
OP, do what feels right to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 23:09:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing about a spectrum is uniform, clean cut, or systematic. One kid might constantly rock back and forth sucking his thumb while the other with the exact same diagnosis is off in the corner just tapping his pen and keeping his self soothing on the inside while he studies intensely. Every aspie is so different. That's why cataloguing everything is crucial.

Your best tool in figuring out how to raise someone with aspergers is through experience and observation. You should keep a journal to write things down about patterns.
For example, if he strongly dislikes a sound, texture, or taste, try your best to remove it (or him) from the situation and write it down for future notice. If you see meltdowns happen, note what time of day, location, and the events that went on before the breakdown occurred. Jot every single thing down if it happens twice or more (or if it elicits a strong reaction from the first time).

The vast majority of aspies feel socially isolated, misunderstood, outcasted, and anxious because of our differences from the "norm". This is why you need to pour so much love and compassion into his life.

Simple things like making sure his favorite shirt is washed on Sunday so he can wear it to school on Monday, asking permission for hugs instead of going right in, listening when he's talking about something he loves without interrupting or seeming bored, asking him if he feels like socializing or if he wants to be left alone. These small things mean the world to us.

I'd strongly recommend [The Out Of Sync Child](https://www.amazon.com/Sync-Child-Carol-Stock-Kranowitz/dp/0399523863/ref=mp_s_a_1_12?keywords=Carol+Kranowitz&qid=1581113020&s=books&sr=1-12) by Carol Kranowitz. Absolutely a must-read for you. I believe there are follow up books after this one that branch into other topics of autism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 22:33:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love cats. Especially [my therapy cat](https://ibb.co/9VWvNTS). He's the reason I'm happy to wake up every morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 22:29:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just straight up say, "I'm on the autism spectrum, haircuts are difficult for me. I'd rather not talk". Since you're the one paying them, they have to oblige.

Being forward with my needs and worries has helped me so much.

You can do this, you're going to look and feel great afterwards. I always do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-06 08:19:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You both just happen to type the exact same way? That added onto the over-the-top, cartoonish wording makes me pretty sure this is edited or entirely fake.

There are people that thought the same thing in the comments and got downvoted for it, so this'll probably fare just as well. But come on. The capitalization in the middle of sentences is a dead giveaway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-06 08:07:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whoever did her hair needs their hands chopped off. That patchiness is criminal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-02 06:16:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Somewhere non-Wisconsin. Sorry, man :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-01 23:41:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm off in the midwest. Maybe he can teleport though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-01 19:08:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Completely normal. Think about first puberty. Emotions running rampant, impulsiveness, sensitivity, and maybe even aggression.

When the body is introduced to an influx of hormones, it causes an emotional reaction. This is your second puberty, so expect that it's going to be as much of a rollercoaster that whacks you on the head with a random extreme emotion whenever it wants.

This can be an issue if they turn into depression, anxiety, or anger problems if they don't stop at just being period-esque mood swings. Make sure you have a support system who knows about these feelings and maybe a professional if it gets too rough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-01 18:53:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's so sweet. I'm happy for you, dude.
Also now I want Mcdonalds. I'm blaming my clogged arteries on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I FOUND A TRANS GUY THERAPIST. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-01 18:51:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've needed to switch therapists for a while now because my therapist before was very sweet but I wasn't seeing enough progress with her. I felt so stagnant.

While browsing a site to find someone else I saw this guy who specifically works with lgbt people and I was like, sick. Time to email him.

When he told me he was a trans guy too I was ecstatic. In person we really clicked and I've been looking forward to our next session all week. Finally someone understands what I'm talking about on a personal level!! He gets it!!

The place he works for has a group for lgbt people too which I can go to if I want. Maybe to learn some social skills and make a few acquaintances?

I think this is going to be a turning point in my life. I think I'm going to get better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-13 08:55:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You look absolutely beautiful. If I was a girl I'd 100% shave my head. I feel like its more of a statement challenging conventional beauty than other haircuts could ever be. Seriously looks incredible on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 18:18:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You probably should have waited a bit longer before taking the screenshot. The "1 second" time mark gave it away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 18:13:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck. Guess I'll never be able to get my mom a dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 18:09:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can't wrap my head around what the dog's purpose was while being next to two things that are supposed to show how she's a hypocrite.
What does her son being gay have to do with marriage? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 08:50:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm calling fake on this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 08:48:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unbalanced.
Socially inept while being reasonably intelligent (even educated on body language and other silent cues, manipulation tactics to appear more confident, etc. but still can't figure out how to implement them).
Very rational and great at problem solving for other people's issues, but freezing when I think about how to get out of a mildly annoying situation of my own.
One moment I'm observing life from a wise old man's point of view and the next I feel like a seven year old who just lost his mom in the grocery store. Needing help for small things that I feel as if I should be independent with by now.
Hyper-focused and passionate while still managing to get nothing done most days due to feeling distracted and retreating back to my "own little world".

My mind is very fragmented thanks to autism. I can't be too mad though. It didn't plan to be structured this way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 00:12:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happens all the time for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 00:07:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It sounds like you're having a really nice day. Love you too :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-08 09:05:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Proud of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-07 19:35:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Mindblowing" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-07 08:39:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now that's a king right there!! He's a pretty damn handsome guy if I do say so myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-06 08:05:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Makeup inspired by raw meat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-04 23:52:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm gay but I want to marry this woman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-03 06:06:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A cute puppy AND a cute lady! Beautiful photo, 10/10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-03 06:02:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone tell these Instagram girls to work out to get an ass instead of getting procedures.

Sure, it won't be as drastic and it'll take a lot of hard work to achieve-- but hey, it saves you money AND won't make your cheeks resemble a cubist painting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-01 13:22:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't even fathom that someone can live 107 years. Holy shit. She's amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-31 23:25:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're not a terrible person at all. From my perspective, it sounds like she's irritable already. I'm very agitated when I'm ill or tired. Even if I love someone, sometimes I say a mean comment before I think about how it makes the person it's directed at's feelings.

Situations like this make us feel alienated and bad about ourselves. But just remember, if you didn't have any bad intentions when you do or say something, other people's reactions to it are the issue.

The solution is usually to ask them what made them upset and ask how you can make it better. Their feelings are as real as yours. How they interpreted what you said matters. All you can do is try your best to avoid it happening again. It's not your fault if you didn't mean to do anything to make her upset.

Communication and compassion fixes all issues like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-31 23:15:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't apologize unless I mean it. It's not favorable to the person that wants/expects the apology but I'd rather not feel like I'm betraying how I genuinely feel to commit to a social expectancy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-31 23:14:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think that age/gender flairs would be the most helpful. Special interest flairs sound fun, but wouldn't be very easy on the eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-31 23:05:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gay community has loads of BBL surgeries. It's not that uncommon to see drag performers or gay pornstars with something surgical going on there. Unfortunately, the ideal bubble butt ends up being a pumpkin butt.

Source: I am gay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-31 22:59:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm colorblind but I'm sure it looks fantastic. Wish her a happy new year for me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-31 22:56:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My parents have two autistic kids out of three children total. Must have sinned extra hard and that's why I'm socially inept and have sensory processing disorder. Makes so much sense, logic simply cannot be more unflawed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-28 20:36:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If your faith isn't strong enough to understand that your God will be able to handle the sins of those who fictionalize things about him/his son, maybe you're not as holy as you thought.

There is no rationality in boycotting an entire streaming platform for someone's (albeit distasteful) creative choice in their project.

I'm not religious but I grew up Catholic. Religion makes people extra sensitive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-28 19:10:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Crabs are just a different kind of spider. Change my mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-28 08:51:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He looks like he gives really good hugs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 22:30:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aren't these supposed to be the people who hate the easily offended? They seem pretty damn triggered by "Big Tech". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 17:00:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone needs to put a sprinkle of rat poisoning in his goddamn sandwich. Fuck this guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Clothes are difficult. Can I have your opinion? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-26 18:36:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One of my new years goals is to stop wearing the same outfit over and over again until the clothes eventually get too worn out to wear.

I've tried buying new "normal people" clothes and I always end up feeling awful wearing them. I feel uncomfortable in jeans and a normal fit tshirt. How do people change into clothes every day and not hate how they feel? Anyways, back to my point.

I usually wear sweatpants and a very oversized shirt every day. I wear them during the day and to sleep. I feel like I should change that.

Should I try yet again to push myself into "regular people clothes" or stick to comfort? I'm trying to find a happy medium between the two but its difficult.

It's even harder to find decent big & tall clothes since I'm a giant. Clothes shopping is a nightmare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-26 17:26:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Firstly, you're absolutely adorable.

Now that that's out of the way, time for my dating spiel. You are definitely going to have loads of bad dates before you get to a perfect one.

I'm a firm believer that there's only sour grapes to make juicy ones taste sweeter. There's going to be one date in the near future  that will feel fucking magical and make all of the previous unsuccessful dates feel worth it.

Keep at it. Don't give up on hope. Discouragement is expected-- we're all humans who get bummed out when things don't go as planned. Just don't let it consume you entirely.

When you find the right person you're going to look back on this exact moment and smile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I only got misgendered once this Christmas! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-26 04:36:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you would have told little closeted me at 15 that in 4 years I'd have completely cut off my toxic side of the family, have come out to everyone else, started T, and would have my entire true family call me the correct pronouns and name, I wouldn't have believed  it for a second.

I am so grateful. My 75 year old grandmother is my biggest supporter. Even my brother, who I just told 2 months ago after waiting YEARS, got everything right. There was a single accidental pronoun slip, but it was quickly corrected and apologized for.

My battles with dysphoria can blind me to how much I have to be thankful for in my transition. There are so many guys out there that don't have the opportunity to come out, or to cut abusive family off. Hell, I never thought I would.

These moments make the struggles feel worth it.

I'm hoping that everyone reading this has at least one good thing to pull out of this holiday season. If not, just know this: you are a real man, you won't always be stuck in this situation, and you are very loved. Whether its by family, friends in person, online friends, or by strangers on Reddit, you are cared about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 04:55:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love you, Porkchop. Very beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-20 02:30:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Weird that the notoriously homophobic political party feels the need to suck Trump's dick every two minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-18 22:29:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your stretch marks look just like mine. Really happy to see someone else has them. Thank you for that, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-18 22:18:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fantastic harvest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-15 16:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, super edgy. That's just so badass of you, man. You're really rebellious for driving your car with a bunch of stickers referencing a 16 year old environmental activist who you've never met. I bet chicks are just dying to get with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-12 22:18:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a extremely high pain tolerance. When I was a kid though, I was hypersensitive to pain. I think that was due to trauma and not because of my disability.

Weather, I can't get too cold but I can get too warm if anything is above 67 degrees. I overheat quickly and frequently. My body temp runs at around 99.5 on an average day. Human furnace.

My sensory issues are major, so I relate to the last portion of what you said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Grateful for Google. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-12 05:56:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wanted to say how grateful I am for how I can type into google, "intrusive thought about ______", and be shown hundreds of results from people like me, or therapists, or doctors explaining their experiences/expertise, reassuring and validating what I go through. I can't imagine if I was in another time with all of my issues and nothing to turn to.

Shoutout to the internet for keeping me (mostly) sane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 19:01:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy birthday!! You're a sagittarius and that's a really sweet astrological sign. I know a lot of people don't believe in astrology, but I do. I'm an aries, which is a fire sign too. Fire buddies.

I'm turning 20 in a few months and I certainly don't feel old enough to be 20. I assume this is how people feel at every age milestone.

It's a shame that more people from your social circle haven't reached out to you yet. No matter what, you have some very kind strangers online ready to embrace you and celebrate your birthday. Everyone deserves love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 08:02:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Insomnia and depression seem to work together for a lot of people. You most likely have a really active mind, so as soon as you cut out stimuli from any activity, it goes rampant.

Personally, my solution has been sleeping with music on so the thoughts don't have to come through and my brain is nice and stimulated even when I drift off into sleep.

But that's paired with having a therapist to talk to and going to see a doc regularly to help myself keep getting better every year.

Your depressive thoughts are temporary and your insomnia can be treated. You are never stuck and you are constantly growing. Always remember that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 07:54:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish I could grow a beard like yours. Could you snip some of yours off so I can glue it to my face? Remember, sharing is caring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Moderately depressing question, but I need some validation if other people get this too. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 04:54:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does your dysphoric internal monologue make you feel like a fraud/imposter? I need to know if other people, no matter what duration of transition or coming out, feel this way too.

And if you do struggle with it, what triggers it for you? I'm nearly a year and a half on T, fully out. Pretty sure its a mix of things. A big contributor is that its holiday season, aka misgendering season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 02:04:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Autism or not. Mental illness or not.
He is abusing you.
I am so sorry that you're going through this.
Get another person involved to help you leave him as soon as possible. You cannot under any circumstance stay with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 01:57:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Extreme social anxiety, introverted to a fault. But when with people I'm comfortable with in a non-public setting I'm normal and often loud.

I wish I wasn't shy by default, but it's a work in progress. I'll never be outgoing but I won't always be anxious either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 00:11:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Only when I'm distressed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-09 19:19:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a very severe case of it. I can't deal with chewing sounds at all (even quiet chewing), mouth noises like kissing, animals licking or eating or drinking water, stirring pasta or any wet sound, overlapping talking. If I hear these sounds I freak out or worse, I have a tic when there's too much overlap where I blink repeatedly and forcefully. I look crazy. I have to put the TV on mute if someone tries to talk. I can't go to dinner at places. It really gets in the way of life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-07 19:31:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First off, I want to tell you that I'm sorry you had to deal with that within your workplace. Whether the person who is putting you in an uncomfortable state knows that they're being inappropriate or not, you deserve to feel safe and comfortable at work.

As everyone has told you, being blunt works best. But I have some tips for that.

1. Have people around while you talk to him about what made you feel uncomfortable. Autism doesn't make us aggressive beasts or anything, but meltdowns do happen and can be scary.

2. You will have to give precise instances quoting his words. Be specific so there's no confusion.

3. No use of metaphors or similes. It's confusing to some of us.

4. Calm voice, calm body language. Make sure he doesn't feel like you're calling him stupid.

5. This one is common sense, but start sentences off with, "When you said/did _________ it made me feel _______".  Easy, simple, firm but not abrasive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-07 19:19:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been a hermit for almost five years now. I regret it every single day because I feel like I should have pushed myself. Not sure if it's rational to get mad at my past self for being mentally ill, but I'm making up for it by making 2020 my year of going out.
Whether that's just to the library, to get coffee, restaurants, grocery shopping, etc. I have to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-07 19:16:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congratulations!! That's a really big step to take </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-07 19:14:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't have any advice for you, just wanted to say you're really handsome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-07 19:09:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a therapy cat for this reason! He's a fuzzy, intelligent, rambunctious giant who I love more than anything in the entire world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-06 22:44:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> His clearly rational and perfect logic:

Woman wearing everyday clothing that shows a little bit of thigh and her back/shoulders = rape bait, a slut.

Woman wearing sexy, formfitting clothes to show off her body that she's confident with = complete rape bait, asking for it.

Woman wearing jeans and a modest long sleeved shirt = innocent and fuckable, not like the other sluts, therefore, rape bait.

This guy just wants to rape someone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-06 22:00:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seeing shit like this hurts my heart. I'm lucky to have a support system that accepts me. Sometimes their love makes me forget bigots are still extremely common, that people abhor me and compare me to Satan for being who I am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I just want to say thank you to this sub. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-06 19:35:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's so nice to be understood and validated, even if its by strangers. Knowing that there are people in the world I can connect with and discuss the hardships we both face on the daily makes me feel so secure.

Even when the thing I relate to is a sad experience. It's an important feeling to know that I am not alone, or a freak.

So, thank you for that. Love you guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-06 19:22:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your depression skews how you view yourself. That's the reason that no matter what anyone says, you don't feel like it helps at all.

People say I'm smart, but what they don't know is that I can't read numbers very well, I can't do basic math (like 19-4, 6x3, and 180-28, I cannot do that). I'm saying this because even "smart" aspies are dumb as hell.

Your life isn't over because you haven't found what you're good at yet. Or that you haven't had sex with anyone yet (saw incel sub on your profile).

Your depression is an asshole. Nothing helps because it blocks any kindness expressed towards you to make you feel like you are an isolated retard.
Just know that you aren't, and that I'm rooting for you.
Life will not always feel like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-06 19:07:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The double standard in diagnosis drives me crazy. I'm sorry your doctor is like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-05 21:16:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have no obligation to be happy, even with accomplishments. Your feelings are important and this is something that you really struggle with. It's not ungrateful to be lonely.

You will be loved, I can promise you that. You're probably already loved by family and the people that somewhat know you. You'll find friends, a good solid group of them that will respect you and love being close with you. You'll most likely find a romantic relationship out of that.

Just because we don't know what the path is to get there, doesn't mean we won't make it to the goal. That sounds cheesy. But I'm rooting for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-05 21:07:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Its a mixed bag. You know those trail mixes people take on hikes that have the m&ms in them? That's my week. I either get sweet or I get something annoying stuck between my teeth. (I know some people don't understand metaphors/similes, so I will explain. Sweet = good situations and food that gets stuck between teeth = bad situations. I keep getting some good times but then a bad moment happens very suddenly).

I haven't been the most productive. But I'm feeling hopeful about the new year right now. I bought a sketchbook and plan on drawing a lot. I feel this urge to create something that I haven't had in a while.

Therapy was... heartbreaking this week. I didn't realize how sad I really was until I said the words I repeat in my head daily out loud and saw my therapists response to it. She got tears in her eyes. I felt bad.

But I think I'm going to be okay :) I am going to make art shamelessly and find happiness sandwiched between spiky moments. My hardships are temporary and I can handle it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-05 20:56:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm almost twenty and have never had a "real life" friend, just online friends who keep me afloat. I can relate.

Congrats on being able to go to school and working on yourself. That's something I strive toward and it's nice to know that its possible for people on the spectrum. It gives me hope for my life changes.

I plan on changing a lot in the upcoming year because I am extremely lonely and need to make friends. Thinking about joining a meditation class and an autism support group. Also going to go to a local gay bar (I'm gay). So hopefully I meet some people through that.

I don't think any of what I said was helpful for you but I wanted to contribute and congratulate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-04 17:19:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-04 08:32:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> King </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-03 17:00:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ebay! And if ebay doesn't have the right ones, Etsy might have some. With Etsy you have to search for one specific cassette to narrow it down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The joy of finding a new special interest. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-02 20:42:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know it might sound mundane but I've always wanted to collect something. For years I couldn't figure out what to collect that was affordable and available while also being a tinge obscure/obsolete.

So I'm starting a cassette collection :)
I've been buying a lot of them, pulling from every genre. To intertwine my other (huge, main) special interest I've gotten some soundtracks too. I would say what they were but some of them are goofy as fuck.

I can't stop thinking about other ones I can hunt down, how I can organize/showcase them in my apartment, etc.

I forgot how great it is to find something new to be passionate and excited about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-30 05:35:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You know when they hit you with the "this is an ancient ______ practice" that its about to be something only a white person with dreads says they do to sound more enlightened than you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-27 23:12:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Public libraries, my cat, modal fabric, the accessibility of films through internet, the passing of time, and the people I love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-25 17:25:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Her features differ in each of her photos which is why I called it out as editing instead of extreme surgery. I think she's mimicking those facial procedures through facetune.
It's crazy how drastic eastern asian surgery is though. The whole jaw shaving thing weirds me out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-24 06:06:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why is there such a phenomenon in eastern asian culture of turning themselves into dolls with editing on their social media? Isn't the goal of facetune making yourself look more naturally beautiful/unedited? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Her instagram posts vs. an old tagged photo (lmk if she's already been posted). </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-24 06:04:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-24 03:43:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-24 03:36:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only thing that brought me out of my depression rut I was in a month or two ago was learning that I am the type of person who needs constant distraction. I noticed my trigger was silence, so now I don't let silence occur. All day I'll have either Youtube playlists of videos from creators I like, a spotify playlist, shows on a streaming service, etc.
I go to bed with headphones on blasting white noise or quietly playing music. Zero silence allowed.

Also forcing myself to complete tasks, then giving myself a reward for it. Keep myself doing things I like doing (for me, it's watching/reviewing one film per day at minimum), then giving myself my favorite thing to eat. Brush my teeth, then let myself put on my favorite cologne (small things matter). Shower, rewatch my favorite film. They're simple things but they make me do what I need to do.

You are going to get out of this depression alive and happy. I promise you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-23 18:24:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn't this sacrilegious, therefore a sin to compare Trump to Jesus? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-18 12:37:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What an asshole. I'm sure you look handsome as fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-16 01:23:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-14 23:10:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry you received those messages from someone who was supposed to nurture, love, and protect you. He couldn't fit that role because he was too ignorant. I can somewhat relate to this with my father.

I'm hoping you have a support system around you that can make sure you know that you're loved and that your identity will always be valid.

Also, even if you feel unaffected by his death, make sure to go over your feelings with someone you're close to or a professional. Closure is especially important so you don't repress your emotions surrounding him and his passing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 21:13:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Hug] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 21:12:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Crackpot by John Waters, On Photography by Susan Sontag, rereading War Boy by Thorn Kief Hillsbery. I like reading multiple books at once to keep myself excited to get through all of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 21:04:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a hard time watching interviews or live TV for this reason. Thought I was the only one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-11 20:46:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know jack shit about her, but I was looking up the whole "self-partnered" thing after seeing people poke fun at it.

Turns out in an interview she gave she covered topics of navigating her life as a child actress, the negative side of fame, her mental health, and feeling like she always needed to be in a relationship to feel valuable (heavily paraphrasing here). So she considers herself right now as "self-partnered" because the only relationship she wants right now is healing herself.

It's silly to anyone else reading it that isn't in her position but hey, if it works it works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-30 21:45:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't get how their logic works. If she says he's fucking other girls and has a dating profile, wouldn't it be so much easier if she chose to split up instead of just doing the exact same things and attempting to justify it by "Well you did it first!" while also saying she didn't do any of it?
Ma'am you're a fucking loon. Can people act like adults and have a mature conversation instead of having a screaming match in a grocery store parking lot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-17 17:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-01 15:27:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah let me just throw a gallon of water at this high dudes head, that's completely not a shitty thing to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 22:15:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Color correction around the piercing area's redness poorly covered up by foundation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Whos gonna tell them </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-23 06:06:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 16:07:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is grossing me out holy shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 20:25:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://youtu.be/lYZObFM5VBQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> From a worst reviewed makeup artist video. The eyebrows kill me. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 08:43:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-03 04:57:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So someone would have to go an extra (tiny) step of effort to look her username up and send hate to her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I feel bad for her neighbors. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-02 22:20:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-28 16:04:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry I'm a faggot. Guess you'll just have to make do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-27 03:19:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey incel king wanna get married </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Wow only $35 for this masterpiece of a tag in the alleged outline of the Blair Witch symbol. The bottom half kills me </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 17:41:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-23 05:43:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ... What </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 22:52:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm getting gay vibes but the weed pants are throwing me off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 22:45:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I read this as "sex doll" at first and was concerned about your wellbeing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 22:32:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cringescrimination </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What the fuck is going on here </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-22 19:03:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-12 15:38:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's obviously a joke. Not the funniest joke. Kind of obnoxious. Very gross. Super ""quirky"". But definitely not serious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-12 15:24:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you lift up her bang it reveals her third eye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-20 04:12:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i left a comment marking the timestamp in the video, you can look again to refresh your memory.
also, your profile has you on some kylie fan subreddits so i'm assuming you think this is a hate post toward her or something. it's not. i don't mind her at all. just think her ass got botched in recent years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-16 23:56:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> King </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-16 23:44:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if you put it in a gold frame next to some plants it could be overpriced "minimalist" urban outfitters home decor art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 15:03:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i thought the same thing when i had skipped around to that part of the video. turns out it's her cosmetics facility.

kims house is so minimalist and ugly though. depressing shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-06 17:20:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [that's why i left a link to the video in the comments.](https://youtu.be/HhM0BYCHL00) it's around 6:58ish or a few seconds after. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-05 22:51:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i used to wear corsets on the daily, can't imagine how painful it has to be to carry a kid while steel bones are crushing your lungs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-05 14:53:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doesn't seem like it's slowing down anytime soon. Butt implants/injections are still one of the biggest cosmetic procedures. praying it'll die down because it almost never looks decent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-05 14:17:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's what pains me the most to see. she has altered her body so much that she looks completely synthetic while being in her early twenties. the silhouette her family strives for is fucking crazy. her body will NEVER go back to being natural or at least non-botched human shaped.

i don't blame her though. her family's careers are based around their bodies and she's been pressured her entire life to live up to that standard of what they find beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-05 06:46:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [here's a link to the actual video.](https://youtu.be/HhM0BYCHL00) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Screenshot from Kylie jenner's "a day in my life" vlog. The diaper ass is strong in this one. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-05 06:45:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-29 21:27:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no one reply to this guy, if you go on his profile you can see all he does is stalk subs to find a way to spew his controversial political beliefs in the comments. don't feed the troll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-26 21:52:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> whenever i see surgeries like these i instantly feel bad for the person.
they have to go on day by day with a result that catches negative attention when all they wanted was a procedure to improve their appearance.
i hope she's able to get revision one day, but i can understand how people don't risk revision after being botched. i'd be paranoid as fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-26 21:47:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what a cunt. he's not even ugly, what is she going on about? he's fucking adorable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-22 22:30:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pretty sure its for a fetish thing. huge over-plumped lips usually fall into a bimbofication kink. with bimbofication, being absolutely braindead and "stupid" are the key traits other than looking like a blowup doll or barbie. the drooling signifies that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-21 21:20:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i don't get why people get huge chests when they go in for augmentation. the results rarely look good. i'm sure at least one surgeon has warned them of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-20 16:36:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> people probably doubted him because of his size and he's out here dancing his ass off better than some thin people can. wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> the tweaker nation tag on tumblr is a goldmine of trashiness. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-14 02:23:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-14 01:49:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> she has to be doing self injections or go to a sketchy doctor. no way an actual surgeon would give her this much filler. her lips are destroyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-13 04:39:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP, dare i ask what niche porn site you found this shit on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> "punishment" for getting highlights as a teenager. fucking ridiculous. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-12 23:17:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 14:54:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the eyelashes are a little oversized for that eye shape too, but you can tell this artist has skill. just needs to fine tune their work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 14:51:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i have deuteranopia and i was so confused until i read the comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 13:59:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no, this is proof for a previous post i made about this girl [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/awfuleverything/comments/bn5kkq/same_girl_three_years_apart/?utm_source=share&utm_medium=ios_app) . where i thought it was three years, but its actually four.
i misunderstood what you meant. sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 13:57:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DM me for the link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 13:56:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i just started using reddit, didn't know i could edit the title after posting lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 13:54:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [context.](https://www.reddit.com/r/awfuleverything/comments/bn5kkq/same_girl_three_years_apart/?utm_source=share&utm_medium=ios_app)
dm me for the link to her profile if you want to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 13:43:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i do kind of regret posting her in case she actually does have BDD. no one can diagnose her through the internet, but its a possibility given how drastic this is and how much photoshop and plastic surgery she's putting herself through.

the difference is a fine line. the key part of the disorder is going overboard eventually. when morphing yourself isn't just "oh i'm trying a new look", it's "i need to do this, i need to change this" in a loop. it's a rigid, hyper-focused way of coping with finding yourself unfinished. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 13:25:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DM me for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 13:23:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it is real, DM me if you want her instagram. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 13:21:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> feel free to DM me if you want a link to her instagram. can't link through here because of the rule of keeping identities concealed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 13:21:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> feel free to DM me if you want a link to her instagram. can't link through here because of the rule of keeping identities concealed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 05:42:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> she goes from super dark skin to darkish tan back and forth, so i guess its a mix of the two. casual longterm blackface...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 05:38:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i've got body dysmorphic disorder (the disorder that makes people seek extreme physical changes to cure things that they feel are flaws that no one else notices. examples are michael jackson and lil kim, and most people who have before/afters like this).

it's pretty intense to have, but doesn't mean she's a bad person. thankfully i get help for mine and i have a support system that's kept me from going down the route of extreme alteration. if she had the same, this could've been prevented.
could be a solid person underneath what her symptoms made her do. you never know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 05:18:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> HOLY SHIT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 04:49:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> her instagram has videos/stories where she looks like this, but she exaggerates using photoshop a lot.
i was gonna add a link but i remembered theres a rule for no identifying information on here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 03:03:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/niceguys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-11 01:49:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lmk if she's been posted on here before. wouldn't be surprised if she was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-09 17:12:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> imagine trying to kiss her. her lips would go down to your chin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-09 17:08:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> she's gotten corrective surgery since then and looks absolutely beautiful. [here's the before and after.](https://www.lifeandstylemag.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/botched-transformations-then-and-now-rajee.png?fit=200%2C1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-08 15:18:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the way he jumped was something straight out of a cartoon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-08 07:19:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you are so cute!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-07 18:00:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i'm deleting my comments on this post because a terf started her usual baseless rhetoric on how trans people ruined feminism, harm children, ect.

i have a lot that i could say to her to explain why she's wrong, but i don't like wasting time on ignorant people who only want to share their bigotry and call it feminism. it's really a shame.

anyone else who happens to read this post, i hope you're having a nice day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-07 08:11:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> she literally looks twelve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-07 07:58:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> say what you want about her body, but the dress is pretty cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> the joker's inbred stoner cousin, The Jonker. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-06 18:01:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 00:45:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it's reassuring that at least one person doesn't have a horror story involved with this rx. i'm praying that i have a similar experience and my anxiety is unwarranted.

kind of hilarious that with every med i'm given for anxiety or sleep makes, it me more anxious and more prone to not sleeping until i get the guts to finally take it lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 00:41:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i've never heard of that one before. thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-05 00:40:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i never usually have days off with meds or rotate them. my psychiatrist doesn't want me to be on ambien long-term because of how addictive it is. it's just until i can get a new medication instead. i could try not using it every day though.

i have been on quetiapine before, that was a medication that sent me into a dissociative episode that lasted for a day.

probably most frustrating thing about medication is that its different for everyone, so i never know what i'm getting myself into before taking it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-04 18:02:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> her username is aolunula on instagram. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-04 16:53:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> she's a teenager going through an edgelord phase. just because she's famous doesn't mean she's not still a child figuring herself out. cut her some slack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-04 06:53:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is fake. [click here to read about the man who actually used this photo to sell a fake deer and got into legal trouble for it.](https://www.thestate.com/news/local/environment/article223398170.html)

of course they use an image of a black woman saying her "daddy" found it and they need to sell it to buy drugs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-04 06:47:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if not fake, this is definitely a troll. people don't talk like that. even the mogai fuckers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-03 23:08:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> jesus, that looks painful. i actually feel bad for this girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-03 21:34:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wasn't able to find one :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-03 20:47:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the two big clumps of filler in her top lip are killing me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> found a video of michael jackson nose girl confirming it's not just bad photoshop. this is so sad. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-03 18:08:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-03 17:27:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's the way she posted it. i was confused about that too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-03 06:30:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> weird how plastic surgery (specifically cheek implants/fillers) can actually make someone look older. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-02 04:31:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> even though its not real blood (given the massive fucking biohazard it would be if it were), this is so nasty.
periods are normal and natural but blood soaked material of any kind hung in a fashionable manner is ungodly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-02 04:28:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> her nose is so tiny on its own. i could be wrong, but isn't the point of nose contouring to make large noses appear smaller? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-02 04:25:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why are there hanged men on her forehead? am i missing something here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-02 04:22:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> e-girl momo vibez </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-02 04:21:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> random russian model from what i could tell from her instagram. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-02 04:20:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i actually came across her page from a modeling agency on instagram. she only had less than 20 photos up herself. all selfies, none tagged anywhere besides the modeling page. all of them had her nose like this though.

given she's signed to an agency, i'm assuming it's not just photoshop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-02 00:20:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sexualizing a little kid's body for a totally original and epic "haha vagina look like beef and women control men with their pussy hehe" joke.
weirdest shit i've ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> noseless wonder: the sequel </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-01 15:19:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i thought it was just bad photoshop, but her nose is this way in every photo on her page </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-01 03:42:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-28 21:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it looks like they forgot to wipe foundation off of her lips. not a flattering look for anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-27 23:42:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *tongue pop* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> That face. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-27 23:27:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-26 16:18:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> voluptuous caterpillars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-26 16:14:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is obviously a troll account. threw in all the buzzwords, just joined last month. come on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-22 23:19:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> $37.68 SPECIFICALLY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 22:52:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not really sure why this is in this sub? it just looks like she's talking about makeup, not editing her pics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 22:35:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that looks painful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Her brows make her face look like its melting </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 22:29:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 22:22:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the lips are nauseating but the rest of the look is well done to me. im into bleached brows / shaved brows so i didn't even notice they werent filled in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> friend of mine when i was 13/14. when confronted about their eyebrows they'd go on a rant on how only fellow punks can understand their beauty. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 23:57:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
