<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject35</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm not sure about my diagnosis. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 03:15:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I don't understand if I was diagnosed or not? A couple of weeks ago my therapist gave me a pdf about anxiety and simply told me to look at it and said nothing else about the matter. Then this weekI was asked if I was okay with being given the diagnosis of anxiety and depression. Like... is that something you're supposed to be asked? It was also called a "working diagnosis" so I feel like I can't trust saying I have anxiety and depression. I feel like it wasn't proper, even though I am satisfied with my therapist at the moment. What the fuck happens now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How do I stop overeating and destroying my body </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 04:14:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never thought that I used to be someone who ate to "fill their emptiness" like those people on my 600 pound life, but I think maybe that's exactly what I'm doing. I'm those people. I've had problems with overeating for waaaaaaay longer than I can even remember and recognize and I think I've occasionally had binging episodes too. In recent years I've been slowly getting over that, just in pursuit to being healthier. I'm at a serious low rn, and my eating habits are so abysmal, I just wanna make it stop. If you look at webmd or other google blurbs for depression they always describe some symptoms to be either overeating or eating very little. Most times I wish I was at the other side of the spectrum, I hate doing this and I know it's no good. I haven't spoken to my therapist about it yet but it's ridiculous after how far I've come in terms of fitness and weight how I'm just gonna throw it all away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 05:20:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, so sorry for your friend but so glad she decided to reach out. I would suggest maybe a gofundme to fund wherever her and her brother might go? There are really amazing people who would love nothing more to help. So if you consider setting one up, count me in! Good luck love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anybody feel like they're betraying their sadness when they have positive experiences? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 05:16:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ya I dunno. I've finally come to the conclusion that I'm empty. Despite that, I always try my best to interact with people positively. A lot of that is natural and not forced. When I smile wide and I laugh it's a reflexive/habitual thing... but they're all just expressions and not actual deep emotions of contentess. After hanging with my friends and family  I wonder if I really am sad... I mean, I act happy right? I have zero clue, I just feel like I'm undermining my sadness when I do that shit. I mean, I want to actually be happy and feel satisfied with life, but that's not how I feel. And acting like I'm overjoyed feels like a fucking lie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 04:53:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, I hear you. I feel the exact same way most days. Today I was very cross about going outside but I had to for some appointments. As much as I wasn't sure about where to go or what to do afterwards, I found somewhere and had a descent time outside. All this to say that sometimes you just gotta go and look where things take you, it doesn't hurt to be spontaneous. But if you feel it isn't working and you wanna go straight home, go home. Don't stick it out for any good reason , listen to your instincts. It's sorta shit advice from someone who can't even deal with themselves, but do as you're willing. Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 01:03:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So glad you could find relief! Just a question how long did it take to get prescribed from your first inquiry to now? Reading the thread I'm currently experience a lot of the same things you described down below and I'm fucking sick of being a dysfunctional blob. Anyways congrats again! :)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 00:39:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looking at this question right off the bat I would scream no. But that's just given my experiences with the people around me who struggle. The way people struggle varies just as much as any other aspect varies. But for me, I am often scared  of engaging with people who struggle  just because I'm scared of the lack of clarity is one's perception and how sometimes their difficulty with interacting with the world might hurt me and trigger me. That's not to say everyone who struggles doesn't experience clarity and awareness. I know people who aren't diagnosed with anything that say or do hurtful things just because. This is coming from someone whos parent deals with BPD and I  think to worry about myself, my parent, and a separate partner would be putting me over the edge. I'm not explicitly against being in a relationship with someone who struggles , if they happen to make me overall happy and give me the strength I need to face daily life then I could not give a single shit. I'm only against it when they unfortunately become too much a burden, and then again that has the potential to do nothing with their mental state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 06:45:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah i suspect my issues might also be coming from depression but i havent got diagnosed quite yet. now that you say it puzzles do sound fun. I'll make sure to go out and find one now. thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 06:42:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh god i remember catcher and the rye. i hated that book when i first read it but thinking about it now the story wasnt at all bad. thanks for the recommendations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What can I do to pass the time while being fucking useless. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 06:18:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is part rant part question. These days I'm so fucking bored. I'm fucking bored of being unhappy and overly anxious and overall useless. I can't do productive things or even things that take little to effort. It's too much. I found drinking is a fun way to pass the time and actually makes me more social but that obviously a horrible idea for how bad and bored I feel all the time. Also both my parents are alcoholics so thats gargantuan fucking no. Can't get high with no connections. I have nothing. Anybody got something they do that passes the time? Reading this post in retrospect, this sounds all really unhealthy but GODD im so over this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> So uh... suicidal thoughts?? What constitutes being suicidal? Experiences? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 04:42:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So, I had my first therapy session today (whoo), and we went through the typical questionnaire thing for anxiety and depression. When we got to the question on thoughts of self harm and "ending one's life", I wasn't sure how to answer? Like it wasn't a definite no, but I haven't thought of actually doing it? It's sorta weird since it doesn't really work with they number rating system. It's more of "oh I wish I wasn't here," although I habitually say "I want to kms" but I genuinely can't tell if that's out of a twisted habit orrr what..... So basically me and my counselor were in a back and forth about this for like 10 minutes until it was dropped.  Idk what the point of this post is, maybe clarity from other posters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 07:28:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yo, fellow 16f. My experience is not too far off from what you currently worry about. I think my mom dismissed the concern I felt early on, but I implore to really press her about it and tell her how important it is, because it is important. If you're worried and others are worried there's nothing wrong with looking for help and your mom should understand that. Annoy her about it and make her concerned. Hopefully she'll come to understand. Talking about it in passing doesn't have the same effect to alarm as saying what you feel, "Mom, I'm in pain and I'm worried."  Secondly, I used to worry about not being able to pay for seeing somebody and hotlines also intimidate me. Ask your mom if you have an insurance plan and there's bound to be somebody who your insurance will cover the payments for. I got a really good tip on this subreddit to look at a website called Psychology Today to find professionals based on area and insurance plan. If that doesn't work check to see if your school provides any resources, but I'm not sure if thats fool proof. I've only just begun my mental health journey and I literally felt the exact same way not too long ago. But be loud about what you want and what you think you need, people will be more than happy to help. More than you think. Good Luck luv. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Update to a post I made yesterday; Thank You! Y'all are amazing </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 06:20:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi again. I have zero clue if anybody from that thread will see this here. But I want to thank this subreddit for the impact it's made on me in such a little time. My issue was that I was having trouble finding therapists and just motivating myself in the meantime without a professional's help. Obviously things aren't going to change in less than 24 hours buttt,

First off I was able to find two potential psychologists I'm hopeful to see soon to help me out with my potential ADD/ADHD, family trauma, and school life.

Secondly, I've been scrolling through this subreddit and it's so touching to see everyone share the deepest parts of themselves with strangers while others give them advice and push them to keep going. The users who helped me and gave me some much needed advice and resources proved to me that the world is still a good place.

Even though it's been a really short time, I've felt a lot better after coming into this subreddit. I didn't really do much today, I just sat at home. But unlike most other days I actually smiled and joked some with my mom which I haven't done in a fat minute. It's not much but it's progress from the days past. And who knows if I'll feel better or worse tomorrow. All I know is that this subreddit has had a direct impact on how I feel for this moment and helped provide resources.

Please don't stop doing what you're doing guys. Your words are invaluable. Whether you're giving advice, sharing your troubles or both. I can say for certain. This forum saves lives.

You all are so valuable and you all make this world a better place. If you feel you contribute nothing to society, your fucking wrong. You just might not notice it, because you're touching people you can't directly see with your words. I know what I'm saying sounds stunted and perhaps cliched but FOR THE LOVE OF GOD YOU ARE IMPORTANT AND YOU ARE ABSO FUCKING LUTLEY NEEDED. You helped me and others can help you.

So again thanks. :)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 05:54:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey. Not at all a doctor, just a dumbass on the internet. But my first thought is maybe BPD?  Before you listen to anyone else, listen to a professional though. There's honestly no reason not to go, it's not a crime to be concerned about your health. Wish you luck :)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 09:07:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I appreciate your comments, I understand that part of life is just working through the pain. I will try! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 09:02:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha yeah, my mom likes to tell me the same exact thing, there are in fact people who are in much worse circumstances and I'm so grateful for what I have. I also wouldn't mind at all seeing those speeches, anything that might help is entirely welcome. But yeah both my parents seem to have responded well to my plea, I think the difficulty in conveying how I feel stems from generational difference in how mental health manifests itself? Like they understand it's something that is serious and real, but I don't think they understand how modern culture and pressures make all that happen? Anyways, I'd be glad to pm about the speeches and music. Thank you so much for taking the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 08:20:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's seriously helpful. Thank You </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 08:08:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> P.S. I hope you do find a way to seriously pursue your passions now. It's never too late! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 08:05:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  First off my primary care doctor hasn't been able to get back and give any referrals, and even when doing your own research they have to be covered by my insurance. In my area mental health professionals are pretty high demand due to quarantine and things like that. With those requirements its pretty scarce as most of them work for the city and are seriously overbooked. I'm a minor so I don't know exactly how all of that goes but that's as far as a know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 08:01:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi it's really comforting to know I'm not the only one who feels this way. I feel my interests are taking me to a more artistic career. I'm looking at becoming an art conservationist or working in fashion?? Who knows. I just love pretty things and I want a life around that. Despite that I would say I'm equally interested in doing almost anything like, law, science or journalism, but I think art and fashion are the things I think the most about. Everything I do now is tinged with lethargy and fear. I'm scared of painting, I'm scared of playing my bass guitar, I don't want to read, I don't want to sew or crochet or bead jewelry. I have so many things I want to do and achieve that I know I can succeed at, but only if I tried. I'm just so scared and I get so upset by actually doing them which makes no sense even though those are the things I think about the most and subjectively enjoy more. I also go to a pretty rigorous school where most aim to go to ivy league schools, so I'm no stranger to being beaten over the head with the need for good time management and a good work ethic, but honestly I'm just barely holding on to my average performance, heading towards neglectful. If something doesn't fundamentally change by the new school semester there's no way I'll be able to cope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can't see a therapist. Need help for dealing with undiagnosed mental exhaustion. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 07:03:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm 16F. I've been feeling really mentally exhausted the past week. I'm trying to find a therapist at the moment but it's been a little hard since everyone's unavailable and the hospital system is in complete shambles. I have zero clue if I might be suffering from anything with a name but it might be likely given my past. The issue is that I can't get and counseling or advice from anyone at the moment and it's not like I'm able to take medication so I'm just walking blindly and trying to deal with myself which isn't going well. The truth is I've been feeling incredibly unmotivated for the past couple of years and whatever I've been feeling just multiplied recently into a complete shutdown. I've been feeling depressed (I don't have depression I'm just feeling depressed). I'm not sure how to get myself to do things or be productive or make myself feel better so I wanted to ask anybody with experience with a doctor or just anybody who found things that made them feel better to let me know what might help until I can go see someone. I just feel trapped and I'm so clueless. I used to be able to just get by and do the minimum amount of work but now I can't do anything. The three conditions I'm most afraid of having would be ADHD, Depression, and Bipolar disorder but I won't know for sure if I have any one of these until I'm diagnosed. Even if I don't have anything these are what my symptoms sound the most similar to. Anything is appreciated thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can't see a therapist. Need help for dealing with undiagnosed mental exhaustion. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 06:56:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 06:36:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey dude, dont hate urself. You don't have to know what you want to do right now. Honestly "what do you want to do when you grow up" is such a dumb question because there are only a few people who have an idea of their future at 13. You're still becoming a fully formed person and finding your interests. It's normal that you're not certain and nothing deemed "practical" really interests you. I believe it's not good that modern society puts test scores on such a high pedestal tells us we all must be doctors and ivy-league students. Some people find genuine interest in that and others don't. And those who want to be influencers, content creators can do just and much good as any lawmaker, scientist, or whomever. That's all a really long saying of saying don't worry, you'll know when its time. Cuz luv ur still young. Pursue what you're passionate about, and it'll be easier find ways you can put your hobbies and interests to use to make money or make a career. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MetLife Setlist </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-18 15:26:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-09 16:52:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> woah woah woah this is crazy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-31 03:38:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So update: I did it... he replies "Huh? What's up?" which is pretty wack to someone saying I like you, I reply "I dunno what to say bro, I like you" He hasn't opened it and its been maybe 3 or 4 hours. Im pretty sure I scared him lmaoo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-30 23:11:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not very close lmao maybe a 4 or 5... im close with his friends though. everyone tells my i also gave him a concussion when we were younger too but i dont remember lol, thats irrelevant but oh well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-30 00:38:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hmmmm okaY; after half a century of getting a hold of mine/his friends they all said no they havent told him, everybody tells me he's generally pretty clueless too. as for me, everyone says that they wouldn't have known i liked him unless i told them so.

 u/Thecheese2474 u/forelefty here r ur @s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-30 00:21:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> :((( I would upfront about it and ask her tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-30 00:13:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> happy cake day brother </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-30 00:08:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In now way, shape, or form, am i an expert but maybe relay some of this to her parents that you fear she might self harm and keep an increased eye on her. as much pain she caused you im glad you still look out for her with her illness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 23:41:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks i'll keep those in mind it really helps me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 23:38:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I added more context in a reply to u/Thecheese2474 look down there, ill edit the post too :)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 23:33:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> aww good for you! were you already close friends? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 23:31:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeh, well im a girl i suppose im in the same friend group as him and i'm pretty good friends with maybe 3 or 4 of his good friends they all know i like him but i have zero clue if theyve already told him, i talk to him sometimes but once i start liking someone i start talking to them less. I have zero clue if they like me or not i dont really see anything there, if i try really hard i'd say that i catch them looking at me pretty often??? maybe im delusional. his friends tell me hes just tryna hook up with ppl (ive heards hes been unsuccessful so far) I'm not rlly tryna spare my coochie but ik that there are ppl that start liking other ppl once they know the like them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 23:18:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> such as... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 23:16:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> indeed they are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 22:56:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my god what breed is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 22:49:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hell no in no way are you fat, ur pants make u look like you a little thiccy tho ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Should I tell my crush I like them </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 21:50:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey r/teenagers, for those of you sorting by new I'm thinking about telling my crush I like them and I'm not sure whether I should do it or not. I'm looking for opinions/encouragement I've liked this person for probably a year now and I feel kind of bored with everything and I feel ready to shoot my shot. Im scared they're gonna play it off tho and send a fucking dumb ass meme in response to my real feelings. I don't really plan on sending a long ass paragraph and instead going straight to the point because right now I'm kind of fed up. ajsjdjkfjdjjdjdbfjfdhjdssj Idk what to do I don't know what there is to lose but I don't wanna be tonights biggest loser :((((

&#x200B;

edit: additional context

im a girl i suppose im in the same friend group as him though im not really the closest to him. i'm pretty good friends with maybe 3 or 4 of his good friends and they all know i like him but i have zero clue if theyve already told him, i talk to him sometimes but once i start liking someone i start talking to them less so its pretty scarce, like quoting one liner memes. I have zero clue if they like me or not i dont really see anything there, if i try really hard i'd say that i catch them looking at me pretty often??? maybe im delusional. his friends tell me hes just tryna hook up with ppl (ive heards hes been unsuccessful so far) I'm not rlly tryna spare my coochie but ik that there are ppl that start liking other ppl once they know the other one likes them

&#x200B; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I have zero clue if someone had done this yet </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-23 19:42:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 10:17:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well the the fact that you're being reflective on this certainly justifies that you are not inherently bad. You'll overcome what you feel, sometimes being a sadboi makes everything unclear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 10:02:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nobody is an inherently bad person, we do bad things sometimes though and we have the power to overcome that. It's about knowing yourself, knowing you can hurt people, knowing people can hurt you etc. People will respect you if you have a good amount of self awareness. As for finding an occupation, I would say, find one thing you really like and find a to turn that into a career.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-22 09:57:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i would kill whoever did this :((( Rest easy kitty  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Because I see so many of these posts </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 22:37:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 21:54:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That fucking sucks man. You'll find someone better. It's better she broke up with you or else she would continue to keep doing this shit behind your back and worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 21:50:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why'd you post this twice i- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 21:47:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No she's currently in a 7 month long relationship, she's dated several other people, and is often hit on. I'm seriously jealous of her but I'd say she knows her stuff when it comes to this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 21:44:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I showed this to my friend who is a girl and she said "is he dumb." I don't think you're dumb but I would say, unless you ask her, I would put it to rest and let go of her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 21:31:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nice? slaves do not have emotions they're property you silly goose! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 21:24:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On all levels ~~except~~ *including* physical, I identify as a ~~wolf~~ retard  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 20:16:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Harvard wants to know your location* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 20:06:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine is not really funny... "man entering the Stadium Centre apartments displayed a gun while arguing with several Florida A&M students. " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 19:42:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> funky shmunky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 19:36:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very cool u/treeslut420! Thank You! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 19:33:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the $1 dollar balance is still too real tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 19:32:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literal shit people dream about, rooting for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 19:30:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seeing your comment history you're 13, your problems will not define the rest of your life, and there are always people to reach out to. Whatever you may choose to do and however you may feel at this moment, is very small compared to the rest of your life. If this is true or a petty cry for attention, I hope you get well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 17:47:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've had knee pains since I was 11 and it hurt whenever I walked or did pretty much anything. This was due to growing pains because I was having my growth spurt at the time too. Im 15 now and the pain now is substantially less, it's more of a sensitive spot and it only hurts if I knock my knees against something. I know a few people who developed the same thing as me though I got it far earlier than them. What you have may or may not be the same as what I have but the condition is called "osgood schlatter" if you wanna look it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 17:38:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's frowning bc his mom wont let him juul in the house </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 17:36:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Dancing King... long and sweet, only eleven-* uh *... teen...* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 17:00:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're like a girl group version of NCT  :>0   I'll be sure †o stan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-21 16:57:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Stares out into the hallway for the remainder of the class period* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-08 02:43:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm procrastinating from doing my english essay by looking at this right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-07 16:57:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mr. Elec^(tric)! Send ^(him) to the priciple's office and have him *expelled*!  >:( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-28 03:00:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That looks like a sad cat meme without being photoshopped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-21 19:48:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Indeed he is full of bash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-22 22:34:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> \*tongue pop\* NoICe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
