<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject46</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-18 02:31:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here. Got mad Hisoka from HxH vibes from that character, even though their way of speaking is quite different. That's definitely him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 18:47:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shit I'm getting old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 18:12:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> porn



laugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 16:47:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 13:39:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's how I got myself a nice video game addiction and held back a year in high school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 12:50:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, at least it's consistent throughout the series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 04:51:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That perfect score felt like an unfitting last resort to prevent drama from changing the good-feels story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 19:41:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You all keep saying it doesn't matter and yet in real life "small dick" is generally regarded as an acceptable insult towards a man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 22:07:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Es gracioso porque el coronel va a violar a una menor de edad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 21:26:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And what are my dead ancestors gonna do about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 20:43:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you know, charisma is literally everything that matters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 13:11:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's really nothing like this series. It's truly unique. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 04:10:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spain. Don't know if the same applies to the rest of Europe, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 19:46:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Laughs in \*insert shitty edgy anime series\* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 11:27:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's an American thing and I think it's incredibly cruel.

Where I live, parents are obliged to provide for their children until they achieve financial independence as long as they show an interest in studying and working. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 19:46:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And isn't it regrettable that hard times are necessary to make it in this world and avoid even harder times? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 04:38:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If it doesn't hurt anyone, either physically or indirectly, then why shouldn't it be "allowed"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 04:22:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spot on. Stardew Valley is basically a reimagined Harvest Moon game, and yet it manages to surpass it by miles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 20:07:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "humor" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 17:25:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah, I'm sure that time when people formally shot at each other to solve disputes was much more authentic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 14:18:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having a kid is literally the less environmentally friendly thing you can do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 04:37:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lmao why would you shave your balls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 19:47:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >Maybe for some, but for some it isn't.

"Some of you may die, but that's a sacrifice *I*'m willing to make" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 02:21:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lol this is just an appeal to nature and the past </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 18:03:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Éramos dos impostores y al primero lo pillaron casi al empezar.

Conseguí acabar con el resto de tripulantes hasta que quedamos 4.

Se me fue la pinza y, pensando que iba a ganar al instante, me cargué a alguien en vista de otros dos: uno al lado y el otro un poco más lejos.

Empecé a reírme diciendo que por qué lo había hecho *el que tenía al lado* delante de todo el mundo, de una forma siniestramente creíble (nunca me he considerado buen mentiroso)

Se ve que el otro no vio bien la escena y lo votó a él también.

Modo pro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 17:27:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> **1:** Even if we were to assume our ancestors had our best interests in mind, one is in no obligation to reciprocate "favors" or "gifts" they didn't ask for, especially when the giver expected something in return.

**2:** Death and non-existence are, for practical purposes, equal, so the extra steps are utterly unnecessary and create the problem of suffering in the first place. The process of dying itself is universally undesirable unless a much greater pain makes it worth going through.

**3:** Procreation causes a new entity to exist, so the recipient can't be considered fictional. Consent is relevant here.

If you can't gather consent, the default answer is "no". This isn't up for debate.

**4:** Same rebuttal as before. You don't go around showing people your junk because they'll be deprived of the chance to see it otherwise.

**5:** There is evidence that the birth process is painful and traumatic for the baby, so the concept of life without suffering can be easily discarded.

> While existence is a conditio sine qua non for suffering

Purposely fulfilling the primary condition for the ability to feel pain in someone else's place can be considered immoral regardless of the actual pain that comes after.

**6:** Natural coping methods involve denial and an optimistic bias that undermine the actual amount of suffering perceived, so it's true we always underestimate pain.

**7:** Back to consent. You can't make decisions that severely affect someone else because, in your own perception, they'll "most likely" thank you for it. What if they don't? "Sucks for you"?

On top of the disparity between estimated and real pain argued previously, people in the worst circumstances (concerned solely with survival) can't even stop to think about whether they're fine with their lives.

**8:** By that argument, you can't say existing is better than not existing, either, so procreating would be pointless at best.

Coincidentally, there's a number to represent absence, which is 0. Existence can't be quantified accurately, but we can deem it either positive or negative. 0 is greater than all negative numbers, so not existing can, in fact, be considered better than existing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 01:35:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, a lot happens, but "nothing" is supposed to mean "extremely mundane life events" in this context.

To someone who is used to over-the-top stories, what happens in K-On is nothing, but not in a literal way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 01:27:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Primera noticia. En ese caso perdí hace mucho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 01:16:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ¿No era en noviembre? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 21:04:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fun i   numb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 21:59:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Badly" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 14:08:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No shit, 95% of the posts are spoilers, how about people actually play the game before coming here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 12:50:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It literally means you helped an F2P survive a campaign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> GO episode 28 in a nutshell </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 04:23:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 03:38:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's anecdotal at best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 13:38:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why write an honest review when you can write a review that gets clicks. OP even made a meme about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 18:58:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because you might not actually be dead when it decides to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 00:09:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Izquierdo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 19:41:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldn't deem someone who has enough money to blow on all this a loser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 04:41:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >"I don't want to" with "hey, I'm actually really enjoying laying on the couch right now and doing nothing" is a big step in the right direction.

Except those sentences have different meanings. People aren't owed explanations every single time they're told "no". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 14:50:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The lack of conflict or grim themes doesn't make it childish. This show is aimed at young adult men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 14:17:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >giving this account free exposure on Reddit

Surely this is what they'd want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 13:57:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >72.3 of the images are family relations and the rest are children of colleagues hes known for on average 27.4 years

The fuck does that change? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 13:54:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously, how do you manage to deny what's in front of your face? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 12:24:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> x+=1; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 02:54:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >Como fan de Evangelion les confirmo que si está medio aburridonga

modo fan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 21:34:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Christian reference = *D E E P* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 17:58:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I want to go into a game completely blind, I simply don't even watch its trailer or look at official screenshots, much less look it up on the Internet.

It's unbelievable how active this sub is considering the active impairment of discussion this spoiler phobia causes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 13:35:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You seriously think you wouldn't have to compete for resources in other eras? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 14:52:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you can get past the bullshit mental gymnastics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 12:31:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being eaten alive isn't the only source of pain. Besides, if these species were left completely alone, they would multiply incessantly until there wasn't enough sustenance and many would starve. Others would also eventually evolve to be predatory. There's no way around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 03:34:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sharing any fanart of a series that came out 9 years ago can't be considered spoiling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 12:29:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Highly relatable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 13:13:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a comedy about a teen girl who gets magically transported to an alternate world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 05:36:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pues que se lo hubiesen pensado dos veces antes de imponerme la vida lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 14:05:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's never *fine*, but it's less reprehensible than procreating fully knowing you won't be able to sufficiently provide for the kids.

But this isn't about economic systems. I'd argue people suffered far more before civilization. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 04:18:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's not a single safe zone in the entire map. An enemy player can literally kill you right in front of a vendor and turn in your loot themselves.

Other crews (which might surpass yours in number) can always ruin hours of your work and are usually extremely aggressive and persistent (I've been chased for a whole hour by some crews as soon as they spotted me from the horizon). Add to that random events which might catch you unprepared/mid-fight and you've got an extremely unfair PvP system on top of that.

The PvE aspect of the game still leaves a lot to be desired. It boils down to spamming basic sword attacks to skeletons. That's about it.

It may seem exciting at first, and I encourage you to try it with a Game Pass subscription or something (the sailing/exploring part of the game is actually good), but you'll probably find that the constant exposure to potentially long fights/chases or the loss of hours of progress in this game ends up being too mentally exhausting and time-consuming.

Also, get someone else to play with if you really want to try. This game makes absolute fools out of people who try to play by themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 14:06:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a fact. People who watch it simply don't care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 13:46:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's probably [this one](https://www.reddit.com/r/memes/comments/ick4yn), though it hasn't been upvoted that much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 16:23:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The VN is harem trash and in my opinion not enough shitty tropes were cut out in the anime adaptation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 14:56:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All comedy is derived from fear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 03:47:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sometimes I forget a lot of people actually believe the latter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 03:13:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Peak r/unpopularopinion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 05:05:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course it's your personal business, but unfortunately with the way things work you're gonna have a very hard time hiding it without entirely avoiding people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 20:54:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hard to avoid giving away that information when one's employment status is one of the first things people ask. Trying to dodge that question looks suspicious, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 22:35:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ser un dictador genocida no reduce tu atractivo sexual. Más bien lo contrario. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 22:00:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's unreasonable to assume OP wasn't talking about *good* sex ed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 20:42:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The abscence of pleasure isn't an issue when you don't exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 04:21:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every god of the big religions commands their believers to multiply themselves, to "be fruitful". It can't be a choice if you're religious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 14:16:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait till you see Left 4 Dead 2's workshop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 05:43:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sums up his character pretty well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 14:58:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I watch it to complain and make myself angry. It's also visually pleasant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-26 16:36:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's tiny bits like these throughout this (and all) anime that make me dislike Japanese culture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-26 04:17:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Qué esperar de un sub donde el pináculo del humor se reduce a ser extremista abiertamente. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 15:30:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A story with great potential only to be ruined by its harem visual novel tropes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 13:06:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone I know kept sending hentai of every childhood cartoon he could come up with to the group chat. Although I didn't cut ties with the guy for that, it was gross and kind of a dick move, so I guess I can understand the feeling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 12:54:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's an exclusively American thing. I live in a western country and the average age of emancipation here is 29. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 02:49:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He started taking her bullshit before he knew anything bigger was going on. Not cutting it out sooner led to him becoming the designated punching bag of the group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 02:06:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kyon belongs in the romance protagonist category, with the addition of being a massive simp for putting up with so much shit from Haruhi. Superb circlejerking otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 13:09:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was following your argument until you fell into yet another idealization of the past. What do people think is so great about a time where civilization and basic commodities didn't exist?

Yes, the current situation is undesirable, but I'd take it a thousand times over the looming threat of being eaten alive by predators. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 11:26:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a plausible explanation. I only watched the anime, so I guess I got the wrong idea.

To think his adoration for Rintaro would go that far... He didn't even do that much for Luka. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 02:06:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But he even asked Rintaro to change the worldline so that he could be born a biological girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 11:18:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >you should be working towards sterilizing the human race

People don't have to dedicate their existence to meeting impossible demands like these in order to justify their thoughts.

>And if not... well... we have a choice.

We legally do not. And if you think the solution can be simplified to allowing unhappy people to go through an extremely painful process, it's clear you don't care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-06 04:13:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> haha, get it? He probably doesn't sexually please women on the regular. Owned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-05 19:22:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ¿Y si te limitas a hacer tu trabajo y no molestar a gente que acude a ti por obligación? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 03:30:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not good at coming up with examples. Just research any real life cases of people who've jumped from mediocrity into high society and see how most keep consuming more as their income increases, or people who've been born into wealthy families and therefore consider unnecessary luxuries a basic need. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-27 15:02:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It would be a pretty big list, since our psyche doesn't allow us to ever be satisfied. That's why billionaires don't step down from their positions even when faced with great hardship and live the rest of their lives in absolute comfort. This example might be a bit of a stretch, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-27 14:09:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We're slaves to our needs, which grow in number and requirements as they are satisfied, so in a sense we aren't truly free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 22:30:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is better for lifeforms not to exist than doing so in constant pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 22:05:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 0 is greater than -1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 16:04:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Modern day apes aren't our ancestors lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 13:28:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They've been back for some time now. I wonder what happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 15:11:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People die a lot more than it's usually estimated in non-mature rated media, they're just very good at hiding it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 13:30:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> With no warning, Clive just starts wreaking havoc in that titanic machine, and London is explicitly shown to be populated at that time. Obviously there's no official confirmation, but that was definitely a genocide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 14:19:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True. These silly restrictions only hinder discussion on the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 00:22:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Basado. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 17:47:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course, if you just look at the conveniently clean spots, the place won't seem dirty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 14:31:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will do when it's an actual poll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 12:44:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Indigenous people are more genetically robust because the ones who're not die in pain. Besides, I wouldn't say they're genuinely happy, but constantly focused on survival, which prevents them from putting any thought into how the situation they're living in affects them emotionally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 10:57:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do you compare the potential agony of suicide and not covering your basic needs with wearing a condom? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 03:56:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When you can't gather consent, you have to assume the answer will be negative. Why isn't that applied equally here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 15:33:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The downsides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 15:33:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like he's one to talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 16:23:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You see this and tell me there's a god. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 14:46:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wet water wallpaper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-02 19:51:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Squidward imagined himself having kids with a krabby patty in one episode, so as much as I like him, I don't think so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-27 13:19:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who jerks his dick to something *ironically*? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-27 00:19:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literalmente dice detrás que el equivalente de "me saca de mis casillas" es "grinds my gears". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-26 13:56:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've always said anyone with two neurons to rub together can see the logic behind this philosophy, it's just that they don't give a shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-26 03:32:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> mmm, antinatalismo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 15:54:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As someone who doesn't usually like shonen anime, it was pretty nice, at least at the beginning. Although it gets progressively worse at a fast rate after Yorknew arc imo.

It's also an anime that presents itself as a goofy adventure but at the same time has fucked up shit happening all the time. That contrast had its charm, but sometimes was too edgy for me and ended up portraying objectively bad actions in a positive light to the viewer.

To stay on topic, I quite liked the dub. It definitely played a role on why I stayed until the last episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 13:24:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Death is not instant, there's a process leading to it that requires you damage another person's body and violate their right to physical integrity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 20:32:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You, like everyone else, are a physical extension of your parents' ego, a token of their symbolic immortality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-17 22:17:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-17 13:10:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >A lot of the time that stuff is played for humor though

Yeah, that's usually the problem, because most times it's straight up sexual harassment which any decent person would rather see portrayed in a bad light.

A good example of this can be seen in an anime that's considered a classic nowadays, The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya. Haruhi keeps sexually harassing a girl from her club by forcefully changing her clothes and making her do stupid shit in public while in skimpy clothing. At one point she also grabs a guy's hand and puts it on her chest so she can blackmail him.

All of this is played for laughs, but they were all pretty uncomfortable scenes, really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 02:14:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Derechito a mi lista. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 15:50:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sí. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 13:43:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then they'll call it an "accident".

It wasn't one if you didn't even try to prevent what you knew would happen. Actual accidents regarding pregnancy are rare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 02:32:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I was in that subreddit for some time, but it's mostly a haven for narcissistic nature worshippers. Its description alone should tell you enough.

I don't hate the human race particularly, I just think consciousness as a whole is regrettable.

Edit: I meant the old sub description, since I checked and it's changed. It was something about hating 95% of humanity and finding the other 5% there or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 18:55:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> kinky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 15:39:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who gives a shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 02:35:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> finally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-07 23:17:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure, especially if you willingly facilitate the means for it without their consent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-07 23:15:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 21:26:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I wouldn't. And I sure as hell wouldn't look up to someone who just showed up and tried to kill me with a method of *their* choosing.

> I Would rather suffer through the most painful torture method ever invented for 3,4 hours ( again MAXIMUM) knowing full well that I wouldnt have to deal with life anymore

I think you're seriously underestimating the amount of pain your body can give you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 21:15:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An instant death is a very optimistic and unlikely case. The way I see it, even a few seconds of consciousness during the act are too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 19:49:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Put like that, I have to admit the point of this post is more clear. However, it seems murder is almost being portrayed in a positive light rather than as a "lesser evil". Since both are impositions, any argument in favor of "relieving" someone of their life loses its power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 19:41:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You literally need to harm the body in order to make it cease its vital functions, there's no denying that. "They won't care when they're dead", well they might now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 15:42:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That part might be subjective. While everyone is biologically programmed to seek reproduction, the deed isn't done until the tests and trials barriering it are overcome, so it can't be assured it's something that will happen by default. I can see why it could be assumed any given person may reproduce with no other information provided, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 15:22:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's assuming having a kid is the default outcome and therefore giving an identity to someone who doesn't exist yet. However, at that point no one is being spared anything. By not having a kid, you're merely choosing not to create a vessel for suffering, so there's no prevention from anything.

You're also making assumptions on the events that *might* transpire on other people's lives. Depending on the method chosen for murder and whatever ends up happening to a person, I believe the process of dying could very well exceed the amount of pain that everything in their life would have brought them cumulatively. Again, I deem the perfectly informed consent of the person to be above anything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 14:56:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a physical harm nonetheless, and you're not "saving" anyone if they don't exist.

Guess it depends on whether you see this as a consent issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 14:02:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As much as I believe dragging someone into the world is a heinous act, I struggle to see how directly inflicting harm upon them without their informed approval is a lesser evil than exposing them to that harm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 03:44:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> keions noclipped through the floor

what will they do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-04 13:33:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't cut yourself on that edge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-03 13:17:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I find it more bizarre to procreate during a global pandemic and impending economic devastation, then make a joke out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-03 13:15:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who do you think makes up the Internet community if not real people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-03 13:13:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >This is a better time to be alive than most times of human history.

It is. And it's still shit.

Besides, disregarding another person's problems because the overall situation is better just isn't reasonable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 11:57:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not much simplification went into this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 12:40:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or, you know, not feeling like some demigod because you've paid for virtual cosmetics and treating other players as people instead of pets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 03:04:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reddit moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 14:03:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You ask us to acknowledge other people's perspective when the reason we are all here is the fact that they didn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 05:20:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's almost like no one can realistically guarantee the continuous well-being of their offspring, right? So where's the need? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 04:24:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dentro de dos semanas esto sí que va a ser una risa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-26 16:18:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I only do sometimes if it's a long-running anime. Openings are a separate kind of art by themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-26 15:01:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well you're not so much of "extreme empathy" if you direct it entirely towards the genocider instead of the innocent who've suffered and would have suffered extensively because of him.

The reason people are happy about his death is that millions have been spared from his leadership, not because they are sociopaths. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-26 13:04:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Es una obligación moral. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-26 12:45:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (Y)ui </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-26 03:13:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only reason we're able to reach that conclusion now is the fact that we're not constantly concerned with survival. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-25 22:11:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are literally not noticing this is a subreddit for closet lolicons? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-25 18:24:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Man, how can a meme be this personal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-25 00:51:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If there are less people in the world, everyone else will try to make up for their abscence by procreating more anyway. The (defeatist, I'll give you that) way I see it, although it's a moral obligation to me, trying to convince other people doesn't make much of a difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 21:57:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly my situation. Sometimes I see antinatalists talk about activism, but I don't see the point. The collective urge to reproduce is too big to counter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 19:46:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ~~mighty fine~~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 17:44:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought that way about the young ones inside the lost river. The ones who are outside, though, are still a whole different deal to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> gelnana and upa torture </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 20:18:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 20:12:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ranked \#2 on one of the most popular anime websites, so underrated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 10:17:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dabbing on Daru for knowingly birthing her into a world war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 08:33:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The car stops instantly if you actually get to the destination. I always do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 04:44:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some people are truly okay with the suffering in their lives, others even idealize it. That's on them.

However, I don't think it's wrong to say they should keep that to themselves. Forcing it on someone else who might not be of the same opinion is in no way ethical, especially when it's in their own interests (which happens to be always). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 04:14:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Physical pain isn't the only affliction that torments living creatures. As you said, people with CIPA invariably lead horrible lives because of their condition.

Like it or not, pain is necessary to protect us. And that's the real issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 04:56:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No tienes derecho a poner en riesgo a otras personas porque te apetezca dar un paseo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 03:44:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Qué hay con la obsesión por Evangelion en este sub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-17 22:01:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This meme shouldn't have died so quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-17 19:22:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Si cada persona puede interpretar una doctrina concreta como le dé la gana, ésta no tiene validez alguna. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-17 19:12:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No puedes descartar lo que no te gusta de tu religión como si nada. No tiene mucho sentido ser un católico que no ve problema en masturbarse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-17 12:42:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Color me surprised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 20:02:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same. Although I wasn't much of a vocal person to begin with, so disagreement usually comes through a screen.

I don't think there's a problem with the logic. The thing is, no one gives a flying fuck about it. I've never seen anyone doing a serious attempt at refuting it without resorting to name calling or appealing to emotion and nature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 19:09:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Ignore any and all logic. Do what feels good, regardless of who's affected by it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 19:06:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, you can't hold individuals accountable for their actions! It's other people's fault I can't do what *I* want! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-15 16:12:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lot of people replied to that tweet with the classic "but some people are ~~being deluded by their optimist bias into~~ enjoying it" or straight up bragging about having kids. They literally don't care. It's just another form of entertainment to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 20:55:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eyes as big as saucers, natural pink hair, ridiculously huge breasts, a hairless vagina that they have *no* shame in exposing, pencil thin arms... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 14:32:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lmao at people who think this quarantine is a productivity contest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 14:17:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Only Re;Birth trilogy and MegaTagmension, and it did take me a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 13:55:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously, why do they do that? Unless it's an announcement, it's completely uncalled for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 13:27:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't played Morrowind either, it's just that it's such a popular game that its most iconic features end up being known to a lot more people. Likely the same happens with S;G and people who haven't watched it, although it's probably not Kurisu's death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 13:13:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I only consume hidden gems among media. Ever heard of Steins;Gate and Morrowind? Thought so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 04:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They really rid her of body mass in the anime version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 04:33:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They literally don't put a single thought into it. It doesn't cross their minds because they don't deem it a choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-13 21:40:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If this was intentional, it's fucking genius. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-13 21:13:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No one knows the absolute truth, that's a given. I'm giving arguments in favor of what I believe.

What I mean with that last statement is that pleasure is but a mere distraction. When you're doing nothing you feel, at the very least, bored. When you fail to sustain your body, a myriad of afflictions will torment you. Inaction invariably leads to pain, therefore I think it's fair to say that it's the default state of being. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-13 20:41:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gifts can be discarded, and suicide is an extremely painful and risky way of doing so.

What if someone doesn't want to deal with the hardships of life? Their many needs will accompany them every day until death, and they never had a say in that.

>and in the end you will be fine

Browse r/morbidreality for a bit. You *won't* be fine.

>be happy and thankful for the beautiful things you got to enjoy

I'm thankful for being able to eat every day and having shelter. However, those are only countermeasures to the default state of pain, that could become unavailable at any time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-13 20:17:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >it is impossible to control everything as humans.

This is the core issue.

No one is truly capable of protecting their offspring from all danger. The people who try usually end up with spoiled brats who'll be eaten alive as soon as they leave their bubble.

If we can't predict, let alone prevent, all risk to our lives, then it's wrong to expose someone else to that risk without their express consent, because it was never *their* fight to begin with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-13 20:02:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed. I was fixated on most people's assumption that they are owed grandchildren, but the reasons for not making them can very well be made only taking into account your own demands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-13 19:39:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just because things have always been a certain way doesn't mean they are worth continuing.

For the entirety of human history, people have died from common illnesses. Does that mean modern medicine is a mistake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-13 15:40:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This bad time only proves no one is safe and therefore procreating is a gamble where only the recipient stands to lose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-13 15:23:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How in the world can *not* having children be a selfish decision? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-11 13:35:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The difference is they wouldn't get empathy from anyone, just mockery. All I see everyday is support for people who can't be with themselves for 10 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 11:55:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> En mi caso se extiende a la vida en general, pero mi forma de verlo no es el promortalismo, sino detener la creación de nuevos seres vivos.

De todas formas, uno no puede evitar que su cerebro reptiliano se active ante estas situaciones. Y morirse por problemas respiratorios no suena nada agradable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 11:44:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This whole situation will definitely polarize already opposing views.

The people who finally realize that these things can happen at any time to their kids may consider antinatalist thought, while the ones who had babies during the quatantine because they were bored (I have a hunch it's a lot) will boast around about the *miracles* of parenthood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-07 23:34:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As someone with a rather noticeable ponytail, I love this version of Freeman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-07 22:46:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The canon is whatever you want it to be except for the original 4chan post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-07 15:03:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't see the distinction. Wanting the amount of people in the world to be fewer is more of a birth strike than "soft" antinatalism, which wouldn't deem any birth justifiable in the first place. The way I'm interpreting what this guy said is that some people believe antinatalism to actually be a practical solution.

In that regard, I disagree. We just don't have the means to completely halt the creation of life, let alone leave this whole planet sterile. We just wait until it's no longer inhabitable and, in the meantime, try to minimize suffering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 15:10:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aprende a usar párrafos, donjuán. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-05 20:46:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gyms don't hold a monopoly to exercise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-05 19:01:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed. Who's this guy harming with this shit? People who specifically search his account and then act all sensitive just to have something to complain about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-05 02:09:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You just said it yourself. Horny people simply don't care, no matter the amount of means you offer. Coincidentally, it's a bit harder to get your hands on birth control during a pandemic. That, and people are being forced to stay together, with nothing to do. The circumstances are too ideal.

I'm calling a second boomer generation by the end of 2020/beginning of 2021. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-04 21:42:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Less than a century ago, millions of people died in the most catastrophic war in history. What followed?

The baby boom.

It happened specially in those countries where the damage was greater and the economic hardships at their peak. In any case, this situation will only encourage it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-04 13:41:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why does the MC always pull rapey shit as soon as someone shows interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-02 22:01:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Driving the seamoth without seeing a landmark is already terrifying, and then realizing you were in the wrong place like that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-02 20:28:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I jumped in while in the prawn suit assuming there was a bottom. Then it collapsed due to the depth and I heard a loud roar, after which two ghost leviathans came out of the void to tear me to shreds. Scariest shit I've experienced in years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-02 13:20:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unfortunately, I don't think so. The fact that people from here quickly get too familiar and close with each other probably aided the virus' spread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-02 11:09:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's why I always hated that subject in school. While necessary, everything exams amounted to was essentially memorising a vast amount of regrettable events and the names of awful people and what they did.

It's nice to see someone else who doesn't idealize the past. The fact that one can still be unhappy living in a developed country nowadays should be enough proof that the world is an unfixable mess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-01 21:58:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Regardless, insulting someone over that is uncalled for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-01 20:16:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They use those? That was on me then. Looks flawless otherwise! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-01 19:52:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The shortened links kinda gave it away, but I gotta say I did fall for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-01 15:17:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aun asumiendo que exista, o bien no es todopoderoso o bien no es benevolente. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-31 21:48:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you seen the guy without clothes, he's ~~using a generic male upper torso~~ fucking ripped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-31 18:32:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh boy I can't wait to see some of them Nae lewds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-31 18:02:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know you all say this as a joke, but just going by the serious content in this subreddit, it should be an unironic conclusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-31 11:23:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm currently playing the first one (5th case) and can confirm.

Just yesterday I had to figure out by trial and error that the game required me to press on a statement right after another when Phoenix apparently got implicit spoken evidence. >!Damon Gant allowed me to ask a question if I pressed him on a specific statement, Phoenix seemed to figure a contradiction which had to be proven just by pressing on another statement after that, quite unintuitive.!<

There was also a statement where non-contradicting evidence had to be presented in order to progress. >!It was Jake Marshall's reasons to rummage through the SL-9 incident 2 years later, for some reason I had to keep his statement going on for him by pulling out the archives and finding the name of a relative of his inside.!<

The game is hardly ever clear about what kind of input it wants from the player and, frankly, it's the most annoying part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-31 04:47:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not really. Almost every villain in this show had a specific indoctrination/event happen to them that messed with their previously empathetic mind and could be directly addressed later. In real life, a lot of people simply get a kick out of others' pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-31 04:33:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The second post is literally a loli with what looks like semen on her face, captioned "yogurt?". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 21:56:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kanna looks surprisingly good with that nose, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 18:08:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You really are comparing cartoons to a despicable crime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 21:27:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If thousands of much worse tragedies throughout history haven't sufficed, this will definitely not, either. Rather, they'll come up with an excuse that this will "fix" the current situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 21:02:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's no point, but the thought of it being limitless no matter what we do is quite scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 13:24:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, there's still the theory that the universe just keeps expanding and contracting indefinitely, and has gone through that process multiple times already.

That would mean everyone will lead a virtually infinite amount of lives, an infinite amount of times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 13:10:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ngl I'm thoroughly enjoying every second of seeing people go mad over not being able to go outdoors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 16:30:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think this sub is specific enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 16:27:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was sick to death of Game of Thrones content being spammed every second of the day, I never even watched the damn show. As soon as I found this site, where I could completely customize my feed and its content was also based around communities instead of individual posters, I instantly left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 15:45:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This but unironically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 15:44:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess it's about taking a different approach. My first (and only) playthrough would have been a lot different if I knew everything from the beginning, so maybe there's a charm in that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 20:48:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh là là, manda dos aportes y le publican los dos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 21:57:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Experience tranquility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 15:54:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fits perfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-21 21:12:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's something that just "clicks" if you start to question a lot of biased assumptions inherent to our minds without letting emotional barriers interrupt your train of thought.

Most people will just stop putting thought into whether procreation is right as soon as they reach an uncomfortable point, like the strong emotion that might stem from imagining their home town empty, or realizing they'll be forgotten one day without being able to "leave their print on the world". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-21 11:59:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish. Deadlines for assignments didn't magically disappear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-20 13:11:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> His legs look a bit too long to me, but honestly the rest makes up for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-20 12:59:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, I can't help but get high on schadenfreude seeing the kind of people who've always mocked my lifestyle and the way I am suffer through all of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-19 22:07:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nonexistence lookin kinda hot doe 😳😳😳 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-19 21:39:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually, you're right. It must be hard to see something you've been looking forward to for a long time vanish like that. That was a bitter take. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-19 21:29:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No joke, at this point I genuinely think I just watch it to make myself angry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-19 21:19:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a one-day event. You can absolutely be upset about it, but some people are acting like that's end of the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-19 21:11:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously, I don't get why, out of everything that's happening, this is what a lot of people choose to complain about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-19 16:06:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Magnificient. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-19 10:42:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From behind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 15:00:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The point is you never know what might happen, so yes, it's valid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 12:32:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jesus fuck, I swear this kind of shit impairs my brain functions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 12:05:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I'm getting a blast out of this. Being a sanitary role model by sitting on my ass all day was never this easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 11:53:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In sexual reproduction, a baby needs input from two people.

While the woman chooses not to end the pregnancy, it's also the man who decides to impregnate her or at least not take enough preventive measures.

Now, this is only true about specific cases in first world countries. In the rest of the world, this decision is usually only up to men, and women are coerced into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 16:07:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is. Wasn't expecting to see them all greyed out when I logged in. I'd like to know why.

Iceborne soundtrack seems to be working as of now, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 08:27:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The original was already like this but someone edited sunrise in. The comedy cycle is now complete. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 07:46:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why would they hide a cute picture among all of that lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-16 03:34:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Disregarding the inherent optimism bias present in every single human, what about those who don't? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-15 22:14:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do people keep thinking antisocial and asocial people are the same thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-14 15:37:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No one thinks shit will happen to them until it does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-13 21:29:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> u/vredditdownloader </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-13 07:54:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "What do you get when you cross a large batch of the population at high risk of dying from a new virus due to old age and their refusal to implement protective measures that would prevent the young from being carriers?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-13 07:45:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That'll hold him alwight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-13 07:40:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I knew this would be misinterpreted lol

It's the same reason why the good old "but she's actually 500 years old" argument isn't valid, because you can claim she's any age you want since it's an abstract concept in fiction, no matter how the character looks and acts, which is the only thing that really matters in this context.

In this case, I assume no one would be able to tell the main characters from Pokémon are 12 and below if they haven't looked it up before because they honestly don't look *that* young. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-13 02:30:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Canonical age is irrelevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-12 18:03:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mis espaguetis están secos, razón por la cual se me ha ocurrido juntarlos con algún condimento. De lo contrario, me temo que tendrán un sabor insípido y soso, e ingerir un plato tan sumamente copioso en su totalidad se me hará una tarea tediosa a más no poder. ¿Alguien sabría indicarme cuál sería la salsa más apropiada? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-12 08:55:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Indoors gang high on schadenfreude atm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 23:06:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've seen that same argument used a lot in favor of bullfighting. "Live and let live" only applies when the freedom of others isn't being infringed.

My point hasn't changed. You're assuming potential pleasure is being wrongfully taken away from them, but even if it was guaranteed, how could we be stealing something from someone who doesn't exist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 21:53:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The nonexistent can't be harmed by the abscence of pleasure. Babies aren't queuing to be born. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 20:25:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For some reason I really hate seeing that specific character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 19:40:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "A free man usually became a serf because he owed a large debt."

Literally the first sentence from the section ["becoming a serf" in the Wikipedia article on serfdom.](https://simple.wikipedia.org/wiki/Serfdom#Becoming_a_serf) Granted, these people could own property and money, but they weren't legally free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 17:49:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never supported the murder of anyone in my comment. I'm expressing gratitude for the things I'm so statistically unlikely to have while acknowledging that, had my needs not been created, none of them would be necessary.

I'm not denying people can lead great lives. It's perfectly possible, regardless of their economic status. Hell, good for them if they're having a nice time here. The problem is no one gets a choice on whether they are born or not. Had I been given one, having perfect knowledge of its consequences, I'm positive I'd be in that nonexistent crowd. The deed is done already for the alive, but any of them have just enough control to choose not to perpetuate this cycle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 15:12:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm complaining about having been brought into the world without my consent, not the current circumstances of my life as a middle class guy in a developed country who luckily doesn't have to worry about food or shelter like most other people factually do.

Thanks for ignoring the rest of my points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 14:32:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So either bite the bullet now or take it up the ass later, right? And you still don't see how forcing someone into that cycle is wrong?

>it seems you agree with the assessment it because you are still alive despite the sufferings you are under.

Disregarding self-preservation instincts and the fact that I can't really complain about my specific life...

Think of it as an evening at the theatre.  You go see a movie that ends up being trash. Although it's not bad enough to make you leave before it's over, you conclude that it would have been better not to go in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 13:39:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your romantization of literal slavery in one of the darkest eras in history is misguided at best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 09:06:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Technically speaking, antinatalism itself doesn't take a stance on whether life is  worth continuing. However, it's pretty established by it that it's never worth starting, so the answer to that last question is yes.

You should check out r/birthstrike, though - I think their arguments align with yours in the regard that quality of life is preferable over quantity, without extinction being the end goal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 21:27:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, suffering is a basic part of life, and yet you still chose to force it upon someone you claim to love.

>my kid is one of the most happiest

Or so you think. That might not be the case tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 16:49:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Hitler-kun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 11:20:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I won't. Although you should remember every time you see yours suffer that only you will have made it possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 07:40:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, ideally no one would, but with knowledge that your descendants are likely to suffer, it doesn't seem as far-fetched to suggest abstaining from it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 02:20:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's so easy to take the risk when it's not you who'll suffer the consequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 02:10:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why did you have kids if you knew severe depression runs in your family? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 22:16:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That does in no way mitigate the gravity of what they did at all. They're aware enough of their actions to make choices and definitely not victims here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 11:29:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it was more because of the threats to his mother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 02:07:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Initially it was about the futility of life. Apparently now it's about returning to some ideal, made up past. Couldn't stand that at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 21:18:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It meant stop, but tbh images with text can still be reaction images. I just prefer when the focus is on facial expressions and gestures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 11:23:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No sabía que necesitaba memes de doge en español hasta ahora. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 01:56:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apparently other people do. It's more about being treated with basic decency than anything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 01:40:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ngl this is pretty accurate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> mfw someone posts yet another image with text </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 01:34:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-06 18:26:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How's that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-06 18:21:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That would be because most couples tend to procreate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-06 07:51:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This but unironically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 22:55:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rule of thumb: if it seems too easy, then you must have done something wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 21:38:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course, to reach that I just assumed the whole situation was remotely possible in the first place lol

But honestly, the original anime was also guilty of this at times. A particular scene that felt completely out of place was when Rintaro headbutted a rounder that was aiming a gun right at his head out of a car. Plot armor is hardly ever justified in this franchise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 14:08:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She should have just killed him like the other goons. Daru's intervention was completely absurd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 23:58:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed, it already managed to be unsettling enough without it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 21:08:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Truly makes me want to take a shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 18:42:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Evan literally killed the first neutral goon he encountered with his fists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 18:05:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I wasn't the only one thinking this lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 11:22:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >I can’t believe I’m bringing a whole human to this nasty nasty world.

No one forced you to. It was your conscious decision to expose them to the evils of existence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 11:19:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So easy to say that when it's not your life what's being gambled with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-01 12:54:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Blessed crossover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-29 15:13:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Este meme fue creado por banda hierba </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 18:45:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >if you hate kids for no damn reason then something is wrong with you.

"I don't have to come up with good arguments if I claim you are mentally disabled". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 18:08:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You fun gang never fail to show up to remind people how boring they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 12:53:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because people choose to be betrayed, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-25 12:04:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who gets to decide which rules are "unjust"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-24 21:30:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-24 08:17:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Leafies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-24 01:25:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not having children and I try not to pollute the environment. With that out of the way, I honestly doubt there's anything else we, as individuals, can do about it. It may be a defeatist argument, but that's my take. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 20:24:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Global warming won't render Earth inhospitable for every sentient being. There will always be survivors to a global catastrophe. This planet has already suffered multiple environmental rearrangements before the existence of humans, so I'm positive destroying all life on it is well beyond our reach.

Practical application of antinatalism is also virtually impossible, so there's no use in pondering on its actual consequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 19:41:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An expensive joke at that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 14:15:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This "article" is one of the most childish things I've read in my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 11:31:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having kids for the sole reason of dumping your emotional baggage on them seems to be a widely accepted reason.

And people will say refusing to do it is selfish. What a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-22 22:18:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> car crucifixion

car crucifixion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-22 22:10:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They look like bootleg Eru and Hotaro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-22 18:56:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously, it's like people believe an imaginary third party is to blame for their actions when it comes to procreation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 16:31:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I did flinch, just not in the usual way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 14:35:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The thing is, there is no point in reaching that hypothetical pinnacle. Every second of our continued existence requires the suffering of both other beings and our own. If starting life is bad in the first place, any reason to further spread it is wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-20 01:12:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Didn't you get the news? You can get away with anything if you call it a prank nowadays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-20 01:00:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a choice between bad and worse, I guess. Either bite the bullet now or let the world and your own thoughts punish you later.

Not too enticing of a motivational technique, but it works for me. And hey, maybe the bad ends up being good for once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-19 10:56:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Acting like she literally can't see that procreation is a choice, just so that she can justify that the negative consequences of her actions aren't her fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-19 10:09:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It baffles me how anyone could even consider bringing someone into a world where they'd have to coexist with people like that. There's cruelty in its purest form, and then there's cartels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-19 10:04:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those subreddits are disgusting. It's almost absurd how positive people's reaction towards brutality is in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 13:08:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >unless you’re blue blood royalty

The whole point is that absolutely no one should pass it on. There's never an objective reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 10:57:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Images you can hear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-17 08:49:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cualquier motivo para disminuir la natalidad es válido. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-16 21:55:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lol the photos are already on the Net, unconvincing apologies are absurd at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-14 11:48:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Smooth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 20:43:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hmm today I'll help another four survivors lower the bridge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 07:55:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not cringe. This is actually a good catch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 23:55:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have to agree there, Suzu sounds like a fucking kid and Rintaro's voice is ridiculously deep. Dub all the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 23:28:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There isn't a set date for humanity to end, but everything perishes eventually. I doubt we'll even be around when the Sun engulfs Earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 18:57:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But it's also required for almost anything and it quickly clogs up your inventory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 10:25:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People would do good to learn some humbleness from this guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 09:56:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can see your argument against porn where real people are involved since it can be a really grey area. The problem is people at that sub are against masturbation of any sort, in addition to fictional porn. Procreation is the only way they can justify getting off in their minds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-11 13:06:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same tbh. The little bullying I got here and there was objectively pretty light, as were the rare pranks from friends. My parents were a bit demanding with grades, but otherwise nice people. Only thing I can think of was their kind of messy divorce. I've always been the overly sensitive type, so I guess I exacerbated the impact those things had on me.

On the other hand, I can't help but believe not getting involved in anything or anyone on my own accord throughout most of my life has prevented a lot of undesirable situations to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 15:51:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ow the edge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 21:31:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, they knew exactly what they were doing the whole time. Stop pretending they're too young to be held accountable. They're not, and they will not feel guilt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 12:05:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dunno, Ritsu is kind of a dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 07:53:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These kind of trends make my blood boil. Remember the "choking game" some years ago? Just giving more protection to teens old enough to be accountable for their actions just because they are underage, and promoting bullying.

Fucking zoomers, I swear. Even in other threads where injury isn't directly perceivable, they'll wholeheartedly defend this as playful banter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 02:33:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You just said you were a nihilist/absurdist, but this sounds like the complete opposite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 02:27:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is some advanced shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-06 16:36:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can't fix a broken plate by apologizing to it, Shoya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-06 16:26:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Based </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-06 07:35:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is exactly what sets AN apart from eugenics and it's important to remember it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-05 17:13:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have a whole sub dedicated to parodying his comics, and you choose to complain about accidental exposure? The mere existence of this place is free advertising. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-05 09:09:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This makes no sense. One can go to a remote place before ending their lives. Some people don't have anyone who cares for them. What exactly makes it wrong in those cases then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-05 08:40:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Meeting the man who knowingly birthed you into a world war fills you with rage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-05 02:15:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When you can't gather consent, it defaults to a "no".

Is it starting to make sense? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-05 02:14:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This isn't about you. You don't get to bring another person into this mess without their consent and feel righteous about it because you're not "giving up". Monkeys do it without thinking twice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-05 02:05:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Notice how you ran out of arguments and started calling names the moment consent came into question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-04 15:41:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course I've been close to jerks like that at times. Continuous "pranks" in the name of friendship is usually how you learn to despise this behavior.

People I choose to be around now don't humilliate me like this as soon as I look away. Even with the occasional roasting, I know I can trust them, that's why they're called *friends*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-04 13:38:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Statistically speaking, it's safe to assume anyone will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-04 13:03:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The problem here is that the guy who gets the blame is the one who didn't do it. Careless? Sure. But he wasn't pulling anything that would hurt himself, other people did.

>However, when you climb into a shopping cart curled up in a ball what do you expect?

Change the action in this sentence and you'll find why this logic is harmful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-04 12:32:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why was this posted here? Are your friends so dickish that it would be idiotic to lower your guard around them? Fuck the guy in the video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 22:50:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a difference between playful roasting and making someone lose their balance and fall with all their weight on the floor. You don't know how easy it is to fuck your body up for life.

Seriously, this tendency to jump at the slightest chance to call someone else names has me wondering how young the people I talk to here are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 20:40:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I, too, wish to expose myself to physical abuse and risk lifelong injuries just to hang out with the cool kids. Wouldn't want to be associated with those boring nerds, amirite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-01 16:28:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course, I'm just talking about being skilled at maneuvering in a specific environment and having reliable safety nets. Strip someone of that and, obviously, they'll be vulnerable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-31 20:17:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah, all that "everyone else is clueless" talk just doesn't sit right with me. I believe some people actually have their shit together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-31 08:39:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Estos reposts de Cuánto Cabrón me traen muchos recuerdos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-31 01:08:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course I've done stupid shit and hurt myself, everyone has. The difference is eventually learning from its consequences and knowing when to cut it out before seriously fucking yourself up. And it's not like the guy in the video is that much of a child, to be honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-30 21:21:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When you're so braindead as to consistently put yourself in jeopardy and end up with permanent injuries, yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 23:12:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When you manage to swallow the pill but you clench your throat muscles too soon and it slowly tears you from the inside as it makes its way down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 22:50:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Team For Tres </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 08:51:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd ask the opposite. Ui was basically her mother by high school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-28 21:17:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah I think you force filled way too many categories. Seeing Biker and the Hobo as "pure" just doesn't fit.

I could see a shorter version being accurate, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-28 19:45:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Imagine basing your worth and dedicating your whole life to worthless post-mortem perks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-28 12:22:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> b but ha*dholding so lewd!!1! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-28 12:19:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Boy, do I have a surprise for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-27 22:29:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 4chan threads are vastly pretty disgusting erotica with the ocasional gore troll. Is there somewhere else to find exclusively SFW? I don't really do the hentai thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-26 22:34:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nigga manny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-26 22:06:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I second this. It sounds a bit authoritarian to say "close your legs", but, to those who aren't being forced into having sex, it should be logical to think before acting.

I've seen the argument "but they can't afford birth control" thrown around a lot. My answer is: learn to control your nonessential urges for a second. I just don't get what's so hard about simply *not* performing coitus all the time. You can get off in multiple other ways, so what's the deal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-25 19:32:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fear and pain are also some of my strongest (and only) motivators. However, I don't think being pushed around by pain to survive is a great way of existing, but that's me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-25 03:38:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To be honest, for how much they charge, they *should* be making miracles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 22:01:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's so easy to fall into and escalate this situation that it's scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 21:18:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's sad that it's the only way, not the fact that life will end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 14:41:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I actually agree lol. They are basically a better version of futas because they aren't grotesquely big and, unlike them, act ridiculously femininely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-23 11:52:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Discord is just as strict as Reddit on this matter, if not more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-21 22:41:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Animals will procreate more under favorable conditions, so creating a better environment merely allows for more suffering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-21 22:01:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My update schedule is nothing but a comedy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-21 21:57:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Crosspost to r/MemeRestoration </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-21 14:05:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How gentleman-ish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-20 21:58:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nauseatingly grotesque. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-20 21:28:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-20 00:22:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Put that way, I admit it's a valid argument. This kind of business could be considered predatory to an extent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-19 21:57:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which part of that statement doesn't sound right to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-19 20:19:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why does so much great official art go into mobile card games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-19 18:02:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> eras mu sarnoso jaja rmcf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-19 13:44:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By that I meant it's dumb to think that the more power a character has, the "better" they are. OP characters aren't necessarily bad, your example is proof. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-19 12:22:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The first statement is still false. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-19 12:20:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Overpowered character ≠ Good character </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-19 12:10:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To be fair you have to have a very high IQ to understand Neon Genesis Evangelion. The plot is extremely complex, and without a solid grasp of human psychology most of the themes will go over a typical viewer’s head. There’s also Anno's atheistic outlook, which is deftly woven into his show- his personal philosophy draws heavily from Søren Kierkegaard literature, for instance. The fans understand this stuff; they have the intellectual capacity to truly appreciate the depths of these characters, to realize that they’re not just cartoons- they say something deep about LIFE. As a consequence people who dislike Evangelion truly ARE idiots- of course they wouldn’t appreciate, for instance, the depth in Gendo's famous line “Get in the robot, Shinji,” which itself is a cryptic reference to Sigmund Freud's idea of the Oedipus Complex and how Shinji is fighting the urge to literally be inside his mother. I’m smirking right now just imagining one of those addlepated simpletons scratching their heads in confusion as Hideaki Anno’s genius wit unfolds itself on their screens. What fools.. how I pity them. 😂
And yes, by the way, i DO have a Eva tattoo. And no, you cannot see it. It’s for the ladies’ eyes only- and even then they have to demonstrate that they’re within 5 IQ points of my own (preferably lower) beforehand. Nothin personnel kid 😎 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-19 11:24:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You disgust me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-19 10:52:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What these people fail to see are humanity's limitations. They believe that *somehow* our species will figure out a way to prevent all suffering in the future, fully knowing that it's the default state of life. A baseless excuse the emotional part of their brains provides them with to justify contributing to the cycle.

As pragmatic as I am, I don't think there is a practical approach to this issue. Everyone who's alive is invariably inclined to procreate, yet only a few stop to think about what it actually causes.

Also, user 3's argument is wrong by default. No matter how many people with a specific way to think refuse to have kids, more will inevitably be born. Antinatalism has been around for a long time, so what's their explanation for the continued existence of people who won't spread their genes, only their ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-18 13:50:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hit the nail on the head.

I've seen some people argue that maybe if the unborn could be shown a trailer about their lives before being asked to come into them, it would be a fair situation. The problem with that is the fact that they can't be truly aware of *everything* that choice will entail by merely watching a video.

Perfect information is a requirement if we're talking about actual freedom of choice. Presenting options completely clouded by the abscence of key details or straight up without context doesn't count. Consent can't be provided without full awareness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-18 13:35:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly didn't see that one coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-18 01:14:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, you take the nightmarish death (if the skip even allows you to have that relief), I'll gladly take prison over the slightest chance of keter duty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-17 22:48:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To be fair, it's not really okay to physically threaten someone over this shit at any age, specially when *he* was the one who started it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-17 22:41:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We're all slaves to out biological needs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-17 22:08:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >Sometimes, I don't mind that I can't bond with people, I don't mind that I feel like an outsider. It only hurts because I feel like I can't rely on anyone to feel safe.

This right here. You're most unsafe when you're on your own, with no one else to help you out of deep shit.

Otherwise, I also fail to find enough incentives to put effort into people. Most of them seem unlikable and unempathetic to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-17 21:43:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have hope for a better future then. It's only human. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-17 21:00:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even the most pessimistic person in the world right now has an optimism bias merely because of the fact that they're currently alive. Nonsensical hope is the only reason people go on with their lives, so it's only natural that most would ignore their ability to reason when it comes to such instinctual matters. Some others are definitely acting in bad faith as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-17 20:37:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, but apparently physical assault doesn't count when you're underage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-17 19:54:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >she is precious and needs to be protected

Pretty weeb way to talk about a drawing but ok.

>They make the excuse that she's 900

Common strawman. No one uses that as a serious excuse.

>in many countries it's considered simulated CP and punishable as CP

Legality does not equal morality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-17 19:19:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So much pent-up anger over a shitty meme. Impressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-17 13:00:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This looks really good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 23:24:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I sure am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 20:21:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Such irrelevant context totally makes this a normal scene and definitely not some cheap fetish fuel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 18:30:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's more of a survival feature, since it allows us to have hope for even a doomed future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 11:48:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Riéndome Fuera Alto </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-15 22:42:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ¿Significa eso que mi fetiche de traps no me convierte en homosexual?

Jaque mate zoomers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-14 13:51:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >All he has are his empirical observations and his lived experience

Sounds like valid evidence to me.

>Why is suffering objectively bad?

ok mother teresa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 22:51:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Imagine unironically calling life a gift. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 14:14:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But they evolve. The theory goes that all first lifeforms were like that, until they started making up multicellular organisms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 14:10:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's sadly the only guaranteed end of life on earth. Otherwise, you can hope for an incredibly massive meteorite to obliterate it during that period of time, which is still a possibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 02:47:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Petition to rename this sub to r/AhegaoHoodieCreepshots </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 02:40:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is pointless suffering. Some lifeforms are bound to remain, and the cycle will be started again. Only an external force can put an end to this.

Looking forward to the Sun completely engulfing the Earth in around 5 billion years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A little animation I made for a project </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-12 01:44:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> shinji evangelion dab </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-11 22:35:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-11 12:55:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The original comic had the exact same message. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-11 12:48:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Didn't realize it was a crossover, but it looks dope. I've never seen a Moemura this cute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-11 12:19:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just wait until you get to the next difficulty spike. They're all over the first remake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-11 12:05:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I *never* would have expected this to become a subreddit for cute loli artwork and I'm definitely *not* glad it did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-11 11:52:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Barren planet gang </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-11 10:57:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Weird how people wholeheartedly agree with the logic in a meme, but as soon as you take it into a serious context it suddenly becomes a disgusting way to think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-11 02:38:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not another talented genius who just happens to be a loser so people can relate to them. I want someone REAL and AUTHENTIC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-10 18:53:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is some next level retrowaving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-10 18:45:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just consider it a story based on the absurd. Because how can a deranged detective board a boat, kill a hundred mobsters armed to the teeth and come out unscathed?

To be honest, I feel it happens with most combat-based games. It's all for the gameplay's sake. The character controlled by the player is always a one man army, able to withstand and recover from an impossible amount of damage or literally going back in time to a moment when they weren't dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-10 13:16:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not a promortalist, but I agree. It's just that the red button is a laughably convenient scenario. Considering sentience developed from what was once unicellular life, you'd have to take it into account as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-10 00:49:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This meme radiates sheer intensity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-10 00:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There'll come a time in your life when you'll no longer be able to. That's why refusing to have children is scary to most people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-09 18:37:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is really well done. I wasn't expecting those unsettling sounds or changes in volume. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-09 15:22:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most circumstances are out of your control. People don't just decide to, let's say, get murdered one day. It simply happens and they can do nothing about it.

Nothing wrong with having a goal in the present. However, it becomes immoral the moment you create another life in its pursuit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-09 15:14:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So a completely one-sided decision that negatively affects other people is ultimately ethical because the one who made it gets something out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-09 14:55:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are very few ways to die peacefully, if any. And they certainly don't make up for the rest of them.

As for its "purpose", I don't think there is some grandiose end goal to all this fight. There wouldn't be a battle in the first place if people weren't continuously being pulled into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-08 22:04:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> > dicen algo profundo sobre LIFE

Vale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-08 21:34:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Schediaphile or nijikon, though you're getting roasted if you use those terms unironically.

Can't answer your second question and would also like an answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-08 19:35:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's true. People will only stick around when they can get something out of you, be it favors or status.

Your self, on the other hand, remains at your side no matter what, so might as well take a liking to the guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-08 19:15:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 0 is still more than -1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-08 18:47:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Man, I don't know who's creepier, him openly wearing a hoodie with cropped porn on it or you taking pictures of him and posting them on the Internet without his knowledge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-08 18:23:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bro if you don't like this imposition you can just inflict pain on yourself bro what's the deal bro it's your fault you can't ignore direct orders from your reptilian brain to stay alive bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-08 18:10:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's lots of opinions on 4chan because people just don't give a shit about what others might think in an anonymous image board where a thread could realistically be just a guy arguing with himself.

The thing that's wrong with 4chan is the absolute anarchy, usually making you come across unwanted disturbing content regularly, and not being able to tell who you're talking to, imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-08 17:22:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is peak Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-08 17:00:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In the end, he just wanted life to flourish back more strongly. What he failed to realize was that the cycle is doomed to be repeated eternally, because that's just how lifeforms act. They replicate until there aren't enough resources for everyone.

As the wielder of the power of a God, it was his moral duty to put an almost instant end to this madness. He chose a painful step backwards instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-08 13:47:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those assholes kept hitting me even when I looked straight at their face, so go figure.

And Metro 2033 is definitely a survival horror, just not *purely* horror. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-06 22:05:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lol why would you hold yourself to a lender's standards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-05 12:51:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> drawings bad, prison rape good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-04 22:23:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The mental fortitude required to go through with it and the physical pain it can cause to a person are brutally high, aside from the consequences one will face if they even survive. If there was a choice to peacefully die during your sleep at a random night, I don't doubt many people would take it, because anything else is just too scary to consider. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-04 21:26:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, tú. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-04 16:55:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *pimche </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-04 15:20:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Couldn't agree more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-03 19:35:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exposing someone to the elements without their approval counts as being a dick.

Edit: Why was this removed by a mod? It was just a disagreeing comment lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-03 14:44:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's always a choice between bad and worse. Jeez, I'm so glad I'm alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-03 05:41:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because being pushed around by fear every day is a great way to live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-03 04:50:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, I recall him saying he worked out a bit, but that's some next level gains for a hikikomori. Then again, he doesn't really fit the mold of one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-03 02:45:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why's Subaru so fucking jacked, it's almost ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-02 21:02:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's hard for me to tell if the person who made this is being self aware, because many times they're not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-02 14:27:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's with these people who think being into anime somehow provides them with extensive insight into Japanese culture? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-02 05:58:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People aren't entitled to anyone. This isn't about *them*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-02 01:30:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> (S)he's a girl to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-01 22:09:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't lewd the mafia boss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> gotta get a time piece </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-01 16:32:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-01 03:21:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "hurr durr i don't waste energy on menial tasks"

\*cute girl asks him to*

"wtf i like solving mysteries now" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-31 20:35:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The planet isn't "dying" though, just the current environmental balance, and it's going to take a catastrophe out of mankind's reach to kill it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-31 20:26:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have fun hanging out with people who'll steal from you as soon as you lower your guard, I guess. I'll keep my wallet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-31 15:34:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're not being treated with respect by your friends if they're taking shit from you while you're drunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-30 23:30:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't fathom why [this stunning art](https://www.pixiv.net/en/artworks/57540067) has so few bookmarks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Casual </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-30 23:27:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A true gentleman leaves no SCP uncontained </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-30 00:14:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A true gentleman leaves no SCP uncontained </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-30 00:02:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-29 05:41:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Source](https://i.imgur.com/XJgAKvY.png) is a puzzle from Professor Layton and the Azran Legacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A true gentleman leaves no SCP uncontained </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-29 05:25:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-29 01:12:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Full res](https://danbooru.donmai.us/data/__uni_and_dogoo_neptune_drawn_by_tsunako__60c652b547e90dd095ae3fd5e4b8aa76.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Melting </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-29 01:11:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-29 00:38:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One of the few series where I feel it's balanced and proportionate, and actually belongs and adds value. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-29 00:18:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Facts don't care about your feelings.

Astolfo might, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 21:27:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> {Wasted potential} </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> tfw the cheap harem tropes of the vn made it into your otherwise decent anime adaptation </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 21:25:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> shut the fcuk up luka </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 21:00:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 14:26:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, it just teleporting to random locations is way too overpowered. Although less scary than your hypothesis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 13:51:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> enemy gamer spotted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 04:47:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, one of the blandest MCs in the history of anime and the personification of 2D trap fetish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 04:54:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn't the set of values it's supposed to convey the complete opposite? Anime is usually loaded with pro-natalist propaganda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-23 19:38:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 0 was better than the first season tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 12:13:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> > If humans didn’t exist we’d just have nothing.

Which is still way better than what we have now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 10:46:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think the devs put that much thought into it, but it's a very nice theory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-20 17:55:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know where this character is from and I can't for the life of me find a source. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Carrying a bag </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-20 17:55:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-20 12:31:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Giving people a taste of gilding seems to make them crave more, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-20 12:29:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've already expressed my concerns regarding this issue in other posts.

The thing with trying to put an end to animal suffering, aside from the fact that it's virtually impossible, is that we wouldn't really be fixing the root problem. As long as we don't know where life originated, we can't start aiming our efforts into completely stopping its creation since we would just be cutting off branches.

Although I still see a valid point in the belief that research might one day show us how life came to exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-19 13:46:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Creo que tenemos prioridades muy distintas en la vida. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-19 02:06:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That last paragraph hit the nail on the head. We still don't know where life came from, and it's scary to think that some chunk of inanimate matter could have just gained conscience and started replicating out of nowhere. Who's to say the cycle of suffering doesn't exist somewhere else in the universe, or could effectively be stopped at any time on Earth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-19 01:36:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >just spent a couple hours

That's far from what most people deem low effort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ngl this is me when hacking to the gate </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-18 23:06:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-18 12:15:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Selfless people don't "gift" human beings. And if their future grandparents are the ones demanding them, there are few other adjectives to describe that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-18 10:41:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, parents are certainly not thinking of what the person who doesn't exist wants when they're making it, they are only thinking about themselves, so it seems logical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-17 23:43:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ironically, with their deep fondness of nature, the guys over at r/misanthropy made me realize that it wasn't specifically humans what I hated, but the concept of sentient life itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-17 20:58:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ngl I never thought that damn pink-haired fiend would grab my attention </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-17 20:08:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >!Tsukasa en tu casa!< </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> You've heard of Elf on the Shelf </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-17 20:07:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-17 12:49:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like introversion is basically a disability nowadays. You just can't live up to society's standards and remain content if you need to recharge all the time while other people are able to gather energy from it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-16 20:30:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The fact that such a cramped country is having problems due to a lack of births speaks volumes of how unsustainable this whole system is. Endless population growth just isn't possible, so it all inevitably ends up collapsing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-16 17:15:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not even that method has a success rate of 100%.

It's crazy how you can't really take the risk away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-15 14:27:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >I feel like some social harassment is also beneficial for someone to become a well-adjusted adult.

Try telling that to people who can't function in society due to being relentlessly bullied throughout their lives. Even better, to the ones who've killed themselves over it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-14 22:14:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So, an AI without a personality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-14 12:22:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Source](https://www.pixiv.net/en/artworks/61827137) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> On a date </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-14 12:22:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-13 20:10:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can't act in the best interest of someone that doesn't exist because you have no way of knowing what that would be if they were alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-13 15:05:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know, already got the image. What I don't know is why you're being downvoted now, that was funny af </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-13 15:04:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit, talk about humblebrag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-13 14:43:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eat my shorts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-13 11:16:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No that easy to swallow either when they can't acknowledge it even if it's right in front of them.

Not getting to spread their genes is a real bummer to many people because, initially, it just feels inherently wrong. Only when you put aside your kneejerk reaction can you see the value of the argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-13 00:12:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You know it's over when adults keep remarking how mature you are as a kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-12 13:23:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why did they feel the need to make a smug remark about your ban? That space should be reserved for clarifications. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-12 08:02:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ok boomer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 22:32:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No sperm don't go!! Oh my god he has airpods on he can't hear us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 22:23:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, OP is a real piece of work lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 21:58:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wouldn't happen to be [this guy](http://rq87.flyingomelette.com/HNK/1/51/13.jpg) being thrown into a bed of spikes in episode 51, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 20:35:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It'd be real nice of them, but how would you go about forcing them to tell you that? They could just make up a shitty ending that's worse than a cliffhanger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 20:25:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every time someone screenshots their own reply I physically recoil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 16:04:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wicked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 15:46:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> u/vredditdownloader </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 12:39:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a few good ones, but most are trash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 09:05:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is spot on except for Hat Kid, but I guess there aren't any other characters in this game full of pricks to fill that spot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 08:30:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You underestimate the privilege that is being left alone by other people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 08:27:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You powertripping mods ruined this place, and then childishly try to mock other subs with wacky unfunny remarks. That's the real comedy here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 16:38:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's certainly a challenging dilemma, but the answer is clear to me.

If this unbelievably convenient method to end all pain existed, it would be anyone's moral responsibility to use it. Because sentient beings *will* continue to violate the consent of new lifeforms.

Being fully aware of this, could pressing the button really be considered a misdeed? What takes priority, the right of present life to keep existing or the prevention of countless repetitions of the cycle of suffering? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 15:57:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thx king </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 12:39:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You put out my thoughts more eloquently than I ever have.

The problem I see with promortalist efforts in order to reach an end of suffering is that we simply lack the power to perform them flawlessly, and mistakes can lead to far worse situations than the fragile balance of civilization we're lucky to have nowadays.

It is definitely a defeatist attitude, but as you said, the future is already looking bad for those concerned with these issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 08:52:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Source](https://www.pixiv.net/en/artworks/44968811) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Uni </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 08:51:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 08:39:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Certified bruh moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 08:32:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe Kevin wouldn't be so butthurt if he had died working in one of those mines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
