<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject1</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This is why you don't program in JavaScript. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 22:15:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 20:59:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ME SAY ALONG RAML OH GK TO MOLS KREILSYSTEM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 20:51:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> May my responses be used for the good of people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 18:35:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks Stranger, I'll be trying my best. Remember to take care of yourself out there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 18:34:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At first it was just a bit of a fog, then I thought about it and knew everything was wrong. Thank you for the kind words, and I wish you the best of this world as well, take care! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 18:33:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 18:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! Dad said he'd try to help me any way he can, so I think I'm gonna be alright. Take care of yourself out there too, mkay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 10:59:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm only 13 and don't know too much about medical stuff, but your fingers look fine to me. You probably just never noticed that your fingertips are slightly raised </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 10:52:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That really sucks, I'm sorry to hear that. I kinda get that. I actually talked with my dad just because he's a lot more patient and doesn't exaggerate stuff. I really hope you're doing okay out there, and if you're not doing so nice, I hope it can all get at least a little better. Take care out there, and thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 10:49:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you. I've been workin' myself up to this for even a little before my post on my alt. account, took me all day yesterday to even say "it's alright, you'll be okay, go do this". Kinda hard to think about that last point though, and kind of sad. Makes me feel bad for a lot of people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 10:46:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you Stranger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 06:14:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 06:13:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you too! I hope I can help as many people living with stuff like me as well, so that no one has to go through it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I (guy, 13) told my dad about how I've been abused for the past 2 years </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 05:47:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So one thing I wanna say, I actually posted a bit about this on an alt account a few days ago ( /u/HwaypointH ). I actually owe quite a bit to the few who decided to take the time to read and comment, because you were the reasons I even spoke to my dad.

I'm feelin a little bad for the guy who was doing these things to me, but my dad reassured me it wasn't my fault, still though. I'm happy though, I can finally move on and not be worried about all this stuff. Short and a little disorganized I know, but I just wanted to tell somebody.

My advice to people who are going through any form of abuse: it will be okay. Just prepare yourself a bit and let it out a little to somebody you really trust, and they'll help you. Just don't wait till it's too late, you do stupid stuff then, and believe me, it's not worth it. Just take care of yourself out there.

Thank you all for your kind words! I'll be alright over here, and I hope you all can be too, or at least get a little better soon. Here's a quick little update if anybody's curious on what's going on.

Dad got a hold of some pastors from out church (they are close friends, and this guy was from the church) and we talked today, it was mainly me reciting what I already told Dad. Anyways, Dad will be filing a police report tomorrow, and I don't really know what the church will do. So, there's that. Again, I wish you all the best of this world. Take care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> i see </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 10:17:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 00:47:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take our upvotes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 05:59:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm only 13 and certainly not an expert but I do believe you should get that checked out, specially since it looks infected to hell and back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 21:35:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah, okay. I'll keep watching out then. I also think I'll be able to figure out why this is happening and... go from there I guess. Thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 21:08:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey thanks for the reply. I'll be trying to talk to my parents about this today and hope for the best. I know you said you wouldn't but I have a strong sense of curiosity, what are a few things that could happen if this goes uncontrolled? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 09:37:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Howdy stranger. It's kinda omforting to see someone who's going through the same sort of thing. I do know I need some help (and have for the past 7 or so years, I'm 13), and really get it though. I keep telling my parents but they say I'm "fine, just normal", that stuff. I think I'll tell em about this one and maybe I can start to get some help. Thanks for the reply, and have a good one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Hallucination creating unusual issues </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 08:21:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm just keeping this one short and sweet. I've been hallucinating this girl I like for a while now (she is not a real person) and I really like her company. I know it probably isn't common for someone to like what they're hallucinating but I don't care. I just really wish this person was a real, physical person. Oh and yes, I am generally pretty lonely. And this person really keeps me company well, but the mere silhouette of a person I see and can sometimes feel just isn't enough. I just wish I knew some way to really interact, see them, in whole, for real, but thinking about this is just kind of getting me a little.. crazy? I don't know, but I just wanna know if anybody else has felt this way and how I could maybe fulfill my desire. Thanks if you read, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Serve-index question </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 09:14:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey, newbie here. Got myself a bit of a test server running here and I'm using serve-index to serve my file tree. Can I make the file sizes human-readable? Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 02:06:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn man I wanna be him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 02:04:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeo who are they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 19:38:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And as for my name being -behc, it was a joke in tehcs name laf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I lplqya nie ncraft </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 19:36:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 09:55:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, *Im* a virgin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 09:29:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This man gets it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 09:09:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How about the people who go, "Your point is irrelevant because of <something a president did>. You also missed the placement of a period on column X of your post, and I also think that people with that type of username are ridiculous. <Insert sassy conclusion here>"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 09:02:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awesome job on coming out, OP! So proud of you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is rooting a Samsung Galaxy J3 Prime possible? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 08:01:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been trying stuff for a few days now with no luck and believe I almost bricked my phone, and I was just wondering if anybody had some suggestions on rooting this device. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Steelseries Rival 110 completely broke </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 06:57:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I've had my Rival 110 for about a year now, and I went and plugged into my laptop (Yes, I know. I'm poor.) and after working for a few minutes, it completely died. No LED, no sensor, and probably no power. Anybody got a solution? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 11:10:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ryou Seibai! Gakuen Bishoujo Seisai Hiroku </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Thoughts and physical sensations </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-04 17:47:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay so I've been living with this "condition" as I've called it for most of my like. Essentially, I can link conscious and subconscious thought to physical feeling. It can be really fun to mess with sometimes, but today it's just awful and the most power I've felt it. Basically, I had a nightmare and was shot in the head. I woke up 10 minutes ago and I can feel the bullet and the hole and it hurts. What is this "condition", does everyone have it, and is it normal/healthy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 23:07:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That one actually got me, almost choked on my damn cheeto lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 01:51:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Yeah dont mind me dad, just uh... F\*cking the goat?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
