<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject38</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 15:21:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bien, trabajando. ¿Tú qué tal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 22:43:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Soy una persona que vive en la Islas Canarias, Tenerife para ser más exacto. Siento joderte un poco la ilusión pero aquí no vengas buscando trabajo de hostelería, porque no lo hay.

Los hoteles están todos cerrados, excepto por unos pocos los cuales deben estar con ERTEs porque no hay ocupación.
Mi suegra trabajaba en un hotel y lleva en el paro desde marzo y no hay noticias de cuando va a volver a abrir el hotel.

Mi pareja estaba estudiando turismo y lo dejó porque viendo el panorama no vale la pena seguir.
Todos mis conocidos que trabajan del turismo están en el paro y sin saber nada.

Si no fuese por el COVID tu idea sería genial. Con la situación actual las islas tardarán en volver a tener el mismo turismo de antes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 10:03:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The ending of the tradition to kiss cheeks or lips to everyone you meet.

In Europe there's a lot of countries with that kind of tradition. In my country, if you are a woman, you have to kiss both cheeks to every person you meet.

I understand kissing close friends and family but why do I have to kiss someone who I just met? Or a weird neighbour?  Or that friend of a friend who stares at you like a creep?

Fuck that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 21:56:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh wow, I follow you on youtube! Before seing your username I was ready to fight you for stealing  and claiming to be your work hahahahahaha
Nice work as always!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 22:43:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm from Spain and my mother was almost put into the ICU on March. Was constantly without breath, very high fever, couldn't move, she was with an oxygen mask and the doctors didn't know if she would survive.

Luckily she did and after 1 month she went home without any important long term condition. It was a scary time because we lost our father 2 months  prior Covid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 21:40:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Olé. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 21:49:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Visca el Barça!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 16:03:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apparently I won him over by saying angrily  "don't be such a brat"

We were playing Overwatch and until that moment no girl had ever said anything like that to him. I was the first one to be clear and put a stop to his childish behaviour after a bad game.

We are still together after 2 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 15:06:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm from Barcelona and I've never been to La Sagrada Familia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 22:23:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok I'm crying. Thank you for showing me this comment, I wasn't prepared for that image. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 21:53:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This dog named Kevin with the most ugly and funny haircut ever.

Here the post:
https://reddit.app.link/CujG08KUk8

And more photos of him:
https://imgur.com/a/YUBplNH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 01:28:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My boyfriend's grandma picking a snack at 2 am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 13:06:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks god this video is not about the accident I'm talking about.

The hole where Julen fell was about 25 cm diameter and over 70 meters deep, it was impossible to have any person lifted down without danger.

This is the hole I'm talking about.

[Julen's hole](https://images.app.goo.gl/gAVS6PYJFBHeTjJ56) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 23:59:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The body was found between two layers of dirt. The first one probably was because the well was abandoned and with the humidity the dirt fell over time.

The second layer was done during the kid's fall, the experts say a landslide was created while the kid was falling.

I'm a Spaniard and this accident was all over the news for weeks, it really was sad to watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 11:54:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's cute. I do the same with my bf and I even pet his hair and sing a song softly when he has nightmares. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 02:20:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> obviously duh

I had a massive crush on him when I was a young teen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-04 19:36:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's me every month. Last month I cried because there wasn't any chocolate at home due to quarantine. The other month I cried because I saw my puppy do something really cute. Another month I cried because I remembered the ending of "How to train your dragon 3". PMSing really sucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 20:02:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Esa hembra es mala" by Gloria Trevi. I rewatched the telenovela "Teresa" during this quarantine and the intro song is sooo good. I feel like the bitchest bitch on earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 21:23:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi! I'm trying to enter the queue and it seems it's gonna be a while XD

how many minutes are left?? thanks!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 23:00:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry for that last internet crash but my shop is now closed. Thanks for coming!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 22:37:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my dms are not working sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 22:13:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guys I don't know why but my responses are failing to send, the code is 9DKY4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 19:52:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> BTW this is my second switch so I don't have the island looking good. Don't judge me please! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Nooks] 575 bells for turnip, DM for code! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 19:35:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 04:18:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The sister from this post

https://www.reddit.com/r/funny/comments/7p3ar0/late_post_but_i_think_we_found_out_who_my_parents/?utm_medium=android_app&utm_source=share </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-11 17:12:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cats. No need to say anything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-15 12:04:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love Bill,  I was so happy when he gave me his photo!
Let's see if I have luck, I'm in quarantine and I can't go to buy the game lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 13:03:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Waiting to die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 17:54:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For the things I read here it seems like your education program is not the best with languages, we start learning English when we are 5 years olds and you have the opportunity to learn a third language when you are 12 or so. You said Spanish is the "unofficial 2nd language" that's more reason to learn it. The thing is, I'm from Spain, I've never been in another country and the people I'm talking about don't know how to say a simple "Hola, ¿cómo estás?"
That's one thing I'm too European to understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 17:29:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How you only speak one language. In most Europe you learn a second and even a third language in school.
I'm from a country where we have a lot of tourists and it's my pet peeve when a tourist comes expecting to be attended in English without trying to even speak a greeting in our language.  Most of the times they are american, the typical white suburban family with a Karen demanding to see our manager. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> She knows how to get the food, sit and be cute. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-02 01:43:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-31 18:03:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA it's sad but probably they have another group chat without you... Hope you find better friends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> She is tired of all the photos I take of her. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-02 20:37:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-24 17:12:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I played the demo a few months back and it's amazing! I have it in my wishlist since then. Great job guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-23 15:23:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The story of how steelix became my favourite Pokemon is a weird one.
 I never paid attention to it or to Onix but one day out of the blue I dreamed that the team rocket was chasing me.
They wanted my Pokemon and I was running from them. Luckily  I had a shiny steelix with me that saved me from them, it made a tunnel and we escaped.
After that dream I always have a shiny steelix in my team and I really love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 00:20:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just watch a video about "castellers". Its a cultural tradition from Catalonia, they do human towers like that but without this ending. It's incredible the heigth they can reach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-17 13:50:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just played the demo and it's beautiful, all that color amazes me. I really like this type of platformer games and I can't wait to play the full version. Do you know how many hours of game can we expect?

Great job!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-16 01:12:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Adiós Chimuelo....Ave María... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-19 13:43:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Only one research for pokestops. In my town there's only 7 so GG. I've done them all and no shiny. The next event like this one I'm staying home. It's not worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-17 18:05:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really tried to read Norwegian Wood but it was impossible after one hundred pages.  Really slow and boring,  I didn't even know what the story was about so it didn't hook me up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-06 01:27:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> added! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-02 13:07:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can I add you? Your safari is perfect for shiny hunting, I love them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> LF Magneton, Bronzong or Metang </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-01 14:47:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Need that metal coat to evolve my Onix, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-30 19:34:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can I add you? I'm looking for metang and bronzong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-28 01:09:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Added you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-28 01:08:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Added </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-28 01:08:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Added! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-27 15:41:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks, added back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-27 14:12:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Added you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> LF Onix but gonna add anyone </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-27 13:49:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trying to start a new shiny dex and shiny Onix is my favourite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-27 03:27:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! That's cool  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-27 02:55:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Done! Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-27 02:24:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi! I added you, can you help me know what my pokemons are? Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:52:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, it works anytime! Try it, it's really useful :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2016-09-22 02:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guys, with the new patch they added an option for healers to comunicate their possition. As a healer (mercy, lucio, ana, zen) just press the "need healing" looking at the member of your team, the person will be alerted by voice and an icon above the healer's head will appear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
