<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject9</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-19 05:48:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But what's that got to do with being gay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-18 21:16:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's fucking vile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-18 18:54:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm just trying to understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-18 17:11:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is the significance of a lack of personal hygiene? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-18 16:35:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every damn thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-18 16:33:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me, I can't take advantage of bulk buying because I live in a small flat. I'm sure that's a factor for a lot of people too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-18 10:10:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's the significance of black underwear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-17 13:32:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is your sync mode set to video? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-17 13:31:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like faulty LEDs. I'd contact Hue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-17 09:47:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bet they pronounce half of these wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-17 09:43:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 6) Inherit a 6 figure sum from a relative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 19:26:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spent more on home improvement. Less on eating out and meal deals. More on takeaways. It's largely been a wash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 19:25:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry for your loss.

There have been lots of great helpful comments here but I just wanted to add a point. You say you'd like to stay near your social circle, but if they're largely your age and planning to go to university too, then you may find that you end up scattered in different places in the country during and after university anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 16:40:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dang. You give psychology advice alongside financial and legal advice? What can't you do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 10:57:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've not done it but I think you could use iron on hemming tape too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 19:46:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! This gives me reassurance that I'll be able to fit it on my 50" as I'm able to get close to the edges like this too on mine. You've got no problem with the edges of the zones being in the wrong place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 16:39:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Normal stairs photographed at a jaunty angle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 16:34:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alternatively, the wristband would be yet another device that people need to charge. If it could be integrated into a smart watch, it would at least be a multi function device. If someone is prepared to buy a device just for that one thing, why not get something that does other things too and looks better at the same time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 16:32:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's the hearing people that need to fix their attitude then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 11:53:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't put money under free parking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 23:50:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How long do you spend looking at each application and how can one make theirs stand out so you actually read it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 23:43:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because they're the underclass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 19:46:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well when it's mixed with milk, it's not 80% sugar. But shit tasty. That's how we can drink it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 12:12:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I count in twos but I like to use the odd numbers. Somehow I can keep my place more easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 11:57:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would set a routine so it goes off at night after I'm asleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 22:45:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you using the free router? Replace it with a decent one and see what happens. I've been using my own for years and I pretty much never have problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 19:31:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not a good idea. You're doing fine with what you've got. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 09:35:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never pay interest for the sake of building up a credit history. There are plenty of ways to do it without paying interest. A credit card paid off in full every month by direct debit, a 0% loan, phone contacts, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 00:44:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now I'm wondering which charity it is... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 11:43:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dressing gown or long coat with nothing underneath then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 09:37:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is grim as fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 09:04:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been using them a few years now and never had any crack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 22:59:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or Milton's sterilising fluid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 22:42:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use glass containers and I microwave from frozen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 22:38:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/MealPrepSunday is a great resource.

I often go for chicken, rice, and broccoli. Either peri peri or in soy sauce and honey. Yesterday I made sausages as part of a meal so I bunged the rest of the packet in the oven at the same time and I can put that in a box with frozen mash for lunch at work this week.

Either making a week's worth of meals at once or making extra portions when cooking dinner sorts your lunch for a week! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 21:51:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I found them cringe. But it's still entertaining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 11:14:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I couldn't even read the whole thing. Too long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 01:55:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Flowers on a first date is too much imo.

Good luck out there and have fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 15:55:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use it ironically sometimes. I don't even know where I got it from. I'm from London. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 15:47:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The fuck kind of place is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 15:30:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you have a £30k deposit, you need to have a £60k salary to afford a £270k mortgage. Lenders won't take the lodging income into account for affordability. You need to be able to afford it on your own.

Also, where are you even finding a 3 bed for £300k? Turning a living room into a bedroom means you're further limited to properties with a separate kitchen which is another challenge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 12:06:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cook big meals and use the leftovers for lunch or dinner for a few days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 19:12:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not American and not interested enough in American politics to have seen a video with his name in it. I have no idea how it's pronounced. I read it as butty-geeg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 15:14:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/ExNoContact </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 14:03:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/TIHI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 22:46:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the whole "normal speed SLO MO... normal speed SLO MO" thing is a little overdone here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 22:39:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy 30th! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 20:01:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vanilla is a great flavour, but not everyone is into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 18:42:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That shit's in your bum and it's going nowhere! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 17:54:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tax is automatically deducted from pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 14:55:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It'll be there when you finish. Chill. Keep learning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 06:38:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maintenance and product handling could be done by local teams who use smaller vehicles and meet the truck wherever it goes. The service could be cheaper for the companies who can receive and unload the products by themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 06:26:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in a small studio flat so I've nowhere to put it. Admittedly, some of it I don't need to keep but other things I'd like to keep long term but it's not bothering him so there's no reason to move it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 20:53:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 20:10:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The solicitor will see IDs from us. Doesn't need us to do anything else so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 20:06:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends where you live. Some places, employers don't need a reason to fire you. Post on one of the legal advice subs for your location. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 19:02:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just asked and he said to avoid inheritance tax. No other complicated reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 18:52:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Married after 1.5 years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 18:48:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, it can't hurt with the eventual sale of the flat. The road is not controlled parking and you can get a space on the road 99% of the time but who knows for the future?

I'm not complaining if he wants to give us something. :) As long as it has no negative impact for any reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 18:25:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My sister and I do have some belongings in his loft but it's nowhere near full and he's not asked us to move it. Our stuff combined would be nowhere near to filling up a garage - maybe less than a quarter of it. I could probably get all my stuff on one or two shelving racks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 18:21:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> !thanks we already have homes so no stamp duty affected.

I think he'd rather buy the garage for us than give us cash because he can use it in the meantime!

I'm financially stable enough that I don't need cash right now so I'm happy to have it in a garage for now, with it just being a bonus at some point in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 18:04:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ha. Thank the NHS for saving my dad from becoming a Walter White? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 18:01:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, possibly. He's 72 now so not super old but no spring chicken either. If it is for this reason, could that cause any problems? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 17:58:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He'll be paying cash. He's not great with finances but he's not that irresponsible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 17:57:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess that's his train of thought but I didn't think he had enough assets to have IHT payable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 17:32:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can see how you're suspicious but I genuinely can't see a nefarious reason for it from him. I think he just wants to give it as a gift to us since he got a little cash recently. He generally doesn't offer much financial help to us so I figure why not take it when it's offered? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 17:28:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> !thanks good point but forgot to mention that sister and I have already purchased our own homes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My dad wants to buy a garage in mine and my sister's names </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 17:12:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A garage behind his flat has come up for sale and he'd like to purchase it. He wants to use it, I think for storage rather than a car, but he wants to buy it in mine and my sister's names. Is there any reason why or why not?

I believe he plans to leave everything to the two of us when he dies, but I think all he really has is his flat and no other significant assets. The flat is worth around £400k now. But, of course, if needs to sell it for care expenses, etc, that may not end up happening.

I have read that garages tend to be a good investment generally as they have a good rental yield, or we could offer it to any potential buyer of the flat one day. The garage is around 30-45 minutes from where we both live so I don't expect we'd ever really need/want to use it much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 23:11:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nowhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 23:07:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah it's funny because I'd say Ashley is more of a male name than a female name in the UK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does a shampoo bar need to cure? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 22:06:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know the soap lasts longer if it's left out for a while to cure but I wasn't sure if it was the same for the shampoo bar. Just picked up a Snow Fairy bar today but happy to leave it a while if it makes it last longer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 17:51:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought it was something to do with "pray tell" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 14:40:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As you said, they're gonna find out anyway so there's no point delaying it. Let them know upfront before you come so there's no last minute confusion and embarrassment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 17:56:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Drone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 14:57:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Forky's cousin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 14:54:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well it isn't actually useless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 08:02:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/straightspouses
/r/latebloomerlesbians </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 07:49:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aromantic seems more fitting. Or even demisexual or something along those lines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 22:38:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I honestly considered applying for a job with them when I saw one come up, but I don't think I want to be crawling around on the floor. I have no problem with the pest side of it but dealing with all the floor traps would bother me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 15:08:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used the size of my TV in the title and in the body text. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 15:07:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because it's smaller and if the strip is too long, it's going to hang off the end or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can the gradient light strip be used on a 50" TV? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 11:52:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The size starts at 55" but I'm wondering if it'll still fit on a 50". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 12:03:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Women are not a singular entity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 19:25:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I prefer the hammers. 🤷🏻‍♂️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 12:14:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You could just unfollow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 10:28:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Aiden actually has an adult face. In that top picture, he looks like an adult with a tiny body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 21:53:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The game says season one ends in 4 days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 21:08:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn't that something out of Arthur? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 21:00:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't recommend a schedule if you have pets. There are plenty of anecdotes online involving vomit/shit/other animal excretions and robot vacuums. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 20:52:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't even really have anywhere to keep a normal upright hoover so I've got a robot one that tucked away under the furniture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 20:33:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup, was using around £20-25 a month on a meter before. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 20:06:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If it is to be refunded to a current account that you switched using CASS, it should come through still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 19:55:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine is about £32 a month for a studio/one bed with Thames Water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 19:39:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fwiw, advance train tickets are on sale 12 weeks before the travel date and can be a lot cheaper. Plus, even better if you can get a Railcard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 16:47:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you ask to work from home part time? Say for one day a week for a month, two days a week the month after, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 00:55:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/TIHI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 21:54:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't understand how they're ok with you replacing the wallpaper but not with a solid colour repaint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 21:51:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just paint the whole thing one solid colour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 20:30:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely. Looks way too different to a real one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 20:29:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can buy Henry spare parts, including the entire body housing. Don't let your dreams be dreams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 20:27:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rail timetabling seems ridiculously complicated from everything I've seen. I imagine it's not simple for it to just stop. Plus not cheap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 19:52:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go for a free consultation with a mortgage broker and get some letting agents in to give you some quotes. You'll be able to give the mortgage broker some hard figures of the rental income minus the letting fees.

Also, your options for let to buy mortgages can be affected by your own income. My broker said there were only a few companies that lend to people who earn under £25k, and they're usually a bit worse in terms of interest rates.

I did this same thing when I wasn't getting any offers on my house, and we were confident that it would be easy to rent out. Mine was owned outright (inheritance) so slightly different circumstances but they basically would lend on 75% value of the house.

It was an easy process generally but one delay I didn't anticipate was that the mortgage company wouldn't continue the process once they discovered the house was still technically on the market - I had already given notice to the estate agent but it was another couple of weeks until it was officially withdrawn.

Of course, now I have to be a landlord and all of the obligations that entails. I can barely keep my own life admin together let alone complying with all the landlord regulations etc. I pay for a fully managed service and I don't have to deal with any of that, which is well worth it for me as I already have a full time job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 18:28:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My favourite was when one football was randomly replaced with a banana. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 17:22:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The first person to give a number loses. They'll always negotiate you down but they'll never negotiate you up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 01:10:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does the refund come in the March payslip or some other way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 23:20:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't buy cigarettes? It's not that serious.

Don't eat that chocolate bar? It's not that serious.

Don't starve yourself? It's not that serious.



People can be addicted to many things. People belittling their addiction isn't going to help. Internet addiction is a real thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 22:46:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *quite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 19:42:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Women. Human adult women. Not females. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 11:38:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's no problem with them having your real name. They just have no more right to ask you your name than the guy you saw at the bus stop this morning has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 11:28:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that for just teaching? What about head of department/head of year/other SLT roles etc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 10:13:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> London. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 10:11:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nor am I but don't discriminate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 09:31:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just the one. But that's one more than none so I'm doing ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 08:18:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Too much food is never a problem. It just means leftovers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 08:05:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like a great day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 08:04:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am on lates this week but still woke up at 6.30. Bleh. But I gained a girlfriend over the weekend so that's cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 23:32:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's the same kind of logic as privacy arguments.
"I've got nothing to hide so why does it matter if they can see my information?"
Because they may end up using it to your detriment in the future. The more you allow them to have, the more they'll take until you wake up one day and realise your freedoms are eroded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 23:26:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On iPhone, you can even create a shortcut to it on your homepage that looks and behaves just like an app so it doesn't even matter. Android must have a similar option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 11:24:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! This is my most convenient store so it's good to get an idea of what their displays are like before going in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 17:37:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why not both? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 19:56:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn't this basically saying "I don't know how to please a woman"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 19:16:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love a yellow front door. I live in a flat so I can't do the outside of my door but I want to do the inside in yellow, just to add a little colour to my tiny hallway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 10:45:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably cheaper than playing the lottery weekly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 08:31:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A small chance is still a chance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 08:20:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God damn. Probably gonna start putting my money in premium bonds because then at least I have a chance of winning big. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 06:29:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What did you think railing meant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 15:49:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am the 75%. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 09:20:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Slammerkin by Emma Donoghue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 22:44:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I tried this but all I got was a story about a teenage prostitute from the 1760s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 20:28:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can still see it? I can't unsee it either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 15:39:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Penguins? Uh.. no, no, that's a typo. Yes, we definitely meant ravens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 06:06:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least it was a dry day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 22:51:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just realised I could never be a postie because I'd spend all day petting the cats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 21:32:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every vehicle has limited space. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 20:52:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not bothered by it. I don't like receiving presents for occasions like this either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 20:51:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm deaf and have never heard it, but I can feel it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 20:50:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm deaf. I can hear things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 20:24:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I suppose they like to see that you're the kind of person who can keep a job. Although I worry that it looks worse to have had a job for one month than to not have one at all, especially in these times when so many people are redundant anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 20:21:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. This is very validating. I don't think I'm in a position to leave with nothing else lined up though. I'll have to start playing the lottery. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 20:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The major reasons I don't like it are integral to the role so I don't think there's anything that can be done in regards to that. Good point about the probation in general though.

And yeah, previous job roles have been 2 or 3 years at the same company so shouldn't be too much of an issue.

I think my notice period is still a month during probation, which is quite standard I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 20:18:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I have too many bills to pay to just quit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 20:17:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my experience, it's easier to be relaxed in an interview because it's "this would be nice to get but ultimately I have a job already", so no desperation coming across. I will have to apply for some roles and see what happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 17:15:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you know what sound is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 17:05:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's tatted the fuck up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I've been at my job for one month and I'm finding the hours very difficult. Is it weird to find a new job now? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 17:35:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I worry it'll look bad for future employers. I took this job as it was the first one offered and I was facing redundancy in my old role, but it's absolutely killing me.

Also, I worry about changing jobs during a pandemic and all the risks associated with that. My new/current employer should be quite stable so I don't know if it's stupid to take another job and open myself up to possible instability.

I'm worried about the effect it's having on my mental health. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 21:29:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Noice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 19:25:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is there a way to see how many games you've played? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 19:21:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do you effectively stall it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 19:17:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Should be completion. My friends had exchanged prior to the stamp duty relief but still had it applied as it is paid on completion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 19:14:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a big fan of Spendee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 18:03:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't used a "free" router in years and I basically never have a problem. Including one year with Vodafone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 11:25:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Clarks Desert Mali in beeswax. I'd love a pair but they don't do them in the UK. 😭 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 23:40:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shitty idea then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 23:35:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Massive shoutout to Open Barbers in London! They take payment on a sliding scale of what you can afford and appointments are by type of cut, not gender. Love that place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 23:13:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It sounds like you wouldn't be considered for implant surgery at the level you are now - I'm not even really a candidate for it and I can't hear someone's voice unless they're literally centimetres away from my ear. You'll likely get some relatively small hearing aids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 23:07:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not saying it causes it but it exacerbates what's already there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 22:56:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lots of people have identity issues but being an identical triplet probably compounds it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 22:22:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What happens if you take the leave and then you actually catch it? Do you get paid twice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 21:18:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OP has said the breaks are paid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 16:54:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you able to call them through text relay/textphone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 07:37:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't find getting moulds uncomfortable - I actually really like it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 23:17:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But if someone's life goal is to be a stay at home mum, they've gotta do something in between leaving school and getting married. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 23:12:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You've gotta date them before you marry them.

Hey, I'm single. Can you pay for all my living expenses and I'll clean your house? I'll move in tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 23:08:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If all you want is a cleaner, there are far more efficient ways to get one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 22:56:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can hire a cleaner for far less than it takes to support an entire adult human. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 19:11:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you speak from experience? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 11:56:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice! Can't wait to download the update. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 23:43:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I definitely thought they meant a mankini. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 23:41:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The product pictures crack me up. Of course everyone keeps their toaster and their kettle on their Eames table in their living room. Where else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 21:42:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think the iPhone was a big factor in that. Apple didn't want their logos and had the clout to enforce it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 23:59:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't have mine pierced but I played with someone who had hers pierced. I felt like it was super limiting in what I could do to them, and because they were more sensitive, I couldn't play with them as long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 20:31:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But he hadn't worn it in decades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 12:26:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was just sick in my mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 10:32:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought they weren't supposed to be because the heat escapes from the window. They usually are because it's convenient. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 23:43:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's several theories and no one actually knows for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 22:58:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's your duty to produce ginger babies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 22:51:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly I'd love to do a 3 day work week if I earned enough to be able to. I work to live, not live to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 14:29:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I miss having a job with normal hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 06:34:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah, Britain. Where the seaside shops sell woolly hats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 05:56:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I miss the days when I was up this late. Now, I'm up this early. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 09:36:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In London, it's pretty common to see them early in the morning or late at night. During the day is rare but not unheard of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 19:28:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know if I'll ever win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 18:09:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doesn't sound very slo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 13:56:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never even got that far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 11:04:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a dickhead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 10:48:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wasn't she going to return it but they stripped it before she could? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 16:02:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly I want about 80% of the stuff in the kids section but they don't make it for adults. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 06:47:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The wonderful thing about queer is that it means whatever you want it to mean. Anyone who's not cishet can use it for themselves if they choose. Personally, I use it because I find other terms too binary or specific. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 07:11:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally no one else likes this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 06:41:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can be 2m in a straight line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 17:59:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 100% this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 16:26:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never had anyone try to rope me into a threesome with their boyfriend. Butch privilege? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 21:16:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The first episode of Umbrella Academy was slow. Basically it just tried to get all of the character introductions out of the way. It really starts from episode 2! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 08:14:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I personally love having a flat. I lived in a house before and moved to a flat. I like that I don't have to maintain the garden or the building and I like the ease of having everything on one level, e.g. I don't have to carry laundry downstairs to wash and then upstairs again to put away. I much prefer to have a flat in a better location than a house outside of London. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 23:21:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Woah. Did not know this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 20:34:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually no, but I really should. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Spotted in Soho </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 15:25:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 09:57:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My fixed monthly expenses are about half of my monthly income. Should be slightly less than half now with my new job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 07:50:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I only wear them if I go out or if I'm watching TV. The world is noisy and I like my quiet escape in my flat. :) I've been wearing them for 28 years so I'm plenty used to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 17:10:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From 2am to 4pm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 15:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my character isn't ugly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 06:46:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My woman character is butch as hell so that's probably why I've never encountered this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 20:35:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ^[psst](https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-51722301) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 21:55:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just started a job as support staff in a school. I've been working for the past week and it's fine because there's very few people in but I am a little bit anxious about the kids coming back. It was either take this job or be unemployed though! But I shouldn't need to be near the kids too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 18:02:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 08:55:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God, I'm so glad to be gay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 07:17:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't given an employer a P45 in years because it only comes through after I've already started. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 06:57:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You 100% need to change this. My bills went down noticeably when I changed the timer on mine. I once had a shower 23.5 hours after it comes on and it was absolutely fine so they're well insulated enough to not to need to be on all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 06:40:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not only talking about trains being late and trains being crowded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 22:52:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always think people who move to other areas just to have cheaper property must not have family and friends around them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 22:47:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People always bang on about these trains that are half an hour to London, but that's way too simplistic. There's so many other parts of the journey to consider! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-22 13:45:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could you put one of those mini fences? Like a foot tall? Creates a border but doesn't ruin the view. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-22 11:59:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know brothers called Jonathan and Nathan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 22:00:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's GAYE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 21:52:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Boom, still got it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 08:12:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've tried on stuff with a wider leg and I want to like it but I don't think it suits my body type. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 07:44:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Had you washed the sweater before? Often it goes away after washing it, or at least significantly decreasing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 07:23:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly it makes me worry that I'm gonna end up looking like one of those dudes who can't give up his bell bottoms and still wears them today, like every day since the 70s. Am I gonna be stuck in this era of fashion forever? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 23:28:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel the same way about Five's actor as I do about Tatiana Maslany in Orphan Black. You so believe that he's an old man in a young body, just like you so believe that all the clones are different people. It's easy to forget that they're not actually. Yes, other actors are great but there's something that sets them apart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 13:14:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you think doctors have the time to be dealing with signing off letters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 11:49:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doesn't work for all styles of glasses. I no longer wear glasses but I have sunglasses. Some pairs let me do this but some don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 11:02:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not only can you not get a mortgage on it because it's a vehicle, but also because it's a depreciating asset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 10:06:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Average it over a year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 06:58:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eyyy, 47% buddy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 06:56:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Surely you know how much money comes into your bank account every month? That's the figure you need to put in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 06:54:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plus people have income that is not from a single PAYE job. I have income from a few sources so I put my average monthly total net. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 06:46:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I imagine the majority of that 40% are single parents who have childcare obligations and are unable to work or work only part time.
The statistic must only count income from earning and not benefits because £750 a month isn't getting anyone anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 06:21:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm 30. Got my licence at 19. Lived in London so went 8 years without driving. Had to buy a car when I lived somewhere with awful public transport and had a job that finished late. Now I live in London again and I've absolutely not missed it.

Do you determine the worth of someone by their car? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 20:50:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 0.

I don't need one. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 20:44:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you think C2W is giving away free bikes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 16:02:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Öga for öga isn't exactly high level Swedish. I don't know any Swedish but I still worked it out based on general knowledge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 15:10:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One other thing to consider is what redundancy pay you'd get at your current job. If you've been there less than 2 years, you're not entitled to anything and if you've not been there much more than 2 years, it's hardly worth anything. Then your clock will be back to zero on the new job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 15:02:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait what </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 08:40:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely, I don't have anything against the individuals, but rather the societal ignorance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 16:27:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But if you have an accident, even just the most minor of accidents, that's gonna put you in contact with other people, unless you bring a notepad and communicate by writing and holding it up to the window. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 06:37:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's because it's a screenshot of an interactive map. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 23:28:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or when people say "oh my brother's cat is deaf!"

Cool. Can it sign? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 23:27:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apparently I'm feeling wordy tonight. Maybe it's because I'm procrastinating.

Furthermore on the idea of community:

Does someone have to actively identify as being part of a community to come under the community's umbrella term? No, I don't think so.

Mary paints on the weekends, but she is self taught and doesn't have any friends who are painters. She never exhibits her work but just does it for pleasure and hangs the pictures in her house. She's still an artist.

Abdul was born hearing but gradually lost his hearing and now has moderate hearing loss. He wears hearing aids and doesn't sign. All of his colleagues and friends from his mainstream school are hearing. He's still deaf.

Jess dates women but she doesn't listen to Girl In Red or go to gay bars. All of her friends are straight. She doesn't frequent /r/actuallesbians and she doesn't know the memes about being useless. She's still queer.

This has gone on a bit of a tangent from my original rant! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 23:12:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yes, there is a ton of bi-erasure, especially for men. Just as HoH is unseen and misunderstood, so is bisexuality.

I think words to identify the communities as a whole like queer and deaf are very useful, with sub labels to clarify further to anyone who wants to elucidate when explaining, but I think HoH for example is seen as separate to the deaf community when it shouldn't be.

For example, someone may have a colleague who wears hearing aids. Someone asks them if their colleague is deaf.
"He has hearing aids because he's hard of hearing but he's not *really* deaf."

A similar scenario, someone's friend might be bisexual.
"He's married to a woman. He's not *really* bisexual."

It's not really a direct parallel here but these sub labels aren't seen as being valid members of the main umbrella term.

Another slant on this topic:

If someone says they're an artist, that doesn't come with a preconception. Maybe people will tend towards more of an assumption that they're a painter or illustrator, but they will never explicitly assume them to be a certain type of artist.

A sculptor is an artist. A painter is an artist. A photographer is an artist. People (generally) accept that they're all artists. Is it because these labels are not self identified that they're accepted as all belonging to the same group? Is it because they have a tangible output? Is it because art is accepted in society?

If someone says they're deaf, that comes with a whole bunch of preconceptions that are largely inaccurate and based on past representation that they've seen of one type of deaf person.

I don't need to have met a sculptor to know that they're an artist and what they do. People don't need to have met a HoH person to know that they're deaf and that they can hear you with hearing aids and speak "normally" and enjoy music etc.

We need a wide range of people openly defining themselves as deaf if we want people to not keep coming up with the same misconceptions and questions time and time again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 21:43:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unless you build the house yourself, you're always coming across someone else's shortcuts. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 21:34:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've had a few interesting conversations about the parallels between queerness and deafness in the past too and I'll add a little point about that here too.

I see "queer" and "deaf" as being labels that are umbrella terms which are open to interpretation by the individual. People may have a perception about what being queer or being deaf means to you, but it's only for you to define for your individual circumstances.

Deaf can mean a hearing aid wearer who communicates through spoken English, or it can mean a person who uses sign language and no hearing devices, or it can mean a person with a cochlear implant who both signs and speaks, etc. etc.

As for queer, that could mean anything from a man who likes men, a nonbinary person who is asexual, a woman who is attracted to people regardless of gender, etc. etc. All of these people might choose to identify as queer.

Queer has become more popular as a term for people with all different types of experience. Why shouldn't deaf be the same thing?

At the same time, I'm not saying someone shouldn't use a different term like gay or bisexual or hard of hearing to describe themselves if that's what they feel works best for them.

Of course, in another ten years, we may find that all of these terms have become outdated and we'll be on the next set of labels. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 21:17:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah people are obviously free to choose the words that they feel fit them best, but if they've never seen anyone like them using the terms, they'll feel like they don't apply to them. Which is where you can get the division. Communities are constantly changing and evolving, along with the language used within them.

Words and labels are a good shorthand to succinctly represent part of your identity, and I think they become less important as those aspects are more accepted and recognised in the wider society.

As long as people don't judge others experiences by the shorthand they use, we can move on to greater acceptance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 21:05:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bound is fantastic. It uses hot lesbians to draw you in but you get really hooked by the actual story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 18:01:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Instead of having to charge the NES controllers (and any Joy Cons) on the Switch itself, you can buy a dock that plugs in to a USB port to charge them. ](https://www.argos.co.uk/product/6836577) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 17:52:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was it you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 17:36:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can buy Joy Con charging stands at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 17:32:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've done that and still had the paint come off the wall. The Command Strip stuck just fine to the surface, but the surface did not stick fine to the wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 17:29:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, are you?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 17:12:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have a spreadsheet with the people you've asked out or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 16:49:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yikes. Yeah, definitely worth it in that case. Mine are basically just an inconvenience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 16:19:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well they care enough to ask the questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 16:18:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I'm sure it's fine for most people! I don't want to take the pill though because I don't like having to take something every day. Other methods like an IUD or an implant squick me out in other ways too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 16:15:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sometimes I fantasize about slamming my hearing aids down on the counter and starting to sign to them instead so that they get the message. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 16:14:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you think we've changed the name of a country because a frozen food shop is named the same thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 16:13:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dream of a world where this is not necessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 16:11:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm happy living with being deaf. I just wish that people were more deaf aware or at least able to go and do some research before asking questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 15:53:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The better question in that instance would be "what do you use to communicate (with hearing people)?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 15:45:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is why I use the term deaf. I don't like terms like HoH etc. because I find it to just be divisive. We are all deaf, no matter our level of deafness or communication preferences. Hearing people or people outside of the community see the word deaf and assume profound deafness and sign language etc. The more people who encounter people using the word deaf to describe themselves, the more they'll see representation of a variety of deaf people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 15:32:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I always get scared of the side effects. I guess I'll just put up with them until they stop. 🤷🏻‍♂️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 14:11:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg interpreters need to have a world of patience. I see people asking interpreters the same questions and I wonder how they keep from sighing!

"Oh I've always wanted to learn sign language!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 14:07:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Auditory processing disorder was my thought. There is also some research into hidden hearing loss happening right now, where people are testing ok on hearing tests but struggling in some environments. The research is very early days and I don't know if they've found any links between auditory processing disorder and this hidden hearing loss that they're researching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 14:00:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love how pretty much every comment is to use sign language.

I've met so many people who have learned to sign as an adult who all wished their parents brought them up with sign language. It's so much harder to learn it as an adult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 13:48:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just to add to the discussion - many alarm clocks designed for deaf/HoH people have alarms with adjustable pitch and volume in addition to the flashing and vibration. You can typically choose to use only one or any combination of 2 or 3 alarm types at once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 13:46:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I stay in hostels when I travel. I will book whatever's cheap even if it's like a 24 person dorm because the noise doesn't bother me. :) I'm only bothered if people turn lights on, which is inconsiderate to do at night so that's a rare event. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 13:44:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the idea of the deaf grab too, but the Weddle grab was one of the suggestions that Weddle himself made so that's cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tired of answering questions because no one has ever met a deaf person before </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 13:40:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Either online dating or just meeting people wherever. Like, I get that people are curious about stuff that they aren't familiar with and I'd rather they ask questions instead of live with misconceptions, but I'm just getting tired of the conversation taking a whole different direction just because I can hear less than them.

Plenty of times I've met people with various conditions or disabilities and I prefer to just react with "oh ok cool". I can Google that shit if I'm not familiar with it. If it comes up again in a relevant circumstance, I might ask how it affects them in that instance.

Do I like talking about the deaf community and the linguistics of BSL? Sure. But answering questions like "can you hear anything?" or "do you lipread?" etc are just... The same... Over and over...

Just my Sunday rant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 12:13:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/WordAvalanches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 12:04:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's got some bits attached to the sides of the house so it's a linked semi detached? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 11:51:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's also not recommended to daisy chain extension cables, i.e. plugging in an extension cable to an extension cable. Just buy the UK cables and plug those in directly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 11:37:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine are either on my face, hanging on my shirt, or in their case in my bag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 10:12:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My new String shelving for my bathroom arrived on Friday. My Sunday DIY project is to put that up. I'm so excited to have it up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 10:07:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People always talk about sunglasses being easy to lose but I've never lost a pair. I think this comes down to the individual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 09:54:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Two is great for having one always charged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 09:21:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did this in GTA Online. No timer for a heist prep so I stayed in the facility and got up to do a couple of things before doing it. I came back and there was a timer on it 🙄 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 08:56:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They can be filtered out on Rightmove too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 08:50:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You sound like you've got your head screwed on tight. If you never spend more on your credit card than you have in your current account, then it's a good idea to get one. I was looking at my credit report the other day and it's a positive that one of my credit cards is 8 years old, so it's good to get started as soon as you can! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 08:42:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If I was living at home on £33k, I could contribute 15% to my pension and still save like £1000 a month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 08:34:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What good is a paid off mortgage if you don't manage to find a job in the next 8 months? What happens in 8 months time when you've got no job and no jobseekers allowance? You still have your other bills and living expenses to pay. Have you got a way to pay for those? If you end up with no money, are you gonna sell your house? Go into debt?

You have 15 years of expenses if you don't pay off the mortgage. Isn't it worth it to keep hold of that until you have a job and your circumstances are more steady?

As a compromise, could you just pay off your 10% overpayment amount for now and keep some cash until you've got a new job? Especially in these uncertain times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 08:19:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should have seen the look on the American's face when I asked him if I should bring a jumper before going out. Such confusion. My brain shorted out and it took me a minute to work out why he couldn't understand what I said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 20:05:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The band is called Destiny's Child though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 19:55:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As far as we know, he's slept with multiple genders but has only had relationships with men. Possibly could be bisexual and homoromantic but does it really matter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 19:25:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The opposite happens a lot when British characters in American shows use American words. If they're a character that lives in the country full time, I just take it as them adjusting their speech to be more easily understood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 18:47:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I only know one spoken language fluently and I could tell what it meant. Along with his eye being stabbed, it was pretty obvious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 16:51:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The spelling mistakes are impressive, especially when they used two there/theirs but neither of them were the right they're. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 07:38:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oops, missed the LISA bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 23:23:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does your savings account pay more than 3.7%? If not, you're losing money every time you put money in your savings account. Clear your debt and then start saving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 22:49:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which one applies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 08:52:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The problem is that a guarantor has no benefits from being one but carries a massive risk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 08:39:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/latebloomerlesbians might be of interest to you. Check out the master doc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 07:40:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Glaswegian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 21:55:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I spent 3 hours on the application for the job I just got. First you've gotta write the statement, then you've got to fill in all of your information in the blasted form. Long af. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 10:21:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can I uh, get one of these devoted fans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 20:32:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Adjustable standing desk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 17:27:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reply to them with increasingly awkward images. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 15:16:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Buzz Lightyear was judging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 07:45:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/PointlesslyGendered </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 07:24:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sure everyone will believe your 3 bed terrace has a chandelier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 23:17:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I tape the shirt up, I have to put it over my head. I'm used to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 21:15:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Adding a button and hole is above my skill level and too labour intensive for the amount of shirts I own. The only thing I ever sew is holes in socks. Plus, I've had some shirts with this built in and it isn't quite as even as the fashion tape method.

Velcro seems like it might be too thick and thus obvious and visible from the side, so I'm not sure about it.

I'm quite happy to have a permanent solution so if hemming tape is going to be strong enough to stay put even with the lateral forces, then I'll use it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 19:39:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I wear button up shirts a lot, but they gap at the chest. I use fashion tape between the buttons to keep it together and it works great, but it comes off in the wash. This gets tedious having to do it every morning so I want to do a permanent solution to all of my shirts so I can just put them on and go. I'm not great at sewing so I was wondering if iron on hemming tape would do the trick? Does hemming tape stick well enough for this? I don't really have any shirts that I would sacrifice to an experiment so I'm hesitant to try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 22:06:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How the fuck does that help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 15:11:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cex trade in value is usually pretty good compared to selling on eBay once you take the fees into account. Only worth it if there's something they sell that you were interested in anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 10:07:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I'm weird and hang them inside too. They dry quickly so it's not a problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 19:25:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A short sleeved button up shirt seems like an easy option for something that can be undone but is not quite getting naked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 12:41:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Someone's really into emulation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 00:23:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm personally less concerned about predators and more concerned about giant moving metal boxes piloted by idiots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 00:04:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've heard that estate agents will pass on project houses straight to investors before it goes on the market because it's a reliable sale to people who aren't fazed by renovation projects. Maybe it's worth contacting some local agents and seeing what their process is for this kind of thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 21:28:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/legaladvice/comments/34m92h/update_ma_postit_notes_left_in_apartment/?utm_source=share&utm_medium=ios_app&utm_name=iossmf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 21:24:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is your carbon monoxide detector working? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 20:17:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love the idea of gays living in a church, given the church's history with gays. I've always said I'd kinda wanna live in one so I can have outrageous gay sex in it just because. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 20:14:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really need to learn how the Welsh alphabet works. I feel like such an ignorant English person when I see Welsh things and have no idea how to pronounce them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 19:19:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interesting.
But doesn't that end up being the same thing in the end? If it's still a 10% chance of you being in the area that's raining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 18:40:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lush do the corn ones in their online deliveries and I heard they were technically edible so I tried one but it just tasted like soap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 16:48:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you recently opened or closed any accounts or changed your address? Anything like that can cause a fluctuation but it doesn't actually matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 09:29:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It'll probably use less space to pack them all in one box with bubble wrap anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 23:33:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got a sample pack from Who Gives A Crap with their kitchen roll and I'm quite impressed. It's taking forever to get through it, although I'm only an occasional user as I use microfibre clothes for most things. I mainly use the paper for gross things like picking up cat vom. I'm not sure if I'll buy it again though as it comes in 6 packs and I don't have the space to store that much, especially with how long it lasts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 20:24:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How are you making sure no one is able to steal your mum? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 20:24:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My guess is to mimic the green that copper statues turn when oxidised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 19:08:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Only finger bum holes with prior consent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 18:05:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sometimes you don't have a specific goal in mind yet, but it's helpful to be halfway there when you realise what your goal is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 16:42:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pre or post Coronavirus? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 15:46:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 15:43:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At that price, I'd be selling them all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 15:38:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you have a network port in your apartment? Can you plug in your own router? It could be argued that you're paying for an internet connection and not a WiFi connection, so you would need your own hardware. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 15:33:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If I match with someone online and they type like that, I generally don't take it further as it's my first impression of them and it can be hard to really build a rapport. However, if I've met someone IRL and know them through our existing interactions, I find it easier to put up with as I am familiar with their good qualities already. Some people just aren't good at reading and writing and it doesn't mean they're lesser, just different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 15:30:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Typing like in the OP is typically done by first language speakers, as you learn a language very differently if you're learning it as an additional language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 15:27:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why are there multiples of these? I remember when it first appeared at the school near my house. I've now lived in 4 different places and the bin complete with poster is still there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 12:37:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bisexuality is real. Don't assume he's gay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 11:27:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I started reading this and I couldn't put it down. I was laughing out loud at points and then I had to go somewhere so I took it with me on the tube and was basically giggling all the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 22:25:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The general public are disgusting animals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 21:57:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It can be plugged into any power source, including a portable power bank. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 08:48:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would not have left without the cat in the first place! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 08:42:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can walk around Mill End. Therefore, it is a park. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 08:41:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They didn't have tools at home that would have got it off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 23:39:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Assigned female at birth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 15:17:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even more extreme, subtract your monthly/yearly fixed expenses from your take home pay and divide by hours worked. That'll give you a true figure of your disposable income. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 15:09:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Buy nice or buy twice, if you like a rhyme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 15:08:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you considered the iPhone SE? Latest specs in an old body so it's fast and it will be supported for years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 23:27:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have to in my kitchen because it is 2m x 2m. Not much choice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 21:58:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Prime candidates for mismatched shoes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 20:57:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bruh. Most people don't start off with a family home as a single young professional.
If you live in London, your parents won't need a bedroom to stay over in. What if you meet someone and you want to live together but they can't/won't live where you bought your house? In the time between then and now, would you rather be living in a house that's too big for your needs and commuting a long way and paying a lot of money for it, or have a more modest place with a commute the third of the time?
Places like MK might take only 40 minutes on the train but you could still have half an hour either end, depending on where you end up working/living. Plus, less frequency than a tube or bus. If you're already working long days, you'll never even spend any time in the house with a long commute!
You say you're devastated that you can't continue to live here, but you can. You need to decide if you want to compromise on space or time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 19:21:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fun fact, it's actually moonlight that does most of the fading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 19:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can get mirrored window film. I installed mine a few weeks ago. You get privacy during the day time but if the lights are on inside, the inside is visible. Works well in conjunction with blinds. Also, they make the view outside just slightly darker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 18:49:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RIP natural light. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 18:47:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would love one that was on top of a platform. I'm too old to be scrambling up from a sofa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 18:44:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I imagine it locks normally still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 14:29:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm certainly intending to go less often. I don't trust myself to cut the long bits on top or to do a fade on the sides, but I think I'll do a one length trim on the sides in between proper cuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 13:46:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How did you pay? You could try the chargeback route if you used a credit card. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 23:31:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I had this until it ran out and I replaced it with Fairy Liquid. I actually found the Fairy Liquid a bit disappointing so I'll have to try this again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 22:42:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I suppose no one that goes to a nightclub lives with a vulnerable person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 00:53:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tabletop sub? Yeah I didn't think that meant what she meant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 22:20:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try /r/sneakerfits or even /r/streetwear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 22:33:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup, can confirm that Wilko is like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 22:26:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They usually technically can but don't like to because of the higher fees and longer processing times. At the small independent shop I worked in, my boss didn't take it for this reason but we occasionally had one or two slip through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 22:23:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought the signs were just hurling homophobic abuse at me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 09:56:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even the functional items can be beautiful if you don't just get the first one you find. I have beautiful freezer clips, a beautiful stapler, a beautiful tool box, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 09:54:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If they insist on something, ask them for something consumable like food or drinks or toiletries etc, that way you don't have to keep them around. If you don't like the item, you can always give it to someone else without the possibility of the gift giver noticing that you no longer have it.

The other option is experiences - not just going out for a meal but any other kind of special occasion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 09:31:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You probably have a different hair type. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 01:23:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would have loved to buy an ex council flat. They were frequently among the best I saw when flat hunting. I ended up in a private built 80s flat which I love but the council stuff was usually the top of my list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 19:15:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't see this as being gendered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 19:03:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have fallen in love with Quicksand. I bought it when my hair was a bit longer and it didn't really do anything useful to it but now that it's shorter, it's my go to product. I have quite fine hair but this makes it stay in position, doesn't go greasy, and gives volume, but doesn't give me the feeling that there's something in my hair. I can still run my hands through it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 18:50:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have so many things to schedule and so little motivation. I need a PA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 18:40:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I call it plateauing. Maybe you can climb the mountain faster but then you're at the same place as everyone else anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 22:11:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These were two of my first Lush perfumes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 19:36:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's Pakistani though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 10:03:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The other buyer was probably in a stronger position to proceed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 10:01:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Make an offer and schedule a second viewing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 09:39:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And if it were London, you could get the tube there. But it's not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 03:14:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can get unflavoured toothpaste, if that's any help. It's called Oranurse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 01:46:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup, I accidentally fell asleep for about 1.5 hours this afternoon. Not good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 20:51:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Nope - no route to get there.](https://i.imgur.com/u7lStpe.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 19:53:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who doesn't? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 17:26:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Comphet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 11:51:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's a very chill old man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 03:53:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So many types of bread! I call him my tiger loaf and my cinnamon roll too. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-26 22:25:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This comment manages to be homophobic, transphobic, and racist all in one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-26 21:46:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My office is not far from the station. The only days that I've reached the office without realising I still have it on are the days it's not sunny enough to wear sunglasses. I currently do a swap of mask for sunglasses! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Streeeeeeetch </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-26 19:16:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-26 17:03:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Girls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-26 16:13:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cutie pies! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 12:45:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Use it to start a discussion but don't assume that she swiped right because she likes you that way. I've swiped right on a friend on Tinder just because it's funny to see them there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 11:40:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also /r/childofhoarder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 11:31:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Next to a story which seems to be about a pedophile teacher on meth? Classy paper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 11:28:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Only if OP wants serious replies should they post there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 11:23:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh no... Not another Reddit post about a safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 02:17:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 01:24:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I prefer helicopter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 22:23:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well they didn't say *how* you have to wear your mask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 22:07:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank god it's not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 19:36:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I totally hate carpet. I've had hard floor in my last three places/bedrooms and I loved it but I bought a flat with carpet and I can't stop thinking about all the ick that's caught up in the fibres. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 19:27:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unless...

I'm happy to heist with you sometime! I'll add you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 16:58:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a knob. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 16:49:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How much time did he even save? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 16:47:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's worth talking to independent or smaller agencies too as they're more likely to personally know the landlord instead of them being a name in a spreadsheet and they'd know who would be more open to pets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 13:10:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Biggleswade is two stops closer. Take a look at the whole line but be aware that the smaller stops like Arlesey have less frequent trains and they're the first ones to be skipped when there are problems on the line, which were very frequent when I lived there (Biggleswade). You can rent a two bed house with garden for about £750-775. My commute was 1 hr 5 minutes to Highbury door to door when there were no problems. But I moved back to London because the trains were absolutely dire. I'd really recommend looking on the outskirts of London instead of Bedfordshire etc. because then you at least have alternative transport options in the rare event that the tube is fucked. If you live in Biggleswade and the train is fucked, you literally cannot get there any other way except driving or begging a lift off a stranger who's driving! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 00:02:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair point. I had considered it but I don't know how much it would be affected, or if the mic has any kind of noise cancelling etc. Maybe if I put it down to a low mic volume? I'll have to do some testing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 21:52:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was trying the menus that were accessible from the popover menu thing as I was playing the game and couldn't go into the full settings. I found one and I'll have to test it next time I'm in a party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 21:51:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can see the selection for output device and it shows at the top "select the chat audio output device to use" so maybe it'll work? I'm not in the party anymore so I can't test it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 21:45:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> With any 3.5mm mic? I suppose you've never tested it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 21:06:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm happy to get one if it'll definitely work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is there a way for the party audio to come through the TV while using a mic? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 20:56:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I find the headset hard to hear (I'm deaf) and the sound coming through the TV/my sound system is easier to understand, but then I have no mic. Is it possible to have the audio through the TV but have a mic on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 16:26:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vinyl spray paint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 20:24:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe try some grow lights before making a hole in your house? Seems a bit easier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 20:15:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who wants a toy that comes in only one size and can't stay hard forever? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 18:20:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Now I'm the lunatic in a park laughing until I'm crying. That made my day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 16:38:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe you should start paying attention to the speed limit signs instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 09:28:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I hadn't thought of putting a towel in. Do you speak from experience with this? They say not to machine wash the Kanken because of the material and the dye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 17:06:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those shoes and red chinos are both very bold items. I think it would be too much together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 17:05:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know they recommend a Kanken should never be washed in a machine but what about if it's on its own on a hand wash cycle? Mine is quite dirty and previous hand washes have improved it but I couldn't get all the dirt out. And now it had something spilt on it and it smells. I just would prefer the ease of using the machine if possible. It's a bright warm yellow colour also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 16:52:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't even have a landline plugged in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 16:14:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even if it still worked the old way, wouldn't unplugging it and plugging it back in be effective? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 19:49:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. That's a bit annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 16:08:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair enough.
Does it turn your lights off if you turn your phone off while at home? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 16:06:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, good idea. I've never really used Shortcuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 09:47:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does your dog have his own bedroom? I was expecting the Stephen King book to be Cujo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 09:45:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd forgotten what a weekend feels like. First weekend since going back to work felt like it disappeared. My last weekend was about 4 months long so I guess it makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 00:46:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I suppose. I've not really noticed it. The WiFi trigger is Android only though I guess? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 00:45:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't do anything too crazy with mine but one of my favourite practical applications was to set some routines that help me keep on track on a work morning. It's just simple things like having the lights fade up and then change colour at certain points like when it's 10 minutes until I need to leave so I know I've got to get a move on, etc.
I have the wake up routine in the bedroom and I also have the lights flash with an Alexa timer or alarm so I sometimes set those. I can't use Alexa as an alarm to wake me up but having it flash is useful.

Another practical application is having them switch off when I leave and on when I get home. A bonus for me is that I have electric radiators on smart plugs so those go off too. They're expensive to run so it's a godsend. Before I got the plugs, I accidentally left them on once and came back to an absolutely roasting flat! But that's quite a niche application.

You can set up a lot of interesting triggers with IFTTT but honestly I find a lot of them quite gimmicky. I mostly use routines and motion sensors. I find I very rarely need to use switches or manual controls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 00:37:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was there a reason you picked the WiFi option instead of the location option? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 00:02:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lush Dirty hair styling cream smells incredible! My hair is too long to really use anything effectively right now but it gives me just enough hold to keep it from being totally floppy. Getting it cut on Wednesday though, yay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 23:43:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Childfree, not childless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 22:23:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that an ashtray? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 22:18:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that a Kodak Thermos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 21:26:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The NHS rainbow should be 🌈 and not 🏳️‍🌈 but I don't think people care about the difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 20:20:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely a llama. They're bigger and have the banana shaped ears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 20:02:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spendee and Money Dashboard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 14:22:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You literally said nothing about physical games or secondhand games so I guess not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 14:19:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But poor people are probably better off in the long run buying physical games so they can trade them in to recoup some cost, and buy secondhand games cheaper than the digital store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 14:09:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, I'm saying that you have no choice to buy secondhand games which are often cheaper than the digital ones, as you've then got no choice but to pay whatever PlayStation are charging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 10:32:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No it's not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 10:25:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sure the console is cheaper but then you're locked in to paying the digital price. No cheap secondhand games for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 01:35:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cex is much better value if you're trading in, so it's usually worth it if you're planning to buy something else from them. Plus, way less faff than eBay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 01:30:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And it adds a bit of colour! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 01:27:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When strange things happen.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 01:12:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just because the serial number matches doesn't mean it's your meter. I had a new kitchen fitted so they turned the water off at the meter but it didn't go off. He tried a different one and it did! The water company came out to investigate and the meters were switched with next door. Got a £300 refund on past usage! It's probably not a common thing but try turning it off at the meter and seeing if your water runs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 22:39:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 10:29:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really need to get a bonded pair one day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 10:18:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use an Anker one that stands the phone up. I like it because it's impossible for it to be off centre from the charging contact point and it's easy to see notifications when they come in. It's the first wireless charger I've used so I've got nothing to compare it to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 10:12:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in London so even renting a room is more expensive than renting an entire house in other parts of the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 10:04:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At my work, I've heard of loads of people working at the end of their bed. I think it disproportionately affects people on a lower income who are more likely to be living in a house share or with their parents. Higher paid people are more likely to have a spare bedroom or some other space to work in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 10:00:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lots could be done with smart home routines. One idea could be to have lights come on different colours on weekdays and weekends and then it's easy to tell at a glance. My wake up lights come on later on the weekends too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 09:48:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Start looking for jobs now before furlough ends and everyone gets made redundant at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 08:47:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well they don't need to be full on disgusting. I'd be happy if they were just a little bit less dazzling. They just take me out of the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 22:05:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My rough budget was up to around £2000 but I'd consider things up to around £3000. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 22:03:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, I wouldn't have thought of either of those brands! My mum has a Habitat sofa and it's been better than my IKEA ones but it's starting to show its age now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 22:02:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Friheten? I had it before haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 18:37:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having worked in stockfile management, I can tell you that would lead to a whole load of customer disappointment and the staff having to placate the angry ones. Most retail companies wouldn't be able to achieve an accurate enough stockfile. The issues that make things inaccurate range from theft, to delivery issues, to things being left in the wrong place. It's basically impossible to maintain it to an accurate enough level in most places. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 17:55:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plus the internet will be locked into a contract. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 17:43:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in London so I'm sure there's somewhere. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 17:39:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> £15k is a little above what I was expecting. ;) I only have space for a more compact sofa, no chaise. Mine is about 170cm which is perfect so around that size. Other ones I've seen recommended here have been around £2000 for one this sort of size, which I think is ok for quality, and I'd probably max out at around £3000 for something I really loved. I'm not looking to buy right now but it's something I'm considering for the non immediate future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 17:32:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. I'd heard of their cabinets but didn't know they did sofas. Some of them are quite nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 17:20:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. I'll take a closer look at them but they do look quite nice with good customisation options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 16:17:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The race to the bottom, eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 16:10:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most of their stuff is vile anyway! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 16:08:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was on furlough until this week so it was fine until I started having to go to places! It's hard so I'm kinda limiting my interactions. It's quite easy to guess what someone is saying in a supermarket, for example, but other places are harder. I try to ask closed questions where possible. I'm generally not going to many places due to the whole Coronavirus thing anyway, but communication is definitely just another thing to add to the list of why I'm not going out much.

Action on Hearing Loss have been campaigning for things like people talking to lipreaders being exempt from wearing masks, etc and I think they're aiming to bring out some communication cards explaining the rules for deaf and hard of hearing people to share with anyone who's challenging them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> High quality sofa brands? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 15:58:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My family has a couple of Multiyork sofas which have been going for about 25 years and showing no signs of slowing down, even after several moves etc. They're basically just indestructible and even the cushions are holding their shape. Multiyork have closed down but I'm wondering what alternatives there are out there, as I'd like my next sofa to be indestructible too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 15:55:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not recently but I have had things like that in the past. Promos with the dog treat company. I gave it to a friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 09:57:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Speaking of polished, isn't it odd how his teeth are absolutely gleaming when the rest of him is dirty and unkempt? Other tailies have been shown with teeth that you'd expect to find in conditions like that but they didn't bother to make the lead's teeth more believable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 09:40:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would love a category for toys that don't look like dicks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 00:09:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's such a babe! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 00:01:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sneaky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 23:53:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can't confirm. Have had Hues for a few years and have had an entirely Hue flat for almost a year and I use the colours regularly. I have a couple of colour scenes that are nicer than having a plain warm white for winding down in the evening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 23:48:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do Yourself It. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 21:46:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Walthamstow, North Finchley, New Southgate, Canning Town, Tottenham, Southfields... These are a few off the top of my head. I personally picked Walthamstow for the transport links, although my budget was smaller and I got a one bed/studio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 03:55:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yas! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 03:47:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No it's not.

🤟🏻 is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 03:07:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Matt black would be great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 02:21:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 01:55:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine is showing an average of £55 a month but I haven't lived here a full year so I don't know the true figures. Winter uses more but the direct debit is averaged out over the year. This is in an all electric studio flat. My bills excluding mortgage and service charge are roughly £200 a month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 01:35:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you really need that stuff if you don't even live with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 01:29:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That'll be to do with the Royal Mail sorting office zone than the actual geography. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 00:41:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any idea where the SE comes in this whole thing? It's new but it's basically a turbocharged 7/8. I have an old 7 but I think the mic might be a bit busted or something coz Siri never understands me on it, so I would use the SE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 00:33:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Clean it every time you get in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Freckle lips! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 21:36:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 18:42:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pivot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 17:53:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Apple logo has only recently been in the middle of the phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 17:50:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Imagine her Halloween costumes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 23:46:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did he notice? I'm imagining him getting home and being like "I swear I just bought some foam board" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 23:43:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gotta account for ambient temperature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 20:09:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That doesn't sound like a real place either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 18:36:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 17:21:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Help To Save was the first thing that came to mind but you already know that one so that's good.
My other thoughts would be going to the dentist and vet treatment at the PDSA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 15:43:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have two. One is around the base of my media cabinet so it glows from underneath. The other is going under my kitchen cabinets, if this website ever manages to get my diffuser to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 02:24:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/AmateurRoomPorn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 02:22:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would suggest angling the armchair in to face the sofa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 02:09:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We call it a petrol station. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 01:55:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's String shelving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 01:48:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pity Me is a place name?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 01:41:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have got work in the morning. But I'm still up.
I went back for the first time today and it was only for four hours but I quickly remembered why I was starting to look for a new job in March. I've got one month to go before I start the new job now so just gotta put up with it..
Starting to feel like I'm slowly going back to normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 00:47:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know how you feel. You're lucky enough to have a built in gender neutral nickname though! I don't. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 00:29:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And the bisexuals are forgotten again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 23:23:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've viewed some with my mother who is looking. Some agents required masks, one required masks and gloves, but a bunch of others didn't say anything at all. One of the ones who required masks went in and opened all doors etc before we went in and then waited outside. No hand shaking was done with any of them. So, basically it varies widely between agents and by area. The mask ones were all in one area and most of the unmasked ones were in a different area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 22:58:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does it have to be white? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 22:05:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They should have shown someone wearing it under their nose. Someone wearing it on their chin is clearly taking a break from it. Someone wearing it under their nose is a total fucking idiot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 21:57:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm terrified. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 21:52:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like it! I don't even have anything interesting to say about my commute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 21:33:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was too wacky for my tastes. I'm glad I started watching the show before the movie because it might have put me off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 21:14:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I basically want all female characters to be queer at all times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 21:01:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It seems that Ruth has been single the entire time on Snowpiercer, judging by the conversations with the jackboot guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 20:52:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That would be interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 20:51:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even if they did, I wonder if they could just plow through it and send it off the tracks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 20:47:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Layton has been in power for what, less than a day? Hardly time to change conditions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 19:33:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They said something about batteries earlier. Perhaps they have some power stored up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 19:18:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wasn't it the point at which Big Alice was connected to Snowpiercer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 19:16:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ben saw them on the satellite before Javi picked up the radio signal. He had his time to be shocked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 19:06:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The thing that confused me about that is why not just have the children do it in shifts of a couple of hours? It would just become part of life, perhaps it could be an incentive for studying if that was the punishment for the lowest grades, etc. Seems fairer than one child doing it for hours on end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 18:53:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Melanie could end up inadvertently cutting her daughter off.
But I feel like they want to show more of the relationship between them so I don't think that will happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 16:59:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Another reason I'm glad I had LASIK! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 16:34:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do they have that rule? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 16:32:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Had my first commute since March today. Was on the tube around 9.45 so not peak time, but literally had no one else in the carriage until one stop before mine. Felt very strange. The way home at 2pm was a little bit busier but still only about 6 people in the carriage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 16:28:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh shit. Is that actually why it's called WKD? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 00:40:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My cat is just the same, even down to the ginger and white colouring. He loves a belly rub in bed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 12:03:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a couple of Innr smart plugs that I use for my electric radiators and I'm satisfied with them. The only thing is that they don't show up with Homekit so I can't use Siri to control them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 11:10:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks a little high though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 11:09:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can get some lovely 2 beds in your price range! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 11:09:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Never been mugged here. Never felt unsafe as a single woman walking alone at night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 02:16:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you looked at Walthamstow? Victoria line plus overground(s) means it's very well connected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 01:41:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Remember, every storm passes. Some are longer and heavier than others but just remember how good it feels when you can see the sun again. I'm glad you have hope again. Don't let it slip away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 13:12:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It means good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 13:11:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It means good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 02:58:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thomas the Tank Hedge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 02:53:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Barnét for Barnet. There was a spate of alterations to the road signs in the area to reflect it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 02:48:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I often end up sitting on my bed but then being too lazy to get up and go brush my teeth and feed the cats so then I feel extra bad about lying on my bed instead of lying in my bed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 02:45:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your children would have you broke and alive over broke and dead any day.

Many people have got out of debt far bigger than yours. Have you spoken to Stepchange? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 02:41:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She's so pretty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 02:41:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was up until 4 last night. I had a video call at 3pm today and I could see the tiredness in my face. It's bad. So bad. I'm back to work part time next week but luckily only starting at 10am. And then I've got a month to get my shit together for 6am shifts at my new job. What have I got myself into? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 02:35:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's the chicken on the end you have to keep your eye on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 02:35:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My ex grew up in Borehamwood and apparently they had the incredibly original nickname of Boringwood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 02:31:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Snorbans for St Albans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 01:53:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just to add, these are often called Employee Assistant Programs (EAP). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 01:15:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Quite possibly the car was parked there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 01:12:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I try that but it just fades away or goes behind me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 01:11:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, that's it! I think that's the explanation I understand. I'll have to give it a try next time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 00:36:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I prefer a "thank you" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-10 17:47:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, that's a really useful insight. You're right, as a person who lives in a majority white country (UK), black hair is not something that is known about in the mainstream. I'm typically learning about it from the internet rather than from general society and it's taken for granted that I have a hair type that is mainstream because I'm of European descent.

When you put it like that, it is kinda ridiculous that I hadn't even heard of shrinkage, even though I consume a lot of international (ok mostly north American) media. From a personal perspective, it's not my individual lack of interest as I love to learn about anything different from my circumstances, but I can see it's not presented anywhere that I'd come across it, which is the problem.

I can imagine how grating it gets to have to constantly explain your hair or whatever other aspect of yourself just because people don't hear about it. I think a lot of people might have the mindset of "it's ok to ask because I'm just curious and not asking maliciously" but I understand it's not any black person's job to explain to anyone who asks. I can kinda see this from the perspective of having a disability that people ask about. I don't mind that they're asking because I know they're just curious and they may never have had the chance to ask it before, but when the same misinformation and misconceptions come up time and time again, it does get tiring to have to explain what you feel is just basic information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-10 14:43:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One of my good friends has the same first name as me so we were always called by our last names, or a variation on it. She's very not butch and is hetero, and I wasn't that masc presenting when it started. I actually hate my last name so I don't like to use it around other people so I'm stuck hating all my names haha. Anyway, there's a whole ton of reasons why people might use their last name so I wouldn't think it's weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-10 04:01:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What if they really had cut their hair though? This one I can understand that people aren't aware of shrinkage but is it so bad that someone asks if it's cut? People say it to me when I've really obviously had inches cut off my hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-10 02:12:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love everything from Lush including the fragrances! They have all sorts there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-10 00:54:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apollo doesn't show crossposts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-10 00:07:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did this. I also liked looking at all the men's clothing and I didn't really twig why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-10 00:00:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is really random but I happened to pick up a book in a Spanish flea market that happened to have lesbians. It didn't say anything on the cover about it but I was probably like 13 and it was quite the awakening. It's Blue Genes by Val McDermid. I should re-read it and see what it's like now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 23:56:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your flag is upside down. Are you in distress? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 23:40:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So sad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 23:26:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For anyone who hasn't heard this term before - this is what TERFs call trans women. They say this to reinforce the idea that they're men pretending to be women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 22:53:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look up time based light </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 21:51:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I was furloughed on 100% pay and then I saw the writing on the wall for redundancies so I applied for a new job with a higher salary and more holiday so I guess that's how I've benefited. I might not have accepted this job if I didn't need it though, as the early shifts scare me! Otherwise, I've probably actually spent more money on doing home improvements seeing as I've been home since March! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 21:04:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I keep playing GTA Online because it's in the PS4 and it's so easy to just turn it on and go. Really, I'm supposed to be playing Tomb Raider. I bought one a few weeks ago and I want to play that, and then there's another one free this month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 20:18:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry, I actually meant the wake up/go to sleep routines. My bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 19:36:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would it support sunrise/sunset automations linked to the calendar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 19:35:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. I'm p happy with my set up generally so I didn't want to have to abandon it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 16:48:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. I was hoping not to have to do HA. I prefer easier methods.

If I set up HA, do I have to migrate everything to it or can I use it in addition to my current set up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How to deal with routines when working different shifts? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 15:56:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For my current job, I had some routines set up for my Hue lights doing sunrise and alarms flashing them, plus scene changes to signify when it's time to leave etc. I have them in the Hue app and the Alexa app.

I worked at the same time each week so it was simple. My new job will be alternating weeks of early and late shifts and I don't know how to automate this. I don't want to get up at the same time on my late weeks because it's uncomfortably early. The idea I've come up with so far is to have the routines set up and just turn each one on and off each week, but that requires remembering.

Maybe there's a way to integrate it with the calendar? If I could say to start the routine 1.5 hours before the event starts or something? I use the iCloud calendar but I would be open to using a different one.

Any other ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 15:30:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to be able to do that with some dry shampoo in between but now that I've got short hair, it just sticks up from sleeping and the only way to get it back to normal is to wash it. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 01:07:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're saying that the people are *not* considering their children their first priority. Which makes them shitty. You can absolutely date as a parent but you shouldn't be putting dating before your children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 21:52:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More like her child and 99 of their peers. Then you can add on things like "what if their best friend ate it?" and so on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 21:40:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sofas aren't that hard to move, if it's not a behemoth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 20:55:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm happy if my lights last ten years. They are gadgets, after all. My entire flat is Hue and I don't know if I'll even be living here in 10 years! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 18:40:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It probably had steps up to the original front door. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 18:16:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/bottlebrush material </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 15:47:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I read speculation it could be a year validity, which would work.
Also, the longer date you give people on things that they need to claim, the higher the chance that they don't claim it, which I'm sure the government would like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 13:42:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because lipstick is made out of fish scales? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 12:18:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It doesn't have to be backpacking in Asia. I went traveling for 3 months around the US when I was 22. More expensive, but it's what I wanted to do. Surely there's some places you'd like to go? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 02:12:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It basically says staff must do work while at work. Why would this be a problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 01:11:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 22:49:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 4 years! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 20:37:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What year is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 18:47:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been thinking about getting a cleaner when I'm back to work full time because I really do hate cleaning, especially all the nitty gritty bits like in between gaps and skirting boards, etc. I live in a studio flat though so it would be really awkward to be there while they're cleaning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 18:44:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He was a serial killer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 13:48:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Another cat sub?

*sigh*

Subscribe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 04:00:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you use lactaid pills? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 03:46:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ಠᴗಠ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 03:40:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 4 months is a good start but really full no contact is the only way forward. You don't want the same things from each other so it's never going to work out and it's just going to cause you anguish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 03:13:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe they'd get wind of the poisoning and start a revolution.

......

Oh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 02:53:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Quality shitpost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 02:39:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seems like there'd be easier ways of population control. Poisoned food perhaps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 02:34:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So two days into Miles' training is when they stage a revolution? Shouldn't they, you know, let him get trained up so he can run the train when the engineers are gone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-06 23:07:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just got notification today that I'll be going back next week, although not for normal duties as those no longer exist. Basically we're going to be cheap grunt workers helping with the closure of our office which is leading to us losing our jobs. Luckily I've already been offered a new one but it's a bit of a kick in the teeth for those in my team who haven't yet.
Now I'm gonna have to finish all the DIY projects that I've been putting off for months this week.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-06 20:32:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To shreds, you say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-06 18:42:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ominous ellipsis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> SHRAMP </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-06 17:40:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-06 15:02:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's also the gayest thing I've ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-06 13:17:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> P amazing. 😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-06 13:15:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-06 00:41:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try Walthamstow. If you're ok with being not super close to the station, it gets more affordable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-06 00:20:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The great thing about London is that anyone can become a Londoner. I count anyone who lives here to be a Londoner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-06 00:18:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I respect your right to have an opinion but it's wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-05 23:59:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TV in the left bottom bit. It's waaaay too high up there. Bookshelf in the right bit. And plants all up in the top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-05 23:52:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Repainting the walls and changing the blinds will go a long way, and it's not expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-05 23:06:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's quite hard to find toys that aren't explicitly dick shaped but they're out there! It's also pretty hard to find anything that isn't pink. 😂 My favourite toy is the Womanizer Duo - got it with my birthday discount at Lovehoney so it wasn't quite as steep as the full price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-05 19:41:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me, I tend to keep things for long enough that the box won't make any substantial difference to a second hand price. I used to keep them when I had a loft I could ditch them in but now that I've got a studio flat, it's pretty much a few days until I've tested them and then the boxes are gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-05 15:36:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Asking the important questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-05 12:35:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've got time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-05 04:07:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And people deride console owners.

I like knowing that I don't have to worry that my console is going to run the game and I don't have to troubleshoot it or upgrade it. If PC building and maintaining is a hobby for someone, that's fine, but the hardware is just a tool for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 22:06:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But... why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 19:42:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You either /r/tili or /r/tihi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 19:32:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thing is, many of those places will have a month's worth of rain in a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 19:30:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well it shows the next four. Kinda pointless to have it for something as frequent as the tube but for trains, this would be more useful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 19:25:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why 24 hours? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 19:21:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well the same can be said of any kerb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 19:16:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why does this exist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 19:09:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/tihi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 19:07:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why does your garden have a rug in it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 19:01:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah. If you know the walk is 12 minutes and it's showing one in 14 minutes, better get your skates on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 16:01:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just to add to the discussion - I had a credit balance on a card that I didn't use very often. They ended up doing an automatic refund to my current account. I would have got around to spending it eventually so I didn't really care, personally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 12:08:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also comes with a 12 month warranty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 01:21:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You feel great that you managed not to do it this time right? Remember that feeling and use it as fuel for next time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 23:48:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Viakal maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 23:45:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The first photo is hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 23:43:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Be strong! You got this! 💪🏻 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 23:31:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like comphet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 23:17:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But if I say "he wears glasses" do you picture him with a couple of tumblers on his head? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 16:42:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FUCK YEAH! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 16:20:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just got the call to say I've been offered the job. Stoked! No depressing unemployment period following a depressing lockdown period for me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 13:14:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah for sure. I just find the whole process a slog. I've done a few and just waiting to hear back about an interview this week but just ugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 12:46:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Weebl and Bob. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 02:20:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why don't you want to stick them on the TV? The adhesive comes off cleanly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 02:15:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 2 weeks. Oof. I've got two months at least, but still finding it hard to motivate myself to do job applications. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 18:22:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My neighbours are ok! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 18:01:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. I have Ones for surrounds but as I mentioned, no plan to get the sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 17:55:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, great to read the comparisons! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 17:27:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooh, a three way comparison!  Good to know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 17:25:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My flat is not that big so I'm not sure if that would make much difference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 17:23:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interesting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 17:22:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ballin! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 14:28:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably best to just get some decent Bluetooth speakers then! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 13:06:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can have a WiFi network set up without an internet connection. I don't know if that's any good, especially as it would then block the phone from connecting to the mobile data network. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Has anyone gone from a Playbase to an Arc? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 13:03:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see plenty of Beam to Arc or Playbar to Arc posts but no Playbase to Arc. I can't afford to get an Arc right now but I was wondering how it compares to the Playbase, especially without a sub.

Personally, I got the Playbase because I wanted a bit more bass but I live in a flat so didn't think a sub was wise. I see posts saying the Arc is mostly only worth it if you have a sub too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 12:33:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I moved so I didn't need a similar sofa. I ended up finding a Landskrona in the bargain corner and got that. It's not bad but the seat cushions are definitely less firm than they used to be. I'm probably going to buy a non IKEA sofa when I have a bit more money going spare! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 02:49:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't really looked at it so I wouldn't know! IKEA showroom is pretty great for showing the stuff that gets battered really fast though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 02:39:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it depends what you get. The particle board with laminate stuff gets pretty fucked pretty fast, but I've got a couple of metal cabinets that I don't foresee having problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 02:37:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stockholm is supposed to be their higher end line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 02:35:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a Soderhamn. I got it for my spare room as an occasional sofa that could be used to sleep on as it's roughly the size of a single bed, but it kinda sucked. It looks nice at first but it looks deflated and flat really quite easily - remembering that this wasn't even my main sofa. It also wasn't great to lie down on because of the gap in the middle. I only paid £185 for it at the bargain corner so it was not too bad as my occasional sofa for a few years for the price, but I definitely wouldn't recommend it for an every day sofa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 02:30:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And more expensive to buy blinds for. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 02:27:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've got the same sofa in fabric and the cat hair just sticks to it! I've resorted to using a big throw to cover it and only uncovering it for company, so I don't get to see my sofa looking nice that often! I'm envious of wipe clean but leather sofas are not really my thing, sadly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 01:56:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got Hue Aurelle ceiling lights and I use 3D printed switch covers with the Hue Dimmers for them. They're not as beautiful as some light switches can be but I think they're inoffensive enough, plus everything in my flat is white so they don't stand out. It was the easiest option I could find that doesn't require workarounds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 01:50:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can indeed.
Game mode does black as off and video mode does black as dim white. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 01:42:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 01:41:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm on furlough until the redundancy takes place. Hurrah.. I don't even know what I've spent the last few months doing. I was thinking about doing an Excel course online to make myself look better but I haven't been able to make myself do it yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 01:38:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 23:02:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then why was it an extinction event? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 01:17:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why would someone buy one of those? It seems way more inconvenient than a pavement legal one. Longer range? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 22:31:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I guess I'll find out. :)

I put them up today and they've been holding ok with repeated opening and closing. I do feel like I have to be delicate when pressing the button on the housing or opening the battery compartment as it feels a bit wobbly but I'm not usually a brute anyway.

I actually had to redo one strip as it stuck the bracket perfectly to the paint - the only problem was that the paint no longer wanted to be stuck to the plaster! I moved it over a couple of centimetres and tried it again and it's all good. At this point, I'm more worried about the paint coming off the ceiling than the strip coming off the ceiling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 19:48:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never knew I needed a pair of Tommy Wiseau pants until this moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 19:47:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tommy wants to be supporting your balls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 16:02:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, interesting. In the UK, the sizes are listed as the fabric width. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 15:29:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would I still then have to navigate using the Sonos app? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 13:54:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Doesn't a hard search just show that they've searched you, not whether it's been accepted or not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 13:08:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Socket location on the floorplan would be nice. Often, I start imagining where furniture will go but sockets can affect things. I don't think it's the kind of thing agents would bother to do, especially as they're often hidden behind furniture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 13:03:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If this was in a home, it would be easy to flip the breaker. But in an office, you're not likely to know where that is. So yeah, not your problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 12:53:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only thing is sometimes I see a job say you need to have got a C in English and Maths. But I'm sure with enough proven experience in a field, they wouldn't care about that either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 04:48:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you checked the dimensions of the actual unit? It's a bit bigger than the listed size. I'm not familiar with the sizes in inches but for example, the 80cm blinds have housing that's about 84cm wide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 04:22:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Amazing! Thank you! If it's been two weeks, hopefully that's forever. :) I wanted to try it so I actually have stuck my brackets up but left them until tomorrow to mount the blinds, as I wasn't waiting around for an hour for them to stick plus I figure overnight is even better.

The next thing I would have considered is maybe gluing up a strip of wood which I could drill into, but that's effort and I already had command strips. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 04:10:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is the significance of 🦀? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 04:03:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you could get rid of it, so can they.

It's one thing if they're blasé about it or ignoring it and letting it build up, but if they have a solid plan in place to pay it off, what's the problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 04:01:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't buy everything at once. Once you live in the space, you realise what furniture is needed and what isn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 03:55:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The iPhone is a backup, in a way. The iTunes library lives on an external harddrive on my Mac mini, and I have a second hard drive backing up all of my content so I have it in 3 places. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 03:52:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live alone in a small flat so my set up works just fine for me.

1.	If I'm playing music on AirPlay, audio like alarms and video content plays on the phone speaker. I don't know what else I'd want on my phone while music is on.
2.	 If I'm listening to music on my speakers, I'm at home. I don't need my phone to be offline and it's definitely not going out of WiFi range.
3.	 All I have is my iPhone and my Mac mini to play music from. The Mac mini is connected to Playbase and Ones through the TV if I want to play music from there, no need for AirPlay. Honestly, it's pretty rare that I do play from the computer though because there's no point when I can just play from my phone. How many devices does one person need to play music from?
4.	No biggie, it doesn't die that quickly. If it is low, I can pop on the wireless charger or plug it in.
5.	 No one else needs to access my collection. If they do, I can have my Mac mini on and have them use the iTunes Remote app but that has literally never happened. Or I could even just hand them my phone? What a crazy idea.

So, none of these reasons make me think I need to be doing anything other than AirPlaying from my iPhone. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 02:48:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> White paws with black beans? Ultra cute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 01:55:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Am I the only one who has no idea who this is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 01:44:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or do a smaller hole in another sheet to go on the inside of the door? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 01:36:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup, has worked for me for a while! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 01:27:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't have a NAS and don't really see reason to need one when it's all on my phone already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 01:15:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a big iTunes library that I've had for like 10 years with lots of custom playlists and I have it all stored on my phone. I don't like paying monthly for streaming services when I already have music, and it's so easy to just say "Hey Siri, play Sleater-Kinney on living room" for example. I got Sonos because there's very few AirPlay 2 speakers on the market and they seemed good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 00:43:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My question too. I'd love this but I play through AirPlay 99% of the time.

Edit: gosh, I didn't realise it would be so controversial to use Sonos as an AirPlay speaker! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 23:59:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmm. My flat is a lot more expensive than the blinds so I may try the Command Strips first. Plus, I'm not sure my drill is good enough to go through steel. It's kinda on its last legs and not gripping the bits very well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 23:38:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not sure if it's a good idea to drill into a structural element? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Putting up Fyrtur with Command Strips? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 22:22:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awful idea or will it work? The Command Strips are rated 5.4kg for a pair and the blind weighs less than 2.58kg. The Command Strips are right around the same length and width as the Fyrtur brackets so it would have a full surface area.

I put one Fyrtur up successfully in my kitchen but my living room appears to have a steel joist running across. I can only drill about 1.5cm before hitting it and I don't have screws short and thick enough for that.

I would follow the Command Strip instructions in full including the rubbing alcohol - which I don't bother doing for light frames. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 16:56:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The population isn't big enough to need large volumes. After all, they're already living off the food grown in the train, which doesn't appear to be machine farmed at present. Plus, you can imagine that the population will spread out and form multiple smaller communities, which could each grow for themselves. Food growth can be scaled up as the population increases over time.

Do we know the population of the train? There's 400 tailies so I can't imagine it's more than a 4 digit number. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 16:45:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see it as being akin to religious text. There are plenty of quasi religious tones in how the passengers talk about the train and Mr Wilford. They say things like the engine provides, so I think 1001 cars long is just another phrase they use, just like people say amen or god bless etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 16:39:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think brakemen have any authority over the jackboots, more just that they have a different jurisdiction over the passengers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 16:32:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think they know this as they showed the reveal and it seemed to be a surprise. Although what's worse - knowing it's ground up bugs or having mystery protein bars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 16:28:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess it's a case of not putting all your eggs in one basket. Or all your passengers in one carriage. Shame they didn't do that for the cows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 16:25:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interesting point - where was the chip? Was it the same hand that got frozen off? If so, it's possible that Till got it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 15:48:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a port hole. Perhaps originally designed for another purpose such as ventilation or services. I imagine they're throughout the train. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 23:25:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is seeing a film as soon as possible really the selling point? I would have thought it was more to do with the big screen and sound etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 22:51:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did mine through IKEA and they do 0% finance for 36 months. I had cash in my accounts but did the finance anyway for flexibility. I had to pay the kitchen fitter in cash as they weren't affiliated with IKEA but some kitchen places will sell you the kitchen and fitting in one transaction which can be financed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 21:19:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're going to send CVs en masse, you should at least have several different versions. For example, you could have an admin one, a retail one, a customer service one, a sales one, etc. Obviously they'll all have the same work history, but you can highlight different competencies depending on which are more relevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 17:36:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 15:46:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well not all of London is urban and dense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 15:26:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi, it's me, your wife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 15:18:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh those pancakes sound incredible! I have ingredients for pancakes and bacon and maple syrup but not really the time to make them... Maybe tomorrow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 15:17:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Job interview tomorrow morning on Zoom. Kinda bricking it. I hate calls in the first place, and to people I don't know is even worse. So today I'm gonna tidy up so I feel organised, and I'm going to practise interview questions. Eek! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 14:22:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah my reference may have been too obscure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 12:23:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you checked your full report from three different providers?
Check your Experian full report at MSE Credit Club; Equifax with Clearscore; TransUnion with CreditKarma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 03:57:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds like the perfect situation to ask a mortgage broker about. Look for one with no upfront fee. Most of them either take their fee from the bank when you take the mortgage out, or charge you when you take a mortgage so the initial consultation is free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 03:30:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Many people have commented that it's not a great idea for a bunch of reasons, but let's entertain the idea if you were happy to put up with the pitfalls and the possibility of not being able to sell it. I'm going to go for a worst case scenario where you can't sell it at all.

You don't have enough figures in your post so I'm making up some random ones for illustration.
Let's say you're renting and your rent costs £10,000 a year. How many years would you have to live in the flat for you to break even on that purchase cost? If it's a £50,000 flat and you lived there for over 5 years, it's no big deal if you can't sell it as you've broken even compared to renting anyway right? But if it's £200,000, that's 20 years. Most people don't want to commit to living anywhere for 20 years, let alone student digs. This isn't even factoring in the service charges, etc.

If it was £200,000 and you lived there for 5 years, moved out, rented it out to a student, would you be happy with the rental return considering that you can no longer access any equity in the property to use for other purposes? If you had purchased a traditional property, you could either sell it or remortgage it to get cash.

If instead you bought a £400,000 property with a £200,000 deposit and a mortgage on the rest, you're likely gonna come out of that with more than £200,000 in equity. You'll be able to sell it, get your £200,000 back plus appreciation with a lot less trouble.

You say you're not buying it as an investment but all property is an investment, that you happen to be able to live in. Most properties appreciate in value in the long term and are generally a safe investment. As you've seen in the replies, this one is risky so you'd have to prepare for a worst case scenario. Maybe you get lucky and you can sell it, but who knows?

Maybe play around with some hypothetical scenarios in a spreadsheet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 02:08:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 🤢 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 02:06:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why would you say AAAAA when it clearly says AAAA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 02:05:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's an E number anyway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 01:01:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this his support bubble? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-27 20:00:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is an important aspect that should be put in your main post so that people can advise better on Sharia compliant options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-27 16:53:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've had two boys who love belly rubs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-27 15:56:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Online dating is fickle! I can only do it for a while before getting fed up and taking a break. Don't forget that you can always come back to it in a few months if you're disillusioned for now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-27 15:48:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, Lex is an app that doesn't have any profile photos.

People from Tinder ghost alllll the time. I wouldn't correlate it with the photo. It could be any reason! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-27 15:44:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was it Lex? I think it's a great idea but there does need to be some level of physical attraction and maybe she just doesn't like blondes? There's plenty of people who are going to dig you, and I think it's quite evident from the comments here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-27 15:09:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm frugal so that I can afford to buy utensil trays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-27 13:48:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah it's more about the room than matching the devices. I have a black Playbase under my black TV and white Ones against my white walls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 23:10:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cries in single 😭 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 20:25:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had mine as Sir on one of them. Made me feel important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 20:10:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In London, we measure our journeys by time taken, not by distance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 17:19:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope, singletons are at a financial disadvantage in many respects. In London and the south east, the only people that I know who have been able to buy have had 5 or 6 figure gifts from their parents for a deposit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 17:07:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought the average salary was around £30,000 so I've just looked it up and [this article](https://www.theguardian.com/money/2018/may/12/salary-what-get-paid-talk-about-it-makes-brits-cringe) says the median average is £28,600 which is not far off.
[This page](https://www.findcourses.co.uk/inspiration/articles/average-salary-uk-2018-14105) also puts things at a similar level, and higher for full time workers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 16:55:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could be that they saw what your house sold for and it got them thinking about what that could buy them closer to family, work, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 16:37:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes it's uncomfortable if you asked them out and waited for an answer and she was stuck there. But giving them your number as you're leaving is ok as you're immediately exiting the interaction and leaving the ball in their court. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 16:24:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had the opposite in a grotto in Spain. The signs advise you to bring a light coat in and when we got down, all the French and Spanish people were putting them on, but us British people were perfectly comfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 15:48:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Put a freezer block on it.

Seriously.

I was playing Uncharted Lost Legacy for a few hours and it started stuttering and I realised the console was hot AF. You can wrap a freezer block in a teatowel and put it on top to cool it down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 13:39:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't want to move to another part of the country when all my friends and family live in this part of the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 13:38:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's assuming you're buying alone. A couple each on a salary of £25,000 would have enough household income. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 13:12:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The household energy consumption data for the UK exists. But it isn't broken down into supply types. Averages are an average, regardless of property size, type, lofts, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 13:01:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a lot! Mine seems to be ranging from £40-65 for a one bed/studio. But do you know how many kWh it is? I've ranged from around 10kWh/day to 16kWh/day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 12:55:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because I'm looking for data, not anecdotes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 01:38:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Considering the tank is well insulated enough to take a shower 23.5 hours after it was on, I wouldn't have imagined that the ambient room temperature would make that much difference, but maybe it does! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 01:13:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does outside heat really make much difference to heating water? Because it's slightly warmer coming through the pipes or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 00:31:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I'm furloughed since March but May's usage actually went down, strangely enough. It just got me thinking about it and why it's gone down in May. March and April were higher than February.

Most of my usage will be from the water tank and the heating so I just wanted to check that it's not using obscene amounts. As most electric flats will have the same set up, it would be interesting to compare.

True point about it being different based on different parts of the country, but even so, properties vary by how well insulated they are, size of water tanks, etc so averages are still useful as a baseline. Plus, London alone has almost double the population of Scotland so I imagine it would skew towards the south anyway (which is where I live!). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 23:22:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. I've tried various search terms but not turned up anything, but maybe there's a magic phrase that'll find it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 23:18:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This seems to be an average of all consumers across the UK, which is adding together electric only and dual fuel households, unless I'm misinterpreting it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does anyone have any sources for average electricity usage in electric only properties? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 23:07:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm trying to work out if the amount I'm using is average or above average but I'm having difficulty finding sources that list averages for electricity only properties. Obviously would want to be able to compare to similar properties, so break down by property size/type would be necessary.
Edit: to be clear, I'm looking for kWh usage, not cost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 21:03:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Offer to buy the furniture off them and then get rid of it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 11:50:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's wild how I didn't even know that wouldn't be a normal sentence in America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 11:28:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Finances aren't the place for sentimentality. Get her to open a new account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 02:00:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't put your address on your cover letter. You're not expecting them to write to you by post when you're sending them an email. If they need to post you something, they'll get your address then.

As for the form, I don't think it's a problem. People do relocate for various reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 01:39:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! I figured 3 could be quite easily done with work plus living in a foreign country, but your French roommate was the wild card. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 01:38:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Luckily it wasn't me who lost the meaningless internet points. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 01:34:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "My bike has a flat tyre" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 01:31:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wasn't the one who originally pointed it out. Honestly, the few little things I did find weren't enough for me to really pay attention to the fact that it was non native. Lose the bus was the only one I properly picked up on until I deliberately looked for more. Sometimes, there are more mistakes and bigger mistakes that really make me notice. The rest of it is high enough standard that I would have assumed a native English speaker.

English speakers are the worst for not knowing other languages. It's quite embarrassing. I even have parents who speak a foreign language fluently or natively, yet I only knew one language for the majority of my life. My second language isn't even a foreign language!

Out of curiosity, what 4 languages do you use on a daily basis and what circumstances mean you need to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 01:18:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably impossible to get anything that covers pandemic related causes but if you think it will last out the pandemic, it could be worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 01:14:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's just cheap. You should have all got one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 01:05:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 🏅 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 00:51:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In theory, couldn't you just make like 20 models and 20 sets and 20 times the people and get it done 20 times faster? Where does it get to the point of diminishing returns? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 00:45:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wouldn't most people use their phones these days anyway, which would just end up with a bunch of thumb face videos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 23:48:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mamoswine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 23:25:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Lose the bus" is the most obvious one to me. Living "on" a student residence could be one or could be a typo. "Floor number 10" would usually be 10th floor. Didn't notice anything else. It's better than most native speakers, generally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 23:13:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I buy grated coz I'm lazy. Also, keeping a cheese grater in my small kitchen cupboards for the occasional times I need to use it isn't worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 23:12:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As long as it's got a flared base. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 19:42:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> eBay or Etsy tend to have Turkish sellers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 11:37:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dog tax outstanding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 11:32:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 11:27:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ryanair took about 3 months to refund me. 7 days, my arse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 11:05:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm ready to have a pet fox.

Although I don't know where I'm going to put a fox sized litter box. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 02:05:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thing is, we don't say London Tottenham or London Arsenal, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 02:00:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm too old to have been young enough for this but also too childless for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 01:45:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get some upholstery cleaner or carpet cleaner. They often come in a bottle or can with attracted scrubbing brush. Hopefully should do the job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 01:34:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All deaf people are deaf. Fragmenting the terms only serves to fragment the people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 01:32:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More jpeg please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 01:25:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This looks like one of those things that looks easy but is actually hella difficult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 01:18:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But tall ladies are hot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 00:28:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I suppose, but you have to be in the mindset of seeking out those things. Many people will just end up at somewhere that's convenient from work or home.
Car insurance is definitely weird but I know that for me, it would have doubled when I moved back to London if I'd kept the car. Didn't plan on keeping it anyway, viva la TfL!
Generally, aside from property, transport, and drinks in pubs, I feel like costs of things are broadly the same across the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 00:11:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most tiny homes aren't built on land. They're built on trailers and are parked on land. I don't know the full legal details but it wouldn't need planning permission for building, but I don't know what restrictions there are on parking a mobile home on private land, if any. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 23:51:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Redundancy insurance exists, if that's something you'd be interested in. Otherwise I'd say train up and keep an eye out for jobs elsewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 23:27:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In some ways. Don't forget that you'll get a Freedom Pass at 60 for free travel! Buses tend to be cheaper than elsewhere in the country. Car insurance is more expensive though.
You're more likely to be closer to a discount supermarket but I can't think of many other ways that London is actually cheaper on a day to day basis. What were you thinking of?
Obviously there's lots of free cultural things to do but if you're living somewhere that doesn't have those things, doesn't mean that you'll be going out doing expensive things instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 20:57:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can see promotional material for the train in Melanie's room in the first episode. It looks as though it may have been built as a luxury cruiser type thing, and repurposed into an apocalypse train later on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 20:56:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If they went The 100 way then it would be a different show. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 20:54:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A kid doesn't need to be an engineer to take crud out of a machine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 20:48:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The bit that confuses me is they celebrate the new year at a certain location but the train doesn't maintain the same speed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 01:37:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why would your identity revolve around your spouse's occupation?

/r/arethestraightsok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 00:57:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know there are direct trains to London from Glasgow but it's a bit of a long commute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 23:16:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've only seen these at work, and they take up pretty much an entire unit underneath. Do the home ones have a smaller capacity, thus using less cupboard space? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 12:06:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah, the filament bulbs would look fine. Regular Hue bulbs will look goofy, that's for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 12:03:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They don't need constant internet connection to work, but they do need the bridge and router to be on. Then they can be controlled locally with dimmer switches, an app on the same network, etc but won't have out of home control or voice assistant control etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 11:59:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just replaced a hardwired under cabinet lighting with Hue. I did this in the UK so possibly wiring here might be different to wherever you are but essentially I have a junction box where the old LED driver was hardwired. I simply removed that and I wired in an extension cable with sockets. Then the Hue plugs in with no modification. Easy peasy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 01:42:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What kind of commands? Control through the app should still work as long as the device is connected to the WiFi. Voice commands need the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 01:39:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would kinda love some colour in my bathroom but I just went for the Adore ceiling light instead, which is ambiance only. Still, the warm light on dim is nice for a bath! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 01:24:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolute worst feature when a game launches straight into a cutscene with no option to put subs on first. Little ol' deaf me is like cool thx. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 01:11:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Crunch it all up in a bowl and use a spoon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 23:47:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The PS3 with the Uncharted games next to it and the ring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 11:04:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But you never told your parents that you liked men. Why do you have to tell them you like women? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 20:26:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Visionary! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 20:09:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not sure if you've noticed, but there's something going around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 18:53:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why is it necessary to come out when in a hetero relationship but not in a homo relationship? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 18:48:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably stolen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 18:15:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Still, hiring a car for times when you want to get out in a car is a great option. With the added bonus of not having to faff about with getting it serviced and MOT'd etc. For short trips, something like Zipcar is really easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 16:28:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You literally just subtract 12 from the number. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 15:23:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use ones like the left one because I found my thumb slipping off the edge sometimes but I've never used the tall one on the right. How does it affect control? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 15:22:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 12:51:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are your TV and Arc and bench social distancing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 12:14:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Luckily they haven't tried to hand me over to DPD but they do take a while to respond to my emails so it's been a few weeks already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 03:44:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And I bet you're now a customer for life and will recommend him to anyone who asks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 03:37:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My place ebbs and flows. Sometimes it gets messy for a bit, but I always manage to tidy it up again. Lockdown has disrupted my routine and made it harder to stick to a tidying routine, but I can't live with it being too bad for too long.

The key thing is to have an organisation system in place. Everything should have its own place, so tidying up consists of putting it back there instead of shuffling piles of things from one area to another.

There are loads of methods out there but one that's popular at the moment is Konmari. /r/Konmari and the Netflix series are good places to start, and the book is a deeper dive. For me, it's really helped me keep discipline in certain areas, especially clothes. I used to fold them and put them away piled up, but the piles would inevitably get messed up and I would end up dumping clean things haphazardly in the drawers as it was messy already so what's the point? Now I take great pride in my neatly folded clothes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 03:20:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm 30 and there's absolutely 0 chance I'd be able to buy a property by myself where I live now, if it weren't for parental help. I'm fortunate enough that my mum decided to help me out by gifting me a substantial sum as she'd rather see me benefit from it while she's still around instead of me inheriting it in X years time. The only people that I know who have or will buy property have been given gifts from their parents, even those who are earning 2-3x what I do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 03:16:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Time to buy a tiny house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 03:13:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lot of it can be avoided by buying a flat as external things are covered by the service charge. Still, things like the boiler/water heater, kitchen, bathroom, flooring, etc all need to be maintained and updated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 03:00:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't underestimate the lobbying power of a union. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 02:50:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I tried one off Amazon that was well reviewed and it made a slight improvement in my shirts but nothing I'd feel comfortable wearing to work. Gave up, sent it back, continued ironing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 02:48:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I usually just run it through a quick rinse on the machine for 15 minutes. I find it more effective than spraying it, and I'm on a water meter anyway! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 02:45:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's called code switching.

I talk generally normally around my parents but I do easily say things in a silly way that I wouldn't necessarily in polite adult company, but maybe that's just because I'm very comfortable with them. Plus the kid voice of "mummyyyyy" or "daddyyyyy" comes out when I'm asking for something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 02:33:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm having a right mare with a parcel from DPD now. Their website says they will take a photo with the open door as proof it's delivered. Mine was left at my closed front door when I was not there to receive it and it got stolen afterwards so I'm trying to get the company to replace my parcel as DPD didn't fulfill their delivery obligations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 02:02:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. I've recommended that website to a bunch of people in the past but I did just run my theoretical circumstances through it again and looks like I could claim new style JSA which isn't much but combined with savings, my disability benefit, and a mortgage holiday, I might be ok for a bit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 01:51:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Check out the Modkat top entry. I've used the linked one and the Modkat, and the Modkat is better. The Modkat has a flipping lid so it's easier to get in and the lid just flips back down, whereas the linked one is an awkward thing to put back in the right place when you take it off. Also, the grooves accumulate bits of litter and general dust and dirt and it's quite hard to clean well because the grooves end in tiny sharp corners.

Personally, my current cats aren't a fan of the top entry so I'm using a couple of Modkat XLs with the side entry right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 13:53:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Might have to look for stuff that's not ideal but anything that pays will be helpful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 13:04:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Two job applications in already and working on a third. The first of many, probably! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 12:59:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do weekends even matter right now? Nothing is happening anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 12:59:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Surely you could find the screwdriver online for a couple of quid? Worth the punt to see if you can fix it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 12:44:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Finally found out yesterday that I will indeed be made redundant. I can't say I'm surprised as the writing had been on the wall for a while, but it's still not what anyone wants to find out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 11:26:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't worry, it won't ever be needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 11:26:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not even just the elderly. Pretty much everyone of note. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 02:44:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They are the world's fastest couch potatoes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 21:38:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not black or trans or a lesbian actually.

Simply put, JK Rowling was saying that the word for "people who menstruate" is "women", which is exclusive as not all people who menstruate are women and not all women menstruate.

Thus, she's saying that trans women are not women as they don't menstruate, and trans men are not men as they do (pre-T). People who menstruate that don't identify as a binary gender are also excluded. She's also excluding all the people who don't menstruate due to a variety of conditions such as intersex, fertility issues, even menopause - which she herself will be in, for maximum irony.

Trans women are not seeking the inclusion of being called "people who menstruate" as that's not a fact. What is a fact is that trans women are women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 21:19:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes.

It is easy to remember by remembering that trans is an adjective. Just like you might refer to someone as a tall woman or a German woman or a brunette woman. A trans woman is a woman to whom the adjective of trans can be applied. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 20:12:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Black trans lesbians strapped to the roof. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 19:43:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tbh I would fall in love with someone who gave me a bouquet of Parma Violets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 19:40:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this why I've always loved Parma Violets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 18:27:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think WhatsApp gained a lot of traction in the early days when it was still fragmented between iPhone, Android, and Blackberry. It was really the first big cross platform app for all platforms and then it just remained the default choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 15:19:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in a studio flat. I have one drawer full of decorations and a 3ft tree at the back of my wardrobe. It's enough! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 01:53:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hoarding is a recognised mental illness, which it sounds like she may be affected by. It doesn't have to reach the stage where things are piled up to the ceiling and tiny pathways through things are the only way to get around for it to be detrimental to their life. There are different levels. You should look at resources for helping hoarders. There's no shame in it, just like there's no shame in depression or anxiety or any other mental illness. Ultimately, you need to tackle the root cause. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 01:40:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You've fallen prey to the sunk cost fallacy. You've already spent the money and got the use out of the items, so what does it matter now anyway? You don't use them anymore and probably 99% of it can be streamed online.

Anything in decent shape with cases can be sold on. In the UK, we have services like Music Magpie where you just scan in the barcode and they give you a price, then you package them all up in a box and send it off for free. You get the money via PayPal or bank transfer. It's not much money but money in your pocket is better than no money!

I gave up on all my CDs and DVDs a few years ago except for a few special things and it is a relief. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 01:30:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If some of them are retro, perhaps you could emulate them on a computer instead? Would just be some MBs of space instead of physical space. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 01:08:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/SneakyBackgroundFeet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 00:58:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! Fantastic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 23:31:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a bit late here. I went to a mortgage broker literally before I'd got my first payslip from my current job but he said it was ok. I had payslips from my past job and had been continuously employed for the last couple of years, which may be something a lender cares about. It may reduce your options but it's not off the table - although for me this was over a year ago so I'm not sure what lenders are doing in the current climate in regards to this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 22:57:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which is to say that some years the spend will be £0 but other years it may be £10k. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 22:53:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can log in to your personal tax account online and update HMRC with the amount that you expect to earn during this tax year. This will update your tax code to reflect it, which will automatically be sent to your work's payroll department and you should see it reflected within the next couple of payslips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 22:10:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are the transactions definitely both cleared or is one or both of them still pending? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 22:07:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I very much felt like that the first few weeks of the office being closed before I was officially furloughed. Uncertainty is killer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 21:46:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To expand a little further, they/the freeholder will have insurance on the building and the building falling apart should be concerning to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 21:12:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about a solution that hides the bed, like a Murphy bed or similar? You wouldn't have to put it away every day but just when there's company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 20:35:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't give you any legal advice but I can give you some of my own experience which may be useful.

A workplace must make reasonable adjustments for disability. I'd say in this situation, you could take the route of either proving that you don't need any adjustments, or the route of getting the company to make those adjustments for you, which may be more straightforward.

I also wear hearing aids, although I do wear these all the time at work. I can hear the alarm with them on, but managers have offered me a personal paging device for the fire alarm which would vibrate when the alarm is going off. I declined this as I wouldn't need it. Plus, the building had flashing fire alarms in addition. The managers at that company were very good but some managers may not be aware of what is available. Could you contact a health and safety department of the company? Presumably your hearing aids are your property or NHS property so I'd say if they have a health and safety concern, they should be providing whatever equipment they deem necessary. You could look into making an Access To Work claim where someone is sent to your workplace to assess what you need, of which the first £500 (I think) is covered by your employer and the rest is covered by the government AtW funds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 19:49:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't have any legal advice to offer but interestingly I am also waiting on a parcel dispatched via Tuffnells. It has been received by them but has had no activity on the tracking for several days. I suspect they have a backlog and are probably having difficulty clearing it right now. They're not a courier that I'm familiar with and I've worked in reception in an office so I regularly encounter all different couriers so I imagine they're a small outfit who can't meet demand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 19:28:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you get in contact with the management company for the building? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 16:52:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yas! Looks great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 16:37:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where I live, all electronics have a 1 year warranty for faults. Your best bet is to talk to the retailer and get it refunded or replaced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 13:49:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This doesn't surprise me, somehow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 13:21:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a similar story except I said I was from England. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 12:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Luck was on your side that day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 03:21:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Story? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 02:17:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean... I don't know what $20k means really as I don't live in America but to say under no circumstances is a bit dismissive. What if someone is living with their family still or has a paid off mortgage? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 02:06:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 5 year old phones work but it's a bit ridiculous to say they work the same as a new phone. People value different things in their technology and there's plenty of reasons to want a more modern phone if you can afford it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 02:05:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know about their full offerings in the UK but I have a Marcus account which is regarded as being the best easy access saver around so they're doing something over here at least! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 01:38:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It works really well in person. I've never found it annoying across games, TV, or movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 01:36:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hue Sync Box. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 01:33:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being hit with an animal bat makes it bizarre. Being hit with a sports bat makes it terrifying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 01:19:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the second time I've read blind in this context but I don't know what it means. Can you enlighten me? Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 01:11:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At first I thought bat was the animal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-16 00:41:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I tape fashion tape on the placket between the buttons. It holds it together and no gapping! I really should do a permanent solution but this works well enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 03:14:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love my Turkish towels. I tried them and never went back, and actually get annoyed at regular towels when I'm away from home. Bonus is that they take up less space in my flat too. I got a couple from eBay and I've seen them at TK Maxx occasionally too.

I would be interested to try linen too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 03:12:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dryers are quite uncommon in the UK. I've only ever known one person with one in their home. We're quite used to hanging things up over here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 02:59:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What does the neon say?

I like all the different colours! Makes a change round these parts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 02:09:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're welcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 02:05:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't go to my school party because I didn't like any formalwear. I think it's quite a common fear, especially for teenaged GNC people. Glad you got out of the situation easily. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 01:55:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A picture of boxes. Top quality posting. Thanks for sharing with us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 01:28:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't forget to mention that the amount of money a bank is willing to lend you for a mortgage is dependent on your salary/income. Typical numbers are 4-4.5x the gross salary, so earning £20,000 for example would give you a mortgage of £80,000-£90,000 of mortgage.

You need to add together this number of how much they'll loan you plus how much deposit you have in order to work out how much you can afford to buy a house for. Don't forget to keep a few thousand aside for fees.

/u/milesh015 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 00:44:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello Miles! I love you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 00:36:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guess it goes to show it's not all about how the stats look on paper! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 00:34:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just watched a video today on Architectural Digest YouTube with Bobby talking about the renovations. He said his team get dimensions and layouts etc so they can order big things like flooring but they don't know any personal details.

He also said he gets asked about the plant care a lot and says most of them are fake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 23:59:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People who don't know any sign languages typically have trouble getting to grips with the NMF (non manual features, such as facial expressions and body language). You'll already have that down so that's easy. Plus, using classifiers to describe things is something that will be easy.  As well as just generally being confident in making correct handshapes and reproducing signs correctly. Plus, you have the advantage that ASL and BSL speakers both use English to some degree, so having to fingerspell a word you don't know is a possibility, which wouldn't be the case if you were learning, say, Spanish sign language.

So yes, it is learning a whole new language but it is probably easier for someone who already signs than someone who's never signed in their life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 21:53:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wtf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 16:05:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I'm seriously considering it! If nothing else, I'll get a chopping board out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 15:56:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you saying she's not bi if she's in a relationship with a man? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 13:41:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice! There's a place near me that does a chopping board in the induction workshop but I've yet to go. I might go once things are back open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 03:05:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I moved house, I took them off by simply twisting them slowly until they came off and then I packed them in a box. I don't remember how long I left them in the box, but it was either days or 2-3 weeks-ish I guess. Then I just stuck them back up and they've been stuck since September/October with no problems. Just make sure nothing gets stuck to the adhesive when they're not mounted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 02:41:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Although the types of game played tend to differ. Which is not a bad thing obviously but some guys have the mind set of a casual game not being "proper" gaming. To which I say, fuck y'all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 02:37:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 10/10 kitty cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 00:55:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe it's something about this scent in particular - wherever I wore the body spray, my manager would comment on being able to smell it from quite far away. I only ever use one spray! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 23:03:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Once things are back open again, you should 100% do a level 1 course. You can find a local place to do one on either the Signature website or the iBSL website, or even just googling your local area + BSL level 1. A teacher and classmates is the best way to learn and will help you with feedback on your mistakes, which you don't get with online courses.
Learning basic signs online is a good start but it doesn't tend to help with the structure as much. Also, be prepared for you to think you're signing it right but your colleague not understanding what you're trying to say.
If you tell him you want to learn and improve, he may help you out. On the other hand, it's not his job to teach you if he doesn't want to. :)
I'm sure he'll be appreciative of you making the effort to engage with him! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 21:28:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To be honest, you'd probably get a similar reaction from me. I've never even heard of a VHS man before this. I must be too young. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 20:39:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a pair. Can't have one without t'other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 19:15:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! I've just finished writing the statement so now I'm just filling in all the nitty gritty parts on the form. I'm quite excited at the idea of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 18:59:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fancy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 18:58:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When it doesn't taste like you're doing anything wrong, that's when you get into trouble! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 18:57:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please video it. Cats in harnesses is so awkward and cute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 18:56:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ouch! I hope you're icing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 18:55:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Currently doing a job application which I've been putting off for about a week but it closes Monday morning so I want to get it done today so I didn't quite submit it last minute. :) I'm feeling a little spurred on by an email from my work which says they're currently undecided about extending furlough past the end of July but says they're not opening the office until at least the end of September. Those two unaccounted for months are a little terrifying. :) The fact that it's Saturday night has really no impact on me at the moment! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 18:16:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It looks like it will fall over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 18:16:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not sure. A broker would be able to tell you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 17:08:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great insightful comment! Have a !thanks even though I'm not OP. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 16:57:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're not wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 16:31:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The higher ones are for higher income. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 15:38:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do prefer this to the actual design.

However, they're both ugly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 15:36:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> PS5 can go horizontal. It looks dumb as fuck in horizontal but it's possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 14:52:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This isn't really possible right now but you can always book a driving instructor for refresher lessons. I didn't drive since the day I passed my test, then I had to get a car about 7 years later so I had a couple of hours in a car with one just to feel more confident.
If you don't end up driving this time around, it's something to consider. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 14:15:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're such a dog lesbian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 04:20:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine taps me if she just wants attention. It's so cute that I have to give her scritchies! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 04:19:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're not supposed to have favourites but I definitely do... I had him less than two years though. 😭 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 04:18:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> P sure he's just old and saggy. You don't notice it on most cats because they have fur. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 21:34:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should be able to tell by pressing a button on your meter. It should cycle between two kW readings, the smaller one being the night one. As for the timing, that can vary. I emailed my provider (Bulb) and they answered me pretty quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 20:56:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use a 2014 mini for Plex with Sonarr and Radarr too. All my files are stored on a USB HDD and I have a 4k TV connected as the display. I run the Plex player from it too, but I occasionally watch Plex from an iPhone too. It works fine for this and web browsing/YouTube. It takes a little while to start up fully from completely off but can be kept in sleep mode if that's a concern.

I have run The Sims on it and it looks decent but I couldn't tell you about any other games as I am a filthy console peasant. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 20:45:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually run it on my Mac mini media computer. Someone converted it from Apple TV apparently, and it does give me the option to choose! I guess that's not much help to you though, sorry. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 17:48:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aerial screensaver? That scene was just on my screen a few minutes ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 17:06:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you have an economy 7 tariff? You should make sure the timer is set for the cheap hours. I don't know how long my tank takes to heat up unfortunately but I put it on at 04:30 when my electricity tariff increases at 06:30, just to be on the safe side. I believe it automatically stops when it reaches the correct temperature.
I have showered almost 24 hours later at around 4am and the water was still hot, but YMMV with a different tank.
Mine was new about a year and a half ago but before I moved in so I didn't choose/install it.
Perhaps you could find some more information in the manual if you have it, or online somewhere? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 15:04:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't believe you've done this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 12:23:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy cables! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 00:35:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's all vegetarian too, isn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 00:06:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You could put a paper collar on him to see if he's got another family on the side. I'm sure Google will turn up good ways to make one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 23:55:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I actually looked into getting one but it's too expensive for one game and there weren't really any others that piqued my interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 23:51:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I enjoyed Lost Legacy. I don't see a problem with something in the same universe but different protagonists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 23:51:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah but it was intended as just a DLC to begin with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 23:45:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Idk I'm probably not going to buy it for a while. Would be happy to get a slim version for like £300 in a couple of years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 23:42:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, do people never wash their hands? Is that why we're in this situation right now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 23:42:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was shown horizontally. Google it and you'll see pics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 23:39:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It can probably go horizontally. They always show consoles standing up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 20:47:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think my nearest Walmart is a few thousand miles away but thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 20:37:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Contact your bank and do a chargeback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 20:37:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 20:24:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah didn't they say the series was definitively over? I would love a new game in the series but I'm not holding out hope. If they do a new one, Nathan Drake won't be the protagonist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 19:05:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What time? And where should we be following? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 18:44:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only thing I'd seen before is that tweet saying she stood with that FART. Which was enough for me to label her one too, but now she's said more explicitly bad stuff. Jammie Dodger on YouTube just commented on it too saying the first tweet, you can give her the benefit of the doubt of just being a confused old woman who doesn't really understand the issue at hand, but these new comments really cement that JK Rowling is a FART. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 18:40:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's gotta be on purpose so the average person casually reading it is like "yeah that makes sense" without realising what it actually means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 18:34:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You know it's not as simple as that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 18:25:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't think of a better piece of home decor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 14:48:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should look into your rights around the deposit. If they haven't put it into a proper deposit account, you may be able to chase them for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 14:43:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like you could probably move the majority of it yourself and then hire one or two people to move the furniture. Like Taskrabbit or someone from a local Facebook page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 14:23:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My eco program is 3 hours but it's a massive 9kg machine. There's a half hour program but you can't do a full load with it. It doesn't really bother me because you just set it and leave it. In the before times, I would often set it so that it would finish right around the time I got home from work. Sometimes I run it at night for the half price electricity. Why am I having another conversation about laundry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 14:13:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds very strange! I don't like espresso though. My mum sent me some sleeping tablets which arrived today so I'll try those! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 05:49:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you namedrop the brand though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 05:49:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who is that guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 05:45:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Buy an alarm clock and keep your phone downstairs or in another room overnight! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 05:40:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They also need regulations on parking spaces. You can't sell estates full of 4 bed houses with one driveway and then make the roads so narrow that you have to park up on the pavements on both sides. It's not uncommon for a 4 bed house to have 4+ cars, especially when these housing estates are built in the middle of nowhere with no public transport. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 05:36:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please clean your kitchen. 🤢

Good news though, kitchen taps are pretty easy to replace. Just look it up on YouTube and it'll take 5 minutes to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 05:26:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But I want to be # TeamSleepThroughTheNight :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 05:25:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's actually technical differences between a couch, sofa, and settee and they have different origins. Why they've settled on a different one, I don't know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 05:19:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy trinity:

Crystal Maze

Gladiators.

Catchphrase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 05:18:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I *loved* Catchphrase as a kid. I think I just liked Mr Chips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 05:13:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or he could have *gone to the fucking door.* If you can't take the totes up, go to the door and tell them that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 05:07:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oof. I'm surprised you're managing to do it with a kid in the house! It's just me at home so no one to keep me on track. Hope you sleep soon. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 05:03:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who do they think created the vagina then? Surely god isn't offended at its existence if he divinely created it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 05:01:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It got later and later for me and I was falling asleep around 6am mostly. So sleeping until 2-4pm meant I haven't been tired but it's no way to live! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 04:56:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the worst. That's been me most nights lately.

I'm gonna try and go back to sleep in a bit and wake up at like 9ish. Don't wanna keep sleeping in until 4pm.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 04:54:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why were these characters everywhere? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 04:50:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or Dot Cotton sitting in an ugly armchair with a cigarette. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 04:49:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or Peggy saying "gerroutta my pub!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 04:48:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair dos! I don't exactly need voice control for my robot vacuum cleaner either but I have it. :D

The linking the washing and drying cycle sounds like a useful feature. I wanted one of the machines that has the little hatch to add more midway through the cycle but couldn't bring myself to spend money on luxury features. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 04:45:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you do the car about to run Tiffany over on Christmas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 04:40:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought I'd fixed my sleep pattern. Last night I went to bed at around 12.30 and got up at 8.30. Tonight, I got tired and went to bed around midnight and actually fell asleep, but woke up at 2am and I'm still awake. -_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 04:30:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just curious, what are your use cases for wanting to control laundry by voice? If I'm putting laundry in the machine, I might as well press the buttons while I'm in front of the machine. And I can use the timer if I want to put it on for later. So I guess I just can't imagine the reason for it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 04:19:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never thought of using a holder to position it like that! It's a good idea. I sleep on my front and side a lot though, so it's no good for that. I've actually got smart lights which flash with alarms but I've slept through those even though the whole bedroom is flashing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 04:16:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's not happened to me in a video game. But a few weeks ago, I was playing Uncharted and a couple of times, a character goes "did you hear that???" and I'm like no!!! Wtf was it??? Most of the time, sounds that are important are subtitled and Uncharted was generally good at it but it slipped through a couple of times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 03:54:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Possibly there was a censored version but they didn't bother to change the subtitles for the uncensored one. I've had it the other way around too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 03:50:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hearing aids are effectively amplifying sound. So if he has 0% in one ear, 100x0 is still 0%.

Really, deafness is measured in decibels and what's what you should be using. I've no idea what 20% means. Maybe it's a standard thing in whatever country you live in but it's not in the country I live in!

Anyway, if the ear can't hear sound, no level of amplification is going to magic up sound. What may work for him is a cochlear implant, which is a device that bypasses the outer ear. This is not an easy option. It's a surgical option that requires a lot of work post surgery and is never as effective as natural hearing, especially if someone has been deaf from birth and never learned to hear.

There are plenty of legitimate reasons for not wanting a cochlear implant and it may be out of choice rather than financial pressure or other external influences. Maybe he's considered it, maybe he hasn't.

Is he part of the deaf community and does he sign? If he signs and you don't, the best thing I can recommend is for you to learn to sign.

Also, "hearing impaired" is a term that doesn't go down well. Better terms are deaf or hard of hearing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 03:25:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldn't use "really". I would just sign "miss you" with the appropriate NMF.

I'm assuming you're not officially teaching BSL or are a native signer yourself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-11 03:02:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can never decide if red or purple is best so I go yellow > green > orange > purple/red/purple/red/purple/red. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 21:48:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can mute them so they don't show up on your feed if you don't want to completely unfollow. Remember that social media is a highlight reel and doesn't reflect reality! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 21:21:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you say it in a situation where you're passing or immediately leaving, I can't see how it can be construed as anything other than a genuine compliment. If you say it and then stick around waiting for a response, or you're in a confined space with them with no escape, that's a different thing as then it could be understood as you trying to start a conversation/hitting on. I think a lot of women get disingenuous and unsolicited conversation openers from men so if you're aware of that and take care to do it in the right situations, I think it would be more appreciated.

^(I once got on the wrong bus for one stop and waited for mine at the next stop to get away from a guy who opened by asking for the time and then saying I had nice eyes.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 21:07:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I couldn't tell you! I was looking in the UK. It was also hard to find any reviews or hands on experience. I found some in German! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 21:00:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ever heard of actinium, americium, barium, berkelium, beryllium, bohrium, cadmium, calcium, californium, cerium, cesium, chromium, copernicium, curium, curium, darmstadtium, dubnium, dysprosium, einsteinium, erbium, europium, fermium, flerovium, francium, gadolinium, gallium, germanium, hafnium, hassium, helium, holmium, indium, iridium, lawrencium, lithium, livermorium, lutetium, magnesium, moscovium, meitnerium, mendelevium, neilsborium, neodymium, neptunium, nihonium, niobium, nobelium, osmium, palladium, plutonium, polonium, potassium, praseodymium, promethium, protactinium, radium, rhenium, rhodium, roentgenium, rubidium, ruthenium, rutherfordium, samarium, scandium, seaborgium, selenium, sodium, strontium, technetium, tellurium, terbium, thallium, thorium, thulium, titanium, uranium, vanadium, ytterbium, yttrium, or zirconium? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 19:46:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I bought some Aurelles and an Adore for my ceilings and there were hardly anywhere selling them! Most of the places that did were small or foreign online shops. I found the best price on Coolshop which looks dodgy but is actually ok! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 17:39:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *shudder* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 16:54:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Greed ruined it, basically. It should have been kept as the one season that it was written as but money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 16:50:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We believe in you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 16:31:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Generic white dude pop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 11:25:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fair dos! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 09:38:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it Lex? Everyone knows messages on Lex are buggy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 09:36:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm pretty sure I saw a post within the last week saying the Tradfri works on Hue. I believe it wasn't possible on old firmware but it shouldn't be a problem with any purchased now. But I'm not 100% on it as it's not something I've personally used. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 01:26:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm as atheist as they come but I'm all about Christmas and Easter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 22:52:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Two TVs! Extravagance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 22:09:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably he likes it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 20:03:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely gradually, even if you do things like 3D planning. I had some 3D plans of my flat but things felt different once I was actually inside! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 19:59:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why not both? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 19:37:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Both the mirror and the TV got bigger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 18:57:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't touch it then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 17:49:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you don't care about dimming, perhaps a smart plug will do the job? Hue make one but you can use other Zigbee ones on the Hue hub such as Innr ~~or Tradfri.~~ ^(idk check Tradfri from somewhere else, I've only used Innr) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 16:46:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This event probably had a big impact on him and something he probably thinks about a lot. I wouldn't jump to the conclusion that it's about a relationship. I don't see the harm in going for lunch one day (except for the Coronavirus thing) as long as you're sensible about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 15:38:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I definitely noticed those candlesticks. I did wonder if they'd say anything about them. 😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 15:19:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't keep much more than I am currently using. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 15:15:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Getting dressed to go out soon. I think you've inspired me to wear these today! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 15:12:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You'll find your Elena one day. Don't worry about all the Chloes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 15:02:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every time I see these, I get bummed that I didn't buy them. Pink laces look great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 14:53:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about hetero couples doing hardcore kink stuff? Does she imagine that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 14:17:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only good but is a butt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 14:06:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've tried other types and Hue has won for me in reliability and integration. It's a bit more expensive upfront but it's good value. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 06:54:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 👀 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 06:37:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YAS QUEEN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 06:35:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At that point, you might as well just stay up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 06:02:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> GET

IT

GIRL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 03:38:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am an accidental landlord letting out my last house. I basically don't expect to break even for about 5 years. With all the hassle of renting it out, I don't recommend it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 23:25:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This post was literally the first time I saw it clarified! And I saw it 4 days late too. I was trying not to think about it too much as I'm still on furlough anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 23:22:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which has been super unclear in all previous statements! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 22:24:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've always hated hedges that extend past the wall or fence. The wall is where your property ends, bitch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 21:25:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're cute. You're already on a picnic with a cute girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 20:56:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the worst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 20:37:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's literally next to the ceiling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 20:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/TVtoohigh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 20:19:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I don't think they could make that movie today. But because it's old, people view it with nostalgia. I watched it for the first time last year and was horrified. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 20:12:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't see any posts in your history so I've no idea what's going on :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 20:09:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that uncommon for people outside of the UK? I don't think anything of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 19:57:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> /r/TwoRedditorsOneFedExTruck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 19:40:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very little, actually. I kept checking it but it was fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 12:28:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're obsessed, dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 11:52:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a freezer block, not ice. No water to melt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 08:20:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, thank God. 2020 is almost over. That went by unexpectedly fast in the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 08:19:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Little Mr Perfect Face! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 08:14:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was playing Uncharted Lost Legacy on one of the really hot days recently. I was on the train bit when it started stuttering. This never happens to me, so I checked the console and it was super hot. Got a freezer block out of the freezer and put it on top of the console and I was good to go. It didn't need a rest, just some refreshment. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 08:11:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oops. Close enough? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 05:22:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a weekly evening course in Peterborough and it was the year Pokémon Go was big. I'd often go up a few hours before my class and play the game because the small town I lived in sucked for it. I got to explore quite a few different parts of Peterborough. I can honestly say it's a whelming place. It's not anything enough to be overwhelmed or underwhelmed. Just whelmed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 03:25:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Make sure to show them Ashes To Ashes too! We love a bit of Keeley Hawes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 03:05:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 02:34:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Perfect for lockdown! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 02:29:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not about home organisation, but Queer Eye is about life organisation. It's people getting their shit together with the help of a professional, just like Tidying Up. Maybe it'll scratch your itch, and a new season just dropped too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 01:58:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly surprised that people don't recognise Kardashians, even if they couldn't name an individual one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 01:56:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's my favourite kind of fit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 01:46:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a key reason this question shouldn't come up so much. The name is clear on the website when you buy it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 01:12:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Philips Hue Play *HDMI Sync* Box only syncs HDMI input. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 00:22:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not implied but outright stated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 00:19:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> With two daughters and a son too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 23:57:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree that it wasn't a good juxtaposition. I think they're just trying to show that people from all walks of life can be in need of help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 23:44:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's some pro level Facebook stalking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 23:43:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If it uses the space well, it's just as good. Plus it'll be easier to park! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 23:37:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *yeet* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 23:36:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What, you're saying $500 jeans are not perfect for dog grooming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 23:28:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I find those boutique stores to be a bit... intimidating? That sounds a bit odd but it's definitely different to shop in one of those if your body type falls out of the acceptable norm. It's like in an earlier season where they took the hero to Target. It's showing them that they can dress stylishly within their normal budget in a regular store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 23:19:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At first glance, I thought it was a political tee too but I remembered he has worn The National band tees before. Would be clearer if it weren't all caps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 23:15:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well it's not like we can go and ask the author. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 23:05:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know enough about watches to say what it is but from memory of the glimpses, it looked like a chronograph watch. For the strap, you can find one similar by searching "rainbow NATO strap". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 22:58:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A search for "rainbow NATO strap" will bring up a lot of options. Although I think this one is not a NATO as it doesn't seem to go underneath the watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 22:55:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [It’s from the ACLU. ](https://shop.aclu.org/trans-people-belong-tee-navy/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 22:53:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I found it to be much more of a Jewish movie than a WLW movie. Like, the WLW is the catalyst for the events in the movie but from then on, it is really just about the reaction of the community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 22:48:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What I've heard from people is that they're separating the art from the artist. I know Harry Potter has a worldwide reach but here in Britain, it's part of the fabric of so many people's childhoods. I think it's harder for people to completely cut out Harry Potter because it was such a massive thing, whereas for me and many others, cutting out, for example, Lostprophets was a lot easier as it didn't have anywhere near the same reach. Harry Potter is books, films, merchandise, theatre, clothes, fanfic, home decor, tattoos, children's names, spoofs, video games, studio tours, fuck knows what else. The majority of fans won't even follow closely enough to know that she's said all this stuff. It's going to be hard for her to be truly cancelled. Meanwhile, she's going to sit on her giant pile of money and not give a fuck.

Luckily for me, I never liked Harry Potter so I can continue to not support JK Rowling. I don't know how I'd feel if a franchise I love turned out to be created by an awful person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 22:16:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unfortunately, Harry Potter is still beloved by too many people for JK to be truly cancelled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 22:15:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good. Fuck her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 21:37:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Quick, get those monkeys some typewriters! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 21:37:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually kinda want a print of this for my wall now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 21:27:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As long as I'm in first class and not a tailie, it shouldn't be too bad. No worse than lockdown is right now anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 20:24:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3 rows would look better. 3 is a magic number. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 20:21:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love those yellow shelves! There's a lot of cool pieces in here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 18:57:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I felt that way when I went for a walk in a local park and saw massive groups of people and people using the playground equipment that had been taped off. It feels like a waste to stay at home alone for months on end when they're out gallivanting and flouting the rules with incorrectly worn masks. In the end, you can only trust that the majority of people are taking it as seriously as you and staying home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 17:57:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That was my first thought. If they're on a low income, they should check entitledto.com and make sure they're claiming everything they're eligible for, and hopefully that will allow them to open a Help To Save. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 17:11:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know you can get a 2 bed house in Biggleswade for around £200,000-230,000. Trains are about 30-45 minutes to Kings Cross. I personally prefer to live somewhere smaller in London and have a more reliable commute but it depends how much you're willing to put up with trains. It wasn't worth it for me.

My advice would be to figure out how far you'd be willing to walk to a station 5-7 days a week. Pick a station on a tube line or a train line and select your radius. Anything in your budget? If no, move to the next station out. Once you find something that you can afford, then research the area. Maybe it's cheap because it's rough AF, or maybe it's just cheap because it's really far out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I live in a flat. Is there any way I can integrate my entry buzzer with my smart home? [UK] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-26 21:10:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a simple [buzzer](https://i.imgur.com/rRjZFQw.jpg) on the wall that has a button to open the main door and a handset to speak to. The handset doesn't work but that's neither here nor there as I don't really need it. The button outside is part of a panel so I can't modify this or put my own kind of doorbell or anything outside. [This is the inside of the buzzer.](https://i.imgur.com/LyePa7U.jpg)

I am deaf and I can't hear the buzzer when I don't have my hearing aids in, which results in missing deliveries. The council are supposed to visit to help me with a flashing alerter for it but this has been delayed due to the Coronavirus. Obviously this will just be a dumb flasher and no smart features. I'd love something that can flash my Hue lights. I also use Amazon Echos including a Show but I don't see how they could be of use in this circumstance.

Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I live in a flat. Is there any way I can integrate my entry buzzer with my smart home? [UK] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-26 02:50:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a simple [buzzer](https://i.imgur.com/rRjZFQw.jpg) on the wall that has a button to open the main door and a handset to speak to. The handset doesn't work but that's neither here nor there as I don't really need it. The button outside is part of a panel so I can't modify this or put my own kind of doorbell or anything outside.

I am deaf and I can't hear the buzzer when I don't have my hearing aids in, which results in missing deliveries. The council are supposed to visit to help me with a flashing alerter for it but this has been delayed due to the Coronavirus. Obviously this will just be a dumb flasher and no smart features. I'd love something that can flash my Hue lights. I also use Amazon Echos including a Show but I don't see how they could be of use in this circumstance.

Any ideas?

Edit: [Just took the cover off and this is the inside.](https://i.imgur.com/LyePa7U.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I'm playing Uncharted Lost Legacy and it's really refreshing to play a game with two female protagonists who are strong and clever and not dependent on any men </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 02:53:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're also not in competition with each other and work well together. (I'm hoping that doesn't change and I'm only halfway through the game so no spoilers please!)

Off the top of my head, the only other game I can think of where it's just a strong woman lead is Tomb Raider. I actually really suck at Tomb Raider for some reason but that's another topic.

Then there are the games that let you pick from various characters like Pokémon or GTA Online or whatever, but they don't really count as it's a player choice and it doesn't make any difference.

It's just really nice to see strong female characters with no emphasis on "oh look how brave she is *for a woman*." They're just characters who happen to be women.

It's something I didn't realise I needed until I played this.

Please share other games with female protagonists! I'd love to play some more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I repotted this spiky boy. What else should I be doing to keep him healthy? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 20:47:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One pink jellybean poking out! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 03:12:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How do dress at the age you are now, compared to how you thought you'd dress at this age 5, 10, 15 years ago? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 13:42:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm about to hit 30 so naturally I am thinking about various things. One of them is how I thought by 30, I'd be more grown up and I wouldn't be wearing trainers like Jordans anymore. However, I'm definitely still rocking the Jordans.

I do have a more refined style overall and I do dress a little less casually than I used to, but I'm not quite the formally dressed adult I thought I'd be.

What will I dress like in another ten years time? Will the Jordans have finally gone? Will I stop wearing denim every day of the week? I hope not.

Have your perceptions of future you ended up being what you thought they'd be or not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bitch, I'm fabulous. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-21 13:38:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Konmari'd my toolbox. It sparks more joy now! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 13:38:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tommy has mastered the curled feetsies. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-23 13:05:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I never thought I'd get so much joy from folded clothes. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-13 20:13:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is you doing? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-12 12:58:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Paddy was definitely helping. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-06 17:23:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Just brought this boy home. Open to name suggestions. :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-25 13:58:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A little mrow as I came over to say hi. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-19 14:17:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I haven't had time to properly do the process on my whole wardrobe but just starting a few drawers has helped me feel more optimistic about the whole thing. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-17 17:50:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I just did a trip with my smallest bag ever. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-03 18:32:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a big onebagging fan but I had typically travelled with a more generous backpack, up to cabin bag size.

This time, Ryanair forced my hand a little as I didn't realise it was such a small bag allowance until I'd already spent ages deciding on a flight. I couldn't be bothered to look for another one and I didn't want to pay to upgrade, so fuck it, tiny bag it is!

For my 5 day trip, I used just a Kanken backpack, which is just slightly under the Ryanair size. Between that and my coat pocket, there's nothing I needed that I couldn't carry, and it's been great to shove it in any little space available. I found that my packing cubes were perfectly sized too, which has been super useful.

I will be forever impacted by the ease of moving about this week and will think twice before packing a larger bag! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
