<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject7</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 01:42:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >I am usually joined by a cat.

Heaven! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 23:45:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah that's what this looks like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 21:25:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 20:41:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is your profession? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 15:56:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >Especially since communism is a STATELESS society. Meaning that nobody is in charge.

That would be anarcho-communism. Communism is the economic model and anarchy the political model. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 14:48:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds more like Fall Out Boy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 14:38:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They can be both. Communism refers to the control and distribution of resources where as theocracy refers to who is in charge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 14:33:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm curious, do the Amish vote? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 18:27:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://youtu.be/Su9bxtBh3ug at 0:24 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 15:07:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depending on the cause of your depression, you could try l-tryptophan. It's supposed to help get up your serotonin levels (that actually can be depleted from taking SSRIs). I weaned myself off Celexa earlier this year and started supplementing with l-tryptophan and I think it has helped.

5-htp is also an option and also helps get up serotonin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 14:26:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> u/Linguistin229,

"I've said this to you before and I know it makes you uncomfortable, but you're thoughtful, and you're brilliant, and your ambiguous ethnic blend perfectly represents the dream of the American melting pot." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 17:57:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >I hope she levels herself up and people forget who he is again.

Well the good news is I already don't know who he is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 13:56:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are...are we the oldies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 01:59:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you do for work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 05:03:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ...not even close! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 02:27:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wth I just watched this video and saw that comment and this was the first reddit post on my feed 😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 22:14:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congratulations! I hope to do the same someday with Spain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 18:17:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you're from Puerto Rico you can apply for Spanish citizenship after two years of residency (I heard it actually might take longer but you could look into it).

After you get citizenship in Spain then you can legally reside anywhere in the EU afaik. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 16:09:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> May as well carry a purse! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 16:04:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cyan's got the gift </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 00:30:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They could conceive of pocket phones but not silent mode lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 22:32:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This sounds like when the Church accused people of being witches for their knowledge of how things work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 21:42:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or the Saperstein's lawyer brought it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 18:31:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, and I had one the was just a red afro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 00:17:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >as an Argentine you get residency in only two years

I believe it's that you can apply for citizenship after only two years of residency, as opposed to ten years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 02:44:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes it happened to me too! I think it was happening to the other players in my game too it was really weird </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 23:15:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm already out after the first line </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 16:49:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's like they want to have curvy or plus sized models without actually having clothes that fit them lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 15:31:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think for women starting out or who are more casual in strength training, they might do more knee push-ups. Sometimes I do knee push-ups if I want to do more reps. For regular (like with arms pretty close but not super narrow) I can only do three decent ones, but I stick to these because I want to get stronger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 14:46:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sometimes I'm just having an off day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 17:42:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I did find it strange that people out Always. Like that's not possible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 15:15:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not sure about this, but you can see if you can get switched to contractor status at your job and get a self-employed visa. You would have to file taxes separately of course, both for US and Spain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 01:53:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. And he seems really immature for a 28-year-old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 20:18:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah saw him vent earlier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 17:43:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty cool! And it looks really cute. I don't think I've ever seen that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 17:10:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >I just don't jive with the American lifestyle and culture

What is different about Europe that made you thrive there vs the US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 16:32:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >remote working but living in Europe

I want to do this in Spain, but it seems like it might be discouraged? I've heard people get rejected for visas if they are planning to do this

>it’s going to polarize economically even more over the next decade

What do you mean? I do see this happening right now but am curious to hear your thoughts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 15:20:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's what I've heard. Though I guess it could be subjective </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 03:25:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are there houses on the bridge? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 02:36:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lmao this lady is still going? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 00:10:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah. There was a movie, Emma Stone played Billie Jean King. Steve Carrell played the male opponent but I'm blanking on his name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 00:05:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Istanbul is Constantinople! 😭 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 23:34:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why did you choose to move to the Czech Republic? I've always thought it looks nice but unfortunately haven't got to visit yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 22:14:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I'm looking to get into computational linguistics so am planning on going back to school for my masters in Barcelona. I think there will be good job opportunities there too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 20:40:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It would be interesting to see a list of all the extra things one pays for in the US compared to EU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 20:34:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I also work in cybersecurity! Are you planning to stay in the field? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 16:23:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand the salaries are a lot lower in Europe. Do you feel that the quality of life makes up for that? Do you still feel financially stable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 16:19:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I did read somewhere else that you are not supposed to work remotely on that visa, though have also heard some people have done it. I guess it doesn't seem like a good bet at the moment.

 I did also read that there isn't anything in the law that forbids it so it may just be up to your local consulate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 16:15:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I need to ride this train </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 15:22:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The one good thing is that at least the network subscriptions are only like $5 per month </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 04:12:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You know, I keep having dreams where I meet a nice French man. Maybe it's a sign... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 02:48:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True. In that case they would both be sus if you know they were all three together </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 23:34:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw I love Charlie! He's kind of a dope but he means well. And he just has a different perspective of things as a nonhuman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 22:12:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Voted 👍 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 19:11:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You would really need three people to be together because like in this instance you could end up with two imposters together </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 19:09:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is metagaming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 15:36:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah it seemed very real, not like the more "polished" New York you see in a lot of movies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 15:35:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. I think 90% of the movie was Adam Sandler yelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 15:28:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This explains the issue really well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 15:26:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did see some stats on a reddit post about this yesterday, it seems to be true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 15:25:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >But, it is hopeful to remember that the longterm trend is toward greater equality and a better society. The current situation is a backlash

Yeah I was thinking this. Even though we have more rights now, the societal thought hasn't caught up yet. Once it's ingrained that women are equal these issues should not be as much of a problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 15:03:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well at least you can still get permanent residency after five years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 02:34:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >The Best Flavor of Gatorade

🙌 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 01:16:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow that's really messed up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 00:43:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Food truck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 23:41:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want this but I'd be scared that I'd accidentally throw it away when I think it's an old avocado I forgot about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 23:25:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you pay a lot in fees to transfer the money to your Spanish bank account?

>I have friends who didn't transfer money each month and now they are scrambling to figure out what to do for their visa renewals.

So were they just using their debit cards from their home countries? Don't you get charged a percentage of each transaction then? Seems like that would add up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 23:20:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yeah I think even if you are working remotely it's expected you keep it all above board and file taxes in both places.

I can see how some people might not know or even try to circumvent it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 22:34:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've read a lot of comments about people getting the nonlucrative visa and working remotely. Why is it a gray area? Is that not the visa that you have? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 19:45:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's good to know! It's seems like maybe it's only an issue if you would have something so delinquent it shows up in background check (or tax return somehow?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 19:35:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah plus it makes them seem boring, like my appearance is nice but it's literally the most uninteresting thing about me to talk about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 18:55:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah it makes me uncomfortable, but I can't quite articulate why </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 17:34:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An oldie but goodie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 17:29:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tenzin has the best mustache </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can a nonlucrative visa to Spain be denied if you have outstanding loans in the US? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 15:47:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Asking as a US citizen looking to reside to Spain while working remotely.

One of the Spanish consulates website mentions this as one of the requirements

>11. Copy of most recent Tax Return. Residency applicants cannot have/leave loans or mortgages in the United States when applying for residency in spain.

Has anyone had any experience with this? Does this include all loans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 14:52:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I need to see it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Discussion] Can a nonlucrative visa to Spain be denied if you have outstanding loans in the US? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 14:08:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 02:29:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've gotten a few things from Frank and Oak, which is online (they have a subscription service but you don't have to make them automatic) and I feel like the clothes fit really well and are made of nice material. Definitely recommend trying them out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 21:40:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I heard you can get a "Certificate of Puerto Rican Citizenship", and that way qualify for the expedited naturalization in Spain. But not sure cause I haven't seen it always mentioned when the other Ibero-American countries are listed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 16:31:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What part of Spain are you in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 16:27:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What part of Spain were you in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 15:50:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What country are you in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 15:48:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >That said, my mental health always improved while living outside the USA

That's interesting. What do you think caused it to improve? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 04:37:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can also try 'dopes' lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 04:30:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sept 2022 is pretty far out, why do you have that date set? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 03:08:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like to call them fools </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 03:07:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apparition association </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 03:05:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah and float through walls so you can get around faster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 02:28:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I wanna start that myself. My skin has been atrocious lately </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 02:26:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you want to try it, start with a very low dose! I've tried it before and even just 1g made me feel like my skin was crawling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 21:51:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is a two-stall system? And why do they think American showers don't get you clean enough? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 19:26:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Czech Republic is so pretty, I'm so fascinated by it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 03:14:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Expat can't mean someone who's moved permanently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 02:32:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you done remote work while in Spain? How did you find a company? Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 21:21:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He has a perfect cat face </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 17:53:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah like the other impostor will be on a killing spree and get voted off, then I just kill one person and the game is won lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 15:28:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a job pretty close to that, working in the office of a parking authority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 05:48:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where is your god now?!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 05:39:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nom Nom would definitely snitch on the other impostor lol

Who is Hector? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 05:34:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right? Like where do I get assessed? I assume there's some certification I have to get, and then provide that to all potential suitors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 04:11:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love this so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 03:39:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is hilarious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 03:36:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Is that a pig or a cow?"

"Yes" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 02:55:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 00:18:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes omg I did so much research of salons to find some that did the hard gel extensions. I've found two here only and I live in NYC! There might be more though idk.

It's annoying though but you would think that nail techs as professionals would actually know about hard gel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 00:04:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think OP is looking for hard gel extensions. It's a fake nail that is built onto the natural nail with hard gel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 23:58:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can get hard gel extensions. You have to seek out a salon that had this because not all do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 23:56:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But hard gel extensions exist, that have nothing of acrylic in it. What is gel acrylic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 22:15:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well if she wants the hard gel extensions, she might have to explicitly say gel extension.

Gel manicure is just getting gel polish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 22:13:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah that's sus that they used acrylic but said it was gel. Like they're either horribly misinformed or they are being deliberately deceptive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 21:47:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also my Puerto Rican cousin and his brother who believe in like every conspiracy theory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 14:44:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I went to college in Bethlehem! I love the Lehigh Valley. I'm from Reading in Berks county </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 05:49:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's used in southeast Pennsylvania </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 21:47:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg wtf, that's a death sentence for the woman! The pregnancy isn't even viable like wtaf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 16:16:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do they say she's 'out there'? She seems pretty reasonable and level-headed to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 16:11:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The sugar packet is not like other girls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 16:09:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She's *really* not like other girls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 14:48:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's true! We see that Ben falls for her here but it's also meant to show the audience "This is Leslie Knope!". Tom being totally unfazed by it really shows that too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 14:40:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww yeah I just saw this episode and thought the same!

It's funny too that she's also a complete mess the majority of the time cause she was sick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 14:38:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >As the decades have passed, it seems to be getting harder for women, not easier.

Yeah we're expected now to have jobs but also still do all of the household labor and even emotional labor. And if something is amiss in the house it's the woman's fault.

Expectations for an individual woman's aspirations have gone up, but expectations haven't gone down for the domestic sphere in proportion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 04:58:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Finally a rose the Queen will be pleased with </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 03:39:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What kind of psychopath... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 03:08:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nakey kitties </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 20:35:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kitties love fresh sheets the most! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 14:31:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We need to know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 23:43:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe multiphilia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 19:35:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah UPF is even expensive by EU standards, but it's like 6k for me, a non-EU person, and it's still way less than anything in the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 18:53:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I'm mostly considering Computational linguistics so it limits my options a bit. Universitat de Pompeu Fabra has it though.

Part of what got me thinking about the EU was cost, and 20k GBP would be way too much! For that much I would probably stay in NYC! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 17:01:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you doing linguistics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 16:22:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm going to apply to linguistics programs in Spain. Leaning towards Barcelona </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 16:21:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 15:58:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >bonus point if you learn Spanish.

What about Catalan? Do you use it a lot over there, or do you stick to speaking Spanish? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 15:54:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How much Catalan do you use? I am trying to learn Catalan right now (I already speak Spanish) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 15:44:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RSU is restricted stock units, so he gets some equity in the company! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 15:09:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you vouch for the Wolfram one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 15:08:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah and the salary is really good for Spain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 14:45:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is the L1 what is always given as a work visa? I had thought it was the H1-B.

I looked them up and L1 is Intra-company transfer and H1-B is temporary worker. So if you have an L1 is it difficult to get another visa type? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 14:39:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you guys have good testing in place? That really makes a difference too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 00:56:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The name New Zealand comes from the Dutch province Zeeland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 15:13:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think coño is literally cunt. Or very close anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 14:55:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's the mentality in Germany? Are they just not as concerned about social status? It seems that Germans are more realists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 01:24:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you hate about the US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 01:23:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >a big difference in the amount of misogyny I faced as a young woman vs in the USA.

Do you mean you found more misogyny in France? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 01:14:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you mean by that? Where did you move from and to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 19:18:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It kinda looks like the Catalan independence flag too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 17:40:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah he basically admitted he's trash and no self-respecting woman should date him! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 16:45:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least Naga had a friend in Pabu, so she wasn't alone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 05:42:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ^^*Puerto ^^Rico </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 03:48:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Both Pennsylvania German and Pennsylvania Dutch are correct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 02:46:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *Pennsilfaanisch Deitsch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 00:13:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well Afrikaans is based on Dutch (from the Netherlands) whereas Pennsylvania German is a dialect from the Palatinate region of Germany </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 23:50:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm planning to get my masters in Spain and work there afterwards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 21:26:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Speaking of being a basic bitch...I need that skirt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 20:57:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm in love 😍 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 20:48:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your autumn mood looks deadly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 17:29:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How are wages compared to the US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 17:14:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that specifically for Germany only or an EU thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 16:43:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where in Spain do you live?  And what are your expenses like? I understand that things are generally cheaper at least but doesn't totally make up for the wage difference compared to the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 16:39:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you able to get a visa if you are doing freelance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 15:52:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah he probably got with her cause she was "young and fun" and then life got too serious so he was trying to get the fun back with an open marriage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 03:10:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is your school there in French or the Basque language? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 20:15:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I imagine smooth jazz more as the background music to New York City </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 05:17:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gotta let the haters know he still sees them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 21:57:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah this happens with Catalan as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 21:27:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's no boarding time on that one. Though I guess it's usually just 30 min prior to departure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 20:39:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do you like it there compared to back home? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 19:04:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What country did you go to? I am thinking of doing the same (except I do speak the language for the most part) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 19:02:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How did you get a handle on your ADHD? I have it as well and it's really affected my work life. I really want to go back to grad school, and feel that I am getting better about it, probably more focused than I was in my early 20s, but sometimes I feel like I am going backwards and my mind is all over the place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 18:54:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you talk with a career counselor? Where did you find them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 16:25:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why did you choose Hungary? And how well do you know the language and where did you learn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 16:17:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh right. I knew I remembered her getting sick from something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 15:54:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She only wanted some of them gone! Not all of them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 15:33:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "... Councilman Howser" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 15:27:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Like that lady who at one part comes to talk to Ron ~~about the sandwich in the park.~~ And he's at his circular desk and just keeps spinning away from her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 15:23:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the part in that where somebody says there's cops outside and they both get scared and immediately leave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 15:13:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And that's the Word with Perd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 01:37:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well Galician-Portuguese was one language for a while </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 01:12:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not about proper vs improper, it's just a less common way of speaking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 17:23:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are pine trees in Puerto Rico! But I've only seen them very high up in the mountains. Also my uncle told me that somebody had brought the seeds from elsewhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 17:17:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She lives in Pennsylvania. My dad's family is Pennsylvania Dutch so I know some of her English was probably affected by that accent/way of speaking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 14:59:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >they overuse do support when they start

That's interesting, I wonder why that is the case. Maybe it's that they are getting use to this new verb form when first learning it and overuse it til they learn that it's not actually that common. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 14:29:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you noticed non-native speakers using 'do' and 'did' more? Native speakers seem to use it more for emphasis, but my mother, who is a non-native speaker, seems to use it just regularly when speaking English. I think I've noticed it in other non-native speakers as well.

My mom's native language is Spanish and I don't really see an equivalent in Spanish. Except maybe the present perfect, which she doesn't even use that much in Spanish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 14:18:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait til he hears about French numbers above 69 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 20:32:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's not even answering the question. Innocence is not something he has in common with an 18yo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 17:53:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same why did we think that 😅🤦 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 17:41:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I'm not religious but I'm convinced now. The only way this all makes sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 02:51:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg Karen, you can't just ask people why they're green! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 16:21:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I second trying 30F, I wear that size and have similar measurements to OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 03:38:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even slumber does not stop the spready toes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 02:34:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will never not dance to Suavemente </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 22:20:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love the Alamo Drafthouse! It's one of my favorite places and I've really missed it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 22:08:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >"does my profile attract the kind of woman I want it to?"

Or even, does my profile attract any woman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 22:06:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought you could swipe right as much as you wanted in the free version?
Unless he wanted to see people from different locations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 18:28:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Our queen! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 16:21:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Explaining interest is kind of hard. Like for me I've had a lifelong interest in the general field but only recently became interested in the specific field I want to specialize in.

Like how do I convey a lifelong passion without sounding tryhard but then also convey a new interest within the field without sounding like I just stumbled upon it?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 16:16:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >meanwhile I thought I sounded like a child when writing it

Omg I feel that.

Maybe they want you to sound more natural and conversational? Idk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 15:51:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! The CV! That's almost stressing me out more than the motivation letter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 15:50:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It took me years to decide what I wanted to do re graduate school, and only now at 30 am I ready to start applying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 15:49:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >your passport is about to expire,

Yeah mine is already expired, just another thing I have to take care of! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 15:47:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe try to set aside some time to specifically vent about it, and then the rest of the time don't talk about it. Might put everyone more at ease but you still can get it out of your system </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 15:45:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same, I'm just thinking 'ok just get ideas on paper' so I'll have something to build around, and I try not to put too much pressure on myself but I really want it to be good so I get accepted...

The program I'm applying to is in EU so they don't have as many admission requirements, but that means more weight is put on the letter itself 😭 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 15:42:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I graduated college eight years ago and I'm trying to tie in my work experience and stuff but my mind is all over the place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 14:51:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The thing I worry about with that is if the value of the home goes down. Of course for long term it definitely makes more sense if the payments are reasonable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 04:12:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wth! How is that even comfortable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 04:09:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Welcome to the world Phil! We love you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 04:08:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So do they just sleep on top of the bare mattress? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NYC -- LSAT Prep Books! PowerScore LG Bible, LSAT Trainer, Preptests (72-81) from LSAC </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 00:02:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Check out this Three LSAT Prep Books for $30 on OfferUp https://offerup.co/pRWC5UioE9

Price negotiable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NYC -- LSAT Prep Books! PowerScore LG Bible, LSAT Trainer, Preptests (72-81) from LSAC </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 23:57:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Check out this Three LSAT Prep Books for $10 on OfferUp https://offerup.co/GSeJEOLnE9

Price negotiable. I bought these all last year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 20:16:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only way live action would be worth it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 20:06:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I would assume coming in on a student visa would be an exception if we are still restricted from traveling.

What part of Spain are you in? I'm looking to go there next year to study </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 16:57:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is the 3-month sex rule? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 18:43:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yay I love the languages of the Iberian peninsula!

Basque is so fascinating. It kind of sounds ancient if you hear it spoken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 00:54:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 00:07:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where do the names in green come from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 23:07:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You will not!

You can't change how you feel, but you can still choose to leave him regardless.

After you break things off, you will still have feelings for him for a bit, and it will suck. You'll want to get back with him, but fight it! With time, the feelings will fade and you'll be in a much better place, without someone dragging you down.

I am going through something similar right now so I really empathize. It hurts, but we'll get through it! I believe in you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 20:08:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's all Germany? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 20:06:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would love to visit Istanbul! Is it safe to travel there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 19:57:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That dog has good taste </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 16:08:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What did they do? I had thought they were neutral? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 11:28:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Measuring in double hamburgers?? Now that's just crazy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 11:27:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm confused. How much is that in alligators? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 11:21:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When you workout at night, do you still have a protein shake or eat something afterwards? Or do you just wait till morning to eat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 19:22:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is future faked? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 17:08:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you like better about Ireland compared to the US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 04:16:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Amish come from Switzerland?

I'm Pennsylvania German and I did an ancestry DNA test and it said my ancestry was probably Swiss!

^^^(also ^^French ^^which ^^was ^^even ^^more ^^surprising) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 04:10:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you been to the other Nordic countries? How do they compare? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 01:46:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >1. Bureaucracy. Be prepared to fight for what you need.

That's interesting you say this. I had a friend from Israel and he actually complained about bureaucracy in the US and how everything had to be a certain way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 01:42:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ^^psst..you ^^mean ^^2021? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 20:22:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >"you're a stupid American wanting to regulate everything" comment.

Are Americans really known for wanting to regulate things? I would have thought the Dutch have a lot of regulations as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 20:01:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What part of the US do you live in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 14:01:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes for real, if they properly had my size I'd probably never wear another brand! I have their one bralette and it's so nice but it just barely fits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 13:58:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I recommend them, they're really soft and comfortable, it feels like you're wearing nothing; it's been really nice for the summer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 20:11:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm glad you asked because I've been wondering this for months. I really need a new sports bra but it's hard to find ones that fit well for to my shape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 02:27:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I wondered what sub I was on for a sec </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 14:27:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Adorable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 13:39:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does it make your clothes smell like vinegar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 04:31:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Blasphemy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 02:55:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Real life Nic Cage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 19:32:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did still get paid that week. They gave me the 'You have exhausted all benefits' message every week since then, but I still got paid every week as normal. I have a job now though so no longer calling them.

So it seems that the message was just an automatic thing that you hear after the normal expiration of benefits time, but since benefits had been extended I was still getting paid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 18:21:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't know I could love someone I don't personally know so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 02:34:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I look up the lyrics in the language and try to figure out what they're saying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 02:22:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I second this. Their hotpot chicken is 🤤 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 01:21:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where civil blood makes civil hands unclean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 21:59:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where in Europe do you live? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 14:45:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He has happy cat eyes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 14:39:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beautiful ❤️ Now I'm crying again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 14:35:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Venice too I believe, and Verona </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 14:03:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ~~Was the Weimar republic before and during WWII?~~

NVM I forgot there was a regime before Hitler came to power </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 04:41:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Memes have truth in them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 21:37:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do you have health insurance? I thought healthcare was free. Does it cover everything?

Also what city do you live in? And are you able to save money? Do you feel like you have to save money as much as you did back in the US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 19:33:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He was such a beautiful person. I am heartbroken </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 15:34:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Óla a todos. Faz unos anos que estudo o português, mas não o falou muito. Preciso de unos programa de televisão em português. Tambem comecei estudar o catalão mas não quero esquecer do português. Estudo o catalão porque quero estudar em Barcelona para meu mestrado. Atualmente moro no's Estados Unidos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 20:51:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hard pass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 20:38:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Yeehawians </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 20:16:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah but they could still tell if there was too much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 19:33:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Schrodinger's hat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 19:20:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought it was continental soldier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 14:45:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >incel black pill

I thought it was red pill? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 14:41:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is actually, I just miscounted 🤦 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 14:41:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It seems I just forgot how to count 😅 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 14:26:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But then it's no longer a haiku. I like this version though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 06:29:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow Pokemon Go is getting intense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 05:41:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What have the Amish ever done to you?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 03:52:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 03:14:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Somewhat related, the Catalan word for 'breakfast' is 'esmorzar'


('Lunch' is 'dinar', and 'dinner' is 'sopar') </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 19:15:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my limited experience meeting Italians in Spain, it seems they prefer learning Spanish to English?

Of course I probably met a biased sample but that is what they told me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 19:12:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> > People are always finding worms in their water and nearly everyone experiences hair loss when they move here because of how terrible the water is.

From bathing in it? Or drinking it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 19:03:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What part of Spain do you live in?

Also how do you find the food there healthwise? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 01:44:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really appreciate you sharing this! We rarely hear the stories from regular people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 22:13:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never had a dog but I think Rottweilers are so cute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 17:35:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I've rarely taken the bus in Manhattan, but I live in Brooklyn nearish to Barclay's center and the buses are convenient to getting to places that are a little far to walk but not so far as to take the train.

Also it's nice to stay above ground sometimes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 15:07:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What borough do you live in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 14:44:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anecdotally, my Puerto Rican family does do a more cutesy voice sometimes when talking to babies. And everything to them ends in '-ito' (the diminutive).

I don't think its too over the top though and probably comparable to what we do in American English </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 14:34:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah seriously, therapy would be the bare minimum for this situation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 06:10:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Already besties! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 04:44:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! In my experience it's used for keyword or a code </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 04:31:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> VA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 02:45:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They Crisco'd the poles and people still managed to climb them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 02:39:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a beautiful girl! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 01:46:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Huh, I never would have thought of Nazis in Puerto Rico </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 23:20:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you have to pay a fee? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 19:43:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They really should put a train that goes from Bushwick to Atlantic Terminal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 19:59:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I came here to say the same! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 19:58:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How much upkeep was the hair? Did you have to bathe or groom her more frequently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 19:50:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Chinese for loaf even has 'meow' in it! Kitties must have been loafing for millennia! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 19:17:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You did the right thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 16:39:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love this little street </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 04:49:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It says he was part of a FB group where guys post pictures pointing a gun at their crotch, on order to trigger liberals.

I don't get it? How is that supposed to trigger liberals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-23 03:09:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why does Putin look like Max from Max and Ruby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-22 17:28:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it helps also that they probably don't pay rent since they live in a cave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-22 01:10:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What was the bet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 23:30:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wanted one for a second, then I remembered I have a cat... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 20:58:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously! How are you gonna become a speech pathologist and make fun of kids' speech?? That's your whole job!

It's like if you became a dermatologist and made fun of someone's acne, or became a physical therapist and made fun of a person's limp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 17:15:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please do not shake your kittens! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 17:07:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you handled that pretty well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 16:47:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> GOOD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 16:45:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ???? Yes??? We care about other people?? How is this bad...

These people fail to see that the individual cannot exist without the collective. Supporting the collective is supporting the individual </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 16:10:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That blue is so pretty and looks great on her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 04:06:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This looks like a soccer team logo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 03:08:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love them so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 01:10:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, a little piece of flimsy silicon is going to irreparably enlarge my vagina </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 22:56:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like how everybody standing around is just politely bobbing their slinky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 22:12:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This does make waking up early sound a lot cooler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 22:11:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn't that what happened in book one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 20:26:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw a couple studios in BK heights for $1700 on StreetEasy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 17:45:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And the kids have cancer too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 16:05:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It sounds like Russian to me as well for some reason. (I'm a Spanish speaker too) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 14:33:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! I recommend them, wearing one right now! I'm 30DDD and wear the XS in the Curvy bralettes. OP would probably wear size P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 05:07:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are paper wasps the black ones? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 02:32:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The animation is... something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 23:10:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a fiery Pabu! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 23:08:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NI has an interesting mix. I've always been curious about the politics and thinking there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 22:16:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> b2b? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 22:11:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was unemployed for a couple months before the quarantine already, and I finally got a new job a couple weeks ago!

From like March to mid June there were barely any jobs posted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 20:11:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm trying to go to grad school finally! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 20:08:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I heard that as well, but presymptomatic people apparently can spread it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 14:27:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >Dude, I don't even know you exist. Nothing I do involves literally any consideration for you.

I wish every man understood this. Like you're not even a passing thought in my mind, you don't matter as much as you think you do! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 04:26:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fluffy loaf and smooth loaf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 20:58:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm still sad about Drogon, I feel like that was the most heartbreaking part of the show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 19:54:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >Momo Ramen

Their soup dumplings are 🤤

Also a fan of their Dan Dan Ramen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 16:20:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's interesting. Do you have any reading on the subject that you recommend?

Also how did people live before suburbs? Was it just urban communities, and rural communities right outside the city? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 13:51:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Apt metaphor for Cersei Lannister </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 02:43:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's really beautiful. Where is it from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 19:30:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Animal Crossing IRL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 14:19:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love when Ikki was having a tea party with them and they all had ridiculous names </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 21:56:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like the snake from The Jungle Book! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 21:26:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm Pennsylvania Dutch (but Lutheran, not Amish) on my dad's side and I don't use those words for my grandparents. We don't really speak PA Dutch anymore but that was what my greatgrandparents spoke and my grandfather did speak it when he was little.

I call my grandmother Grem and my grandfather is Pop

I should mention that the Amish do still speak PA Dutch among themselves so they probably do use Dutch words to refer to grandparents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 17:08:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes exactly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 21:41:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or it resembles one in another language you learned!

Then you feel smart for remembering and making the connection </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 19:33:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Teenagers don't dress like that anymore do they? That's a very 2000s outfit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 19:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mean Girls doesn't even need a sequel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 19:31:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is just straight savage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 19:05:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Top of the Rock is open now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-15 18:09:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which is why 'Wherefore art thou Romeo?' really is saying why are you Romeo? or why must you be called Romeo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 17:16:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you have an Instagram? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 14:19:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do you know when to get it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 14:17:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why couldn't I figure out the last letter? I was like African American Vernacular... Experience?  🤦 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 22:03:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any events at Flamingo and PH like last year? Or is it strictly Paris and Bally's? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 19:23:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can they not call their pastors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 19:12:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can NAC worsen anxiety as well? I was taking it a few months ago and didn't feel great, but it may have been the 5-htp I was also taking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 03:09:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmm haven't got that one yet in Animal Crossing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 03:04:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes Second Avenue Deli is amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 02:56:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love the floppiness of this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 20:45:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you use the Roomi booking? Or did you just apply normally through the landlord? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 10:31:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg they have sorullitos! 🤤 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 10:24:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah so they had been dating for eight months when OP found out...and the girl was currently pregnant so Like. That's a very tight timeline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 09:14:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What gym does he go to? I thought he lived in Park Slope and went to the Y there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 17:30:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't these guys know we fought the Nazis? It should be seen as unamerican.

But I guess their loyalty is to race, not country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 13:53:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >But there’s LA diverse and NYC diverse- no comparison at all.

What do you mean by the that? I've never been to LA but am curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 22:42:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I read the internet. Yes, the whole internet, all of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 20:40:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rottweilers are so cute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 20:31:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lmao I put that in Google translate, it has the same sentiment! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 20:30:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kitties knocking stuff off tables since the beginning of time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 20:21:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see modern day Toledo and Salamanca in Spain! Interesting that Salamanca is part of Lusitania </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 20:16:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I usually tried to play but I was terrible and would get hit right away. also dodgeball is kind of terrifying. Even with just the little squishy balls we had in gym class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 17:16:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These all sound kind of cute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 04:22:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also every sane person left in America right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 18:44:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think something like that has been developed, I forget where I saw it though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 04:32:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So we shouldn't date attractive guys but we also should definitely not date unattractive guys.

And if we're not supermodel hot then we might as well go live in a cave away from the rest of humanity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 20:49:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do you say that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 04:29:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >and not the mathematical and empirical descriptions of the divine

Right, like they should at least respect that their deity likely created the world to operate in understandable and predictable ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 03:56:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rooftop bars are open? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 02:26:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it more than pre-corona or more than during quarantine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 01:04:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where do you live? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 22:26:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm looking at Universidad de Pompeu Fabra, it's like $5700 in total.


>Also, and this might need fact checking, but I believe that if you are from the Spanish speaking Americas then you can study for free or get a scholarship/grant.

It would be nice to get a scholarship or grant but I am from the US, though I speak Spanish because my mother is from Puerto Rico (and studied it in college). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 21:51:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I was looking at a university in Barcelona for a master's program, and even their higher non-EU rate is cheaper than the in-state tuition at a public university here in NY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 18:22:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah it's the dumbest thing ever, I went into the settings and you can't even configure it to send you notifications for message replies to your phone. Only email for some reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 18:12:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm looking for a room and also haven't got any responses back to messages I've sent out. I'm paranoid that they are not even getting the messages. Like if it's as you say I would think that they'd be more eager to talk to potential roommates! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 18:09:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you dm me your Roomi link?

I live in Brooklyn currently and am looking to stay here (in Park Slope area), but I am not sure about Prospect/ Crown Heights since I've heard crime has been going up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 05:26:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >A lot of the Facebook comments were about how she obviously didn't social distance, or she'd have been safe if she quarantined like she was supposed to. Which while funny, also completely tactless.

Yeah like we are aware other dangers still exist, nobody is claiming otherwise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 05:05:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought this it was gonna be a wholesome thing about feeling connected to people through memes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 03:40:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He was ahead of his time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 23:04:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is an interesting sociological experiment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 22:43:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes Puerto Ricans do this as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 22:38:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is why it took me forever to figure out how to open my locker when I started middle school 😫 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 22:03:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you report it to the police? I assume your store has cameras so hopefully he will get charged </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 21:50:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooof well do I have news for him... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 21:44:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah that makes a lot of sense. I think a good place to focus their energy then is to help those that actually are being oppressed. I know some christians do do that, but I wish it were a wider and more accepted message. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 17:50:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I also found the wires really stiff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 17:33:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What brand is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 01:56:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your NTA for not reciprocating her feelings and setting boundaries. She seems a bit delusional </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 01:28:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it still helping? I really hope so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 00:55:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where can I get one with a wavy rim? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 00:53:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >High lumen flash light

Interesting. Do you have a recommendation for a specific one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 22:19:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well...now he can't play any games 🤷‍♀️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 19:47:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My two favorite Marvel heroes are Thor and Black Panther, I bet that would make their heads explode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 19:45:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For real it's ruining viking shit for the rest of us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 18:26:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Affordable housing? Or am I being too optimistic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 18:16:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why does it even matter if she's "really a nerd"?

And what nefarious intentions does he think she has? To have friends?

Plus two years is a long time to pretend to be into stuff you're not into... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 06:07:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was wondering this as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 01:54:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are we evolving backwards? The demon sperm thing sounds like something straight from the middle ages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 01:51:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right? Like if they saw it in the trash and were complaining, why are they looking in the trash? If you look in the trash can you're going to see trash idk what to tell them 🤷‍♀️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 00:53:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For real you'd think that you had your blood stained used pad just on display. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 00:53:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah when I was in college one year i was I'm a coed suite so me and this girl shared a bathroom with a couple guys. She was so concerned that I didn't wrap the empty wrappers from the pads. Like she was like 'you have to wrap your pads!' I'm like 'yeah I did', really confused. She then explained she meant the wrapper too. I just looked at her like she was crazy. Like...pads exist?? It's just a clean plastic wrapper. Like I think the guys will survive it. Plus none of them ever complained. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 00:02:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do they not realize that the 'faceless mob' are the civilians that they supposedly swore to protect? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 22:10:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd like to see the protesters co-opt this flag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 22:04:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yet we can't get a cohesive federal response to the pandemic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 22:00:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think I've seen this flag (or similar) in protests over there in Spain. Now I know why! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 20:29:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These are so cute! I love the simplicity and clean lines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 15:46:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me anything fatty goes good with coffee! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 03:16:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are the apple people protesting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 02:17:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah isn't it called Steelworks or something?

Reading, which is about an hour away, also repurposed some old factories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 02:04:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No millennials? That's cutting out over a third of potential applicants for no good reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 23:25:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What differences are there between the two that made you pick Austria? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 02:48:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We had to start somewhere! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 23:16:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you're missing an r in the subreddit title, it didn't load for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 21:38:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Miel ayuda en equilibriar la bactéria en la piel, entonces ayuda con el acne, y también acelera la curación de la piel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 04:18:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/madlads </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 01:49:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm interested, 30f I live in Brooklyn currently.

Bored as hell lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 21:27:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >This is a group project with the dumbest kid in the class insisting they are correct at smarter than everyone.

While also punching everyone in the face </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-26 17:23:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can't Congress do something about this?

Also where is the outrage from the right? I thought they were all about states' rights! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 22:20:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What law are they talking about killing American children? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 21:29:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah cause they're  playing a game of their team vs us and get confused when you're not playing too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 18:41:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah seriously, he's done her the favor of giving off so many red flags in just one day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 17:55:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My BIL is a nurse at a nursing home and he doesn't really think it's a big deal, says it's just like the flu. And that people die from the flu all the time...I mean, I guess that's true? Idek what to say to that.

 It's not really that simple, and even if he hasn't seen devastating effects doesn't mean it's not happening. Plus wouldn't severe cases be more in the hospitals and ICUs anyway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 16:48:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why did you take the cat? Or how? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 04:33:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It never ends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 04:24:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do they think that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 01:13:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously. They're calling Jenna Marbles ugly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 21:36:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What career did you end up pursuing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 15:57:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know I've really outdone myself when they send three sets of utensils </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 02:10:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even if you were open to a man with kids...a newborn??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 01:01:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been out of school for eight years now, and let me say that studying for the GRE has been humbling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 21:54:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >Now we’re adopting policy to adapt to changing circumstances

Idk what is so hard for people like this to understand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 17:13:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Once you get properly sized like other commenters have suggested, you could look online for cute bras in your size. A lot of us here have to do that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 06:37:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's interesting. Like are women really expected to have kids in their 20s? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 04:42:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd love to live in Brooklyn Heights. I just think it's so cute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 04:31:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know if I would feel safe going to California right now. You might consider just going away to someplace closer, like upstate or even Pennsylvania there's some nice parks and cabins, etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 23:39:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! I ordered two different styles but had that problem with both of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 23:01:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well a sinkhole opened up on the UES so we're not far off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 04:22:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA. why would you even do that. You didn't even try to come up with a justification </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 02:41:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NAH. Kitty is family! It's an unfortunate circumstance but I don't think anyone was in the wrong here, though it's a tall ask for her to ask you to get rid of your cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 22:27:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can relate to how you are feeling. I also live alone and spent about three months straight totally by myself in my apartment. I didn't even have my cat because I had left him at my mother's place a state away.

Before this all started, I was already unemployed since November, but had started to keep myself busy with going to the gym and eating healthy. I felt I was doing well and was hopeful that I would soon find a job since the holidays were over. Well the quarantine kinda put a stop to anyone hiring in my industry, so I kinda have given up on even finding a job (now things are picking back up again).

Some days were better than others, I tried to keep myself occupied. I was able to stop taking antidepressants and I seem to have it under control with some supplements and vitamins, which I was able to experiment with being unemployed/stuck at home.

The last few days I also have been feeling really lost though. Like I'm running out of money and the extra pandemic unemployment payments have run out for me. I'm at such a crossroads and my mind is just going crazy because I know I need to get a job, but I don't know when I will and don't know if I should stay in the city or just go to live with my mom for a bit or even find a cheaper place. Thinking about moving is giving me a lot of anxiety though because I've never done a big move myself and I don't know if it's worth the hassle if I can find a job.

The other thing is that even though I need to get a job, I also want to apply to go back to school for my masters and change my career, so I feel frustrated that I have to put so much effort into finding a job that I know I will ultimately leave in a year or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 20:44:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/comfypasta </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 23:55:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What even made him think that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 20:38:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh. My. God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 01:47:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> From what I know of Hitler, that doesn't even seem like something he would say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 19:19:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. The child's well-being is the most important thing here. You did the right thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 04:42:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What was there even to do? Everything was closed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 03:05:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ESH. Yeah your SIL was still a jerk but I think your comment went too far even if she may have deserved it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 02:45:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. Your stepmom is being ridiculous and not at all reasonable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 02:36:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or people from that one Doctor Who episode 🤔 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 21:44:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If only to see more Lucy and Ron together. I think they would get along </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 03:26:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah and then she took the drink away from him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 03:25:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 04:07:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's even a subreddit r/zoomies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 19:21:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where do you check your effective days? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 19:21:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> After I certified on the phone last week, I reapplied for benefits and still got paid.

This week they still said I exhausted my benefits so I'm not sure if I'm gonna get paid this week? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 23:36:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are people really doing this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 03:49:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They won't accept it until it kills on contact </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 03:46:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a sweet face! ❤️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 03:33:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you know a good dupe for their framboos serum? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 01:20:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah actually if I were OP in this situation I might even request him to use some slightly less noise cancelling headphones too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 01:15:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA and your husband is being a huge jerk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 23:16:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg 💯 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 23:10:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Palatches seems like they're pronouncing it as if it were Italian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 16:51:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aren't they allowed to apply for asylum or refugee status? As I understand it is not actually illegal for them to come here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 16:36:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA. You knew she was self conscious about that picture and posted it out of spite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 16:12:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. I think this is a good idea and you understand the significance of these items and the importance of understanding them for society as a whole. Sometimes it's better to stare our ugly past in the eye rather than ignore or try to erase it.
And obviously when it's posted up in the museum it'll be with context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 15:40:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No because they were keeping the name secret </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 02:33:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is accurate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 15:38:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah and in one of the edits OP said he talked further with his son about options and that he would end up with about 50k in loans. Like that's still a huge amount and would be a burden for a few years, why would you subject your son to that when you don't have to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 05:24:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA. Sure you're making a point but your son seems to be pretty open to discussion.

It's an AH move to take away his tuition money just to make a point, he already seems like he wants to help others or at least make society more equitable, and it would be easier for him to focus on that goal without having a huge amount of debt to deal with after he graduates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 05:08:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really hope you're right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 02:03:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People have negative opinions about that sub? I like to read the posts there a lot and have always found that commenters were pretty supportive and logical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 01:49:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aww I forgot Pabu was there too, that makes it even sadder! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-05 19:51:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He says 'its not that bad guys', but the danger isn't while you're out, the virus doesn't jump out and attack people. How do they think viruses work? You don't know you've gotten sick until much later. I just don't understand this thinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-05 04:23:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. Also, leave him, please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 14:23:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I don't think I could go through the insertion, I've passed out from pain from having a PAP smear before (I think the doctor was just pressing too hard) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 06:32:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We can use the Chance and Community Chest cards from Monopoly, laminate them and add 'Official' to the bottom. Then when we show them to people they have to do whatever it says </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 06:26:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a sweet little cinnamon loaf! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 06:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you for my future nightmares </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 06:11:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. Idk she'd probably go harass the family or stalk the child </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 05:53:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For Catalan did you just make Barcelona green? I would think you could make all of Catalonia green though it is part of Spain still technically </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 04:20:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The prophecy is true!

Edit: https://youtu.be/knGhzlGsGtk (full version) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 03:33:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right, isn't it common enough that babies come a little late? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 03:29:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unfortunately she might then blame OP for somehow not controlling when she gives birth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 22:02:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know something about the texture makes them be like 😻😼 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 20:49:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Excuse me don't you mean 'the wooOoOoorst🎵' ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 20:44:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I was thinking AT LEAST we are halfway done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 20:21:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that an Ikea mattress? I have one and my cat likes to claw at it too for some reason 😹 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 20:17:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What...how are you supposed to greet each other then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 07:36:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Majestic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 07:08:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that the brand name? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 03:05:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah seriously. When I was a young teen and would go visit my dad on the weekends, he would be playing loud music until the wee hours! I'd ask him to turn it down/off but he just said if I was really tired I'd be able to fall asleep. 😡 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 02:54:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA and your husband absolutely is TA! He is not respecting you or the sanctity of your home at all by putting his friends needs above yours, and he could easily go to another room. I don't understand why he is insisting he talk loudly on the phone in your bedroom while you sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 20:30:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's just evil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 20:30:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me neither, it's absolutely sick! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 20:15:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh cool my grandparents have one of those! I think theirs does spin a little. They live in Pennsylvania so these must be popular all over </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 06:31:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's adorable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 06:23:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would say that modern English is almost like a heavily French-influenced creole of Middle English.

Though part of the Germanic family, I wouldn't say it's German, though it gets the essence across.

Edit: if you want to hear what English may have sounded like without so much French influence, look up the Frisian dialect of Dutch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 04:41:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Careful who you says this to, soon we'll have people yelling about how not only should they not wear a mask, but they should be able to pick their nose wherever they want! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 23:44:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Other subs this would fit in-- r/justnofamily and r/justnomil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 21:12:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok but the behavior is happening in OP's house, while being employed by OP. I think it's acceptable to tell someone their behavior is not appropriate in those situations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 21:05:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. I feel like you put him in his place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 22:06:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 08:15:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And I know because I'm a bear. Thanks owl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 07:43:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love all of them beans! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 02:49:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love his chunky face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 02:20:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Sansa was just wary after all she had been through. In my headcanon though I imagine they were in on it the whole time to out-sneak littlefinger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 17:02:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I was wondering the same since she then mentioned for them to refinance in MIL name. As I understand the loans are separate from the title of the car </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 05:44:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's really cute idea. Basically, people need to learn decorum!
Also, damn were they such a mess that his mom knew to being nice jeans for him? Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 05:39:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We should do that like the kpop fans were doing for #whitelivesmatter ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 05:31:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eu diz, bem vindos irmãos lusofônicos! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 05:27:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interestingly, my family is kind of the opposite. My sister and I will always refer to our mother as Ma. And with our cousins, if we are talking about someone we always refer to them by our relationship to us, rather than their relationship to the other person. Like if my cousin is talking about my mom he'll say "Titi" and if I'm talking about his dad I'll say "Tio" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 04:29:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I don't get people who come in jeans or whatever to a wedding. Like if you don't wanna put any effort into looking nice, just don't come. I feel like it's a huge sign of disrespect that they just can't be bothered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 04:00:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah that's confusing me too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 03:59:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah that's how I'm interpreting it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 03:55:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA, it seems you went off on his mother unprovoked (by her anyway). She was just asking what happened, though I understand that you were very upset by what your bf had done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 02:33:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah exactly, that's the problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 01:24:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's flutes d'amore which are in different keys (I think usually D or Eb). I believe typically these are used to play baroque music or music form the middle ages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 01:17:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Olenna Tyrell is an icon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 01:14:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plus when do we ever see an older woman with a much younger man in movies? And even when we do, it's a big deal, unlike with the older guy/younger woman pairing which we're just supposed to accept as normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 01:12:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For real she should be playing his daughter not his love interest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 00:33:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But I'm sure they appreciate your honesty and self awareness! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 22:41:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pets are not disposable! They are family!

😡

NTA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 22:36:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I forget, how did lava guy die? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 22:35:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I think that's what makes it so sad, because you see that maybe they will be able to have a good life and redeem themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 22:34:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like Atla was tame compared to this. There weren't any explicit on screen deaths. Like maybe the closest was Aang going down while in the Avatar state after Azula attacked him, but a murder/suicide with your own brother with whom you just reconciled is another level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-26 19:46:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tbf she's the only one that had the opportunity to because harmonic convergence only happens once every 10000 years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 19:31:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have CBS All Access which is $6 a month with commercials (you can also get a free trial). Or if you want a free site I've used kimcartoon.to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 19:25:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a Mary Sue! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 19:24:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I agree actually. But idk why people wanna say Mary Sue, they are the Avatar, who is supposed to be really strong, so I'm not sure what they expect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 19:23:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah they only had the first two seasons on some streaming sites for some reason. CBS All Access added 3 and 4 recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 19:19:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes definitely watch it, it's kind of wild but I really liked it.

Edit: if only to see Aubrey Plaza's Eska 😅 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 05:48:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously the Amish are no joke. I think some are lightening up but not sure really </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 05:38:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We're bad consumers because we're not buying something that doesn't exist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 05:31:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is such a slap in the face to people with actual disabilities. Tf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 05:01:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pinto pinto beans! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 03:07:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oooh lmao 🤦. I guess I just get excited to talk about cats that I forget common sense 😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 00:04:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She's birman and ragdoll. (You can see her on her Instagram @missenell)

I didn't know being crossbreed causes crossed eyes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 00:03:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know, I love them so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 19:49:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I turned 30 a few months ago and feel the same way.

I think partly it's because there's no longer pressure to get married by 30 as is the stereotypical goal age. Since I'm already past it it's like 🤷‍♀️ and I've realized that I'm still pretty young and I don't have to force myself to settle (relationship or otherwise).

I'm really trying to focus on living my life the best way for me right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 19:44:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where did you grow up? 29 doesn't seem that old to me

 I'm 30 so that's just making me wonder what my family thinks of me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 06:43:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's what he gets for eating Momo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 23:47:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow this was brutal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 22:02:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're taking about the blue ticks in WhatsApp that appear on a message after the person has read it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 20:47:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I think I like Sokka so much because he seems like the realest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 20:46:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw but he's trying his best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 08:19:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know I thought it was really cool, and it was neat to see all the airbenders fighting together, since we've never been able to see that before. You sort of saw a restoration of a lost culture but the birth of a new one at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 07:14:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been wondering, where do the combustion people come from? Are they just mutants in the fire nation, or do they come from a specific region? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 06:49:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah maybe so because I don't remember the lasers at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 06:43:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I think they only mention what they are the second time we see them. So the first time seeing the penguins is like ??? lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 06:39:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The best villains are the ones you low-key want to win </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 06:29:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 06:24:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just rewatched this today and there was some strong tearbending going on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 06:22:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She only had to fight Vaatu and risk losing Raava because it was harmonic convergence, which only happens once every 10000 years. So no other Avatar before her besides Wan had to fight Vaatu. We don't know if any other Avatar would have suffered the same fate because they were never put in that position. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 06:04:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Young Bumi looks a bit like Sokka </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 05:56:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh interesting. I thought the whole raava/vaatu thing was really cool and showed another layer of the world and how energy and spirits interact with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 05:51:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How is making more airbenders fucking it up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 05:37:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you have to pay extra (like on top of your prime subscription) for Nickelodeon shows? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 05:36:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They also have it on CBS All Access </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 05:33:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're otter penguins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 05:19:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Season 3 of LoK is seriously amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 05:18:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you mean by the bad fan fiction plot in season 2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 04:53:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True, and the fact that he didn't have any other children </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 22:55:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know some people hate this scene and the fact that she lost the connection, but just cause the connection isn't there anymore doesn't mean the previous avatars ceased to have ever existed. They still all lived and we can still speculate about their lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 05:52:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't really have advice for you but I just wanna say I feel this so much as well.

It is exhausting feeling like you never really belong but also there are expectations for you to belong specifically to one cultural group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 04:58:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do we know the reason metalbenders can't bend platinum? Or is it just accepted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 04:47:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope they make Bolin holding Pabu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 04:45:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This has been my first time watching both, and I am an adult. I definitely loved both of the series, and they're so different that it's really hard to compare them. LoK did hit different though and I like that the characters were older. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 04:31:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >Besides that, Bolin didn't "just happen upon" his lavabending, he learned it by standing his ground, a classic earthbending trait

Yes exactly, and I mentioned in another comment but he was in pretty extreme circumstances when he got it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 04:22:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >She also thinks that using funny faces copies ATLA

Umm isn't that like pretty typical in this style of animation like wth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 04:20:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >11. Anarchy is a bad philosophy to illustrate in Korra’s attempt at morally-gray villains on the merit that it is an ill-thought ideology that is doomed to fail because it inherently creates a power vacuum. Zaheer is automatically invalidated by his own unintelligent philosophy, so the choice to write on anarchy is taking an easy route to continue to avoid writing an actually morally-grey plot.

I thought that Zaheer was a very compelling character, and I can believe that he genuinely believes in anarchy being the best way for the world to be. And actually it was a little more complicated then that, I believe he thought that somehow in chaos the world would reach balance. So not sure if that's exactly anarchy, though I guess some anarchists probably do think that way as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 04:16:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Regarding point 7, I don't think the different aesthetic takes away from the story or could inherently make it garbage. It's just different. Besides a lot of it still had Asian influences and personally I thought that mix was cool. Also, it's not like that 1920s aesthetic only existed in America, though it is clearly heavily drawn from that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 04:13:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >Bolin just “happens” upon his lavabending.

I guess, but in a similar way that Toph got metalbending when she was desperate to escape, Bolin didn't discover his lavabending until his and other's lives were in danger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 03:07:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love Bolin! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 01:15:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like it should be that way. The point of having kids should be to raise a functional responsible person. Having a kid cause you think they're cute is actually a terrible reason.
Of course this doesn't mean you can't enjoy your children when they are little! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 03:45:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Uncle Iroh would be proud </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 08:38:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah it's more like pro-existence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 19:51:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know! It's like the pets were just placeholders for their future kids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 19:47:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I turned 30 in December and it's amazing how quickly my giving a fuck has dropped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-02 04:47:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn I would be really hurt if somebody referred to me like that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-02 04:37:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is...that supposed to be sexy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-02 01:14:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >But most of all, alienated from society and knowing that this society cherishes property above people, he is shocking it by abusing property rights.

I was feeling this when I was reading about NYC putting in a curfew after looting in Manhattan. I guess I understand why they put the curfew in place but

Like honestly I don't care that the Louis Vuitton store in Soho was vandalized. It just seems like such a minor issue to me compared to what is being protested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-02 00:53:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you taking any supplements? I've known I have mild adhd for awhile but I've always struggled with depression and anxiety as well, so right now I'm trying to help myself with supplements like 5-htp, tyrosine, nac, and gaba.

 I really wanna go back to school next year to get my masters, and I also want to be able to focus at work (I'm unemployed right now and I think my inability to focus really affected my performance at work so I was eventually let go). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-02 00:40:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >“With what your husband makes why not just be a stay at home mother?”

🤮

Ugh. It's like what I actually wanna do with my life doesn't matter at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 19:19:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >One didn't mind if he didn't see me for two months

Omg did we date the same person


>I don't NEED to be with a man, so I'll only change my single status if I find a man who's really worth it.

💯, I don't understand what people don't get about this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 07:39:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Especially takedowns in other languages 😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 00:10:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't understand how we're parasitic though if we use way less resources and pay more in taxes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 00:08:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ooof yeah I can see that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 04:35:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never really understood needing to have kids for your grandparents or great grandparents to meet. Like they already know you, isn't that enough? And we don't control when our elders pass away..idk it's such a strange thing for people to be fixated on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 04:23:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which is really stupid since they're just finding out now about a pretty serious issue kids can get from covid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 21:54:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right?! Like I don't have kids but that doesn't mean I exist as a robot with no feeling or attachment to anyone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 06:28:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should have a good reason for wanting/having kids! Not for not wanting or having them!

Like I don't go around obnoxiously asking people why they don't have a cat. I love cats and think they're amazing but it's still a commitment and a serious choice to get one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-06 06:08:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But millennials aren't all broke twentysomethings. Don't they realize about half of millennials are over 30 now?? And nearly all over 25? We're adults now, most of us understand our choices, stop belittling them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 08:37:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn that's really messed up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-03 19:23:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly Jennifer Aniston is living the dream life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-03 19:12:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously it's the only thing you can say, and it's the truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-03 19:11:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lmao. You don't need to be pretty to have kids just FYI to those people. They must feel so good about themselves </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-02 04:33:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's possible actually and makes more sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-02 04:30:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A Spanish professor in Spain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-01 22:32:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not exactly what you're asking, but I was told that in Old Spanish the V used to be pronounced as an F sound. Which is how it is in German, so very interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 06:45:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe call the cops and leave an anonymous tip. That's really messed up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 16:28:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a hobby for me but has been a life-long interest and passion for me. I am planning to go to grad school for linguistics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 20:02:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What grade do you teach? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-22 23:13:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey it seems you have a good workout setup at home, what would you recommend as basically to start out?

I'm at a bit of a loss right now with the gym closing 😭. But balance does seem to be a good place to focus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 06:32:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No because I don't want to possibly spread it outside of the city. I especially wouldn't want to get my mom sick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 02:54:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't understand how you "took it" from a family. Like they can also buy a house.

I mean are childfree people supposed to just live in a 300 sq ft apartment forever because apparently we have nothing important to house? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 23:20:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> > Also, people coming in for last minute flu shots thinking it will help.

Lmao omg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-29 01:04:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alice in Wonderland is the ish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-27 16:42:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do people want to gatekeep empathy and sadness?!

I had a partner who had a baby who died when she was a few months old (this was years before we met). When he told me about it, of course I felt very sad. I still feel sad when I think about it 😓 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-27 16:36:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >I want and do enjoy my life.

Gee what a concept 🙄 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-27 16:29:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those kittens are your babies! You're doing the Lord's work ❤️❤️❤️😽 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-24 23:58:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Biscuit-making kitties are the best ❤️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-24 23:49:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >Pops is a great drinking buddy and a not so stellar parent. He never had to, mom got me when they split and he only ever had to be “the fun one” I’m pretty low contact with him these days.

That sounds exactly like me and my dad 😅 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 23:20:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No matter how many times I write it, I always forget if it's two Ps or two As 🤦 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 23:17:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah this is one thing I don't understand about Spanish speakers, like at this point in the US and especially in certain areas, you should just assume that everybody around you can understand Spanish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 22:57:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RIP JT 💔 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 02:53:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Subspecies does makes more sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 02:40:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's interesting, what I don't understand is how would different species breed together? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-15 21:43:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is such an unnecessary Twitter post, like childfree people don't care but it's twisting the knife for those who want children but can't have them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 00:15:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> _cries in whitest Puerto Rican girl you know_^^^well ^^^half ^^^PR ^^^but ^^^still </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-04 19:30:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a happy baby! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 23:36:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And then the parents will really be lost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 23:35:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >Unicorn clip on hand sanitizer containers?

I think we have the same one! I was completely uninterested in those hand sanitizer clip ons until I saw this little dude, it called to me 😍 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 23:28:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok but four doors are good when you have some friends in the car too! Or if you have family visiting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 23:24:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As it should be! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 23:08:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can only have a hatchback if you have a kid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 22:25:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just found out I'm related to Portuguese royalty from five centuries back!

Unfortunately hasn't really affected my life at all, like you said, who really gives a shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-03 22:20:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg yes, I totally agree, it's crazy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 01:56:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's so weird too, like you're a grown-ass woman. Like lots of adult women are on birth control, was she going to say that to every woman who walked in?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-25 20:43:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But what kind of dog! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-25 20:42:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for sharing your perspective! I'm a fencesitter and it's enlightening to hear different experiences.

Also, people are telling you you'll change your mind when you already have a child?? Does it really never end?! And that's rude to your daughter, it's like saying she's not enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 22:38:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >any booze that gets left behind in my fridge ;)

Of course! That's the party tax! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 22:14:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Umm actually WTF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 21:43:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah threatening to kill someone's pet or any animal is definitely not cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 21:39:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What?? Why would he say that?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 21:20:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If it's just the party, it would be fine. Like it's always nice to have an excuse to celebrate. But expecting tons of gifts each time is extra af. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 21:18:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd come! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-24 02:26:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, what I don't get about that is, if your child is your only source of meaning in your life, what do you even teach your child about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-21 07:41:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seriously. That's my idea of hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-20 03:46:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah and it's freeing to not using that mental bandwidth to criticize people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-20 03:45:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes times 100 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 18:47:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think their idea of progress is that children are allowed in and catered to everywhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 18:31:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >can't buy liquor at the gro sto or on a Sunday.

Same in PA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 06:04:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg I love her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 05:41:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> LMAO

Omg, it's not like I have a cat to replace having a child. I just like cats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 05:22:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It sucks that some people need to have children to realize that other people are deserving of respect and empathy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 05:19:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What career do you have? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 05:16:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is what always confused me about having children, even since I was little.

Like the point of life is to have children? So then they can have children? And those children will have children? Like why exist if our whole existence is just to create more existence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 05:11:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am most offended by the Federalist list in that it claims that my desire to learn as much as possible and travel the world makes me of lesser character than a parent.

Like???

Plenty of parents are ignorant and don't even care to look past their own nose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-06 07:03:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >excuse to get rid of the kid for a whole week lmao.

Lol probably true, there are so many more reasonable options for this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-06 06:14:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nikola Tesla never had kids and we still talk about him. His ideas are discussed to this day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-06 06:13:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel the same way, and if I don't have kids I will have more time to devote to that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-06 05:42:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They could just get a couple private English lessons. Then when their kid is older (and doesn't need babysitting) maybe send them for a summer or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-06 04:55:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *cries in American*

😭 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-06 04:11:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wouldn't she feel weird if someone else's seven year old son was in the locker room? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-05 08:16:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah it's not like it's an easy thing to go through </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-05 07:38:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >I would defintely be in danger of adopting more cats though.

Same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-05 07:34:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah but they don't accept everybody's eggs, like if you ever in your life smoked marijuana they don't want them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-05 04:02:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok, I think babies are cute, but I don't post photos of random babies??? Like I don't understand what she expects, it's way more normal to post pics of random animals.

I would be concerned if someone was posting pics of random babies they found on the internet, that seems kind of creepy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-05 03:50:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a woman, this is a reason I'm leaning towards not having children. It seems that no matter how much you give or how much you sacrifice, when you try to have something for yourself that doesn't include your children, you're made to feel guilty and selfish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-05 02:20:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even if Tina would have kids in the future, she doesn't have to deal with them now, that child is not her responsibility.

I hate this thinking that just because someone may one day become a mom or is a mom, they have to mother every child they come in contact with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-05 01:23:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, I didn't know that all those issues came along with Downs Syndrome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-04 21:33:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's crazy. I feel like in taking for two months I would mention pretty much everything about myself so they know what they are getting into. It's just a waste of time to keep critical aspects of yourself that could be deal breakers hidden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-04 21:31:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you encounter a lot of deceptive dates on there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-04 21:28:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank god for the unmatch feature!

>“I have kids but I don’t see them, they live with their mom.”

Okay but now I like you even less because you're a deadbeat dad.

>“You just haven’t dated the right single dad.”

But I don't want a single dad period! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-04 07:50:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >40% of the population is now obese in the US

Wow that seems really high, where did you see the statistic? I'm really curious to read more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-04 07:32:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Shouldn't it be nietos in this case? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-04 06:18:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg not just the children but I would not want to have to deal with three different baby daddies! 😱 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-04 06:16:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't understand though she is also single with no kids?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-04 05:34:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >"Omg how?"

Omg this drives me crazy! Like have people never heard of birth control... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-03 09:00:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >said I was immature and needed to start planning for the future.

>I'm independent, single, childfree and I have a steady income that supports all my hobbies.

It sounds like you're all set to me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-03 08:56:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a few when I was in college too and they're great, like genuinely curious and excited to be there. And they don't have any of that awkward social angst that still plagues most younger college students, so they seem to be more talkative in class, ime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-30 22:26:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also see: "Yes, freedom" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-28 01:53:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >The most ironic part of all? Like a month before she got pregnant she posted something like "I'm not sure I'll ever have children"

Oh god </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-28 01:12:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly people like this need a hobby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-27 22:01:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That explains why I'm usually okay if I drink soda very slowly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-26 18:01:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Goals! 😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-26 17:38:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg WAT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-26 17:34:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg yes! Can't play around when it comes to ice 🥶 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-20 22:02:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I strive to be the aunt they can talk to! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-20 22:01:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wtf! Cats are amazing and precious! How rude of them.

Like I would never say that to someone no matter what pet they were talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-13 06:44:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When is this so I can be sure to avoid it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 22:37:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg. This technology doesn't even exist. If it did a lot of women who actually desired the pregnancy would have used it! Unfortunately it's not possible, and it's insensitive to suggest it.

These politicians act like they're geniuses for coming up with this stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 22:20:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Replanted ectopic pregnancies??? 😱 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 22:18:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So you were 43 when you got married? And people were still pressuring you about kids?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 03:19:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >I just don’t see a point in dating if I don’t like the guy.

Yeah, that's the whole point! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 02:59:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right??? Like it's not Kmart but still??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 02:56:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right? Like if you don't have a child your priority is your own self and well-being. It's just called living your best life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-08 19:11:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a handful of Puerto Ricans too, I can always tell cause they'll have a Puerto Rican flag somewhere in their yard or window 😅

I lived in Canarsie for about a year when I first moved up here, and as a white/Puerto Rican person, I definitely stood out.

I do kind of miss it sometimes, the area I was in was really chill and quiet. It's just so far from the city to commute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-08 18:32:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >claim clinical depression as my career, it doesn't sound so bad.

... you're onto something here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-07 21:54:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I thought it would have been Tormund too. I guess it's just left to our speculation, though I don't recall who's left there out of named characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-07 21:41:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-07 21:41:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 'Given name' would be better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-07 21:40:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do we know who became the 1000th? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-07 21:33:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't mind existing either, but it really is exhausting sometimes.

Definitely one of the best parts is getting to look at cats 🐱 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-04 22:50:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Omg like let the child live her life first at least!
It gives me stress when people do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-04 22:41:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you work in machine learning? I'm looking to go into a computational linguistics program so might end up in machine learning as well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-01 05:28:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I second getting the Gemeinhardt, and if it's in decent condition might just need a tune up at the repair shop.

Also want to add that taking it to the repair shop is good because then you'll know any issues you're having aren't with the flute and are just some technique or tone issues you might need to work on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-29 23:02:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What was it about the job that made you depressed? I've considered speech pathology as a career so am curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-24 02:41:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd probably use flutist more as I think that's more natural sounding in English. But I still like the word flautist, and it makes sense to me since I am a native Spanish speaker and also speak Portuguese. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-08 20:18:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Puerto Ricans do this too and 100% of the time it's meant affectionately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-01 22:46:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who said that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 21:40:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The cheapest of decent quality that I have seen are $479.
The Nuvo flute might be a good way to begin though, like u/CongregationofVapors mentioned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 03:06:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Makes sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 02:40:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Puerto Rico they sell 8oz in the couple places I got coffee. In NYC I think I've only seen 12oz as small. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 02:35:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you typically have the light roast out too? I always forget to ask and they default to medium roast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 02:30:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You get a tall because it rhymes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-02 02:28:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's Tall

Edit: I don't know of many places that sell 8oz coffees, I wish more would though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 15:37:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So how would you use 'de hecho' in a sentence?

And actualmente means currently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 15:34:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 'Soy caliente' es como decor 'soy guapa'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 14:46:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's probably good to know those basics (noun, verb, adjective, adverb), but otherwise I don't think you need to understand all of English grammar to learn another language. In fact, learning another language and it's grammar helps you understand more of English grammar!
Like I didn't know what verb conjugations were until I started studying foreign languages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 04:41:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beautiful! I love Lisbon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 02:46:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is that very tall building? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-28 02:27:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like how the blanket says HONK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 18:20:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What bc? I've never heard of that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-27 18:01:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Even back in my hometown, I would only acknowledge people if they called my name, then I knew they actually knew me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-24 01:43:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://tenor.com/6zTs.gif

- that delivery guy, probably </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-22 02:27:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A+ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 19:17:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It looks like alfil just means bishop. But has roots from the Arabic word the elephant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 18:39:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes that word certainly is. I've always heard elephant as elefante though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 18:38:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Elephant?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 18:35:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Não falou muito o português, qual é a correta? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 18:27:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/snowing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-20 18:25:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So cool! I didn't know it snowed in Istanbul! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 02:50:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There's a newfreefolk now?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-18 01:02:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On some of these trains I wouldn't be surprised if I ended up on the moon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 06:30:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She was just looking for an excuse to show off her rad new shirt 🌛 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 06:05:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What movie is that from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-16 05:55:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For the liquid polish pic did they just dunk their hand into the polish?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 02:23:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also, I recommend the book Thinner Leaner Stronger. It gives a lot of good exercises targeted to women who want to strength train. I used it and I feel like it really helped me start out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 02:14:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you looking to go after work? Which one is closest to your work?

I just joined NYSC and am looking to get a routine going again. I work by the one on 41st and 8th. I also belong to blink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 01:58:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Short! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 01:51:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is really something else y'all wild lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 01:48:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What time are they doing this so I can make sure to not be outside? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-15 01:46:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> LES Scooter Gang </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 23:40:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is cool! There are some bars too that have a few board games to play. It might be a nice way to break the ice with someone you don't know that well.

I also searched and there's Brooklyn Game Lab in Tribeca and they do Adult Game Nights M-Th. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 23:25:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yeah I've always been interested in joining some groups at the Judson church in West village, but not sure of the religious component 🤔 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 23:22:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll be your friend, I'm 29F, live in Brooklyn, work in Midtown. I don't have many close friends in the city, and I've lived here for three years. I have a good community at work though. I used to go to a language Meetup and got close with some of the people, but then stopped going so most of those friendships kinda faded.

The other difficult thing about New York is that you always have to go out (well mostly) to be with friends, and that can get exhausting. Which is part of reason for my situation, I just live the hermit life too much.


But feel free to on me, if you work near me we could meet for a drink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 22:55:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At any and every opportunity people like her always love to suggest getting out there guns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 22:08:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those are love stares! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-14 18:29:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> See I knew I could put my cat to work as a mouse catcher!

My apartment has had two mice in the few years I've been here. The second one, my cat must've bitten it pretty well, and he was carrying it in his mouth and it was dripping blood everywhere.

So just beware that sometimes a cat can be a messy solution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 05:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NAH. It seems your dad and you have different expectations. As others have said, it may be good to have a discussion with him about those expectations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 05:08:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. You need to protect yourself! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 02:38:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agree. ESH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-13 02:37:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes Dec 23rd child checking in here.

On the plus side, hotel prices in Las Vegas are pretty cheap around Xmas time.

NYE is definitely a worse time though because it's a party everywhere! But that could be good too. It's really a double-edged sword </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 20:09:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, when I was in high school, I was always surprised by people bragging about how tired they were because they stayed up till 2am.

Like?? Go to sleep. Sleeping is the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 19:57:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The legend is true! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 19:46:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where can I get one for my cat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-10 19:33:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes I second Park Slope 5th Ave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 20:32:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They are so creepy! 😣 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 20:31:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would rejoice. I work nearby and would be so happy to never have to see any of those ever again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 05:54:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love the sassy leg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-09 05:02:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That poor child </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 20:13:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a lovely loaf! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 19:38:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, aren't they supposed to be parked facing the street? Ie, not parallel to the curb like a car, but more perpendicular </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 07:54:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course. In fact he demands them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 07:54:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw he's only about six, but he does have big cheeks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 03:49:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a r/kneadycats ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kneady boy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 03:33:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 00:15:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did she get more white fur around her face as she got older? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 00:14:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well kitty wants to be babied too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 00:00:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They are speaking Hindi probably </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 23:23:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OMG same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 21:24:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I'm not a teacher but if I were, I'd be super happy with something like this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 21:20:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine has not, have lived here almost three years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 19:22:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So much belly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 19:07:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is that third one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 18:58:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not for long. Ever since I discovered sunblock, women have been lined up around the block! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 18:56:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got it done at a salon, but the nail tech just used a brush and did a few coats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 04:33:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sauce: https://www.reddit.com/r/SkincareAddiction/comments/d0n0oy/misc_alright_as_a_23_year_old_male_you_have/?utm_medium=android_app&utm_source=share </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I, a man, have discovered sunblock. Behold </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 04:32:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 04:26:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OMG the little dog is like the size of the big one's paw! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 04:21:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Top coat, from top left to bottom right:

regular, matte, matte, regular

matte, regular, regular, matte </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Trying out matte and regular top coat on sparkly art powder over pink/white ombre </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 04:18:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 04:06:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TL;DR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 02:10:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OMG that's adorable when he just sits and looks confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 02:05:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Praise the chonk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 02:02:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She made her nose look cartoonish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 02:01:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is the first BMW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 00:09:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/didntknowiwantedthat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 00:07:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well that's nice but he wanted to blow it up?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-07 00:01:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw poor baby, somebody help him! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 23:59:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I think SHE wants to date her son </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 22:59:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh ok, I got confused cause of the shape </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 22:52:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Floof-catching is my favorite sport! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 22:51:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can kings go in any direction? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 17:31:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look up the meaning of a pyramid scheme and you will soon see... that they are all pyramid schemes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 17:27:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>     >.<~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 17:26:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a cute bird! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 17:23:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That looks like Arecibo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 07:52:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He's so excited, he's wagging his whole butt! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 07:42:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So sweet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 07:41:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No time to unblep! This is an emergency! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 07:39:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a good handsome boy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 06:16:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well that was hard work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 06:08:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How was it in regards to getting your data, like your photos and stuff? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 05:49:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/fakealbumcovers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 02:45:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I've just been considering switching to iPhones and this is definitely a pro lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-06 02:22:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is a mousepad for a serial killer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 18:47:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ugh. Poor kid. I don't understand what is going through her mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 18:27:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OMG this breaks my heart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 18:18:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I miss him too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 18:06:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for that. I've seen some say 2-5%. I think going below five percent is usually only for a short time for competitions and stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 18:02:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really hope she didn't find a trainer that was going to give her son steroids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 18:00:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Afaik, men can have body fat that low with no issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 04:29:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But how then did Eastern Europe get chai? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 23:06:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Harvest Moon? And Pokemon together? Am I dreaming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 23:01:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You could get a plastic tub and fill with water </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 19:33:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You could check out Prospect Heights, it's near the 2/3.

North Park Slope is good too, as it will be close to Atlantic/Barclays center, which has all the train lines you mentioned minus the A. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 19:08:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That looks really fun. Is this a real game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 19:04:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who are they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 18:54:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Los Espookys on HBO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 18:53:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have to be a member? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 18:49:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well maybe it's a workbook, either way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 18:48:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So basically, she's saying they have shit lashes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 17:50:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A whole hour?! You monster! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 17:35:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where did you get that mug? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 17:28:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why would they put that in a kids book?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 17:22:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 😞 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 09:25:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Um...but you are actually Scarlett Johannsen! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 09:18:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What neighborhood are you in? Do you want to stay in the same area? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 05:45:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The straw is black? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 05:23:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  The driver may respond 'Sí' or 'Vale'. Vale means okay. They use this word a lot in Spain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 05:22:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 05:19:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What kind of roof is that in the second pic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 05:11:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 'Puede parar en una tienda de tabaco?'

What country are you visiting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 05:08:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 05:02:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True, maybe it's low dose meth. Still a helluva drug! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 04:11:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is... Is it meth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 03:42:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think if he's not gaining weight, then the amount is fine. I keep my cat's bowl in the kitchen, and when I go to the kitchen, he'll also eat some leftover kibbles too, so I think that's normal kitty behavior.

I found this article which gives some numbers for cat feeding, may be helpful: https://www.catster.com/cat-food/how-much-should-i-feed-my-cat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 03:37:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah that's what I did. Then started giving him a little less since he seemed to not need that much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-04 03:25:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you're feeding him too much actually. You should give him enough that he finishes most of it at meal time. I feed my cat 1/3 cup total per day (half in morning and half at night), and he is fine with that. He's about 14 lbs. I do give him treats some days as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 20:31:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where do you get these boxes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 20:28:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How much clothes do you have now? And about how much storage does it take up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 19:57:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. I live in Park Slope and I love it. It has almost a small town feel, a lot of local shops on 5th Ave. I'm a single 29F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 19:44:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Paw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 19:41:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that Istanbul? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 07:43:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do they sell? Press on nails, or just polish? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 06:25:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He kind of looks like the dog from All Dogs go to Heaven </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 06:03:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nails? Wow there's really an MLM for everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 04:06:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Still scrumptious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 04:02:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which cabs? I've taken the regular yellow ones and it was fine

Edit: for anyone reading this who comes to NYC via Port Authority Bus Terminal, go to 8th Ave between 40th and 41st. There is a line of cabs and a dispatcher. These are legitimate NYC cabs. There's a flat rate for JFK (and also LaGuardia I think). If you go to EWR it will be a metered fare, iirc. Going anywhere else in the city will also be a metered fare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 03:54:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yeah and if he stands cornering you on a bridge even better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 03:44:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a cute harness! (And kitty of course). What brand is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 03:29:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I've been to Córdoba, it's very nice! Southern Spain has such a cool look. I've been to Sevilla and Granada as well.

I've not heard of the other cities you mentioned actually, I'll have to check them out sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 03:14:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are other suburbs like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 02:56:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey. I want you to get better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-03 02:25:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like green apple candy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 20:08:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Those are good rules! It's great that you are encouraging him but also pushing him in the right direction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 19:45:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to have Harvest Moon for my DS ❤️❤️❤️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 14:12:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cool, that's a good way to travel!

Have you visited other cities in southern Spain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 04:49:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you know if they charge the $200 for every apartment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 04:47:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol, well I should not have assumed you were a man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 04:45:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you in a hotel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 04:14:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh! Yes that context does help lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 03:22:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why would it be a problem that you are married? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 03:07:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a form of respect to not write out the name, iirc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 02:26:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This woman is a pedophile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 01:17:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 🔥🔥🔥 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 00:17:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why are there so few houses? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 00:16:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-02 00:12:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was going to guess Bethlehem at first, but it seems you're taking about a really small town. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-01 23:58:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldn't pay $200 just for the chance at an apartment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-01 17:01:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OMG, I'm appalled that any vet would actually do this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-01 06:16:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That little face! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-01 06:02:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-01 06:01:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They are quite floppy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 05:19:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 05:18:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not blursed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 05:09:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's a multireddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 04:53:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FPH? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 04:10:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You'd think people without kids would be way more chill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 01:55:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I think she felt really bad and jealous about Ann kissing him, and she probably didn't know how to deal with it. I think I empathized with her since she was pretty young.

Once they're together though it's total puppy love! I mean they're a complete mess but they seem to be good together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 01:39:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Terrifying! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 01:37:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I saw Cap holding the hammer I think my heart exploded </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 01:34:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What's the difference with the mayoral/city manager system? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 01:27:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do you say that about April? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 01:25:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same. Teared up the second time too. In fact I'm getting a little emotional just thinking about it rn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 00:52:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah idk how they think having a whole other person in the family makes things easier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 00:50:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How does the second kid trap the woman?

Also what a shitty way to view relationships </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 00:49:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And also you have more money for those types of things since you only have one child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-31 00:46:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I feel like only children can actually be better socially, since they're forced to because they don't have the crutch of built-in friends (ie siblings) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 23:51:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >we’re in hell

Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 22:24:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They love feeling better than people with kids.

I've been subbed there for like a week and idk if I'll stay subbed, it seems kinda toxic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 22:21:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >genetics

For real. People love to act so holier than thou when they look better or whatever but it's largely genetics! Which you have zero control over! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 21:54:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whaaa?!! You mean there are other things in life people care about and put their passion and energy into? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 21:49:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well she was supposedly "calm" and "happy".

How amazing is she for achieving perfect work life balance, unlike the rest of us pores who have *gasp* stress! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 21:47:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For real. The comments make it worse! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 21:28:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Secret to eternal youth: avoid all potential stressors! Your flair says it all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 21:27:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >having kids take a toll on you


Yeah it's hella messed up to point it out though. Like they're basically making fun of them because they have a more stressful life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 21:22:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, like honestly I believe when they talk about some people giving them a hard time about not having kids. But that sub gets so hateful and self-congratulatory. Like look how much better I am than 'breeders'! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 21:20:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I only seek the finest sauce! 😂😅😭 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 19:25:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think this is Brooklyn Bridge Park actually </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My skin care routine? No kids. You pores could never. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 17:36:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
So for starters, I’m female and 48. It’s somewhat difficult to say that (especially here in reddit land where that’s considered geriatric) but the good news— I look about 30-35. How do I know this? Because people tell me ALL THE TIME.

The conversation usually comes up from a clerk who asked for ID when I’m purchasing my adult beverages but because I work with a lot of women, the topic regarding ‘lifestyle’ is pretty frequent as well. My job requires me to do a lot of listening and it’s amazing the amount of bitching and just all around bitterness regarding their choices (yep, most of them have kids) I have to endure. It’s painful and quite frankly, boring. After they go through their FML rant, the convo usually goes like this:

Karen: “So, do you have kids?” Me: “God no!” {And yes I say it with gusto} Karen: “Oh...{confused}..Are you married?” Me: “Yep. For over 20 years now”. Karen: {doing math} Wait...How old are you?! I thought you were like 32!”

I then tell them my age, the astonishment of their overall core being takes place, and then the follow up...

...they want to know how TF I look so much younger.

Me: “Well, I do what I love for a living as well as spend my free time doing stuff that I love. Traveling, spending time with my husband and our animals, plus I love cooking etc. {notice my repetition of the word love}. I also do a lot of charity work and that’s fun for me.”

Karen: “No really. What’s your skin care routine?” {still not getting it} Me: “I don’t really have one.” {I don’t}. Karen: “...because I just read about...”

This is where the Karen will then ramble on the latest article she’s read or what she’s doing (it usually involves what she eats or what yoga class she goes to).

Me: “Honestly? I do some of that but I believe most of it is from choosing to not have kids”. {there it is} Karen: .....

The silence usually lasts about 5 seconds followed by the recognition and agreement of my statement. The Karen is now defeated. I don’t get bingoed, shamed, none of it.

The bottom line is, between the tone of my voice (happy), my overall calm demeanor and the visual proof of my rocking body and skin, the conversation is thankfully, over. Doesn’t come in a bottle hun. :)

https://www.reddit.com/r/childfree/comments/cxg3w9/my_skin_care_routine_its_called_no_kids/?utm_medium=android_app&utm_source=share </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 16:34:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah but it was mostly just one season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 16:09:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Grandmas, the best wingmen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 16:08:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Excuse me this is a BLESSED meatball </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 16:07:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go see a movie at a dine-in cinema </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 16:04:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Barsik is the one on the left? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 16:03:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mmm drumsticks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 07:52:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So he just decided to stay in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 05:11:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Delicious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 03:15:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's sad. The rent prices are just getting crazy, idk how regular people are supposed to live anymore! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 02:27:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That fearsome chonk! 😱 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-30 02:12:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What part of Brooklyn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-29 05:39:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is beautiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-29 05:19:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love Siberian kitties! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-29 05:16:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yess I like to learn about history too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-29 05:15:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! I signed up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 15:39:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a whole city of cats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 15:11:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So happy. So chonky 😍 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 09:27:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You could consider Park Slope Brooklyn with that budget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 09:20:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to go to this practice, which I really liked.

https://www.beatalewismd.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 09:20:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my experience, $400 is standard for the initial appt, then $200 for follow-ups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 07:34:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe just keep the dog to certain places in the house so he doesn't get fur everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-28 07:29:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bagel pretzels? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-27 21:45:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So. Cute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-27 21:43:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same. Everytime I browse the apartment apps in the summer, similar apartments are like at least $300+ more a month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-27 18:43:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love air kneads </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-26 00:27:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What breed is she? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-26 00:25:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wasn't the flag on the left also the Spanish colonial flag? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 23:09:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where are you located? I may need a financial advisor in the near future </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 22:44:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 22:37:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Garfield, is that you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 22:24:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please more Taft! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 22:19:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is a pretty kitty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 22:11:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Husky? I'm sorry I think that is a baby cloud! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 09:24:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No sound? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 09:16:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On OkCupid you can mark Don't want kids, and you can search by that too I think. Might be a paid feature </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 08:09:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He even knocked that girls shoe off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 07:49:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/lostredditors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 07:46:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She shows the toes and the nose! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 01:54:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That seems fitting for the three-eyed raven </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 01:53:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love Bran. He's always just off to the side and comes in saying some weird shit out of nowhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-25 00:52:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 09:14:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I imagine these aren't even useful anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 09:12:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah this seems excessive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 09:10:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that Hamtaro!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 09:06:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Baby 🤗 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 07:41:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And dislocates my shoulders </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 07:38:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 05:22:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Excuse me, I have to go to outer space now"

I know the feel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 05:12:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The toucan has been a nun all along </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 04:35:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, fellow queen! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 04:21:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What episode is this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 04:18:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And you guys thought Andy was special... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 04:15:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OMG this needs to be put in giant bold letters with neon lights all over these subs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 02:24:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Were your heels in your have because you had to take off your shoes? Or because you were running? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-24 01:01:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love him and I'm coming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-23 20:44:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes that sounds like my kitty! But he's gray striped and white. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-23 20:39:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I will never understand how a person could not think the part where the Sept gets blown up is not epic as hell.

Like I'm still shook by it

Also Battle of the Bastards!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-23 05:22:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is so cute! The church is pink! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-23 05:12:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The people who make these must have some shitty friends if they go out to dinner with them and they're always on their phones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-23 04:52:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OMG if I could only listen to one album for the rest of my life it would be FOB's Folie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-23 04:31:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah idk why people are bothered by others not having children. If I were a parent, I would think, 'Good, more resources for my child' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-23 04:21:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I think the homeless in NYC are more spread out around the city and they can get around more easily cause of the train. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-23 04:14:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe Sunset Park in Brooklyn. Depending how close to the train you are could be like 35 minutes to Manhattan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-23 01:59:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't understand why they want people to ogle their stomach. That's not even the baby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-23 01:54:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, it's true! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-23 01:39:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That is quite the transition! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 19:15:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Reminds me of these candies 🤤 https://www.candywarehouse.com/trolli-strawberry-puffs-gummy-candy-3lb-box/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 19:12:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, the colors are Presto gel, pink is 179 and white is 4. I'm not sure what brand the sparkly powder is, but the little pot said artist powder, and it's Japanese. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 04:18:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do they actually sell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Looks like Candy 🍬 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-22 03:34:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-21 21:40:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Andy is something else.

But I love how April looks at the camera everytime he does or says something especially dumb. Like she is still surprised lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-21 21:38:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is no quiet. There is only Doc McStuffins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-21 09:05:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a cute kitty! He looks like an Australian Mist Cat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 21:08:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But how do I avoid stress in the meantime? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 21:06:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know, same. Like I'm many years over 21, and when I get carded I'm like oh this is still a thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 08:39:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >getting fucked by immigrants.

wut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 08:36:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or just go away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 08:26:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah isn't the whole point of wanting resources to provide for future children? You'd want the children to be healthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-20 08:23:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah and what about when a man retires? Most don't hit it rich and have to live somewhat more frugally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 23:08:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OMG where do I get a French toast bagel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 22:58:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 17:45:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was just looking at Azores for a vacation! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 17:31:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 14:47:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The placement of that bathtub...oof </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 14:23:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So if she failed and it wasn't her... Or the company... What was it?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 14:22:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How does this work then? Would you end up paying more for a trip to book with her? Also is she even a good travel agent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 09:19:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 07:27:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't understand, why is Barney now Germanic people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 07:04:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah and why is she boasting about getting a master's degree when you don't even need a degree to be in an MLM? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 07:02:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When my cat was a kitten, the first time he saw a bee he caught it and ate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 06:41:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Belle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 06:35:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TopShop has personal shoppers that will help you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 06:34:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 8) I buy coffee every morning at the Bodega next door for a dollar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 04:27:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of love! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 04:25:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah have they never heard of life insurance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 00:43:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean where did you get it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 00:39:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What globe is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 00:10:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm glad you decided not to go! Besides a pool party doesn't seem like a good place for a 5 day old preemie either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 00:06:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same. How will they know if we don't tell them 🤷

I also like to inform people that they have skin cancer or aids. I go by their aura. 🧙‍♂️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-19 00:03:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OMG how is this so perfect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 15:25:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I feel like the whole last season was more of an epilogue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 15:20:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The architect! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 15:18:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And if you notice in the date one where Leslie gets an MRI, he says she could have triplets right away while looking at the scan! Foreshadowing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 14:17:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What time of year was this taken? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 13:59:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't even think about that movie without getting upset </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 08:03:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/fakealbumcovers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 08:01:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also isn't Tom Holland like twelve? I was thinking Tom Hiddleston when I first looked at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 07:59:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok but counterpoint... Chris Hemsworth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 07:27:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How. Perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-18 07:13:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah but you can have stability and democracy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 23:16:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/catsmirin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 23:09:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah what is his beef with Frozen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 22:46:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah true, but the daughter in the sauce didn't get burned or anything, so she is probably fine with what she was doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 22:41:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok well by that logic, we should all be wearing rash burkas to get full coverage! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 12:19:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess people don't like emoji reactions 🤷

But I did really like the joke though :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 10:50:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have never been charged for changing a flight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-17 10:40:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd be scared it would vacuum them too hard 😕 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cult Beauty uses beautiful model with visibly blemished skin! For an ad about blemished skin! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-16 05:34:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Refreshing!

https://www.reddit.com/r/SkincareAddiction/comments/cqqvv6/misc_refreshing_cult_beauty_uses_beautiful_model/?utm_medium=android_app&utm_source=share </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A galactic feel </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-04 03:25:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is there more to life...than having perfect pail skin? Am I becoming self-aware? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 04:31:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A guy saw me without makeup.

He invited me over to play video games. I had a really bad reaction to squalane oil, and had broken out in cysts and clogged pores all over my face. I was embarrassed, scared, nervous. But I didn't want my skin to stop me from having fun, so I went to go see him. I figured that if he thought I was cool then he wouldn't think my skin was a big deal. So we hung out and... he didn't look or treat me any differently. We had a lot of fun. We stayed up late and he told me he liked me... I asked him "why?" haha. I guess maybe beauty really is only skin deep.

But really I hope he can be my new 20k boyfie ❤️😉🤗💁 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Kitty kept his job! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-27 03:25:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How can I get rid of my dark circles?? Pic of me and my porcelain fur </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-26 05:47:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sweet dreams 💕 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-26 02:29:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Curled paw and sleepy boy </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-26 00:29:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> From r/urbanhell, on a post showing a picture of a group of apartment buildings in China </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 08:25:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Beige with black tape, plus flower accent nail </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-25 05:51:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Most vicious mittens this side of the Mississippi! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-21 22:35:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Pink Aurora Nails with Pearl Accents! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-06 04:43:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How much do I tip house cleaner? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-29 22:04:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am having someone come to clean and organize my apartment for four hours today. How much is appropriate to tip? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is this? Saw it on the subway </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-25 15:49:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Angled French with gold stripe! On gel extensions </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-23 03:39:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> When do you cut your nails if you have acrylic or hard gel extensions? [Question] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-13 20:02:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey guys,


I recently got hard gel extensions done (have had them for about three weeks now with one refill).


So your natural nails obviously are still growing, I'm just wondering when and how (if ever) do they get cut if you just keep getting refills? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Maroon and Copper Pink! With a little bling! 🤩 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-09 06:43:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Help! I feel the sun when I'm outside! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-31 02:35:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How do I block the sun? Is my sunscreen enough? I am wearing SPF 300 but I still feel the sun touching my pail skin. 😭 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Gel extensions with some glitter and chrome! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-26 01:42:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Giant snail slithering on your face? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-08 02:01:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't mind if I do! Just thinking about it makes my skin extra pail 💆

You pores would never.

🐌💆🐌

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Does LSAT Ticket have to be printed in Color or B/W? Or does it not matter? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-29 03:06:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like this is a dumb question but I know they are super strict about everything so just checking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Haul] New Products for enhanced routine, including Muji, Belif, Caudalie, and More... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-16 01:39:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Samson here for FURBALL SATURDAY </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-02 19:17:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> App for LSAT prep? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-31 01:40:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi all,
I am beginning my studying for the LSAT, and was wondering if anyone has any opinions for good phone apps for prepping for the LSAT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
