<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject34</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 17:16:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oversized shirt girl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Self harming and the hospital </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 04:08:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can I go to the hospital for self harming? I’m kinda scared of the idea of being in a mental hospital but I don’t know how deep in the mental illness hole is deep enough for that kind of help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 02:39:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am deprived of cuddles at the moment who wants an internet hug </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Truly expressing yourself </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 21:08:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does anyone else just get so annoyed and frustrated when you share online or in person how you truly feel inside and what you’re thinking and people just act like “everyone has anxiety, you’re not special” or that you’re faking it/trying to be deep? Like dude, I’m just trying to get this out of my system to I don’t have another breakdown and SH, I’m not trying to be “deep” just real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 18:51:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wore leggings today... bad idea... it hurts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 18:03:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bro I got a pack of 10 big bandages for when I SH and I used 9 of them in a week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Here’s mine </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 17:49:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 07:34:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The bleeding has stopped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 07:29:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sounds cool, you should do it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 07:28:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because of how the bandages are and it hurts to move it anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Seeking advice </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 07:04:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I SH-ed worse than usual tonight and I bandaged it up but I can’t really move my arm around too much and I have to go to school tomorrow and Wednesday + I don’t want my parents finding out again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 06:55:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My parents only know about two times I’ve SH’d and my mom scared me into showing my wounds to her and now I make sure if I do tell someone about me SH-ing that it won’t go to my parents </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 06:49:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SOFT HOURS HAVE ARRIVED 🥺🥺🥺 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 06:42:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I first came out to myself it felt weird to say that I like women too but now I can talk all day about how amazing they are. Congrats on coming out and I hope you have a great day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 06:30:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The amount of times I’ve stopped breathing because of pretty girls- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Don’t you love it when your playlist just: </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 05:17:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 05:12:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do. Whenever I hear my name it gets tied back to all the things my mother has done. Thinking of changing it when I can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 02:56:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me: *daydreaming all day about moving to a different country, getting a girlfriend, and cuddling with her forever*
Me: Yup, 100% worth it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 02:49:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Girls living in a completely different continent and that don’t even speak English </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Battling SH urges </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 04:52:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Battling SH urges feels like the toughest thing in the world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 02:30:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They’re alright, I prefer actual people who read them + provide commentary but I’ll watch TTS Reddit videos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Itchy healing wounds </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 01:36:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does anyone else’s SH wounds get pretty itchy while healing but you can’t itch because they still hurt? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 01:34:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Plan on taking over the world and making gay marriage legal in every country </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Me feeling my mental health rapidly declining and just waiting for that one thing to send me into a complete breakdown and wondering why I’m like this </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 01:32:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 06:05:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then they try speaking Chinese to them and they don’t understand because they’re actually Thai </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 06:01:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or when people just assume every Asian is from like same country, that’s also annoying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 05:51:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I never get it when people say “all Asians look the same” like sis it’s not that hard to tell people apart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Taking care of wounds </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 18:18:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How would I properly take care of my SH wounds so that they don’t get infected and have to tell my parents again/go to the doctor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 17:50:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The girl in the black shirt is Shawn from Fanxyred and the girl in the red and white striped shirt is Roy from Fanxyred </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 17:36:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yes~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 16:21:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guess I got a type lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Everyone needs to watch this oh my gosh I get gayer every time </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 04:49:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 02:37:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s Marco, she’s in Fanxyred </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 01:32:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Her name is Lee Jooyoung, she’s a Korean actress </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 23:52:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have you hear their most recent song? It’s really good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 23:51:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Her name is Liu Yuxin, she’s also in The9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 23:50:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I know about them, they’re currently called Fanxyred </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 23:48:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Her name is Lu Keran, she’s in a Chinese girl group called The9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I present to you the women I am a gigantic simp for I FREAKING LOVE THEM SO MUCH~ </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 23:42:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 23:11:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Especially since I live in Canada </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> New me </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 20:01:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ve been trying to get out of the self hate hole I’ve dug over the years but it’s very hard and I want to give up a lot of the time. I always avoid mirrors, pictures, smiling. I’ve been trying to get used to looking at myself in mirrors, in pictures, and taking better care of myself but I need help, I’m not too sure how to do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 01:28:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Once my wounds scab up and stop hurting yup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> She found out again </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 01:25:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whenever my best friend and I vent to each other about our struggles with SH her mom looks at our messages and then calls my mom. My mom then knows once again that I'm hurting myself (I really don't want her to know) and I feel alone since her mom looks over a group chat we have with other friends so I can't vent there and I can't vent to my best friend since her mom will definitely see. This just really annoys me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 20:50:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. I always see people talking about cutting/how to stop cutting but since I don't cut (I scratch) a lot of the things they talk about I can't exactly relate to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 04:07:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I started medication for my anxiety earlier this month but I haven’t seen any improvements yet. I try to make myself fall asleep with melatonin + other drugs (Gravol, Benadryl, etc) but it’s becoming less effective so I feel I have to take more but I’m kind of scared of taking too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> High anxiety before bed </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 04:00:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lot of the time my anxiety gets really high like about 2 or so hours before I go to sleep. I have uncontrollable thoughts, the screaming in my head gets really loud, I can’t stay still, and I eventually get sent into an attack where I usually SH. How can I stop this from happening so often? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My mother </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 05:12:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My mother found out I SH, some of my friends do it, and we have a group chat where we talk about what we’re going through. She then said my generation’s entitled (I’m Gen Z) and that we’re encouraging each other to do it and go further with it (we’re definitely not) and that made me very upset and I almost SH’d again but went for a run on the treadmill while crying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 02:18:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me @ Liu Yuxin from The9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> “Just focus” </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 03:01:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My sleep has been horrible for a long time, I have severe anxiety, I feel awful everyday, and on top of all that I’ve been having trouble concentrating and my mother just told me to “just focus” and I feel even worse now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I feel it coming again </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 02:22:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's happening again, I can feel another breakdown brewing. It feels like there's nothing I can do about it until the screaming in my head comes again and I can't take it anymore I hyperventilate, cry, feel as if the world's ending, SH, and more. It's always super exhausting to go through these episodes and when I try to seek help from my friends or dad they just tell me to think good thoughts and not to SH but all I can hear is the screaming in my head getting louder and I feel the only solution (even thought it's only temporary) is to SH (I'm still dealing with my SH injury from the 17th, it was a rough day). I would like some advice or tips & tricks to deal with these episodes because it's gotten worse lately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anxiety tics? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 20:56:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I feel my anxiety's high or I my trauma gets set off I have these uncontrollable moments. I tilt my head, throw my arm, shutter my shoulder, or blink aggressively. Is this something I should be concerned about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 20:18:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here. My mom used to beat me as a child then as I grew older it switched to emotional/verbal. The beating still has an impact on me, whenever I hear a loud sound caused by someone being angry or when someone yells because they're angry I have flashbacks and bad dreams. Now I can't handle people being mad or people yelling. I'm still scared that my mom's gonna hit me when she gets mad. My therapist isn't much help because she says things like "spend time around her", "forgive her", and "she can't control herself when she's mad". It's gotten to the point where when I'm having panic attacks caused by what happens I SH. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I did it again </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 03:38:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I SH I scratch myself. I do it when I’m super overwhelmed and feel like it’s the only way to get that sense of relief, even if it’s only a little better. After my mother pushed me into a massive panic attack I scratched my left arm harder than I have before. It was super red, hurt a ton, and had orange fluid coming from it (I don’t know what it was). It’s been about four hours since I did it and it still really hurts and I’m still upset about what happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 22:02:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oof I got 7 fingers down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 19:20:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Every time I try to talk about an issue to my mom she says “stop trying to fight with me” or “why do you alway have to start a fight”. It’s very frustrating when I can’t speak my mind to her without her accusing me of wanting to fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 04:18:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know the feeling of having a rude therapist. The one I had before the current one I go to would call me spoiled after I would tell her what my mom does and has done to me. Glad she left that hospital and I got a new, nice therapist. If I were you I’d go to someone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 22:27:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’d love to let it out but I don’t want attention drawn towards me (granted I’m in my room and the rest of my family usually isn’t on the top floor but I don’t want them to come in while I’m letting everything out) so I’ve resorted to things I probably shouldn’t be doing but I feel it’s the only way I can get it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is it normal to have constant screaming in your head? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 21:17:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like I have constant screaming in my head that will get louder the worse/more anxious I feel. Is this normal for people with anxiety? Can I stop it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Too much anxiety to call my therapist </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 07:01:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have been in therapy since summer of 2019 and for the majority of my time in therapy the visits have been in person but since this corona thing came to Canada we have had to restore to doing phone calls. Me and my therapist have set up certain dates for calls but she has also said that I can call her anytime if I need to talk about something. At this current time my anxiety is high than it is usually and I feel the need to talk to her but I feel if I just call her randomly I’ll be interrupting her or disturbing her. I know she did say that I can call her anytime but these thoughts keep filling my head.

How can I push my anxiety away enough so that I am able to give her another call? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
