<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject3</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> When to contact faculty for supervision </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 23:34:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm planning on applying for PhD programs for Fall 2021 and I'm not sure when would be a good time to contact professors to see if they're available to supervise next year. I don't have a specific research idea in mind but I do have a few vague areas of interest and I've listed professors at each program whose interests are similar to mine. Should I contact them before or after I decide exactly what I want to research?

In case this matters, I'm applying to programs in Canada, mostly in Ontario and a couple in BC and I'm looking at sociology and gender/women's studies programs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> When to contact faculty for potential supervision </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 05:30:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm planning on applying for PhD programs for Fall 2021 and I'm not sure when would be a good time to contact professors to see if they're available to supervise next year. I don't have a specific research idea in mind but I do have a few vague areas of interest and I've listed professors at each program whose interests are similar to mine. Should I contact them before or after I decide exactly what I want to research?

In case this matters, I'm applying to programs in Canada, mostly in Ontario and a couple in BC and I'm looking at sociology and gender/women's studies programs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Do most PhD programs in Canada involve interviews? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 01:52:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've heard that interviews are usually part of the grad school admissions process more generally but the websites for the programs I plan on applying for don't mention interviews. Are interviews more of a thing in the US and does it depend on the program? Most of the programs I'm applying for are in Ontario and BC in social science fields. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 18:39:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same. I've gotten so used to holding it in and now it takes more effort to let it out than to keep it in. I usually just get a lump in my throat and tear up a little but that's the extent of it. I haven't sobbed in years and I don't think I'm able to anymore

I'm so happy for you, OP that you were able to let it all out and feel better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Union involvement on resume? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 04:25:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it a good idea to put my union involvement experience from my previous job on my resume? Or does that depend on where I'm applying? I know that if I'm applying for a job at a union (or any pro-labour rights org) then it might be a good idea, since most of these jobs require union experience.

But if I'm applying for a job at a workplace that is not unionized, I'm thinking it may not look good, especially since I was also involved in getting us unionized at my last job (which I probably wouldn't mention). And I don't know how union involvement would look if I apply for a job at a workplace that's already unionized. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-22 20:54:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Watching Netflix and listening to podcasts without headphones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [personal] Dealing with skin purging from chemical exfoliant </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 23:16:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I started using Paula's Choice Skin Revealing 10% AHA body lotion for karitosis pilaris on my arms and acne scars on my neck, back, and shoulders and I'm getting pimples on these areas. I looked into it online and it might be skin purging, which is a normal reaction to chemical exfoliants. Is there a way to deal with this? Is it better to leave it alone or can I continue applying the chemical exfoliant on the pimple? I couldn't find a clear answer when I googled it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Considering getting help but... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-05 02:22:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm considering seeking professional mental health support which is long overdue but I'm still really hesitant. The main issue is that I'm not as comfortable opening up to a stranger as I am with people I already know/trust, but I also don't want to use friends as free therapy or burden them with emotional labour they may not always have the capacity for.

I've tried therapy before and I just find it really awkward and I'm not good at articulating my thoughts/feelings/problems when I'm feeling awkward. For some reason, I also feel like I'm being judged even though I know it's their job not to judge, and I worry that they'll give bad advice which will make it a waste of time and money.

Is there a way to overcome the awkwardness of opening up to a stranger and are clients obligated to always take the advice given to them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Therapy/counselling concerns </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 02:51:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm considering seeking professional mental health support which is way overdue but I'm still really hesitant. The main issue is that I'm not as comfortable opening up to a stranger as I am with people I already know/trust, but I also don't want to use friends as free therapy or burden them with emotional labour they may not always have the capacity for.

I've tried therapy before and I just find it really awkward and I'm not good at articulating my thoughts/feelings/problems when I'm feeling awkward. For some reason, I also feel like I'm being judged even though I know it's their job not to judge, and I worry that they'll give bad advice which will make it a waste of time and money.

Is there a way to overcome the awkwardness of opening up to a stranger and are clients obligated to always take the advice given to them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Therapy/counselling concerns </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 02:21:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm considering seeking professional mental health support which is way overdue but I'm still really hesitant. The main issue is that I'm not as comfortable opening up to a stranger as I am with people I already know/trust, but I also don't want to use friends as free therapy or burden them with emotional labour they may not always have the capacity for.

I've tried therapy before and I just find it really awkward and I'm not good at articulating my thoughts/feelings/problems when I'm feeling awkward. For some reason, I also feel like I'm being judged even though I know it's their job not to judge, and I worry that they'll give bad advice which will make it a waste of time and money.

Is there a way to overcome the awkwardness of opening up to a stranger and are clients obligated to always take the advice given to them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 18:47:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is there a body wash version of this that you're using or are you using the facial cleanser? Does it work for acne scars too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Aztec Indian Healing Clay </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 19:59:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been reading a lot of good things about this face mask and I'm wondering if it's actually as good as people say it is. Would you recommend it to someone with acne-prone, sensitive, combination skin? Does it exfoliate or do I still need to exfoliate separately? Do I have to wash my face first or does it replace cleanser? Does it work on acne/acne scars and eczema on the body too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Product question] Aztec Indian Healing Clay </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 08:35:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been reading a lot of good things about this face mask and I'm wondering if it's actually as good as people say it is. Would you recommend it to someone with acne-prone, sensitive, combination skin? Does it exfoliate or do I still need to exfoliate separately? Do I have to wash my face first or does it replace cleanser? Does it work on acne/acne scars and eczema on the body too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Aztec Indian healing clay </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 08:25:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is a PhD program worth applying for if you don't meet every single qualification? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 08:08:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been looking into some PhD programs and most of the programs I'm interested in require or prefer a master's degree in the same subject (sociology), which I don't have. But I do have a BA in sociology and I'm completing my master's in a similar social science field. I'm sure it depends on the school and other factors, but do grad programs generally still consider applicants who have most of the qualifications and do they care about undergrad degrees? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 21:05:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RE: the new student benefit (CESB)

Do students who were already on CERB now have to switch over to CESB or can they stay on CERB? My understanding is that CERB had already expanded its eligibility criteria to some students (i.e. those who are low income and/or were planning on working during the summer but can't because of COVID), which was when I applied and now I don't know what to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Where do I vote when living on residence? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-27 04:47:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm moving from Burlington to Brantford for university and I'm confused as to which riding I have to vote in during the upcoming election. Do I vote where my permanent address is in Burlington or do I vote in whichever riding I'm living in at the time even if it's temporary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Updating driver's license address when living on residence </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-09 05:13:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll be moving into residence for school this coming September. Do I still need to update the address on my driver's license and other government documents even if I'm living there for 8 months and will probably move back home after?

And do I put my residence address or my current home address on the tax forms I need to fill out for a job? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-22 01:34:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I forgot the a in "activism" so it ended up being "ctivism" (I think spell check on Word was turned off - I'll definitely make sure it's turned on from now on) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-20 19:21:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Public Policy program at UofT is two years, tuition is $20K a year, and they only offered me $3000 in funding, so I would have to go on OSAP and end up in debt if I went. Also, I know a lot of people who've gone to UofT and it sounds too stressful and competitive with the bell curving of grades and lack of mental health support. I just don't think it's worth the unnecessary stress.
Laurier's program is one year, tuition is only ~$8500, and they offered me enough funding to cover most of my tuition and residence fees ($14 500) through a TA job and a scholarship. Also, the program itself (Social Justice & Community Engagement) is a little bit more interesting to me and I think I'll enjoy it more than the one at UofT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Typo on my resume but still got an interview </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-20 19:10:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Has this happened to anyone else? Is there still a chance of me getting the job? Has anyone actually gotten a job offer despite a typo? I didn't notice the typo (my mistake for not proofreading enough times) until after the interview was scheduled.

I'm guessing they didn't notice it or don't care. Should I address it in the interview?

Not sure if it matters, but it's a research assistant job and attention to detail wasn't mentioned in the posting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-20 18:21:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I accepted my offer to Laurier. I also got into UofT so it was between these two </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-18 23:53:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven’t heard back but it doesn’t matter anymore since I already accepted my offer at another school </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One application for two positions at the same organization? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-28 02:31:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm applying for two positions at the same organization. Is it a good idea to make one cover letter and resume for both jobs (since there's a bit of overlap between positions), or a separate application for each? And which one would be more convenient for the person receiving the applications? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> NSLSC (Ontario) still says "in repayment" but I already paid off my loans </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-02 22:11:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I paid off my student loans two weeks ago and it says I owe $0.00 but my NSLSC account still says I'm in repayment. When should I expect the status to change? Is there also a letter they send me to confirm that I paid off my loans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 16:39:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! Is there an option to focus on social justice and education? I didn't see that anywhere on the program website. Or is that just your research interest? I'm also interested in social justice and education.

I don't remember what grading scale I used. I just know I got a B+. I just googled B+ equivalent on a 4 point scale since McMaster (where I did my undergrad) uses a 12 point scale. I did my undergrad in sociology and I never took a political science course which is why I was a little surprised I got in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-13 04:51:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually got in last week! My GPA was 3.3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-12 16:44:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you don't mind my asking, did they offer you any funding through internal scholarships or a TA or RA position?And does it cover all of tuition? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-12 16:11:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Still waiting... But I got offers for other schools I applied to in mid-January. You'd think that because Ryerson's deadline is earlier they would get back to us sooner but no.

For those of you who have been accepted (or know someone who has), is there funding and did they offer a TA or RA position as part of the funding? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-10 17:55:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same. I've seen a few episodes and it does have some funny moments, but it's hard to enjoy with the audience laughing every few seconds. I really wanted to like it though but the laughing ruins it for me. At least it's not cringey like Fuller House and other multi-cam shows imo. If it was single camera I would love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-06 04:40:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beth was FINALLY happy and working a job she loves and then Randall had to ruin it. For a second I thought Randall was about to suggest giving up city council.

Plus, do the girls really need a sitter? Aren’t they old enough to take care of themselves? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-06 01:22:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! B+ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Grad program funding </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-06 01:11:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just got an offer of admission to the Master of Public Policy program with a $3000 entrance scholarship. I know there's the mandatory paid internship component, but are there also any other funding sources like TA, RA, or work/study opportunities that I get during the fall semester? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MA Social Justice & Community Engagement program TA position </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-03 03:10:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got an email saying the admissions committee is recommending my admission into the SJCE program with funding through a TAship. When should I expect an offer letter if it gets approved?

If I get an offer and funding, how does the TA thing work? Is there still an application process like any other job (i.e. interview, references, etc)? Do I get to choose which course I TA for? What courses are available for me to TA for? How hard is it to balance TA work (i.e. grading, teaching, helping students, etc) with my own coursework?

If I would rather be a research assistant, is it possible to ask for an RAship instead?

And how is the program in general?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-02 22:42:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I took math 1k03 when I was in first year in 2014 and I got an A+, and I'm not generally good at math. But it depends on the professor. I had Andie Burazin who did a really good job explaining difficult concepts and her tests were based on practice questions we had done before. She would basically copy and paste the practice questions on to the test and just change the numbers. The TA was also really helpful and she held study sessions the day before to review the practice questions. So, if you have Andie and as long as you study using the practice questions, you'll be fine.

But keep in mind that this was five years ago, so I'm not sure if she's still at Mac or if she teaches the same way.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> TAship questions </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-02 18:28:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got an email from one of the masters programs I applied for saying they're recommending my admission into the program with funding through a TAship.

If this gets approved by the graduate faculty and I get an offer and funding, how does the TA thing work? Is there still an application process like any other job (i.e. interview, references, etc)? Do I get to choose which course I TA for? How hard is it to balance TA work (i.e. grading, teaching, helping students, etc) with my own coursework?

If I would rather be a research assistant, is it possible to ask for an RAship instead?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-02 00:00:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You’re not alone. I’m still waiting to hear from all of the schools I applied to. The only response I got was from one program that said they’re recommending my admission to the graduate faculty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First round of acceptances question </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-01 17:48:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does anyone know if programs only send out acceptances this round or all admission decisions including rejections? I see that people have gotten offers already (congrats!) and I haven't heard from anyone, except for one program that said they're recommending my admission to the faculty of graduate studies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-22 04:18:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you know if they only send out acceptances this round or all admission decisions including rejections? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-22 04:17:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congrats! Do you know if they only send out acceptances this round or all admission decisions including rejections? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Master of Public Policy admission decision </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-22 03:03:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I applied for the Master of Public Policy program and I was wondering when I should expect to hear back. I saw that other schools have started sending out offer letters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Grad school acceptances (MPPA program) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-22 02:51:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I applied for the Master of Public Policy and Administration program back in December and I was wondering when I should expect to hear back. I saw that other schools have started to send out admission decisions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Post interview follow-up advice </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-06 18:20:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had an interview recently and they said they would let me know whether I got the job or not within two weeks. It's been three weeks and I still haven't heard from them. I was thinking of sending a follow-up email asking about my application status if I don't hear back by the end of the week. Is that a good idea? How do I follow up without coming across as impatient or desparate?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-02 19:11:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love that he didn't even say he's nice now when he refused to take advantage of Rebecca </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-05 17:58:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  I do have a B+ average. I also have some basic knowledge of politics and public policy from soc courses (mostly Marxism/neo-Marxism and neoliberalism) which I can build on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-05 17:50:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mac for poli sci isn't my first choice. I'm more interested in public policy at Ryerson (already applied) and UofT. I'm applying to Mac's MA political science program because I did my undergrad there and I've worked and volunteered in Hamilton, so I'm familiar with the city. Also, Mac's poli sci program gives you the option to focus on areas of research including public policy, which is what I plan on doing if I get in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> MA Political Science admissions </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-05 05:20:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm applying for the MA PoliSci program. What are the chances of me getting in with just a BA in sociology and having never taken poli sci courses during undergrad? It says the required credential is a poli sci degree or a related discipline.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-05 18:58:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Villanuevas are a very open and sex positive family (maybe except Alba). If Jane is comfortable taking her grandmother to a sex shop and convincing her to start masturbating I think Mateo would be fine narrating his mother’s sex life lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-11 04:53:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “Why are you so quiet?”

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 23:53:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> - Judy King mispronouncing Poussey’s name and Taystee’s reaction “she called her pussy”

- Piper: “I’m not your wife”  Suzanne: “I threw my pie for you”

- Pennsatucky: "I can take care of myself chingchong china doll" Leanne: "she's Japanese Scottish you ignorant dumbass" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-05 23:42:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was 14 when I decided having kids was not for me so you’re definitely not too young </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-29 19:45:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same. I regret feeling bad for that cunt when she was trapped in the riot and thought to be an inmate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-13 19:06:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Scars on legs and hands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Where can I find body concealer? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-13 01:20:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I couldn't find anything at Sephora or Shoppers and I don't like buying makeup online because I want to try it on first. Also, what brands would you recommend?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-02 22:30:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are no sex scenes but there is a bit of nudity  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-25 22:54:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m glad I’m not the only one! I just find travelling more stressful than fun bc of the packing, going to the airport, sitting in a crowded airplane, screaming kids, jet lag, luggage getting lost, unpacking and packing again, possibility of getting lost in a foreign place, language barriers, etc. I don’t think it’s worth it. Although I do understand the appeal of exploring different cultures, meeting interesting people, trying new things, etc, it’s just not for me and I’m sure there are other ways to explore new things without travelling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-24 05:02:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was thinking that too. If she can’t afford/doesn’t want more kids it would be smart to at least consider investing in a longer term form of birth control like tubal litigation or IUD. And I’m still mad at Hal for refusing to get snipped  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-24 04:55:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually the oldest kid Francis was sent to military school bc his parents couldn’t discipline him. There was even a flashback episode that shows Lois spoiling the hell out of baby Francis and Hal being the strict parent so obviously it’s Lois’s fault Francis grew up to be an uncontrollable little shit that had to be sent to military school.
But you’re so right about everything else! Watching this show is such a good form of birth control  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-07 22:15:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They resolved it at the end when Petra said her kids act like mini adults and JR said that she would love to meet them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-10 17:49:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not to mention trying to convince her grandmother to start masturbating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-07 02:57:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most MSW programs require a BSW and even for the ones that don’t require a BSW, the chances of getting accepted are very slim </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-02-01 22:01:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you know what types of questions the references are asked? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Unauthorized transunion charge on credit card (CAN) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-19 05:15:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> On my credit card statement I keep seeing a $16.95 charge from Transunion. I searched online for ways to cancel it but it says I have to log into my transunion account and cancel my membership or call customer service. The only problem is that I don't remember making an account with them. I had never even heard of transunion before I looked at my credit card statement. Will calling customer service solve the issue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-17 22:22:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ll just take your word for it. I can’t watch that again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-17 22:18:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There is a town in Ontario called Riverdale and there was a shooting there a few months ago
https://toronto.ctvnews.ca/shooting-in-riverdale-leaves-1-man-seriously-injured-1.3656208
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-17 22:02:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What does the redhead at the mall have to do with Jack's death? I don't remember seeing her before this episode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Post-degree BSW program </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-16 22:34:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm applying for the post-degree BSW program and I have a ton of questions for those currently in that program. How easy or hard is to get into? Is there a placement option and what kinds of placements are there? Any tips on preparing for the SWAT? I know it's a 2 year program but is it possible to finish the program in less than 2 years? What's your overall experience been like so far in the program and placements?

I don't know if this makes a difference but currently, I'm in my 4th and final year at McMaster completing a BA in sociology and I've taken social work courses as electives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Post-degree BSW program </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-16 22:20:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm applying for the post-degree BSW program at York and I have a ton of questions for those currently in that program. How easy or hard is to get into? What kinds of placements are there? Any tips for the social justice statement and resume part of the application? I know it's a 2 year program but is it possible to finish the program in less than 2 years? What's your overall experience been like so far in the program and placements?

I don't know if this makes a difference but currently, I'm in my 4th and final year at McMaster completing a BA in sociology and I've taken social work courses as electives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-16 03:20:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My school does have reading week in February so I was thinking of getting in done then.

I've seen Dr. Khaled twice and you're right. He was a little rough with my cat but I thought that was normal since my cat was uncooperative and wouldn't stay still (also normal?). But other than that I thought he was ok and I thought the receptionists were ok too. They're just super annoying and won't stop calling me, so I blocked their number.
If I decide to go to another vet, should I still let Askey know so they can remove my cat from the system and stop calling me?

Update: I just looked at Askey's reviews online they are terrible. I'm definitely switching vets! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Cat vaccination update bylaw </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-16 01:03:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got a call from my vet (Askey Animal Hospital) saying I need to get my cat's vaccinations updated, which is required by law in Burlington. I do plan on updating his vaccines ASAP but money is tight right now and I'm busy with school and work, so I'm figuring out a good time to take my cat to the vet. But in the meantime, can I get in trouble for not updating his vaccine soon? How harsh are the consequences for not updating vaccines? Can vets get the SPCA or the police involved? Also, are there less expensive vet clinics in Burlington or other ways around the financial burden of vet visits?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-01-08 20:00:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is Ian still a paramedic? I totally forgot he worked as a paramedic until he saved the pastor's life..
Carl's an idiot. How the fuck did he not expect Cassidy to assume he was proposing without giving him a chance to explain that it's a promise ring?
I really hope Kev doesn't take the dominance thing too far and hurt anyone. And I'm starting to feel bad for Svetlana </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-28 20:57:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Update: second professor said no and I decided not to ask the PhD student prof

So I’m no longer applying to grad school </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-28 20:56:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Update: second professor said no and I decided not to ask the PhD student prof

So I’m no longer applying to grad school </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-18 00:51:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s been almost 2 weeks. A follow up email sounds like a good idea but I’m worried about coming across as impatient and I know how busy professors are so I don’t want to put pressure on them.
Thanks for the advice  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Reference letters </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-17 00:44:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm applying to graduate school and all of the programs I'm applying to need 2 references and so far I've only gotten one (application deadlines are within 2 months). The other prof I contacted hasn't gotten back to me yet. Unfortunately, the two profs I emailed are the only two who know me well enough. There is also a third course instructor I had who I think would have good things to say about me, but the only problem is that she's still a PhD student and I've heard we should only get well known professors. So should I still ask her to write a reference letter or wait for my other professor to reply? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-14 21:07:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I second this rant. I work at a grocery store and it’s a fucking nightmare during Xmas season! The same 10 songs played on repeat, the extra hours just standing there scanning items and making small talk with strangers, etc. I cannot wait until Xmas is over! I feel like the Grinch at work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-12-14 05:39:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here. I think the real black hood somehow coerced the janitor into pretending to be the black hood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-11 01:12:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do what Chang did </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-10-11 01:11:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bathrooms are my safe haven. I don't know what I would do without them. I also try to drink a lot of water during the event so I can actually have an excuse to go  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Caption this perfectly timed photo </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-19 23:55:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-19 21:49:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not a full scene but the way Richard said "what the fuck" when Jared made the joke about Dinesh's gold chain and putting his penis in his mother's butthole made me laugh harder than the joke itself.

The scenes in that one episode in S1 where Erlich was trying not to be racist

When that guy was explaining what limp biscuit is and Jared adds "sometimes it's a wheat thin" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-19 20:39:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Big veiny muscular body builder arms on guys  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-12 18:53:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was obsessed with Twilight and changed by last name on Facebook to Cullen. I'm so ashamed of it now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-12 18:39:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It ain't me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-12 04:38:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have to study </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-12 04:33:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Listen to them. Don't dismiss their problems or say "other people have it worse". Don't try to fix them. Give them space.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-10 20:04:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Arrested Development - Annyan/Hello! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-10 04:27:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TJ Miller
Retta
Kumail Nanjiani
Aziz Ansari
Aparna Nancherla </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-10 00:57:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As much as I hated Joan and wanted her dead, I have a feeling she'll survive. I'm sure she's smart and strong enough to find a way out of the box and somehow dig herself out.

And how did Boomer not suspect that Liz was behind what happened to Sonia? Boomer knew Liz was witness x and that she felt threatened by Sonia and Liz gave her the tea to give to Sonia right before Sonia went to medical.

But overall I'm pretty satisfied with the episode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-08 05:19:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sloth or panda </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-08 01:14:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> April Ludgate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-07 00:23:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're definitely not alone in this. I have the same fear when other cars are around. My G (highway) test is coming up and I get really nervous during tests. It's also during rush hour that's double the anxiety

When changing lanes I rely more on my blind spots and signalling than the mirrors. If you need to change a lane and there's someone in your blind spot they're usually nice enough to make room for you if they see you signalling

Good luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-06 23:49:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> During the school year I usually say I have a lot of studying to do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-06 23:04:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aaron Paul </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-05 22:41:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Moderately. I only follow rules that make sense to me and ignore the ones that don't  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-05 22:06:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vee from OITNB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2017-08-05 00:16:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here by Alessia Cara perfectly describes my thoughts at every social event...and life in general </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
