<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject22</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 06:09:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> don't sweat it.. it'll all be back on the streets soon enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 06:03:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> man I lost a pipe with about .2 in it nov of 2018, I remember it like yesterday.
I had just got off work (I work from home) I was in my bed room rolling a bowl in my orange hoodie, I had a small pull while I was chatting up a pal on the phone. after the pipe cooled I put it in pocket of my hoodie and popped a sleep tab and dicked around on my phone til I passed out. I was sleeping in a sitting position and woke up that way.


I reached in my pocket and no pipe. I tore up the whole room looking for it, rearranged my furniture like 2-3 times since then, and to this day I have never seen my pipe... it really fucks with me

it's like that thing just phased out of the fuckin universe or some shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 05:32:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lmfao!!!
that's beautiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 04:22:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow that's next level </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 12:17:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hell yeah!

enjoy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 12:16:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> haha that would be next lvl

triple threat that shit with a slam too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 11:04:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> back left

idk why the front left is superior </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 10:41:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hanging in there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 10:40:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> spoiled milk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 10:37:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> clean my home, skip work, and chill for 2 days

on my last day, eat a decent meal, buy a 6 pack of beer and sit out on my patio 'til that time comes... (don't want to die inside cos I doubt anyone would look for me and I don't want to ruin my funiture or floor when I'm all bloated up and leaking) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 10:27:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 10:26:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no bugs

cleaning up snow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 10:19:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I rarely have human contact

a hug would be nice, but it'd freak me the fuck out. so, I don't think I can enjoy something like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 10:17:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dope is expensive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 10:15:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I looked that up and dayum!

that's cool af

thanks for sharing that random fact with us

never knew how cool scallops were </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 10:09:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> doing laundry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 10:03:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 08:50:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i tried it a vape tank, I had to add a few drops of water to get it all to dissolve. I added about a point to a 3ml tank. yeah it works but it aint a good come up like rolling a bowl and the high felt... cleaner?

but ofc with that amount your basically taking super small hits.

one thing I noticed is that if I added some to a bottle of vape juice the twak loses its potency over time... but, that could've just been me tripping


I found the most effective vape tank to use is the ones for thc oil, you can dump hella shard in there with just a lil bit of vape juice and when you pull on the vape it heats up the whole tank, melting shard into the coil... I got REALLY nice rips off that. and i felt that method streched my supply out.

I got that same cleaner feeling high... though not as intense as a come up from rolling a bowl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 08:39:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i tried it and it works </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 08:24:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> same

it's hard to that bowl down once I start. I think I just like smoking in general and that thick, acrid smoke be so damn smooth with that hint of sweet mmmmm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 08:16:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> haha sweet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 08:09:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just checked out your profile

nice lil set up u got there 👌 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 08:05:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh damn thats kinda low af lol


my bad on the bad advice


I do enjoy that leveled out, slow ramp up, long lasting high.. but damn smoking is the shit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 07:50:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> probably the least fun, but most efficient way would be eating it. a chick I worked with told me to get a small glass of water, drop an alkaselzer tab in it, and drop a shard in the water. then just knock that shit back


if not that snorting


I never boofed so I can't speak on that roa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 07:19:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh wow that does look gnarly

no doubt, brother </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 07:17:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no doubt

brother, the others, their thougts have nothing to do with you. don't let some random person you don't even know have influence over you and have you quit doing something you enjoy.

don't give your power away, take hold of it and keep it... it's yours

do what makes you happy and bask in your own glory. those who vibe with you will vibe with you. those who don't won't; and it isn't your duty to change that.

if you enjoy being here and giving advice, do it.

have fun and let the haters be in their lil pit of doom n gloom talking shit while you shine.

shine on 'em,  homie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 07:08:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> accuracy

it'd be nice to slow time and casually do something, than running around all high energy n shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 07:06:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> happiness, health, love, money, fame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 07:03:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dude you're cool and give good advice

you're wanted


don't let a few fuck heads kill your cool, brother.

keep shining, man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 06:59:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i tripped on the foot well of my car, getting out of it. I had my phone in my hand and completely spilled on to the concrete.

my screen died that day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 06:56:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> going out of your way to do something nice for someone and they complain that it wasn't good enough or that I did it wrong

....makes me never want to do anything for that person again in life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 06:53:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not good...really bad, in fact, but I'm keeping hope for the future.

when I save up some $ i can get professional help. I'm really hoping that'll help. so, I'll hang on until I've exhausted my options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 06:50:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sold pills </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 06:49:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> grey

it's a neutral color that's kinda warm...but empty; and it's pairs well with any other color

kinda a mood I guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 06:45:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my absolute favorite is smoking out of a banger in a lil dab rig </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 06:41:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it looks aight

looks like someone tried to melt powder into a puddle and scrape off the crack back... if that just isn't some thick af reclaim

if it smokes clean and gets u right ✅ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 04:48:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wrong sub, bro


try r/mymethylife


there are a few others for pnp but I forget the names of 'em </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 00:20:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "broken glass inside your mind, it sure feels nice" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 00:08:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> holy shit that's looking nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 23:59:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how are people able to get insanely huge dildos or objects up their butt with out critically injuring themselves.

a while back I saw some dude on a video stick a huge horse dildos up his ass, he turned towards the camera and sucked his stomach in and you could see the imprint of it moving as he fucked himself with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 23:53:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> regular car maintenance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 23:50:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 300 pushups a day

that's impressive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 23:39:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DAYUM!!

nice ice porn, man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 22:59:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> for the people who don't have a NY times acc here's the article


White House Blocked C.D.C. From Requiring Masks on Public Transportation

The order would have mandated that both passengers and employees wear face coverings on planes, trains, buses and subways and in airports, stations and depots.

By Sheila Kaplan

Oct. 9, 2020



The C.D.C. order would have been the toughest federal mandate to date aimed at curbing the spread of the coronavirus.Credit...Chang W. Lee/The New York Times


The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention drafted a sweeping order last month requiring all passengers and employees to wear masks on all forms of public and commercial transportation in the United States, but it was blocked by the White House, according to two federal health officials.
The order would have been the toughest federal mandate to date aimed at curbing the spread of the coronavirus, which continues to infect more than 40,000 Americans a day. The officials said that it was drafted under the agency’s “quarantine powers” and that it had the support of the secretary of health and human services, Alex M. Azar II, but the White House Coronavirus Task Force, led by Vice President Mike Pence, declined to even discuss it.
The two officials, who spoke on condition of anonymity because they were not authorized to comment, said the order would have required face coverings on airplanes, trains, buses and subways, and in transit hubs such as airports, train stations and bus depots.
A task force official said the decision to require masks should be left up to states and localities. The administration requires the task force to sign off on coronavirus-related policies.


“The approach the task force has taken with any mask mandate is, the response in New York City is different than Montana, or Tuscaloosa, Alabama,” said the official who asked not to be identified because he did not have permission to discuss the matter. “Local and state authorities need to determine the best approach for their responsive effort depending on how the coronavirus is impacting their area.”



Most public health officials believe that wearing masks is one of the most effective ways to protect against the spread of the virus, particularly in crowded, poorly ventilated public places that attract people from all over, like transportation venues. Many feel that the Trump administration has turned the wearing — or not wearing — of masks into a political expression, as seen most dramatically on Monday evening when President Trump whipped off his surgical mask at the White House door after returning from the hospital where he was treated for Covid-19.


“I think masks are the most powerful weapon we have to confront Covid and we all need to embrace masks and set the example for each other,” Dr. Robert R. Redfield, the C.D.C. director, who oversaw the drafting of the order, said in a recent interview.
Dr. Redfield has been publicly at odds with President Trump for promoting mask wearing along with social distancing, and for warning that a vaccine for the virus won’t be widely available until next year.
The thwarting of the mask rule is the latest in a number of C.D.C. actions stalled or changed by the White House. Late last month, the coronavirus task force overruled the C.D.C. director’s order to keep cruise ships docked until mid-February. That plan was opposed by the tourism industry in Florida, an important swing state in the presidential election. Political appointees at the White House and the Department of Health and Human Services have also been involved in rewriting the agency’s guidelines on reopening schools and testing for the virus, bypassing the agency’s scientists.

Some other members of the White House Task Force support a mask mandate. But others do not, among them Dr. Scott W. Atlas, a radiologist who has become Mr. Trump’s closest adviser on the coronavirus, and Mr. Pence, who runs the panel and sets the agenda



Representative Peter A. DeFazio, Democrat of Oregon and chairman of the House committee on transportation and infrastructure, criticized Mr. Trump for ignoring public health experts from his own administration on the mask issue.
“It’s especially outrageous because the science is so clear: masks save lives,” Mr. DeFazio said. “The millions of Americans who work in and use our transportation systems every day — from bus drivers, train conductors and flight attendants, to the frontline workers who rely on public transit — deserve to know their president is relying on experts’ best advice and doing everything possible to keep them safe.”
The transportation trades department of the A.F.L.-C.I.O., which represents 33 unions with what it describes as “millions” of transportation workers, said that the administration last week rejected its July petition to require passengers to wear masks on public transportation.
Larry Willis, president of the department, said his members were being endangered by a patchwork of rules regarding face coverings on airplanes, trains and buses around the country, as well as in airports, train stations and bus depots.
“Some airports are all in and they require masks when you walk in the door,” Mr. Willis said. “Some places where masks have become too politicized, the right mandates are not in place.”
“I think it creates an uncertain level of health and safety for workers and passengers,” he said. “This is a global pandemic, this is a national emergency. We should have a national standard.”

Sara Nelson, international president of the Association of Flight Attendants, said that while airlines do technically require passengers to wear face coverings, enforcement can be difficult.
“If there is a requirement by regulation or law, then there’s typically a consequence for not following that regulation or law,” Ms. Nelson said. “So that gives us backing and it often serves as a deterrent from bad behavior.”

Site Index

Site Information Navigation

© 2020 The New York Times Company

NYTCo

Contact Us

Work with us

Advertise

T Brand Studio

Your Ad Choices

Privacy Policy

Terms of Service

Terms of Sale

Site Map

Help

Subscriptions

Support independent journalism.
See subscription options </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 22:52:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> as they begin their interruption say "let me finish" and keep talking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 22:44:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 22:43:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> grats for getting help. wishing you a successful recovery

enjoy that last chonk and kick ass in rehab </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 22:35:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fingers crossed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 22:33:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> go back to sleep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 22:31:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> viruses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 22:30:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why do you bully your sister so much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 22:29:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nile red </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 22:00:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Big Thunder Shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 21:31:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would prefer the straw over rolled paper if I had the choice.


I would snip the straw in half, if that were the case n just use it


afterwards you can cut the straw open longways and run a credit card or something down its length to get your condensate out of it, if it's a big deal


you wouldn't want to use a larger roll for more air flow cos...well you'll be pulling in a higher concentration of air to twak vapor


a slow controlled pull is much better imo

enjoy your trip, bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 21:16:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah you'd definitely want to keep it above the puddle lol


the straw may melt a bit, but it ain't too likely unless you're super close to the hot glass


for the paper absorbing your stuff, there will be some condensate on it but it'll only be on the inner roll which is a small bit of surface area. you can use a credit card or something to just scrape that off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 21:11:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lmfaoo this is dumb af


whew! i needed to laugh today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 21:07:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actively avoid people


it's a waste of energy and time; and it sometimes delays or prevents me from doing stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 20:50:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ohhh lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 20:49:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wtf am I looking at??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 20:46:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you can cook a small peice on foil and use a rolled up dollar bill or straw to inhale vapor

a wine glass works for me in a pinch and you can roll your puddle. hold it sideways and use a straw

a glass dropper, just pull the rubber bulb off drop the twak in from that end. smoke from the wide end cos vapor will condense on the pointed end and clog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 19:43:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I switched from internet explorer to Google Chrome years many years ago... it's simply the superior browser

Firefox was lit too. I use them to download all the content from web pages I like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 17:59:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the only time I think open carry shouldn't be allowed is in a show of force i.e. groups of people with political agendas n whatnot walking around trying to intimidate folks.

otherwise it's their gun and they can do what ever they want to with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 17:48:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have bad anxiety that causes me to tremble and tick, sometimes I make ''mmmph" noises when that happens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 17:41:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jessica Hyde </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 09:20:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cereal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 09:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> canned sardines with mustard and hot sauce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 09:16:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> already can </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 08:50:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hell yea

thanks for sharing this A grade porn with us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 05:58:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 04:22:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> looking tasty


enjoy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 03:25:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> beautiful stuff, man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 03:23:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> good advice

thx, man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 02:16:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I couldn't fault someone for stealing food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 02:00:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yep... that about sums it up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 01:39:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wish shit like this could be seen as conspiring to assualt others with a biological weapon or an act of terrorism.

not only is this trashy af but it can be potentially deadly to others and the people they may come into contact with, so on and so forth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 01:27:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  wow they just watched that happening and didn't do shit.

...sad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 00:33:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow that's so stupid it's wierd. I'd like to know what was going through this dude's mind to have him believe throwing 40lbs sandbags off a highway overpass was something he wanted to do.

just...wow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 16:51:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> looks like mental illness

even animals won't sleep in filth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 07:24:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> s/he is 64 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 05:12:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a pancake with a lot of toppings on it and syrups </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 05:08:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> drug laws </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 05:06:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ded </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 21:57:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Blendtec Blender


they made a YouTube show called Will it Blend. they engage with the audience by accepting blend requests from the comments and do lil give aways n shit.


also, the content is fun and easy going. you forget along the way this is a company marketing a blender


I know if I want a monster mega blender I'll buy a Blendtec </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 18:36:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wheat margins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 17:05:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> apples </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 17:04:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a pretty chill dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 16:44:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't

...in all honesty if you're asking health care questions it'd be wise to just quit... that's legit advice. that's what a doctor would tell you.


typical use questions usually don't get the "you should quit" responses


so it sounds like you or your friends are asking questions that'll warrant such a response </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 05:42:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nervous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 05:40:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the general perception of it being gay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 05:38:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Caribbean teak wood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 05:26:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> mowing the lawn and weed whacking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 05:24:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when my dog died his spirit stayed around the house for a few weeks

he'd run from the kitchen and jump on the couch. my family members who came and visited shortly after his death saw him do that too when we were in the living room and it kinda freaked them out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 05:20:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll have to remember this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 05:19:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RD Client: I can use my desktop from the comfort of my cellphone. I mainly use it with a upnp program on my pc to stream stuff from my computer to devices on my network. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 04:45:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you're welcome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 04:43:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow! I did not expect that

we got a fuckin ninja potato over here!

I'm impressed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 04:26:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if you're feeling like you need to do something and get away from everything...clean up , get yourself together,  or whatever

 see if you can move to live with a relative in a different state, apply for the Federal Pell Grant, go to a community college on the govs dime...work on getting a degree and make college friends that'll inspire you to become your greatest version of self

leave the bullshit behind and find something worth living for

while you're rolling that bowl do a bit of introspection. grab a pen and pad and write down what's bugging you and what you want.

start making a plan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 04:07:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd be too nervous to eat

a cold beer would be my last request </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 04:05:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i don't understand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 03:58:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> floppy disks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 03:56:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> overall if someones a chill person I'll like them. open mindedness is a plus

as for hate: cruelty to animals, racism, needlessly disrespecting others </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 03:47:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 03:47:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> green juice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 03:40:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i didn't see any gun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 03:09:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> haha mood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 02:31:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not sure what u mean.. u got ED?


penis pump + cock ring


or viagra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 02:22:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i heard they brought back the old one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 02:07:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> old school runescape is hella addictive to me

it's free and u can play on the pc and ur cell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 22:32:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> gotta love some good ol' david firth

felix colgrave makes cool animations too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 21:27:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> same

congrats on getting clean!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 21:20:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I could get on top of my bills and buy food </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 21:16:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> boxers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 21:16:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> duh uhh... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 21:15:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DTs and seizures? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 21:13:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that a constantly racing mind coupled with scatter brain  is exhausting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 17:29:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> take a nap before work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 17:26:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when my health was failing from using </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 17:25:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> eggs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 17:22:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cereal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 17:13:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> everything isn't a part of God's plan. we have free will </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 16:56:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you weren't put here to entertain others

fuck the herd. do you 100% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 16:09:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thx likewise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 16:09:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://youtu.be/ScdXJOFapMY

this performance art </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 16:05:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> story telling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 16:03:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> she'll be fine

just make sure she has access to water and the drug will clear her system </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 15:57:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 15:43:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> most people tend to be overly selfish, destructive, and wasteful; even if it is unintentional.


even I'm like that


the lack of the consideration of the poly orders of effects one actions beholds and the lack of mindfulness man kind expresses on such a grand scale is disgusting to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 15:31:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> they typically display some sort of sociopathic, psychopathic, narcissistic, anti socail behavior


general lack of empathy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 15:27:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wipe out all humans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 15:16:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> more freedom with more responsibilities and stress

can be tough to find a healthy balance sometimes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 15:06:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the war on drugs - thinking of a place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 15:01:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd feel sad but be well fed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 14:53:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "can I eat your muffin paper?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 14:45:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> scrambled with hot sauce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 14:39:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> beer and/or good food </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 14:34:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> mint </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 14:33:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> kinda embarrassing but when I have bad anxiety and bouts of psychosis I have a giant stuffed bison I like to hug on

otherwise I just eat healthy and take care of myself n try to do nice things for others </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 14:23:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> one thousand two hundred and thirty four </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 14:19:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not focus on it and find happiness in self </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 14:16:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not fucked at all

I'd ask what he wants his name and powers to be and tell the genie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 14:09:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fish in a salad

hot sauce on scrambled eggs

peanut butter on baked chicken

ketchup on box Mac n cheese </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 14:06:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bills and food </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 14:01:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> really? how so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 13:58:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> think I choked on water two days ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 13:53:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> played outside </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 13:51:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> don't see the appeal, so I'd stay the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 13:49:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ...fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 13:44:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> olives </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 13:42:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cloudy / late fall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 13:35:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> customer service </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 13:34:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> water </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 13:33:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> those red and white pepper mints </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 13:31:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> World of Warcraft and Runscape for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 13:29:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> news to me

I'm dumb as fuck and hella lonely </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 13:25:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ricochet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 13:23:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dramatic pauses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 13:12:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if one is going to cheat why be in a relationship in the first place?

if things aren't working out breakup and move on. it saves everyone involved time and feelings.

socail media can play in one's infidelity in a multitude of ways; like seeing how others are in their relationships or lack of and wanting something they don't get in theirs, ease of finding hook-ups, etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 12:44:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow you have a big loot table </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 12:33:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> letting someone control your emotions gives them power over you


I refuse to give my power away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 12:25:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i feel ya

I get so tired of ''everyone gangsta until.."

I don't down vote, tho... it's just kinda lame to see repetitive shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 12:09:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> mhm

aqua hydrate is really good

distilled tastes sorta sweet to me

fiji is aight

tap water... idk just tastes boring. if that makes sense

smart water is nasty af </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 11:17:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hold the glass sideways when you do that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 08:21:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ah

idk what to say about that

enjoy ya sess tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 08:18:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pic is too blurry to see what ur talking about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 07:57:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> never seen one of those before

do they come with kek clips? I'd be afraid of my bowl dropping mid roll

looks cool tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 07:48:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> unfortunately dealers will keep selling this shit cos a tweaker gotta tweak and they don't have respect for the health of their clients who're literally trusting them with their health.

it won't go away 'til it hits the dealers in their pocket.

as much as I love twak I quit smoking that shit cos after a while all I could find was stepped on bullshit.

I got too much self respect to be had by a POS dealer cos I'm fiending.

more users need to walk away for a better product or just quit.

demand quality and expect quality with good service or keep your money... this is business after all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 05:39:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> recovering poly-drug addict with gnarly mental issues, working a basic af job

so... maybe I was never smart to begin with

...but people tell me I am smart and I want to believe it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 05:05:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nice!

enjoy that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 05:01:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> doesn't look like anything is in there

but use 1-2 drops of water and roll it around the stem in a descending spiral down to the bowl and evap the water off with a torch... u might get a puff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 05:10:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> adds= adderall ??

it depends on how much meth u usually consume (what is a low key meth high for you) and your tolerance

it's subjective

pop a few tabs and see how u feel and gauge by that, homie

adjust your dose to what works for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 16:24:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> staining your shirt with food or drink


also sharting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 16:22:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ah okay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 16:15:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought you were supposed to use ammonium nitrate, not sulphate

idk how to do shake n bake so idk

but that may be why </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 15:27:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ...damn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 15:25:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how'd he get your content without paying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 15:18:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh, well then yeah. He's the bad guy in this case

unless you want to make a legal deal outta this; only thing I can recommend is mitigative measures for next time.


Type up a terms of service page and have your client agree to your ToS in a manner in which you can have record of; and have 'em pay you before releasing your content.

sorry to hear you got ripped off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 15:07:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how does your front and back camera play into this?

were you promising him something you couldn't produce due to your front camera not working?

was he aware of that before the fact and still agreed to pay you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 14:59:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can only infer from your username that you sell pictures?


that's your intellectual property. He took your property without your consent. that's stealing.


(In most cases, intellectual property theft and infringement violations are charged as federal crimes. 


there could be two defenses in regards to this particular case:


Lack of intent – The defendant did not knowingly attempt to steal the intellectual property and use it for their personal gain


Lack of ownership rights by the plaintiff – The material was not actually protected by intellectual property laws)


(taken from legalmatch.com) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 14:47:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ABCs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 14:27:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the kinda doc you're looking for is called a psychiatrist


sounds like your depression could be a result of your anxiety wearing you down. your anxiety could be from you not achieving your ideal life despite having the tools to do so and you're just stuck with a lack of direction. so you may overwhelmed cos it may be that you've spread your self out too far, in too many directions wanting to accomplish something with out knowing exactly what it is. so you're looking every-and-anywhere for something, but can't commit to anything because of uncertainty; and you feel bad and stressed about it coupled with anxiety of the future for stagnating. that can really wear you out and sap all your energy.


take some time to do some really good introspection and figure out what you want.


try to focus on doing just one or two things and be invested in it.


try to take life one day at a time and focus on accomplishing just a few small goals a day; rather than focusing on a huge future goal.


chill out on the booze. it's a slippery slope. it clouds your judgment; and ability to find direction and purpose. (take that from a recovering alcoholic) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 13:56:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> benzos work but they can impair your memory and relying on them can cause some gnarly withdrawal symptoms... like seizures and crippling depression. so I wouldn't recommend them unless it's for a very short time; like just to get you over a really bad episode of depression and anxiety. they personally don't make me happy, just kinda emotionless, but not necessarily feeling empty inside like depression can sometimes be; which can be relieving

i know this sounds cliche as fuck, but eating fruits and veg and getting outside for some sunshine helps me. maybe take a walk if you have nothing to do outside
and if you're feeling up to it sneak in a quick little workout. (I know that can be hard to do cos anxiety is tiresome and prevents one from getting good rest.) but if you got a bit of energy to burn a bit of exercise will help make you feel way better

I like to drink green juice from the grocery store and that dials my anxiety back a few notches (highly recommended)

CBD is sorta okay for anxiety

st.johns wort helps me not be so moody when my anxiety wears me down

oh, and remember to stay hydrated

for bed I have a routine and try to get to zzz around the same time

also benadryl tabs help me get to sleep

(kinda embarrassing) when I have really bad anxiety and bouts of psychosis I have a giant stuffed bison I like to hug on. it's soothing and helps me ground some of that crazy energy. So getting a stuffed animal might be something to look in to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 13:27:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> some purdy looking stuff
enjoy that!

they may have a pink hue from the cooking process leaving some unreacted reagents in the products twak made using reductive amination tends to have a pinkish hue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 10:11:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wine glass and straw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 04:09:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> damn!

and I thought I was bad for smoking .5 a day

sounds like you had a fun weekend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 01:27:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> enjoy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 00:46:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh man

the only time I burned my gut was when I was ironing my clothes, before work one morning, slumping over my ironing board. the side of the iron swiped right across my belly. that shit woke me right the fuck up lol

I know touching a hot torch nozzle to your side must've damn near made ya jump outta your skin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 23:02:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel ya

I remember one day I just finished torching a bowl and I was wanting to clean my stem with the torch.

not thinking, I picked the pipe up from the bowl, literally seconds after flaming it. my fingers literally sizzled on that glass for a solid 4-5 seconds before I realized I could set hot glass down.

I didn't make a sound, but that shit fuckin hurt lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 17:43:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> birch reduction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 13:15:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> man all your content is lit as fuck!

wish I had it like you

awesome shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 12:56:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wine glass and straw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 06:30:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 08:59:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> came here to recommend odoban

get that shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 08:31:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i personally keep a partially spent prepaid card that have a $1 or $2 on it to set up free trails.

Many companies only let you spend what's in your account, so it's not possible to dip below $0 nor is it possible to get an overdraft fee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 08:14:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the best hiding spot is in plain sight

get something you'd legitimately need a scale for, like anhydrous caffeine, a supplement, nootropics, or a hobby that'd you'd need to weigh things for and keep the scale next to that.

if someone stumbles upon your hidden scale it'll raise questions as to why it's hidden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 08:27:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it works for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 08:20:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> drink lots of water primarily

wash your face with a soap that doesn't pull all the oil off your skin, exfoliate with a wash cloth thats just rinsed in water

clean the cloth with soap, rinse the all the soap out and wash your face again with the clean cloth

use a moisturizer

do this 3-4 times a day

always use a new cloth when you bathe

if your face is dry all the time you'll produce more oil to counter act the dry skin which will clog your pores and make zits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 08:14:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use a bottle of propane (the small green ones for camping) and a pencil flame brazing torch nozzle

it'll be the best $15 ya spent for twak

cheap and effective </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 02:04:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lots of people in my area like to get their homes power washed in the fall

they pay a few hundred for the service

gas power washers and cleaning solution aint too too expensive

you can use Facebook local pages, Craigslists, and post signs to advertise your services locally

you can use PayPal or square as a point if sale system and they'll send you a CC swiper so you can take card payment in person or just use the online portal if you ain't tryna handle cash


landscaping is always an easy one

flipping Chinese goods on ebay is easy money

folks will cough the $$ cos they don't want to wait 2wks to get shit overseas.

you can get lots of high-quality shit from China 100%. they make most of the OEM parts for 'American made' goods </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 09:58:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you're welcome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 05:12:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> primarily only because you haven't used for a long time and 50mg is still well with in the range of therapeutic doses

speed clears your system fast and initial withdrawal is fast, but it's the brain damage caused from years of use that messes people up in the long term

you're fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-27 04:10:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you'll probably have bad anxiety for 2-3 days and feel sad for a day or 2

hydrate, rest well, eat some foods high in L-tyrosine like some chicken, pop a mega-B tab, eat some fruits n veg

you'll be fine in no time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 04:39:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> time seems to go by faster when we're older because a day relative to your life is shorter

i.e.: a year to a 5yo seems like forever cos its 20% of their life, but a year to a 20yo is only 5%

also, putting down electronics will make your days feel way longer. it's crazy how much time we spend looking at screens and how time escapes us when we're zoned in to entertainment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 04:27:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when it comes to junk food only buy what you intend to eat that day

keep healthy snacks on hand that requires no prep work to enjoy: celery sticks, grapes, baby carrots, shelled nuts, etc... are tasty and you really don't have to worry so much about portion control.

it's a win-win </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 03:22:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> idk know about cats but my dog knows what a laser is and she loves to chase the beam. we couldn't even have an ink pen around her without her getting amped af, cos she thought it was a laser and she wanted to chase the beam...also with reflections, we have a glass back door that will reflect sunlight across the floor when you opened it. she would trick us by acting like she had to go potty and would stand by the door, but when we'd open the door, she bolt in the other direction to chase the light.

...she's an odd dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 10:22:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 09:53:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 08:01:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 08:01:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thought the sub rules said sumn about no dick pics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 07:59:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you in that trash can 4 days later haha

good on u putting it down frfr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 04:21:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes... porn gets kinda boring

idk role playing furry gay shit blow my mind.
it all started playing world of warcraft as a Tauren shaman...and shit got wild

fuck shit was interesting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 03:30:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> haha I will take this in to consideration </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 23:09:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hell yes

I got it on my list

thank's for the great idea! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 23:06:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just Googled that.

that's a whole new spin on builder kits for youngins!

thanks for that!
I'll add it to my list </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 23:05:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> damn... i should've put serious on the thing

I personally would love a live nade.

a baby wouldn't be strong enough to pull the pin, but he'd get bored with it pretty fast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 23:00:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lmao facts!

i thought about getting him a gang of megablocks. (thinking like $500-$800 worth; mainly, to troll my sister and bro in law)

he has mega blocks and his own room ~8'-8'

but i worry he'd get bored with it

I plan on getting him a giant stuffed bison he can droll on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 22:51:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a nephew who's turning 2 in a few months and I want to get him some brainy gifts

I've thought about legos and k'nex but I worry about choking hazards...

what are some cool mentality stimulating gifts I can get my nephew?

I eventually want to get him in to mechanics and electronics when he's older. but really anything that can spark his inventive creativity would be cool.

he's very smart and learns quickly. I don't want him to get bored with what I get him

thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> what are some cool gifts for toddlers? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 22:51:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 22:41:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's some new shit to me

dude shooting some 170c shit in to his arm???

that's almost 2x the temp of boiling water and twak is corrosive

that sounds like insta necrosis and infection </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 21:54:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> happy birthday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 21:50:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> was diagnosed with adhd as a kiddo been on adderall since I was 7

got off addies when I went to college and just smoked weed for adhd

looking for work I couldn't smoke bud for piss tests, but I knew amps will flush out of the sys fast so I got back on addies, didn't have health insurance nor could I afford it
addies got too damn expensive, knew a tweaker girl and she set me up with her dealer

meth was cheaper and a much cleaner high than the pills...so I just stayed with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 21:44:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> shiiit I'd be 90lbs wet if I could get those prices </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 21:42:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 200 a ball VAb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 21:40:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> soo fuckin jealous

enjoy that shit!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 21:33:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yooo so imma need you to post that as soon as it done
that'd be so fuckin cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 18:48:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so you're saying that I have apps running in the background when my phone is powered off??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 08:21:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 08:07:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I try to be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 07:37:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> mannn nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 06:51:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's dope af (see what I did there)

would be cool if y'all made a psychedelic, graffiti style painting on canvas like this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 04:47:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the smell is pretty faint and only slightly sweet smelling in my experience, unless ya burned it

mostly only tweakers would recognize it

I guess a tip for next time would be to have an ecig so u can mask and blame the smell on that and have an excuse for smoke

fun tip: for ecigs you can melt a small bit of twak in water a drop of water before topping off an e-cig tank and add it in to your e-juice for an inconspicuous smoke while at work or whatever

worked surprisingly well for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 03:15:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow this is informative!

thanks for sharing this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 01:10:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> slightly sweet, dense, acrid smoke.. but it's very smooth

nothing quite like it. love the taste </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 01:07:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cum and pre

when u use your muscles clench and can squeeze pre from your cowpers glad in to your bladder, same will happen with cum too

it's basically retrograde ejaculation with out sexual stimulation

...happens to me all the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 23:25:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> put the shit down, shower, hydrate, and force your self to eat. you can do a bump and rerurn to life when you're rested.

if you're twakked out, I'd highly recommend you don't drive, get an uber or just stay home. micro-sleeps and bouts of confusion can occur spontaneously even if you're spun.

the last thing you need is to wreck or get pulled over, out of your mind, with dope on your person.

safety first, always </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 22:08:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so purdy

the super flat edges and clean reflection makes me think n-iso and it being super hard msm

how she smoke, tho? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 22:01:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sleep

you'll enjoy it so much more after some zzz and a full stomach </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 21:58:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I smoked and railed for a bit over 2 years. I quit in may and was feeling super healthy in 4-6weeks.
i was over withdrawals in like a week, but I still crave that shit like a mfer to this day

I wasn't a hardcore user, tho. ~.15-.3 daily of good quality stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 21:47:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> primarily just eat a balanced diet and stay hydrated, my guy. be sure to eat extra servings L-tyrosine rich foods like chicken, turkey, and dairy

when I used I supplemented with wieght gainer mixed with whole milk. serious mass by on nutrition and met-rx are amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> does anyone know about n-iso </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 21:40:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> doing some research and can't find anything on the pharmacology of n-iso.
can someone enlighten me on the effects?

preferably as an isolate (not mixed with twak)

thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 13:14:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> either very benign or very surreal, but not too serious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 03:29:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> old school runescape on mobile is addictive af </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 11:06:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> should have said free for students

you can get a .edu email for free by applying for admission for a community college </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 11:04:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> use a student email you can get for free by merely applying for admission for a community college

you can use a .edu email to get lots of free shit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 10:54:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> uhh...no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 03:01:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> T_T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 02:54:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> full tilt!

let a MFer be happy ffs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 02:52:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> which one is the bear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 02:38:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> damn... you're just gonna take all the  answers, huh? lol

100% facts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 02:33:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> haha it be like that sometimes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 02:31:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm even more impressed how he doesn't crease those clean nikes

wow!
smooth moves </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 02:27:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> right?!

and like.. the whole sewage infrastructure to support that!
wild... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 02:26:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> damn... i don't even think about that

so many man hours put in to constructing and maintain those things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 02:18:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 100%

i didn't even think how great modern ball point pens were

i saw a thing on the science Channel how precise the balls had to be for the ink flow to be just perfect for ballpoint pens

fuck dipping ink evey two sentences... I couldn't imagine such a life haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 02:07:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's crazy how cell phones are almost essential for daily life these days

The latest job I just applied for said that I needed to have a cell phone as a requirement... like.. wow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 01:58:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> full tilt!
i remember my first gaming pc it was a windows 95 with a 300MHz processor and and 6gb HDD

it's  almost scary how far consumer electronics have come!

my cell phone is faster than my custom desktop I bought in 2010 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 01:55:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> full facts!

can only rebuild the wheel so many times, haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are some seemingly simple things we take for granted that are, in fact, marvels of engineering? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 01:51:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 01:14:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's wholesome af </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 01:10:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sigh....yes, I'd like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 01:02:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> an idiot that's much happier than you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 01:00:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> upvotes/likes make ppl feel good... it has something to do with a dopamine response or sum'n

but, anyhow; if I can make someone feel a 'lil bit better as easy as tapping an arrow, which literally takes a fraction of a second, I'd do it.

...as I age I'm learning it takes so much energy to be an asshole

+ if you're nice to ppl sometimes you get cookies! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 23:58:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oof... well I gave you upvotes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 23:56:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> mhm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 23:37:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a paranoid schizophrenic and I don't think thats too normal :-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 23:36:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just did, thanks

another redditor told me I had to swipe to see it all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 23:30:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ohhh tysm for explaining </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 22:50:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i don't get it

someone please explain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 03:09:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> explaining complex things in a simple way that's easy to understand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 03:03:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> looks like like an eastern dragon flying overhead and looping back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 03:00:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> inflation and vore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 02:01:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow major props to whoever made this

very cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 01:58:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> excellent progress!

keep up the hard work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 01:47:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that is such a mood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 19:09:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's such a wild word I had look it up!

definitely writing this one down

thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 14:29:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 7-11 green juice

the one in the glass bottle
they so good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 14:18:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> learn to enjoy them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 14:14:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> self </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 14:14:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> magazines </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 14:11:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i care too much

I'll often find myself doing so much for others that I don't have time for me...which is a bad thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 13:26:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my sexlife is a little bit of a pit of despair


...dayum!!!
that breaks my heart.
but, it's true. I'm voluntarily celibate for my religion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 06:45:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ...damn

well looks like I'm sneaking in a y tile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 06:04:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 05:44:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree that passenger was being a total bitch, but the situation could've easily been de-escalated; just like you said.

too bad ego and emotions get in the way of rational thought... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 05:38:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> is it possible for them to lay down if they wanted too?

it's gotta suck standing for who knows how many hours, rocking with turbulence and what ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 05:33:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow I'm learning so many new words looking at the comments!

I got too many favorite words to have an absolute favorite so imma go with: Juxtaposition

it means to contrast things, concepts or whatever by placing them side by side and picking out the differences </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 05:28:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> imma kill at my next scrabble game with this word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 05:27:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love this word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 05:26:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lol I'm over here whispering "crriisp" under my breath, experiencing the word as it starts at the back of my mouth and moves to my lips

haha what you said is very true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 04:45:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this made me smile

thanks for posting this wholesome optical illusion

shared it with my mom too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 04:39:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how "hold my beer" is actually supposed to happen

but kinda not cool to do that to a calf... it's still a baby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 00:03:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes

fortunately many receivers nowadays have a night-mode setting, which normalizes the dynamics in movies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 23:56:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's amazing progress

very happy for this guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 23:55:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> looks like an alien world

so beautiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 23:53:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow

that's amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 23:45:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's so satisfying to watch

smoooooth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 23:01:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm kinda dumb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 21:23:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> play board games

we have this game called two bars, where we'd rap two bars and the next person adds on to your lyrics or whatever with two bars and we go around like that

reading, drawing, or crafting something is always cool

go for a walk
(we had a snow storm that knocked the power out and we went out for a walk after it passed... it was so quiet out and the moonlit snow looked magical)

edit: off topic but if you ever get a huge amount of snow and you're bored, building an igloo is fun + you can hot box that MF with ya pals if you smoke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 21:12:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes... there's so much more to what makes a person interesting outside of sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 06:10:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sigh....me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 05:34:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> they like what they like and I'll respect that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 05:33:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> do they have cams in the restrooms or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 05:21:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's exactly why I don't like it, actually

you were spot on with that haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 05:20:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 29 I'm gay and voluntarily celibate for my religion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 05:17:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like pickles and tuna in my salad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 05:16:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yep.. that shit is gross as fuck to me

but, you can find it in every other grocery store; so enough people like it to have it on shelves </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 05:14:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> they good with hot sauce, tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 05:11:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> myself

could go for a nice moonlit night at the lake with a few beers and my guitar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 05:06:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I heard programmers still make custom levels for emulators

there's an underground kid chameleon community

definitely a kick ass game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 04:57:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ahhh man... that's lame

the online community is pretty much is dead these days... I'll tell yah this, man; most clans wouldn't recruit you for training unless you an SS ranking (meaning you got perfect mission scores for all missions) and that'd put you at the bottom rung in regards to skill level. that's what made the game so, so crazy...the skill cap was extremely stupid high. it turns to mecha meets DBZ level action

you could force warp (every one could, it's a part of the games mechanics) and the clans all had their secret techniques, they'd hide their stabilizer set-ups (your stabilizers completely tuned the attitude of your mech: how well it could aim, how fast it could swing a sword and how hard it'd hit, how quickly you could engage enemies, how efficient your boosters are relative to power output and boost duration...) I mean... the shit got crazzzzy, brah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 04:43:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ohhh no

you're definitely doing the fighting

that shit gets intense haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 04:39:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah it's a huge learning curve and you can get your mechs to do really wonky shit once you know how to build them and multi-stage boost

there are also lots of hidden mechanics in the game that either your clan teaches you or you stumble upon over time.

I recruited and trained people for my clan it's a crazy dynamic, fast paced game...but, once you get a handle on building mechs and smooth piloting it's so damn fun!

wish I ran into you when I was playing. I would've trained yah to destroy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 04:32:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd go with a blank image...seeing the same thing for rest of my life seems haunting and it'd fuck with me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 04:29:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pray, call my family and friends up and tell them I love them, write a quick will,  drink a beer and eat a huge chefs salad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 04:27:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> gps ftw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 04:26:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> mint </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 04:26:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OC spray </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 04:24:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know if it counts as a fetish, but I like my belly rubbed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 04:23:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> right now blue

I got a multi pack and it had all kinda different colors in it... so now I'm on blue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 04:20:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a comfy mattress

I never knew how shitty my rest was 'til I slept on a proper mattress

I used to sleep on the floor before I got futon... and I thought the futon was an upgrade...nope!

I got one of those fancy multi layer, gel and memory foam mattresses and I wake up feeling like a million bucks... and I be all giddy and shit to get in my comfy bed :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 04:16:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> grats on that progress!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 04:15:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> molest plants </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 04:13:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> read the news and check my email

I'm already on my phone to turn the alarm off and it gives me an excuse to stay in bed for an extra 15min </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 04:07:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a  Mcbaked-fish-on-brown-rice-with-steamed-veggies-on-the-side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 04:02:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when I was a kid I was afraid of the water heater, the picture of the stick man, running while flames engulfed him freaked me the fuck out

also I was afraid of the vacuum cleaner, especially shop-vacs, like the ones they have at the gas station. was afraid I'd get sucked up in to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 03:29:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nice! the dolores series? that was kick ass too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 03:16:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> white crayons and color pencils are used for blending colors
they okay for highlights too


they're hella useful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 03:12:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yooo this looks bad ass tho

they got particle projection cannons too... more research is needed full tilt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 03:08:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> damn

still gonna look it up, tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 03:06:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> never heard of it

will Google it tonight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 02:51:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bruh if you played the game and like the story 100% watch I dolo

it's the story that leads up to the Antillia raid. it's only like 45-50min and its a damn good story

 https://youtu.be/Q-bOSKnYZ9o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 01:29:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh with the parry blade? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 00:52:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had to quit playing that shit

...it's too damn addictive. that game is so fun it's dangerous haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 00:50:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> super smash bros on game cube

L4D

monopoly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 00:45:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> white crayons are hella useful

you use it to blend colors and they're okay for highlighting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 00:25:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know right!
hands down my favorite game

glad to see someone else who has experienced the glory of armored core </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 23:55:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i like these
very unique </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 22:58:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you build a tolerance

I put ghost peppers in just about every thing I eat  (my dad grows and dries peppers and gives me nuclear hot pepper powder I've eaten for years) and I shit just fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 22:51:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> kim cubed??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 22:50:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if I have a son I'm 100% naming him Nohah

idk about girl or gender neutral names </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 22:42:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how someone struck by a bullet goes flying like 5 ft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 20:58:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> he sat next to me when I was eating a muffin and asked if he could have my muffin paper... he wanted to eat it, but i did too haha

15 years later and he's still one of my best friends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 20:11:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> diiv, beach house, windows 96 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 20:09:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> like I should always copy my response to my clip board and transfer it to a Google doc so if the question comes up again I'll have the perfect response ready </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 20:05:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a robot that immediately self destructs upon activation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 19:38:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if I don't enjoy the person, I'll just enjoy the experience.

I ain't wasting my gas just to turn around and go back home </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 19:35:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get carrots, apples, celery, a lemon, and whatever greens I have laying around and chuck 'em in to my juicer and just drink that

it's always have been satisfying for me
especially over ice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 19:32:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the last 16 years of my life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 19:28:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i can't afford health insurance at the moment and a hospital bill would crush me

my new job has benefits so I can't wait to start working there so I can see a doc and also get my dental check up ^_^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 19:25:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> coleslaw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 19:11:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it's a term for race war </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 19:09:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> talking to people and hanging out is extremely exhausting to me

I have good social skills and alot of ppl find me cool, i guess

but, I dread getting that call to come hang out sometimes.

then I feel bad for saying no because I know my friends care enough about me to invite me to stuff...and idk... it's a wierd balance for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 19:03:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> put in the album Soma by Steve Roach and Robert Rich

seven veils by Robert Rich is good too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 19:00:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> liver 100% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 18:57:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when I was looking in to homesteading I researched cattle care and found that yaks were easy to care for on top of only requiring 1/3 the amount of food by weight than typical cattle. learning that I researched in to them deeper and found yaks to be damn cool animals and pretty intelligent

needless to say, I don't think I could bring myself to raise yaks for meat now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 17:54:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yoooo I loved that game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 17:53:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> kid chameleon

damn... so many good games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 17:53:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> mech warrior </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 17:52:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> armored core for answer and the ones before it

zone of the enders

road rash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 17:46:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if that's what ya like... at least they're consistent

all their songs sound the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 17:41:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> beach house, diiv, windows 96, little brother </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 17:38:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> beach house all the way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 17:36:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> they're cool i guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 17:32:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that is extremely cool and wholesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 17:23:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how did that guy's spine not explode?

...I'm impressed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 12:53:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> potato soup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-15 12:52:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bacon and guns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 09:01:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cable television </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 10:30:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's too wholesome <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 00:57:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ummm... is this a joke? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 00:10:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  "Scheherazade" of Nikolai Rimsky-Korsakov

spelled that wrong af haha

but this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 00:08:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Check out Nikolai korsakov Ramses shaharazad

It's an orchestrastrated story about a sailor who gets lost at sea and then finds a love

it's a very dynamic peace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 00:05:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> also back when I was a druggie.. being up for days on meth, when I began to slip in and out of psychosis I'd draw the coolest/wierdest shit.

I still love going back through my old sketch books looking at the odd shit I'd draw and write about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 00:02:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when ppl pay me for an art commission </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 00:01:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> legos and k'nex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 00:01:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> passing kidney stones in the recording booth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 23:59:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw YouTube videos where the robot voice would read Reddit posts ... and I was like "that looks like fun"

....sooo here I am </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 23:57:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> jerk off and eat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 23:57:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> basically something that ain't candy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 23:55:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> having to hold in a laugh at a formal event

...just be over there dieing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 23:54:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> body language

like if they're confident or not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 17:24:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lmao that is odd

never played D&D but it sounds fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 17:18:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nah, I work a regular gig full-time. I am accepting commissions, tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 17:00:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> me neither. I just get their money haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 16:25:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm surprised no one has said wasps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 16:16:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nothing at the moment

got half of an ice cream sandwich in the freezer tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 16:12:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> gorge massive amounts of unhealthy foods </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 16:04:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> furries

they pay me money to draw cartoons! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 16:03:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> meh...

did lots of drugs so that part was fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 16:00:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "kick rocks" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 15:59:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "your assistance is no longer needed here" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 14:53:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lol i love the onion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 14:11:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> getting in to bed after a good dinner and shower </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 14:07:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> benadryl + a melatonin tab

put on an audio book and drift off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 14:05:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 7-10 days not too sure... the days start blending in to one another

happy I don't do meth anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 14:02:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pickle brine is my go to

don't drink more than 8oz in one sitting, tho. it'll give you the shits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 00:51:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh ok thx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 00:50:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what does the I mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 00:48:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> talking behind thier friend's back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 00:44:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> alive in choas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 00:26:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oof </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 00:19:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> over 20 younger than 30 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 23:56:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> schizophrenics are violent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 23:04:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> magpie

they're nature's troll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 22:45:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 22:12:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sounds pretty cool I'll join </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 20:11:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> specificity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 20:09:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if it's agreed beneficial then I could fuck with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 20:06:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wants to change/fix you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 20:01:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 19:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> never fuck with them or their clique again

one and done... I don't like gossippers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 19:07:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> in regards to Christianity it is because woman was cast from man and when man and woman come together in sexual union they make what was once whole in spirit. to have homosexual relations would create an abomination in spirit out of line with what the creator intended... it was a thing for spiritual purity

as for the 1900s I could only speculate that it was because homosexuality was seen as a mental illness as the factors regarding sexual attraction are all geared towards procreation and for those signals to be flipped to have one find sexual attraction in the same sex would be indicative of this. it doesn't make biological sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 18:46:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> California

1-2 times a day (depends what time I work out/do something that gets me sweaty)

4 times a month </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 18:13:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that makes sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 18:10:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ohhhh

thanks for explaining </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 18:09:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> strawberry-banana punch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 18:04:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hide track marks.. not me but a chick i used to work with did that for said reason

also when I lived in okinawa people would where long sleeves and sun hats to keep themselves from tanning, so they can look like main landers. okinawans are naturally darker skinned, tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 18:01:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> appreciative that someone would give me something

but I really don't know what reddit rewards do/ are used for

like do you give the reward you received to other people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 17:58:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> to hide their own insecurities </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 17:56:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> slowly stretch it out overtime, the skin will loosen

could take a few months of consistent stretching

...or have it surgically removed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 17:50:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> mhm

depends on the dog, but typically 2hrs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 17:45:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not sure I understand what you mean

will you rephrase that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 17:25:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> for underwear, securing ya boys and wicking sweat. for socks, wicking sweat so my feet dont smell horrid

commando is hella comfy, ngl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 17:10:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> aww man... now I really wanna know lol

I respect that, tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 17:06:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> people will always find something to get pissy about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 17:04:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> worked at 7-11 for a while and got them for free

they were hella tasty too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 17:00:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 16:49:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when they can no longer function as underwear or socks

I have holes in many of my socks but they still work so I keep em </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 16:43:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what my favorite animal was and why </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 16:38:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> heal all the aliments of man

turn all the lands into fertile ground, booming with life

erase hatred from the hearts of the earth's inhabitants

...then idk... drink a beer or something knowing my work is done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 16:32:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no, a life is worth more than any amount of money... to me at least </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 16:27:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i think all religions should be taught there's alot of good philosophy to be found in them all, imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 16:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> key exchange over an encrypted server

if someone were to record a secure session and had access to the server's private key they can get the keys of the clients and use the client's keys to decrypt

I personally don't know of any more secure ways, unfortunately </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 15:52:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bleed out trying to stick something up your butt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 15:51:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wanted to be a scientist, like off of Dexter's Lab when I was a kid

got a degree in biochem, but work customer service...trying to start up an apothecary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 15:46:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> somehow managed to get piss behind my toilet... this was a 30y/o man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 15:33:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 15:15:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> which way is backwards?

probably explains why I do it, if i do it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 15:12:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> introvert

being around and interacting with lots of people is exhausting for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 15:08:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my time management skills </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 15:07:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you don't... it's a subjective label that carries little meaning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 15:03:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> every day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 15:01:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> regular people with a hobby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 14:58:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> forgot the question mark

answering a question in regards to the origins of curse words, got my post deleted for using said curse words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 14:55:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it's a generated algorithm

imagine it like putting a number in to series of systems of functions

the systems of functions are random making it unique </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 14:42:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you and the person you're sending info to have unique encryption keys for the other person

instead of the network or server decrypting with a common key </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 14:39:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> for HS online

for college in school. it's nice to ask the professor questions, interact live, and hear other's questions. also, you can't do labs from home </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 14:35:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw an episode of gumball the other day and it got a few genuine laughs outta me

adventure time is pretty epic too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 14:05:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> then not everyone should participate in biblical ceremonies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 14:03:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's cool if you're pagan... if that's the case why participate in a Christian ceremony?

have some other ceremony to celebrate your union keep the legal stuff the same... those are laws of man, handled in man's court

There's nothing wrong with gays getting together... Love is love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 13:55:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it's said many times throughout The Bible

it's a Christian thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 13:53:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not imposing I'm my religious beliefs on others... other's are imposing their beliefs on a religion they don't participate in... and think they should be accommodated for it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 13:51:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nothing, to my knowledge

I think it's stupid to perform a religious ceremony if one doesn't abide by the laws of said religion and activity participate in the religion

it's like bringing a basketball ball to a golf course... it makes no sense

I'm gay and I would never participate in that ceremony... it's disrespectful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 13:40:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> marriage is a religious covenant between a man, woman, and their god; which in said religion forbids homosexuality.

it's a slap in the face



I think it's cool for gays to celebrate getting together and to have that formally and legally recognized

but to go through with the religious ceremony is fucked imo... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 09:17:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 09:14:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sweet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 09:09:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 09:05:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> memes and meme references </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 08:59:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Friday

The Matrix

The Fast and The Furious (the first one)

Starship Troopers

Chronicle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 08:51:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 08:48:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> buy bulk from growers

If you buy from a legitimate source, the producers are typically listed on the label or CoA ... contact them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 08:39:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks, man

you're too kind. I really appreciate that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 08:35:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks, bro

it was a bitch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 08:34:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm in to a bit of cock n balls torture... you'd be surprised how big your sack can comfortably swell

but it's like having a wrecking ball between your legs

but i could totally see if you were swollen to the point your sack was as hard as an erect penis how that could be painful af </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 08:30:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how loud I swallow water

...like dafuq?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 08:26:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this one chick used to legit hit on me... for the longest time I thought she didn't like me for some reason... but she was always super interested in what I was doing and wanted to hangout n shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 08:20:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't know a scrotum could get erect

Like, I'm just imagining someone's balls standing at attention and that makes me laugh too hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 08:19:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> got a call </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 08:10:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> d'aww well the cashews really appreciate you too <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 08:09:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can tell you really like nuts haha

are you stoned rn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 08:08:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> macadamia nuts are boss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 08:00:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> food and beer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 07:58:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 07:58:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> caviar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 07:55:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> confidence is a big one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 07:53:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> *hyperventilates while flicking boogers at passing pedestrians* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 07:50:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sparks

it was an alcoholic energy drink. tasted pretty amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 07:49:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my dad used to drink tf outta that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 07:48:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> was gonna say this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 07:45:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I lost count after day 5, they just started blending in to one another, but probably well over a week... glad I'm done with meth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 07:34:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> musk ox calfs...frickin' adorable

also highland cows and yaks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 07:31:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> blue tee, blue jean shorts, black socks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 07:30:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> he knitted me a hat

I think it was cool as fuck that he would take the time to craft me something by hand and I cherish it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 07:14:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ahh okay okay

I'd say if you break the skin, regardless if it hurt, bleeds, or whatever; that'd classify as a cut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 07:12:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hell naw! think I would've died

i was scheduled for a 20hr/wk minimum and could work more so long as I finished what was assigned to me

but, it was just too painful for me to continue on. I just quit and found a better gig

how long did you transcribe for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 07:07:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A few years back I was really getting into the idea of homesteading and I was looking for easy to care for sources of meat and that got me looking into cattle care.

I learned about Yaks as they were relatively easy to care for, have an easygoing disposition and required one-third of the feed standard cattle their weight would require. So I researched further about Yaks and found them to be extremely cool, intelligent animals

well that kinda backfired, because I don't want to eat yaks anymore.

but yeah... i think yaks are cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 07:00:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> could you rephrase the question? I'm not sure what you're asking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 06:57:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> trigun was a really good one too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 06:56:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> facts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 06:55:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Quantum quiet quilt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 06:54:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cursive Z </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 06:51:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think there's a baseline level of respect everyone gets off jump, but maintaining that respect and/or building it is earned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 06:49:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> challenging myself to see just how high I can push the bar

I'm my own competition </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 06:45:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did role-play alot but never had the opportunity to get down with some d&d </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 06:43:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Making up completely abstract stories that make no sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 06:41:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ooo idk... but that sounds like it may be actually kind of fun

the things I was commissioned to transcribe were things like commercials and bits and pieces of documentaries or like the dialogue of a formal interview </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 06:33:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> voluntarily celibate

I'm not in to women and my religion forbids homosexuality

over time i just lost all interest relationships and sex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 06:30:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> transcribing

you listen to boring af clips and type what you hear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 06:25:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> comics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 06:22:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeahhh... i think that may be a winner

i fucks with some potatoes

and they're so versatile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 06:21:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> probably French fries or ramen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 06:16:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "power comes in response to a need, not a want" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 06:14:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sponge bong hemp pants </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 06:14:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how to be a fair minded critical thinker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 06:12:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> watching sports... never understood what was so amazing about watching men play with a ball

I do think martial arts is cool af tho

is fishing a sport? cos that's cool too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 06:09:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really enjoyed hunter x hunter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 06:03:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeh, man.. kinda sucks to be sexualized like that

sorry to hear you go through it too... I think a lot of men get harrassed by women, but don't speak out about it because it's kinda a societal norm

I haven't been out as much these days anyway and work from home so it hasn't been much of an issue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 05:52:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> inappropriate

I've had women i don't know randomly feel me up, or grab my hand and put it in their chest... it's makes me uncomfortable

I'm a voluntarily celibate gay man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 05:45:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> being groped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 05:20:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> practice social distancing, wear my mask when I'm out

1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 05:15:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wouldn't be surprised if there was one

I wouldn't recommend going that route through, cos you'd run a risk of losing some sensation post surgery as nerves may get damaged while they're cutting and stitching ya junk + scar tissue may form... but that's all speculation

i say google that shit, man

also check out Thundersplace.org for a legit community of people to talk male sexual health with.

they're an awesome resource </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 05:10:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> windex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 05:10:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 05:09:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> use a tension device that pulls and stretchs the skin of your cock in a manner that will regrow your foreskin

there are already many foreskin restoration devices on the market and they do work, but it takes 2 or so years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 05:04:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> say thanks


they didn't have to give you anything at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 05:04:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pace you when you're trying to switch lanes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 05:01:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> buy a bit of land to start a few community gardens in low income places and teach people how to grow and preserve their own food. build teams here n there to maintain said gardens and teach other members of their community

go to the next place and do it all over again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 04:50:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> apothecary

I can grow and preserve food

I'm an okay fisherman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 04:46:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when I noticed my body jiggled when I ran up stairs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 04:45:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sorta chubby kid I went to HS with, smoked cigs, and ran a 6min mile

dude was stupid jacked last I saw him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 04:42:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> could you rephrase that?

i am confusion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 04:40:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yepper! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 04:38:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i don't think that's all too popular of a trait minority men go for

blonde isn't a fetish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 04:34:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "survival, living off the land" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 04:31:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> people call me and complain about things they bought and I tell them how to fix their problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 04:22:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when I learned he strangled his puppy to death, tried to hurt his baby bro, and stole from his friends... there was a rumor floating around that he pushed a kid in to a moat and watched him die.

no one can confirm the fact, but the boy died and he was there.

last I heard he was in jail for robbery

I knew him when I was a kid, he'd always try to bully me... I had kicked that kids ass so many times I lost count

...that dude got demons and some mental problems

i feel bad for him...something was/is fuckin' with that boy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 04:11:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pulover's macro creator is pretty kick ass

you can get it free from the creator </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 04:08:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I draw and paint, so I'd have to say my art </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 04:07:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> man, that's too cool

ahh in Australia, never been </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 04:00:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bro, but they got jokes on them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 03:53:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> haha nice! how'd they react to it?

nah, I never heard of the red centre </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 03:49:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> haha nah, man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 03:46:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> get them a kangaroo scrotum coin purse

it's odd but they'll remember that forever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 03:42:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> edging with a weed whacker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 03:37:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "don't write it, don't talk about it, just do that shit" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 03:30:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 03:29:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ate a shit ton of pickles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 03:16:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> English may not be their first language </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 03:08:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> takes too long to eat if your sucking and licking on it... just eat the damn thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 22:42:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Break your goals into small tasks that are easy to complete and chip away at it one day at a time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 22:39:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah... they're family </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 22:38:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really can't say...but I ain't the brightest bulb and I'm still alive so i guess it has probably helped me somewhere and I was just too oblivious to notice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 22:35:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes, young adults like to experiment and if you are in college or have friends who go to school things like adderal get handed out like candy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 22:25:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sko shorty 12 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 22:19:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fiber

Metamucil is really good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 22:18:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> beer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 22:16:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that the dc in Washington DC meant district of Columbia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 22:14:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> was going to say that

yep, this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 22:11:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wiping snot from their nose and scratching their balls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 19:09:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what is it you're feeling suicidal about?

I dealt with lots of suicidal thoughts, hated my self for being gay, fell in to hard drug addiction, and before I was a born again Christian I practiced paganism and sorcery... had lots of not cool experiences

I always wonder why God allowed me to experience such things.

it was like God would let me fail, walk in to fire, but would always rescue me just before I was over my head.

I've learned overtime that me having experienced such things has allowed me to connect with others going through hard times and drag some of them out of the darkness, and it was easy because I had been there and done that and could relate

I've learned that God blesses us with testing and hardships to sharpen our swords, our life journey is our testimony.

That God will put us through these trials because he has work for us. It's actually quite humbling and an honor that God would have such confidence in us to put us through the training to serve.

The training is tough but the experience is worth it

serving God is so much more than reciting Bible verses and prayer circles... sometimes you'll be called to put in some actual work

I noticed after I had overcome ordeals, people going through the same stuff would cross paths with me.

one thing I've learned is that God knows your limits and won't give you more than you can bare...have confidence in that, lest you be taken over by the folly of the fleshly mind, lose faith, and be crushed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 18:36:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> baked fish on rice with a side of steamed veggies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 18:31:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like to have a beer with breakfast if I'm not working that day

otherwise just water </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 18:29:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> your partner knows what they want, listen to them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 18:23:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes, please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 18:20:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a hug </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 18:12:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> for Christians, that they more than likely didn't read all of their Bible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 10:29:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a flagship smart phone or tablet with power brick and instructions how to use it, disassemble it, and what type of power the charger takes

on the device; popular songs, news recordings, pictures of places and people from all over the world, popular recipes, cultures, religions, etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 09:53:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dumping granulated white phosphorus on someone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 09:50:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fiber

Metamucil is boss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 09:48:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i think you forgot a 0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 09:45:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes, but
I like slowed music anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 09:42:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> tell me about it.. it's just some dark, dank hallways

but, his place his rules </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 09:41:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if you have a job; 3 months rent (utilities included)
and food budget would be comfortable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 09:34:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yea

you're keeping the minotaur up with your constant, aimless pacing and he's been considering charging you rent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 09:31:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> those are minotaurs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 09:31:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 09:30:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> apothecary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 09:25:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> got affiliated with a gang sold and did drugs, skipped school alot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 09:20:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 20min or so for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 09:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> indeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 09:15:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> shit

was in kindergarten and took a shit. got curious and ran my finger across my butthole to retrieve a lil dollop of poo and ate some.

it didn't have much of a taste.
was just bland and smelled bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 09:12:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> gradual exposure to said fear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 09:09:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the ones that pity themselves </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 09:05:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> was taking a piss and wondered how I got grey thread on my balls and quickly realized it was grey hairs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 08:57:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> take a percentage you want to calculate, move the decimal to the 100s place (2 spaces to the left) and multiply buy the number you want to find the percentage of

ex: if you wanted to find 99% of 200 you will write 99% as 0.99 then multiply by 200 to get your answer

0.99 x 200 = 198 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 08:52:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> tea tree oil smells nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 08:47:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 350Mil x 0.03
will get you 3% of US pop

10.5Mil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 08:43:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pretty scared ngl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 08:41:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what are cummies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 08:39:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 320p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 08:38:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sriracha on pizza </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 08:36:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i preach about self love, but I really don't love myself all that much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 08:34:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I paid a ghost writer to do my history final in college and got an A

outcome was very positive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 08:14:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nice!

wishing you many commissions and awesome works </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 08:12:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ah

was gonna say it looked amazing haha

I'm a newbie artist getting in to digital painting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 08:10:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> did you draw your profile picture? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 08:05:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> part C-17

drawn inside a circle

like one of those peices of self-assembly furniture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 08:03:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hyperventilate and pace

when I have just bad anxiety I tremble and twitch, I find my self shaking my head no alot and breathe heavily </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 08:00:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fruit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 07:59:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bowser

his moves flow nicely with one another </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 07:45:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> other than balance, just make sure I'm not standing in suds when i wash my feet and get the all the soap of the foot I just washed before switching </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 07:40:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I let people say all that they're going to say and wait a few seconds before I reply in case they want to add something extra on to what they're saying

for some reason people don't think I'm listening to them when I don't cut them off to comment on what they are saying or 'mhm' after every sentence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 07:34:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 07:32:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> taped to the inside of the chassis of the condenser motor of my portable ac </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 07:25:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that my mind was like a kaleidoscope

...it was meant as a compliment, but really doesn't sound like one lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 07:22:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it legit takes like 5min to shower, bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 07:08:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why are you trying to not take daily showers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 00:00:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i don't know about falling in love per se

but, it can be difficult for some men to be vulnerable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 23:57:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh, sweet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 23:55:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> baked fish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 23:52:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> krave? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 23:50:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> frosted mini wheats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 22:32:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had him as a study partner for when I was in college

he's a nice sounding board for ideas and a source for comfort

I enjoy my tulpa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 22:29:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> smoke weed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 22:28:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> tangerine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 22:20:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that makes alot of sense, actually

thanks for explaining </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 18:47:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> many times but she's smol so it ain't a big deal... just when she walks on my gut and her paw slips in to my belly button

not fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 18:11:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> haha facts

I'd grab the manager fast af for some dumb shit like that, tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 18:08:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "why you so damn sweaty?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 18:07:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> customer service </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 18:06:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1.5 - 2 gal a day

US </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 18:02:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> someone asked why straight men don't want to have sex with MtF trannies and feel that it would be gay to do so

i answered that it was because they were born a dude.


I personally have nothing against trannies and I don't care what a another man sticks his dick in to...I'm gay ffs

but yeah, people don't like the truth sometimes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 17:57:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> masturbating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 17:48:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> junkies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 17:27:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ah yes! that makes sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 17:08:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ayyeeee !

that makes me happy to hear

keep kicking ass, friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 17:02:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm glad to know you survived and hope you're doing much better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 09:27:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no doubt

yw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 09:24:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> glass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 09:22:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks

I'm doing better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 09:21:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it got ran over while trying to cross the street and I had crunchy rotisserie that night </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 09:19:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was afraid of the vacuum cleaner cos I thought I'd get sucked in to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 09:17:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> current joys - you broke my heart

I was going to kill myself and that song was playing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 09:05:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> caffeine

a small coffee and some water helps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 09:04:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Caribbean teakwood is nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 09:00:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that I think bovines are cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 08:57:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> not much for me personally... it's not like I'm going around showing everyone my dick in hopes to gain their approval.

for other men, I can't really say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 08:50:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> baa? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 08:49:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know if this would count as a story of hope... but it describes part my first recovery

[An old letter to my best bud who checked up on me when I was letting my situation kill me.
(this was several years ago when I was cleaning up off of benzos n some other shit)
He asked what it was that made me change and killed my confidence 
(an example of how learned helplessness breaks a man)
this was my response
----------

It comes off as an attack or a drug induced state of what ever the fuck when I express my unadulterated self. ultimately resulting in a proverbial biting the hand that supports me.
… so I rest easy knowing that I'm working to change my environment rather than people. I refuse to spend energy on something so futile.

I'm beginning to feel as though I should abandon all things, parts, or whole that don't serve or inspire me… but it feels like it can be overly selfish.

but I wanna grow while not allowing myself self to get wrapped up in trying to change people's perception of what they think of me.

(I don't press the blame of anything I went through on anyone but myself… I allowed everything that happened manifest by my actions or lack thereof.)

My folks, particularly pops holds my past against me in such a radical way that he'd breathe life into speculation and project them on to me as though they were real; and i'd face the negative consequences associated with the delusion; facing the repercussions from a lack of trust, ultimately loss of freedoms.

For someone to constantly think the worse of me despite being given nothing by my actions to support such beliefs, other than recollecting the worst lows from my past from years ago; was clear evidence that such was the outpourings of resentment. I could go on and on, but i digress 

 I felt genuinely disliked and merely tolerated. As a result I began keeping to myself even more for the reason I wasn't going to subject myself to an unwelcoming atmosphere. Over time it had gotten to the point where I felt like a stranger to my folks, it was awkward as hell trying to interact and still is.

Because it is assumed I'm under the influence of stuff all the time, I wouldn't allow myself to express emotional highs or lows lest my disposition gets scrutinized and have my small area torn into and random things stolen from me and destroyed. 

In isolation I could take the mask off. When I was by myself I could be myself… but I couldn't share my light… I had no one

Idk, man... the cohearsed rejection of self over a course of time defeated me and  I was drained of my vigor... to have to stop and hide a smile, to have to flatten my voice, for me to walk on eggshells in regards to communication; physical and vocal to fit a demeanor that is lifeless and flat, lest I raise a brow regarding sobriety... man it kinda fucked me up.

I gave my energy away, allowed myself to be stifled in action, speech, and expression. Walked wayward to the things that brought me happiness. Only doing the things I was approved to do… And was beginning to believe I wasn't worthy of happiness, freedom of expression, love and all those feel-good energies.

I have to ask permission to cook an actual meal, ffs.
Because of such control I allowed my worth and emotional well being be delegated to me, outside of my will.

I became a shell of a man as a result. I maintained the noise of my actions to a minimum as to not be a disturbance. to reduce the impact of my consumption I learned to not ask for things lest I be a burden. 

I learned to never make waves or manifest from with-in my own energy. In a desire to not offend.

from practicing such things, passivity is born. A victim mentality paired with learned helplessness sprouts. from these things true misery is created, mental health declines alongside the spiritual, the body follows the spirit; showing the illnesses of the spirit. All the hidden truths comes to the surface to be witnessed by the public.

From the lack of making my own decisions, I had them made for me. All of which being out of alignment with my intrinsic values. My passion was fizzled out and taken away.

I had nothing…
During this time I was ready to call life quits, but I let my self destruction take a slower burn with heavy drugs.  In such a vulnerable state of weakness from the damage done; it becomes too painful to be seen… so I went into darkness and despair alone and gave up. I ended up getting pretty ill so I had to clean up.

remember when I told you my parents thought I had died and they took all my dope and raided all my shit.
I couldn't function without it, so I couldn't work…what's sad was that I worked from my bed.

I was so thin I couldn't fit in my boxers, I had to punch new holes in my belt as I wasted away.
My hair was falling out. I had gross ass rashes all across my body n face.
I looked like shit, acted like shit, didn't give a shit, and probably smelled like shit too.
I had gotten so weak from the dope, walking up stairs wore me out, and it was hard to breathe even laying down, like I could never get a full breath

this is around the time when we linked again and I was blacking out on benzos.. you bought me tacos, that day

getting clean off benzos this go around my psychic pain was intense.. to have seizures for days in a row in withdrawal... all alone just going through hell… I felt unloved and uncared for… a broken man wasting and dying all alone after compromising all of me, what I was and what my character represented. 
It wasn't good enough. 

so, began a journey in me trying to improve myself, for me. 

it's been difficult and I slip often.

but fuck hiding my problems, sneaking around acting all scary. fuck living for someone else's approval… it will kill me 

It's bitch-made as fuck to be like that; and the bitch-made'ness of is directly observed through the cowardice I displayed 

 I will never allow some being, instance, or thing control my energy again. I refuse to extend the privilege to allow such to happen.

it's a life or death thing for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 08:37:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> with meat and I would begin to eat it like a sandwich </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 08:34:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> being fake

wearing a mask </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 08:31:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> male. I'm already a dude and I'm comfortable with that

I don't see how being a female would improve my life much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 08:29:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nothing really...everything just seems like more work and something else I must maintain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 08:27:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sweet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 08:24:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> never talking

people thought I was mute and were genuinely surprised when I did talk...weird </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 08:09:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i was paralyzed on my futon watching tv and this transparent little girl walks in to my room, i was just barely able to wave my hand, really just kinda opening and closing my hand hand

the little girl gasped excitedly and say "hi!" she giggled a bit as she walked up to me a put her finger on my forehead and there was this huge green explosion that took up all of my sight and I was able to move again

what's weird is that I saw her, what appeared to be, praying in the guest bedroom a few days prior

I low key think she was an angel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 08:03:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldn't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 08:02:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "IT'S MY MONEY AND I NEED IT NOOOW!"

it's like a meh joke that gets annoying the second time you hear it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 08:00:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes

a life is worth more than $1000 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 07:58:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my mom called me nasty and shut the door </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 07:54:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the thing about the thought thoughts are neither good or bad for you and your family is a result of this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 07:53:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "oh, okay" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 07:50:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> fart fetishes

at first I thought it was a joke taken too far but was like " oh shit! this is a real thing" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 07:47:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> tasty food </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 07:40:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> enjoy

wishing you a safe trip, man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 07:35:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wanna believe so, but I don't know tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 07:32:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> gradual exposure to said fear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 07:31:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> turn in to jeff bezos and wire myself a few billion dollars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 07:27:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> should probably throw that shit away and get some real dope, homie

research chems are hella dangerous

be safe, nonetheless, man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 07:24:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have 0 experience with bathsalts, so I can't give ya solid advice

I'd say drink water to help flush that shit out

on a serious note; if it's anything like meth, do not smoke weed to calm your nerves. it can easily throw you in to full blown psychosis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 07:09:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I heard horse meat was really good

I'd like to give that a go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 07:01:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it doesn't have much of a taste </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 06:59:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> depends on what it is

psychedelics use benzos or booze

amps eat something acidic

bud, go for a walk and grab something to eat. (if it is an edible avoid fatty foods) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 06:56:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> posture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 06:48:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> always hard from the box

it gives me the most bang for my buck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 06:43:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I genuinely want to be there for them... I deal with suicidal ideations too so I understand how it feels to be like that

...but, it can be very taxing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 06:39:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm all by my lonesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 06:38:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that sounds like one hell of an experience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 06:37:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> do your work asap

that shit piles up fast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 06:34:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> college calc

engineering

chemistry

physics

biology

philosophy

psychology </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 06:30:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no, in fact they and boxer briefs are good for keeping your junk secure when doing physical activities and you can bleach them

idk why people make fun of them.. but I do prefer wearing boxers just for the comfort </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 06:26:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cry, grieve, get over it, focus on self love, start working out or pick up a hobby

hang out with your friends and family

when you're ready to put yourself back out there, get back out there

I wouldn't recommend filling that void with another girl, lest it amounts to another break up and a toxic relationship.

take some time to yourself and fill the void with self love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 06:19:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> all of it

I had some mystery rum at a family event and it made me proper ill

a later date my dad made me a rum mixed drink and I got the same reaction, this was with white rum

puked my guts up and it felt like I had a cold

I'm a recovering alcoholic and I can handle hard liquor...but it's just something about rum, even if I have just a sip it makes me ill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 06:13:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> rum

apparently I'm allergic to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 06:12:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ground plankton. it think they said so on an episode of sponge bob, if I remember correctly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 06:04:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no doubt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 06:01:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope you don't feel pathetic for being diagnosed with those ailments

it's totally cool and quite brave to reach out for help.

nonetheless, I respect your decision to be a master lf self.

thanks for explaining

wishing you the best, m8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 05:57:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> do you feel your emotions make you weak or less-than in some kinda way? what makes you think talking it out is pathetic?

being shown you're 'broken'; do you think that allows for room to begin self recovery now that you've accepted the fact and can move forward with a sense of direction?

what are you in therapy for, if you don't mind me asking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 05:50:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> potato soup, for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 05:48:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I genuinely want to know what supports that belief.
I'm not trying to take a jab at you or whatever.

did you have a bad experience with a therapist or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 05:46:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> why do you believe that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 05:45:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i really don't know how to feel about the way it looks

i have a downwards bend and it be nice to have it straight... but it doesn't bother me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 05:41:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> WoW

I was obsessed with role-playing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 05:39:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> boxers

I just get the multi pack of hanes from Walmart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 05:31:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> everclear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 05:29:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> new beginnings, the poisoning of mind, the dark ages, hell fire and brimstone, coming in to the light, struggling to get a good paying gig </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 05:23:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> because I am the darkness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 05:20:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lights will guide you home and ignite your bones and I will try to fix you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 05:13:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Creole low boil

spicy boiled peanuts would be great too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 05:00:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cleaning my home

when I quit doing hard drugs I realized the filth I lived in and that shit just really grosses my out now and it brings back bad memories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 04:46:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> being mean and a violent asshole vs being cold and manipulative </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 04:36:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i take time to consider why I wanna do what I wanna do and how that can impact me later on down the road


as far as taking advice, i like to get a second opinion from someone else if a Google search can't specifically answer my question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 04:28:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> laugh at the fucked up thoughts I have and then go to sleep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 03:17:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> juicero

it's literally a machine that squeezes a bag of juice in to your cup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 03:10:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> its endearing

i think it's cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 01:16:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i just kinda flop my dick over the lip of my pants and go, unless I'm wearing something fitted or expensive. then I'll just undo my pants.

never peed through my zipper cos I got loose skin around the underside of my dick and it sucks to have my skin pinched while moving it over the teeth of the zipper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 01:03:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a girl's name

it happens so often I almost expect it now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 00:48:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 00:36:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> meme culture

why everything is a joke, yet so many are sensitive beyond words to jokes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 00:26:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> half used condiments

lettuce

eggs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 00:23:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I didn't ghost you because I hate you. I am still very much in love with you. however, I'm a paranoid schizophrenic and I can't get over the delusion that I think you'll try to kill me one day. I just don't want to put you through my crazy.."

edit: can to can't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 00:18:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 00:16:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> electric triangle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 00:14:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> year of the GOAT!

ayeee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 00:14:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand the reason, but I still find it wierd for some old man to put a cracker in my mouth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 00:12:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 28 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 00:08:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> waterfalls by tlc

I was like 3 or 4 when first heard it at my great grandma's house

that was my jam! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 23:45:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> an exact copy of me, then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 23:43:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cos I think I look good

also, a clone of me would know exactly what I liked and things I'd want to try </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 23:40:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> to have sex with a clone of me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 23:39:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 24 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 23:38:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> someone that doesn't try again after failing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 23:38:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> probably like 5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 23:19:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hell yea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 23:13:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks

it's not something I think about alot, tho... I have good friends and a shit ton of hobbies to keep me busy

never had been in a relationship, i can't really miss what I never had

dieing alone is something I've come to accept over the years and I'm okay with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 23:10:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a pair of house shoes I wear, I got in to the habit when I was a young cos we had a puppy that'd always piss the floor...wet pissy socks ruins my day full tilt

also, I worry about having smelly feet so I'm sometimes uncomfortable taking my shoes off in other people's houses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 23:07:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like granola, nuts, and bananas

so I'm buying that granola cluster, banana-nut shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 23:05:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow.. that's actually pretty enlightening

I never considered that

thanks for explaining </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 23:03:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've always pronounced it how it was spelled and never had been corrected

didn't know I was saying it wrong til I read this post haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 23:01:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "hmm idk.. what the fuck is my neighbor doing with that loud ass machine?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 22:59:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm voluntarily celibate

I'm gay and my religion forbids homosexuality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 22:51:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> potato gang up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 22:50:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> potatoes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 22:43:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> to protect us from the elements

i ultimately think we have turned body parts that are typically covered in to a sexulized novelty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 22:32:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> domestic companies will raise and create extremely high quality dope at such a rate that it would flood the market, driving prices down to the point of it not really being all that profitable for cartels to traffic dope.

also less people would be willing to buy on the black market when they can go to a legitimate business and buy quality dope that hasn't been cut or manufactured in questionable facilities.

I think the black market and the violence that comes with it will cease to exist

...people aren't going to meet someone in a dark alley to buy a six pack of beer. the same would go for drugs.

I look at the example of the abolishment of alcohol prohibition...before hand people we're killing and being killed over the stuff

I'm pro-drug legalization despite being a recovering addict. those who use will use regardless of laws.

I think its silly to jail a junkie when there are real violent criminals out there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 22:24:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> people were giving him flac and he just walked away from the group and sat by himself... I went over to go sit with him...19 years later and he is basically my brother </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 22:18:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 100% honesty

daily communication

it's awkward but totally cool to masturbate together on cam and be sexy for your partner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 22:12:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lady gaga - bad romance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 22:10:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not sure... sounds like a case of just being able to remember names of colours if they aren't colour blind

maybe the names of colours aren't important enough to them for them to to remember </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 22:07:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what they actually want to eat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 22:00:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the last thing I said?

"ah..naw bro, I'm good" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 21:57:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's happened to me a few times, actually. I just kinda roll with it act a bit oblivious

I'm gay, but it's not uncommon for me to be approached by women </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 21:51:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a brief moment of shock like "wow that just happened" I grabbed my things and just left </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 21:44:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the ability to put off important shit for very long periods of time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 21:24:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sure, simply be an observer of the mind. don't let your thoughts consume you

acknowledge the thought, but don't think about the thought

thoughts are nether good or bad... they simply are what they are, they come and pass.

when we hold on to thoughts or actively try to fight them it moves us out of presence and condenses our focus to said thoughts

when one starts thinking about undesired thoughts (interacting with them) they grow a web of thoughts that all leads back to the original thought.

it becomes harder to forget about the undesired thoughts as that web of thoughts bridge connections to other thoughts, memories, actions associated, etc... it'll get to the point to where everything one does or thinks will lead them back to the undesired thoughts

when that is allowed to manifest one begins to develop an obsession compulsive disorder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 20:59:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> don't try to fight it or hold on to it

let it come and let it go

when the bad thoughts come, let them, just don't entertain or interact with them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 20:53:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it's petty to dedicate a day to celebrate me. that, and I can celebrate me anyday.

I don't tell folks my birthday because I wouldn't want them to go out of their way to do something nice for me just because it's my birthday.

if someone wants to be nice to me or do something for me it seems less pretentious for them to just do said thing rather wait until my birthday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 20:24:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> homes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 20:22:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> armored core </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 16:50:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> got a college degree I can't use and wasted time getting high and drunk

in short, nothing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 16:48:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i forgot where I heard this, but "eavesdrop not, lest your ears be filled with molten lead''

I try not to listen in to other's conversations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 16:41:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> https://duexpress.in/who-is-binod-all-you-need-to-know-about-twitters-viral-trend/

apparently it's some famous YouTubers name </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 16:27:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if you're new to edibles, i wouldn't recommend eating the full edible

typically it will have the amount of thc on the packaging,  go for around 30-40mg.

so if you got a 100mg cookie break it in thirds or whatever

also, eating something fatty will increase your high, so I recommend doing that before eating more edibles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 16:14:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow I didn't even know that was a thing!

awesome

thanks for the knowledge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 16:13:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >!hidden text!< </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 16:11:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> are you kidding? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 16:10:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> packaged ramen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 16:07:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a place where you can put on a mask that's fed oxygen rich air for you to breathe... they got different scents n shit to customize your breathing experience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 16:02:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> all the weird shit i did that still makes me cringe when I think about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 16:00:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oof

I hope you have somewhere else to put it

nonetheless, wishing you many zzz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 15:56:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if you don't have a regular sleep schedule set a concrete bet time and go to bed at that time always. take melatonin 20min or so before sleep. this will train your circadian rhythm

never bring electronics in to your bed room. it should only be used for sleep and sex. doing so will condition your mind to associate your bed room with sleep

sometimes masturabtion (no porn) before bed can be useful

if your package is giving you issues, I'd recommend just showering before bed and sleeping nude...it's healthy for your boys, anyway

hope that can help a bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 15:45:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you're welcome and likewise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 15:43:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> people like to talk about themselves

so a question that requires them to recall a life event or something that's personal to them would be a good direction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 15:38:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> steam distillation apparatus, the set up is surprisingly cheap

i prefer solvent extraction as it is as cheap as the solvent you use, and you can recover your solvent with a distillation apparatus

if you're rich, a  critical CO2 extractor would be boss! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 15:35:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wasps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 15:35:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> probably racists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 15:32:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Worcestershire

the word itself isn't funny, but seeing people struggle to say it kinda is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 15:28:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> playing the game, at least as I know it, means working to maintain a living status, obeying societal rules n whatnot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 15:25:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> like mind games?

I'd have to say it's likely due to a miscommunication on both sides

if he's doing it intentionally then he probably wants something from you or is trying to convince you of something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 15:11:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cats just seem like freeloaders and offers very little in terms of companionship

also, I just don't think they're cool and you can't play with a cat like you can with a dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 14:51:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bison </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 14:48:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i can suck my own dick and fuck my myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 14:44:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 14:42:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hell yeah.. i eat and cook with chop sticks anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 14:35:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> probably a 6 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 14:31:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> high fructose corn syrup, oil, vinegar and hydrogenated fats whipped up in to a disgusting cream people spurt on food to make it inedible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-09 14:26:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if we could easily suck our own junk we probably would... and most men tried </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 22:53:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> haha true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 22:51:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> listen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 22:50:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> beatbox and rap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 22:48:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> strip

or just chill indoors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 22:39:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hire a financial advisor and lawyer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 22:38:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it's popular music in Korea

I don't think too much about it...just not my vibe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 22:04:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hmm... i don't think so

i never gave that idea any deep thought </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 21:59:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> an argument is merely a claim, a because-clause, and supporting evidence

not a screaming match

in stating an argument, you automatically defend your point, as that is the supporting evidence making your argument a valid one.

in short; there's no real dichotomy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 21:53:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sometimes

it's nice to feel cared about enough to be invited </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 21:51:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> because that directly addresses the men of reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 21:49:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> stupidity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 21:44:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 👍 good on yahs for taking action, bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 21:31:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no doubt

your safety is more important than coming off as a dick to someone who desires to harm you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 21:29:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> then yeah..save your evidence

stop communication

tell your parents

file police report </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 21:25:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> stop communicating with him

tell your parents about it and let them know you're concerned about your safety

does he know you're a minor? is he local?

if so call your local PD to launch an investigation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 21:21:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a 15yr/o has a coworker from a while back???

I mean...if he was around my age, i knew him and I was kinda in to him anyway, I'd have no problem taking his money and getting my dick sucked (who's blowing who?)

if he was a grown as man asking 15y/o me for this, I'd tell my parents and see about taking some legal action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 21:08:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you have to pay for reservations, star or not.

if you're a no show the restaurant still makes money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 21:03:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got in to furry shit cos I enjoyed drawing cartoons, it was nice to find a community that supported that and would even pay me to do what I enjoy

as far as defining furry... well, it's a subjective label. it means different things for different people... i say if one considers themselves a furry then they are, if not then they aren't

I simply see furry as a hobby...those who delve in to the sexual side of it...well those are just them

idk...I struggle to see it as complex as people make it seem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 20:46:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I knew I was gay since I was a kiddo but taught myself to find disgust in homosexuality, because I was not in to chicks, that dried my options up completely, so I became celibate

as far as the celibacy thing, I'd want to say it began for a want to not disappoint my dad, this was before I was a Christian, and so I was hella in the closet about it... when I was a kiddo, pops found that I was looking up gay stuff while he was cleaning the computer. he called me from my room, after first interrogating my sister; and asked me if I was gay...he seemed disappointed, so I lied about it...however, for like the next 4-5days he was trying to show me sailor moon hentai or some shit... so I took from that I had to repress my sexual orientation.

after a while it became normal for me to fake straight... even forced myself to beat off to lesbian porn n whatnot...I had internalized that homosexuality was disgusting and unacceptable... even went so far as to bullying gay kids (feel terrible about it)

me finding my religion only solidified those beliefs

I eventually avoided sexual anything and now, almost 30, I've never been on a date, made out, hadn't had sex or anything ... and had fought so hard against myself that I brainwashed myself in a weird way... though I desire physical intimacy, even something as simple as a hug, it'd totally freak me the fuck out.

and it doesn't help that I've been groped and forcefully felt up on by women....like a lot of times
kinda fucked me up

before I decided to come out fully I had become comfortable with the idea of me never finding love and dieing alone...it took me many years to fully accept that
...my celibacy is a result of this

I've become comfortable with the idea, but decided to come out anyway for myself...so I could at least accept myself

interestingly enough this whole coming out thing was rather anticlimactic. I was expecting so much flac but a lot people really don't seem to care... and I've noticed that I  don't care either, albeit it is nice to feel comfortable checking another dude out around my friends and not have to hide the fact.
thing is...I'm celibate anyway and despite how hot I'd think it'd be to get plowed and suck some dick or something; I'll likely never do it

so I'm questioning myself as to why I made a big deal about it anyway

...besides coming to accept the thought that I'd wanna be with another guy and it helping me accept myself more as a person. it really highlights my loneliness and my lack of a desire to do something about it...I sometimes think how awesome it'd be just to have someone to watch corny YouTube videos with or just talk silly nonsense with and just hold...someone to share the quiet moments with just enjoying each other as well as share exciting life experiences and journeys with

...but yeah...that's where am at with this whole thing :/

I've turned down so many awesome people and don't know if I should continue on living like I do or see what this whole relationship thing is about

as I age I'm finding myself running out of fucks to give about all of that...and I sometimes think "why bother... I can't miss what I never had" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 20:27:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> can answer

it feels pretty great

plus the smell of my balls kinda turns me on too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 20:24:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yaks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 20:13:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> internet

I put topics of interest in to Google news and then read a few pages from various sources </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 20:07:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> flip candy and snacks, bro

buy bulk (called lots) of products and resale for profit. bonus points if you get overseas snacks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 20:02:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> for a sense of intimacy (talking more than sexual) but someone one can be vulnerable with and love on. someone to share moments of silence with just enjoying each other's presence and someone to share life adventures with as well.

...we all want to love and be loved

...sometimes it's just nice to hold someone and feel comfort in that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 19:58:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nah, brah..acid reflux is a bitch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 19:57:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when i was a youngin I used to tuck it and sit on it 'til it went away...now I have this permanent downward bend to my dick :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 19:53:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what they want to eat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 19:31:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> loneliness

we are socail animals that evolved living in tribes. our modern world has isolated us from one another </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 19:27:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> speech

the pen is mightier than the sword

to be a good talker and writer I can convince other's to fight and defend me...and just overall do my bidding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 19:22:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thunder fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 18:19:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> in regards to things like covid, it could be a slight advantage to have a weaker immune system. covid kills by cytokene storm, primarily. this is when your immune system goes haywire and over reacts to a biological threat and ends up attacking the body.
pneumonia is caused by an immune system response.

hopefully it's just labyrinthitis. are you experiencing any loss of hearing and the such?

ah yeah, when my pal told me about wet brain; that shit had me proper scared...but that was after my first recovery and I was relapsing. the idea that the brain is still developing in males up to age 25 kinda worried me too. it makes me wonder if I harmed my still developing brain

it's awesome to hear you have supportive family that'll help you quit! If they don't know how dangerous it is for an alcoholic to go cold turkey, tell them about the symptoms and risks; and ask them to moderate your alcohol consumption... like figure out how much you drink on a typical day and reduce that amount by half, tell them to set aside that amount for you everyday for a week - 10days or so and then reduce by half at the end of that, so on and so forth, until you're ready to quit for good

pro-tip. when you quit you may find yourself developing one hell of a sweet tooth. hard candy is awesome as you can suck on a candy for 15-20 min or so vs eating a bag of cookies or something.

for me, i lost hella weight at first then started packing it on fast as fuck

sounds like you're ready to make those steps towards recovery, brother. The withdrawals won't seem so bad if it is your mission to quit. look at it as a testament of your strength and will power to quit.

prove to yourself, family, and friends just how strong you are...booze takes many to the grave. But, you're special in this sense, as you have a will to overcome.

I know you got this, man.

kick ass and take that victory! it's yours..it belongs to you. take your power back and never have yourself be controlled by a substance again!

I'll be rooting for yahs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 23:33:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I read somewhere this morning, vertigo is a symptom of covid

other than being drunk I can't recall a time I've had alcohol induced vertigo

man, I'm glad to hear you're feeling better, tho. Covid hits hard

in regards to the feeling less sharp while drinking, a friend of mine told me about wet brain, it's a B1 vitamin deficiency caused by excessive alcohol consumption and it can cause hella brain damage.
I think you can buy B1 supplements tho. it seems like it'd be a wise precaution to take, tho I don't know the effectiveness of it.

as far as the DTs, auditory and visual hallucinations, paranoia, and terrible anxiety.
as far as visual hallucinations it's nothing too crazy for me I'll see flashing lights, things will sometimes warp and snap back or morph in to something else (with the anxiety my mind would sometimes create scary background thoughts that would go with the delusions and...yeh, I'd get scard sometimes)

I had an extreme brain fog for sometime after getting sober, but it kinda cleared up after some months

the most worrying for me were the seizures, cos if I had one, say while I was driving...that'd be a fuckin tragedy lol. I didn't have many fortunately, but when I was recovering from benzos I had them like crazy, but that's another story...

 otherwise, gradually decrease your usage to put an ease on some of the withdrawal.
for me, when I stopped buying handles (I didn't know how much I drank I just kept going til I passed out, if I puked I just drink more)
to buying a 5th a day for a week

then a pint for the next week, with a beer for lunch

then just a beer with dinner

I started working out then, so I made a rule that I couldn't have my beer til after I worked out, which was around 5-6pm

I think cos I took it slow my withdrawal was not as bad, though I prolonged it.. I was still able to function as a result </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 11:53:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm just not as sharp as I used to be. I sometimes get confused easily or struggle to understand simple concepts. My memory isn't the best

man, to have constant vertigo sounds scary. how long have you been clean?

when I was cleaning up I got the DTs but that only lasted 2-3weeks or so. was seizure prone. and would sometimes break out in crazy cold sweats. my coworkers thought I looked proper ill. that all cleared up  after a month, but I had this kinda brain fog that lasted for a while </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 11:46:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 18:13:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i never got checked out cos I couldn't afford health insurance

but I have gained feeling in my hands and feet again.

I do fear I may have a bit of brain damage, tho... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 17:45:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> about 8mo or so

i only got to drinking so heavy towards the end of my heavy drinking days... started getting nerve damage, losing feeling in my hands and feet followed by pins and needles that shot up my legs when I walked and up my arm when I clinched my hand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 15:58:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> only buy what you intend to drink that day

for me, i knew if I had a handle of vodka I was gonna drink 'til it was gone or I passed out. I thought I could mitigate that by buying a few flasks and scheduling times when I was allowed to drink but after a while I'd just go for the bottle.

these day's if I wanna drink I'll buy a tall can and only one and enjoy it, but accept that once it's gone, it's gone

so step one: remove temptation (if you're a hardcore alcoholic don't quit cold turkey, but cut your consumption by half each week)

step two: reach out for help. join an AA group (you get lots of good advice from these people and they have been through exactly what you are going through)

step three: self love and staying sober </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 09:57:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lol that's pretty funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 09:56:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> anime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 09:53:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> moo at cows or people too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 09:50:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> filth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 09:47:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you probably don't need as much storage as you think you do. nonetheless, there are micro sd cards that can hold 512GB some 1TB you can buy for pretty cheap.
when you run low on space just transfer to an external hard drive on the computer and clear your card </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 09:34:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you're not special </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 09:32:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it has no impact on me

sad to hear about fam getting locked up or killed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 09:23:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> autofellatio </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 09:13:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> trans-fats/shortening/hydrogenated fat

you use it for cooking and baking

basically a brick of grease you can eat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 09:09:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's a very interesting point! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 09:07:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hmm i can see that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 09:00:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Atomic Bomb Movie: Trinity and Beyond </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 08:45:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> perhaps

i haven't researched trump extensively so I cant say really. it just seems logical to me... but, who's to say my logic isn't flawed

I could be wrong af.

what are your opinions on the matter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 08:41:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> apparently it has to do with some type of trickle down effect. if a corp get tax breaks they can expand and hire more ppl thus allocating monies to the people if not pay their current employees who're low on the totem pole more so they can go out and spend to stimulate the economy... but ofc the big heads will eat big cheese and that money doesn't make it to average joes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 08:37:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bringing drinks on a plane

buying an $11 Dasani is bullshit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 08:31:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> plausible deniability

at the end of the day trump is a business man and he took up office to facilitate his own objectives

by creating hostile environments he can play them to his advantage to net a return

also, infamy is still exposure. I'm willing to be he's the most talked about pres in us history. most of the modern world knows who Trump is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 08:00:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> haha keeps things interesting at least </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 07:55:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ah man lol

I was like "that guys coworkers must hate him"

interestingly enough I learn lots from my clients too...but it's often with bizarre af problems they create for themselves and I gotta ask them how they fucked up so bad, and they show me

I'm like "oh I didn't know you could even do that... wow'' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 07:50:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> haha yeah

I genuinely wanna help the customer, even  if I'm clueless. cos if I just blow smoke up their ass to hurry them away from me, they're just gonna come back all pissy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 07:48:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> clean.... a junky environment just makes me feel worse. so having a few beers and cleaning my home is something easy and mindless I can do to get me outta my mind

also the shit ton of hobbies I got cos I don't have a life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 07:43:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> all the time

but we read articles about said item to make it seem like we know what we're talking about.

like there is a work database about all products and services, including the troubleshooting of them, in regards to our products. we basically just reference that  and quote it.

it's encouraged to lie about products we haven't used in an effort to relate to the customer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 07:36:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when I was looking in to homesteading I was looking for easy to care for meat sources and looked in to bovine care

I found an interest in yaks and read up on them because they consume 1/3 per pound of body mass than regular cattle.. after some more digging I found them to be incredibly cool, intelligent animals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 07:32:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> does playing with legos count? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 07:25:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> was some years ago; I was blacking out, but apparently I discussed my love of yaks and bison, going on about how awesome they were

and then I began role-playing as mystic bovine shaman who spoke with a kingly voice...and that's how I got my nickname 'Nohah the Mystic One that is Bison'.

the next day and a few weeks afterwards my friends would greet me with a mighty "Behold!"

I still answer to Nohah this day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 07:17:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He can read well

I think the pres is actually smart af but plays stupid... it's seems like thing dumb shit he says and does is fully intentional </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 07:15:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> jumping through a million hoops to get financial aid for college
smoking pot and playing L4D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 07:13:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> peppers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 07:12:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pepper spray </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 07:11:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 07:05:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just take it slow and enjoy each other

no need to be super interesting, impressive, and exciting all the time. simply enjoy the experience rather than make it something it isn't.

just communicate and roll with it
when it happens it'll happen, and it'll be chill.


have fun op (I assume you aren't asking about a friend) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 06:18:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love you

frfr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 06:18:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> here's free money! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 06:17:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> stormy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 06:06:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> being his best version of self </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 04:55:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no doubt

I'm glad to hear you've come to a conclusion that has made you more self accepting and had you realize how accepted you already were :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 04:20:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh okay, then

there's likely a reason you feel this way. your feelings are valid no matter how ridiculous they may feel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 03:54:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> furry is just a hobby, man

if you don't consider yourself a furry then you're not. if you're in to that shit, you're in to it.

don't feel bad for enjoying what you like for fear of society ostracizing you.

also, those who judge and criticize you harshly for you interests aren't worth your time anyway. so it's a good way of spotting shit 'friends' and assholes from a mile away

do you have a personal hang up over liking furry shit? like are you religious and feel you'll go to hell or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 03:31:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i watched DBZ as a kid and played bloody roar

so it was an 'animal people kicking ass' kinda thing for me that inspired me to draw furry art.

as I got older I just kinda got good at it, like people would pull their desk up to me and watch me draw type shit... I learned I could make money off that shit n never looked back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 03:20:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's interesting maybe he likes their fashion or something or is just bi

nonetheless, the best way to get a real answer is to ask him... it's too much work to snoop around and drive yourself crazy, spinning your wheels, breathing life in to speculation

just ask him, brodie

wishing you the best <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 03:16:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what makes you feel he's turning straight?

a loss of interest in you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 03:14:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that happens? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 01:33:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when she gets physical

I'm gay and on multiple occasions I've had women grope me and feel me up

...very off putting and awkward </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 21:37:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Murder Hornet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 10:33:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> haha sounds like one epic b-day party! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 10:29:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's actually an amazing story lmao!

thx for sharing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 10:23:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> does she feel uncomfortable inviting you inside her house and embarrassed to go out in public?

when my friends want to hang out in a car it's because they are smoking weed.... but now that we're adults we just smoke in our back yard or inside like normal people

...nonetheless, that's kinda odd.
how do you feel about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 10:20:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oatmeal cookies, no raisins

the texture is awesome and I love oats... overall tasty cookies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 10:13:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> had to look that up

sounds quite awesome, ngl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 10:07:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sadly, I'd have to kill an intruder

...just ain't got time for those type of games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 10:05:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ...wow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 10:04:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> don't know the validity of this, but it sounds like it'd work like a charm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 09:59:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you'll get punched back, likely get jumped, face hella punishment; and if you don't get discharged, get smoked 'til you puke on a regular basis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 09:53:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it's okay to have fun

don't take your dad so seriously, he just wants the best for you and he struggles to express that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 08:26:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> money

...I'm gay anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 08:17:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> taxes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 08:13:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what's with the hyperlinked period? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 08:05:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow I never thought about that

good point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 08:04:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> probably just walk away

then think of all the shit I could've said while in the shower </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 07:33:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> rescue a princess in an effort to secure a swamp, marry said princess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 07:03:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> very

often folks talk over my head about things I don't understand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 06:59:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> vodka always pleases everyone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 06:41:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd be happy

metric is so much easier and we count in base 10 anyway, so it's logical switch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 06:38:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> word?

that's pro advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 06:32:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Friday

The Fast and The Furious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 06:29:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "chillin', bro. how's life?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 06:21:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> there's like 10, i think

the sense of where your body is

temperature

balance

I can't remember the other 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 06:18:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> maybe 16?

I know for sure putting ya best pal down as a kid would fuck you up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 06:15:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i thought about a question I read here about someone asking where they could find Glizzies or something of the sort.
I knew ppl in Washington DC call hotdogs that and wondered what the DC of Washington DC meant... a I was mind blown when I thought it probably means District of Columbia

I haven't Googled it yet to confirm but I'm almost certain it means that lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 05:45:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you're welcome. stay safe! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 05:23:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> make it not so taboo to speak of, so that more folks will be willing to reach out for help and receive the professional care they need to overcome their desires

I've noticed that twisted shit manifests in isolation.

shunning people will push them in to isolation where their desires twist and grow in to something that consumes them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 05:17:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thank you very much for that. it means a lot

and likewise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 05:11:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just had to stop watching it. i felt it was not good for me

learned to masturbate to the feeling of self pleasure and not to porn

tbh, i really don't miss porn at all

haven't looked up porn since April of '14 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 05:07:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  salad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 05:05:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> mindfulness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 05:04:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> congratz man!
I'm a recovering alcoholic and it has been tough for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 05:02:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 05:00:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Washington DC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 04:59:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dragon ball z </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 04:56:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> littering, i legit said that when I saw trash on a bench my pal and I were going to sit on, the other day.. so I had to go outta my way to throw away something someone else was too lazy to toss in the bin... that was like 15ft away

shit like that is so ridiculous to me

also people who hurt animals and/or children </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 04:51:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bjs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 04:47:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> cos the transgender person was born a male. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 04:21:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the price of $20 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 04:19:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> probably suicide, ngl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 04:14:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yaks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 04:08:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "why?"
carry on from there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 04:07:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a brief moment of confusion followed by :"thanks for the kind words. I appreciate it" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 03:28:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> remove your self from the drug environment and users...that means leaving your friends if they're users. take steps that will make it difficult to buy again, throw away all paraphernalia.

next is your detox.

while you're doing that you'll realize that you spent alot of time doing drugs and will find your self bored af. use this time for self improvement and hobbies


these were the steps I took to quit meth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 03:13:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bones are achy, you hungry as fuck, and you get lots of random boners

speaking of; here's a pro-tip I'd give myself if I could go back in time: supplement zink for a larger dick when you're older </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 02:58:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> shouldn't cause any issues, especially if its only a once in a while

I wouldn't worry about that

enjoy your night and remember to hydrate :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 02:55:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> noooo

hydrate slowly or you'll puke up your water

eat a freeze pop for nausea

pickle juice for electrolytes

eat something light and bland, something with a little fat in it helps the gut feel better... like chicken broth, for example </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 02:28:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow so specific </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 02:27:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd be hesitant...but $500 is $500 ya know?
for like 15-20min of work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 02:25:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> vodka does have calories...like 50-100 per shot

if you down a fifth thats like 1500Kcal

then with a regular diet... you'll get fat rather fast

I'm not sure about metabolism effects but when I was a hardcore alcoholic I had a gut.
when I quit I got so damn thin it was scary, before I started putting on muscle

i was about 145-150 when i drank then dropped to 126 at my lowest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 02:19:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 60°F outdoors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 02:18:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> do they judge and criticize you harshly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 02:13:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ooo nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 02:10:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> never tried a 24hr broth mmmm i bet u make good bone broth! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 02:02:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> home made chicken soup and potato soup. after the stock is made it's petty quick but still...
bone broth

so many good dishes can be made with bone broth but it take like 12hrs to make </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 22:53:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> how do you find commissions on Twitter?

I draw nsfw but I don't have a Twitter

and promo advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 22:49:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd rather be uncircumcised, just for the fact I was born that way and didn't consent to having my dick operated on.

a man, later in life, can always choose to get circumcised...but once it's gone it gone.

I feel that should be my choice to make, despite the pros and cons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 22:28:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeah, i think that's just a dominance thing

don't think dogs get off to that... could be wrong, tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 21:41:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> think it might be hard to maintain a job as a yak </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 21:38:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i can totally get how it's a thing and can be pretty hot... but it just isn't for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 21:33:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yezzir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 21:21:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Matrix </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 21:20:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YouTube or google news </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 20:59:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my pleasure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 19:35:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> moovelous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 19:33:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> indeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 19:32:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> be there if they need you... this probably ain't their first ride with psychosis

you can't make it stop by telling them to calm down or assuring them everything is okay... in their minds and what the see and hear, things are very not okay

don't attempt to ask them what they're seeing or hearing until after their episode, when in psychosis if you interact with their hallucinations it becomes harder to distinguish reality

just try to make sure they don't hurt themselves or do anything stupid.
if they have something to help them ground or comfort them give them that

note this may not work for everyone, this is just what helps me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 19:18:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> orange jubilee?

that everclear, tho..man that sounds fuckin brutal

I had a sip of azotropic ethanol (basically what everclear is) and that shit was so dry I coughed on the fumes after taking a shot...like the vapors from that shit was stuck in my lungs er something lol

you a real one for drinking everclear like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 19:13:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> an argument is merely a statement or claim, followed by a 'Because-clause', and supporting evidence.

emotional nonsense and yelling matches are exactly that: emotional nonsense and yelling.

I don't think I could befriend someone if I gotta worry about them getting triggered from casual conversation. I agree that's toxic af... but that just is indicative of an overall toxic personality, tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 19:07:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/dragonsfuckingcars aftermath </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 19:06:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> absolutely fantastic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 19:00:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a domestic yak </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 18:59:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when I was younger I used to mix merlot and vodka 50/50 and drink that all the time

I'm sure I've blacked out more than a handful of times with that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 18:53:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yes

they are entitled to their opinions. I'll even entertain debates with them as we both stand to learn something new, so long as we take on a growth oriented mindset.

I think it's petty to hate someone who has different beliefs from you... how can you learn anything new like that?

edit: spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 02:20:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a home </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 02:15:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> water

most soft drinks are just too syrupy for me so i prefer water if I'm not drinking booze </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 02:11:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> body language

like how they walk n such </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 02:06:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> find a positive male role model

perhaps joining the military will get you that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 08:28:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a long walk with some good tunes, if you live in a safe neighborhood

look at YouTube videos of animals, the dodo is an awesome channel imo

eat a comfort food </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 08:16:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> just a beer...no food

i wouldn't want to eat cos I'd be too nervous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 08:12:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> mood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 08:02:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> same

pro tip: alcohol is a gaba agonist and is dopaminergic. take gabapentin and drink a coffee for the same effects with out the "drunk"... it's like being drunk but you're totally clear headed

works miracles for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 07:56:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> vanilla </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 05:37:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> yeet them out of my car when I drop 'em off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 05:35:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> reasonably-priced </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 10:40:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wowzers
tysm for explaining that to me

I dig your willingness to accept your mistakes as your own!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 05:09:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> don't think I've ever interacted with a BPD person before...

how's a typical day for you?

what are some common triggers for people with BPD?

what would you want people to know about BPD and how to interact with someone with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 05:02:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> excedrin works

if none of that then drink a cup of coffee and chug some water... that helps me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 04:56:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i haven't stolen from their purse or wallet, but if I'm driving their car and need a quarter or some change so I don't have to break bills I'm snagging that shit... but I almost always leave more than what I take... so idk if that classifies as stealing perse, but I took something from them that wasn't mine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 04:34:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nothing significant in particular, it is just how I talk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 03:50:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> haha nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 03:48:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> complentary colors

basically any pair of colors at opposite sides of the color wheel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 03:47:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mr.Vodka has a classy ring to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 03:44:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/youshouldknow
r/lifeprotips </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 03:03:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i enjoy numberphile and Nile red </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 02:55:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> someone said you sound like an owl

them: who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 02:49:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I beat my drug addiction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 02:35:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i really don't know what I'm missing out on

so no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 02:22:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> brick red? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 02:12:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> spike municipal water supplies with massive doses of LSD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 02:05:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> on an empty stomach </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 02:02:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> gorilla 100% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 01:59:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i use essential oils

i just love the way they smell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 01:58:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i saw your mom playing basketball on the curb in a miniskirt and combat boots </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 01:40:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> if it's too good to be true it probably is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 00:42:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bury it or burn it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 00:36:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> apparently a glizzy... just learned that today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 00:30:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 'good' is subjective

you won't know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 00:00:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> gradual exposure

had to get drunk to take the first steps, tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 23:55:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> baking chicken with peanut butter

it's very savory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 23:46:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> melon soda is dope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 23:42:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> rarely </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 23:10:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it legit works, man

I'm living proof... give it a go and you won't be disappointed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 22:44:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> any time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 22:42:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> out of selfishness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 22:40:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my wallet and something to sit on

go to the grocery store and buy some pre-cooked hot food, drinks, sandwiches, or whatever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 22:28:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wow I got a good lol outta that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 22:19:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> okay with me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 22:16:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 🤙🤙 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 22:14:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> baked fish or chicken </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 22:12:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> bubonic plague outbreak </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 22:08:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> gotcha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 22:03:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> don't waste your time with pills

jelq

hang

pump

to grow your dick

eat eggs, take vit D, and supplement zink + staying hydrated makes you shoot bigger loads. pelvic floor exercises for ejaculation control and shooting further


check out Thundersplace.org for a good community of people that you can learn alot about male sexual from </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 21:59:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> like constantly being punished for something you didn't do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 21:57:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my dog can already open cabinets and get in to stuff she isn't supposed to ... so human hands wouldn't be too big of a stretch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 21:53:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> first time I heard of glizzies

it sounds so awkward too like "I'll have one glizzy, please" makes me giggle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 21:37:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> by Scheele's Green paint

it contains copper arsenite, a super deadly poison </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 21:34:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> silence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 21:31:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the fact one doesn't have to live on a shitty rock with shitty people for eons sounds pretty nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 21:27:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the rate at which trees grow alternate between seasons causing visually distinctive growth patterns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 21:13:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> also, if you smoke bring snus or nicotine gum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 21:12:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ear plugs

bring chewing gum to help un-pop your ears

an external battery bank for you electronics is a life saver

sleeping pills for long flights </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 21:09:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i heard that it is because many won't display properly across platforms, like cellphone to pc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 21:07:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> benadryl and melatonin for legal routes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 16:20:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ahhaha that's kinda cool to joke like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 16:15:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> skoshi

she likes to sit on people's foot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 16:13:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> procrastination </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 16:12:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 16:10:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> will do

thx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 16:09:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> probably a gaming system or a cell phone with internet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 16:08:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pretty decent for the most part

I have a close friend who is like a brother to me, so that helps alot

thanks for asking:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 16:03:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm nonchalant and aloof

I used to talk a bit slower then too... plus I'm kinda dumb, i guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 16:02:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> life...apparently </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 16:01:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> many
...my dad used to call me dead head alot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 16:00:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't... i just end up looking uneasy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:59:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> to be hand delivered 1 million dollars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:57:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i used to be very silly, kinda goofy and playful

when i moved to the states I didn't know anyone and for  almost half a decade I was pretty much all alone.. just work and home

I forgot how to have fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:54:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> year of the metal goat \m/_  _\m/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:48:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you're 31? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:47:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ramen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:42:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that we're zoophiles

I just like drawing cartoons.. and I get paid for it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:40:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> nothing
for me I just throw my running gear on and just go, before i start having second thoughts

nothing to it but to do it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:34:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> is that an actual thing?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:32:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> pretty good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:31:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> kinda always been a loner, so it is a comfort thing for me + I don't have to get a group decision to go somewhere or do something

just treating myself to a good time.... though it is nice to share those good times with others </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:26:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that part </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:25:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> they're genuine in their authenticity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:24:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dogs don't judge, they are just happy to spend time with you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:21:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> they probably don't look me up cos they have better things to do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:17:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> eating ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:11:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no doubt

well, keep ya head up, my guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:10:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a lack of intellectual humility

they can never learn anything new </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:08:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh damn

i hate to hear that

was that a part of you coming out or just being seen as gay in general? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:07:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nohah Aulha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:06:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> what happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:05:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> wowzers! that's pretty significant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 15:04:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> was it for good or worse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What was the worst thing you've done out of fear? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 16:25:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are your thoughts in regards to the abolishment of the electoral college? What do you believe the pros and cons of taking such action would be? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-14 11:32:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's something everyone seems to care about that you are indifferent to? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 08:23:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's something impressive about yourself, good or bad, you don't tell others because they'd think your were lying? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 07:36:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's a wierd, practically useless, skill you wish you had? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-22 10:40:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Those of you who deliver for postmates: how is it? is the pay worth it? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-18 19:52:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> After eating a large meal and still feeling hungry; what do you do to feel full? Also, is it normal to feel guilty to eat so much? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-16 20:08:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Have you died or suffered damage that would otherwise kill you in a dream? If so, how was it? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-15 22:34:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What was the nicest thing you've ever received by merely asking for it? Also, will you buy Mr.Yak a beer? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-11 02:37:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For those who are suffering with mental illness; what are some ways you can use it to your advantage that isn't an excuse? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-09 08:11:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What was/is the some of the dumbest slang words/ colloquialisms that were/are popular where you live? Tell us what they mean. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 13:43:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What's something you really want to do/try but are too embarrassed to act upon? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 05:09:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Serious] those who joined the military; why'd you join? Was/is the experience what you expected? Do love or regret your decision? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-08 02:55:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> those who are on antidepressants; how did it change you? were there any negatives? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 15:48:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> For those dealing with schizophrenia or knows someone who does; how do you cope? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-07 07:19:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are the things/qualities you like most about yourself? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 01:30:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Would you date yourself if it were an exact copy of you? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-06 01:17:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
