<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject80</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 23:42:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> routine: wash with Loma moisturizing shampoo and conditioner. scrunch excess water out with big t-shirt. then apply Not Your Mother's detangling/leave-in conditioner spray (the stuff in the pink botttle). brush hair out with Wet Brush. apply Uncle Funky's Daughter: Curly Magic gel. plop for at least ten minutes (sometimes longer if i get busy). after plopping diffuse until 90% dry (i get tired of diffusing lol). then i get my bangs wet again (they look funky after diffusing) and apply Herbal Essence Curl mousse to them. then i scrunch out the crunch when it's 100% dry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> a good hair day 3 months ago versus now! a curly cut and better products makes a big difference :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 23:42:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 08:48:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dude im kind of in the same situation. my parents (mostly my mom) have SUCH high expectations for my grades. they keep insisting that i won't get scholarships unless my grades are LITERALLY perfect lmao. my parents aren't gonna make me go back to regular school but the nagging is the same :( good luck with everything bro. just remember to take breaks from school and don't overwork yourself! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 00:19:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have no idea. Neither of them got scholarships and my dad even ended up dropping out and going to a technical school. I think it's cause I'm a "former gifted child" which means they expect perfection from me when in reality I'm maybe slightly above average. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 23:04:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks for the inspiration for my survival house :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 23:02:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i love the roof shape! maybe try some landscaping around it? you could add more coarse dirt and gravel or maybe even some podzol to the path. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 18:00:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah ACT scores play a big part too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 06:54:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep! I don't stress about my grades too much cause as long as I graduate college and high school my future jobs aren't going to look at my high school grades lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 06:49:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the reply. I kind of figured that other factors (extra curriculars, volunteer work, an essay, etc) would matter just as much if not more. My parents are just super focused on the grades and it's stressful :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 06:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah a lot of colleges also care about extra curriculars and volunteer work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 06:41:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the reply. I kind of agree. I tried book club for a couple but didn't like the people. I'm also doing online school this year so clubs are kind of impossible. I might try some volunteer stuff but it might be hard with my work schedule. I'm not worried about my GPA because it's at least a 3.7 maybe a 3.8. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Will I be denied scholarships for a few A minuses, even if my GPA is a 3.8? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 06:37:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>
I have been arguing with my parents (mostly my mom) for a couple of years about this. My parents keep insisting that unless I get PERFECT A's in ALL my classes I won't get a scholarship. I haven't applied anywhere yet but I'm planning on applying to some state colleges. I am NOT going to an Ivy League school where they probably wouldn't give scholarships to anyone with less than a 4.0.

Everytime my mom brings it up I can't help but just internally groan and roll my eyes. How is getting a couple A minuses or B pluses going to dramatically affect my likely hood of getting a scholarship?? I don't expect to get a full ride or anything because I don't participate in clubs or sports and I don't really have anything else going for me, but I'm not not going to get a scholarship at ALL. I plan on applying for a bunch of small $500 scholarships too because apparently those add up fast and don't have much competition. Not to mention the fact that I am not going to college as soon as I turn 18, I'm going to work for at least a year to save up.

Are they spewing complete bullshit, partial bullshit, or do I really need perfect grades?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Will I be denied scholarships for a couple A minuses? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 06:34:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have been arguing with my parents (mostly my mom) for a couple of years about this. My parents keep insisting that unless I get PERFECT A's in ALL my classes I won't get a scholarship. I haven't applied anywhere yet but I'm planning on applying to some state colleges. I am NOT going to an Ivy League school where they probably wouldn't give scholarships to anyone with less than a 4.0.

Everytime my mom brings it up I can't help but just internally groan and roll my eyes. How is getting a couple A minuses or B pluses going to dramatically affect my likely hood of getting a scholarship?? I don't expect to get a full ride or anything because I don't participate in clubs or sports and I don't really have anything else going for me, but I'm not not going to get a scholarship at ALL. I plan on applying for a bunch of small $500 scholarships too because apparently those add up fast and don't have much competition. Not to mention the fact that I am not going to college as soon as I turn 18, I'm going to work for at least a year to save up.

Are they spewing complete bullshit, partial bullshit, or do I really need perfect grades?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 02:48:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> when in build mode, click the house icon in the upper left corner of ur screen and add the traits u want from the list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 02:45:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this is such a good idea! i want my nice windows and doors back 😔 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 02:25:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i forgot wood walls exist lol. time to add some to my builds! this looks really nice btw the artwork on the walls is pretty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 02:18:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> where is that hair from??? i love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> he's a poser! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 02:44:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> blurry picture of cats </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 20:14:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 18:44:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> blooming day by exo-cbx is so pretty! it's one of my fav music videos because of how aesthetic it is. the colors are gorgeous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 19:07:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i use BSL shaders :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 20:40:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Mizuno's 16Craft](https://mizunomcmemo.blogspot.com/p/resourcepack.html) :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 04:39:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> no problem! glad i could help :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 04:37:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i use BSL shaders! what world i use kind of depends. sometimes i like building on superflat if it's just a normal build. i use regular worlds if i want to try building on the side of a mountain or something else that might require terrain. using regular worlds can be good for inspiration! you might see a river and think "oh i want to try building a house that sticks out over the water." but in the end, it doesn't really matter what world you use :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 04:14:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i used to struggle a lot with details too. tbh what helped me was looking at other peoples' builds for inspiration, watching youtube tutorials, and experimenting (mostly in creative mode). [here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_vbNeYh3C54) is a video by Grian that might help. i like to fill in empty space with fences, walls, and trapdoors. don't do overboard with details though, too much looks cluttered! using a variety of blocks helps too. another big thing is adding depth! in this particular build i used stripped warped logs as pillars and i made them stick out from the blackstone. i also used warped fungus to separate the first and second floor, it sticks out pretty far. another example of depth would be adding a layer of stone bricks (or cobblestone) on the bottom, in front of the blackstone (or whatever you are using as your main wall), to look like a foundation. it's kinda hard to explain. sort of like building in layers. it takes practice to learn how to add detail but it's not hard when you get the hang of it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 03:58:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 02:51:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> glad i could help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 02:48:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> try different shapes! i like building in an L or T shape. sometimes stacking shapes can be cool too (like building the second floor larger than the first). using different roof styles as well can take your builds to a whole new level. sometimes i build something and it looks really boring until i add the roof! when i build something i experiment a lot and try different stuff to see what works. using a variety in blocks (like buttons, fences, walls, etc.) is good too. you can also use real life references if that helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> warped/blackstone house i built! texture pack is Mizuno's 16Craft :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-17 01:42:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 22:53:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> dude im so sorry you had to go through all of that. i live in UT as well and i am planning on leaving someday. maybe try to go to college out of state? from what i've heard, college is a better place to meet people! maybe try getting a job as well and working on sundays to meet other non or ex Mormons (if your parents will let you). i hope everything gets better and you can meet a non Mormon girlfriend :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 18:12:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> right now i'm on 11.21.9.21 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 03:20:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i also had this issue yesterday on my 3a. if you go into the settings for the Google app, press the three dots in the corner, and uninstall updates it works again! then update the app again in the play store and that should fix it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 09:33:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> go ahead :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> dynasty house i built! it's not very practical but it looks nice :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 06:41:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 19:42:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i will if today goes badly. hopefully that isn't necessary because i have no idea how to get a different instructor. i think she will listen to my feedback </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 08:26:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> quaker instant oatmeal. they changed it about a year ago and now it tastes like cardboard. it's less creamy and the fruit is super weird. even the generic store brand is better :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-18 00:17:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> she's a demon and way too smart for her own good! she's a little menace that can open doors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 21:12:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it's one of my favorite ones of her! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> penny getting ready to bite my finger! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 19:47:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 03:44:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> it's impossible to monitor whether or not students are wearing them too. kids far outnumber staff and when they're told to put one on they'll just take it off once the teacher's back is turned :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 02:25:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> my school is overcrowded with over 2000 students and they want to go back 4 days a week with everyone in the building at once :( my family is looking into doing online school this year. i bet a lot of schools will end up closing again because of the huge increase in cases opening will cause. it's going to be a disaster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 20:30:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> goodbye </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-10 02:14:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i will look into that, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> DevaCurl Frizz-Free Volumizing Foam alternatives? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 21:28:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hello! i would first like to mention that my hair is 3b and fine so i can't use any heavy products that contain ingredients like shea butter or coconut oil. i recently got my hair cut at a curly salon. the stylist recommended some styling products for me to use. i have been using Uncle Funky's Daughter: Curly Magic (a curl stimulating gel) and DevaCurl Frizz-Free Volumizing Foam. i was aware of the DevaCurl controversy but i figured i would try it out anyway. not the greatest idea. i've been losing almost twice as much hair than normal even though i got about half my hair chopped off :/

i also switched my shampoo and conditioner from Maui Moisture to Loma.

i like Curly Magic and i would like to continue using it (i have a huge 32 oz bottle). any good dupes for the foam? preferrably something cheaper. maybe something else to use instead of the foam that would mix well with Cury Magic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> reaching for the sky! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 21:06:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 03:51:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> she wouldn't move when i was making my bed but i don't think she's complaining </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 20:43:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> she was practically posing for a picture :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-04 00:56:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> she's surprised at how fluffy she is </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 03:01:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 18:39:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [sunset](https://youtu.be/jvimpjCbR-w) by KNK is a pretty good song! they've been around since 2016 but haven't gotten much attention :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 06:39:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the only times i went were for baptisms for the dead. i went twice and never again. i felt really anxious the whole time. it was very confusing and everybody but me seemed to know what they were doing. also, standing around in the changing room, wearing nothing but a towel, waiting for a stall to be open was super uncomfortable. and on top of all that, the stalls weren't tall enough for me (i'm 5'9"), i had to bend my knees so i didn't flash anybody lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> small rant! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-07 20:16:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
