<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject74</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 18:22:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> esh. i know what it’s like to come out to your friends and being unsure about their reaction. anything they say that is even slightly off can send you into a fury because of how vulnerable you are in that moment. a lot of people don’t understand how annoying comments like those are, so; she does suck for saying that and not really thinking about it first. but you also came at her a little too aggressively. again, though, i know what it’s like to be in that moment of vulnerability, and a lot of people don’t understand that. maybe apologize to her and just tell her how it made you feel, upfront and calmly? congrats on coming out xx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 22:43:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that definitely looks like it. thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 21:17:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ah ok np </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-07 21:16:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hey im working on opening a plot right now think you can hold her for me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 08:40:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> alolan dugtrio. every time i see it i get chills. they just... did not.. have.. to add.. hair.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 22:46:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ESH but she seems to suck quite a bit more.. this is a whole ass mess and you better get that kitten back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> gmax kingler. gonna need that “pain” flair again </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 04:28:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 07:03:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh are they? im not realt familiar with trades here yet. ill lower them then. thanks for letting me know :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 06:57:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> EDIT: THESE ARE *NOT* SHINIES! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 06:56:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> non </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 06:47:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA. he is not obligated to accept your apology, especially if you “apologize” by calling him a dipshit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 04:55:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks a lot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 04:52:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ign is TOAST code 5832 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 04:47:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> a lapras would be sick. looking for anything particular in return? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-07 21:12:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ah. that makes sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-07 21:03:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i did. i sent a bunch of drampas and when they came
back it said they weren’t suited for the job, so i have no idea what they’re actually looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 01:25:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> oh thats awesome! i love dusk balls too, definitely would prefer that over a repeat ball. thanks so much :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [8] not even an hour ago a three star mantine broke out of the ball after no shakes and disappeared into the den. soon after i found a shiny salazzle, and now this! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 22:28:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I take back my last post. maybe life isn’t too terrible. but this time i wasn’t messing around; master balled the fuck out of this salazzle </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 21:48:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> shiny 3 star mantine just broke out of the ball without even a single shake </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 21:39:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> is there a “pain” flair? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> this was my first time hatching a shiny egg and it took so. many. i was getting a little paranoid and thought i might have done something wrong and wasn’t meeting some requirement to even breed for one. but finally. lots of drampas to still give away if interested </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-13 19:00:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 18:50:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> good to know. definitely gonna have to start working on that. thank you again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 18:40:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ok. thank you for your help :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 18:24:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> so *when* do the EVs apply to my pokemons stats? if im battling and have accumulated say 4 EVs, does it apply to my pokemon immediately after the battle(s) end? or do they only apply when i reach the next level? when will i see their stats actually start to improve? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 17:59:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What are EVs?

im playing through ultra sun and my team is super weak. each mon can take 2 hits max before fainting so im barely scraping by in battles. all at level 30/31. after checking their stats and doing a bit of research i decided the biggest problem was probably EVs. however, im having a hard time understanding the concept. the best example of a mon that needs work is my Rockruff. level 29, ability is Keen Eye, Hardy nature, characteristic is Thoroughly cunning. stats are
HP-70
SPATK-30
SPDEF-31
SPEED-45
DEF-34
ATK-51
as you can see his defense is really not too great. so what do i have to do to get his and all of my pokemon’s stats better so they dont get KOed after two hits?

TLDR: my pokemon are weak so please explain EVs to me like im a 5 year old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-03 22:13:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i get where you’re coming from. my father is the exact same way, except, ALL the time. he’s very disciplined with his diet so he’ll have lots of chocolate/snacks in the cabinet and only eat a little bit every night. last year he got a huge dove chocolate bunny for easter and it was around until a month or two ago because of how slow he was eating it. so i would jokingly say in front of him “you arent even eating it!” things like that. but unfortunately YTA because while it is true, they aren’t eating those delicious looking snacks, it’s still theirs. imagine if you had a chocolate bar stored away for a special day and one day it was gone with the reason of “you weren’t eating it”. maybe buy him some new oreos as an apology :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-03 15:13:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i personally enjoy all of the hatching to get to a shiny. and yeah i felt bad, and i also dont want to have a charizard named “pkmlab.com” seriously what was i gonna do with that? i took the masterball it was holding, im not the pokemon moral police. its a meme buddy if you wanna hack charizards into the game whatever but if you send them to me theyre getting released </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-03 03:36:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> i ended up releasing it. it felt wrong and i probably wasn’t going to use it in battle/trade it anyway so it would’ve just sat in the box forever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> have almost an entire box of gmax charizards. variety of abilities and natures. not looking for anything in particular, dm me if interested :) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-03 03:17:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-01 15:37:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that’s so kind of you! but i think im going more for the experience of finally cracking open that egg, you know? seriously though, thank you for offering </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-01 09:16:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No, but I’m still breeding for the shiny so if I do I’ll let you know :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 05:04:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks. And I know there’s the link code for trading Phantump anyway, but it was just such a (maybe) shitty end to such a nice trade, you know? Easily could’ve been someone who just kept my Zamazenta and left, or anything like that. Definitely overthinking it, but we all know it can be difficult to find honest/courteous people on the internet sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Looking for a user Fatboi904!!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 04:13:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fun title, I know. I was trading with this user on 7218 for a Zacian for my Zamazenta. I changed the name to “SendBackPls” because I really wanted to keep it, you know? They sent it back immediately which I was really grateful for. I of course sent back their Zacian, but we continued to trade for a bit. I sent them a Drampa and an Oranguru hoping it would fill their dex. However. They sent me a Phantump. Which I had not discovered yet, so that was cool. I figured we were both done with the trade and I had thanked them the way I wanted to, so I left. But at the time I didn’t know that they probably wanted the Trevanant back to fill their dex! I’m probably just overthinking this but I feel real bad about it. Maybe they don’t care at all. Who knows. But it’s really bothering me. So hopefully I can somehow find them and give them their Trevenant back and whatever else they may need. Any help would be appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-04 13:27:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> watching chiaki die in both the anime and SDR2. especially in the anime. i played/watched in a weird order, i watched DR3 before i played SDR2, so i knew chiaki was an AI before i started playing; so when she died i knew she wasn’t coming back when they woke up. the despair inducing part was the feeling of helplessness knowing that there was just nothing i could do, she was completely dead in every sense of the word and there was absolutely no way i could bring her back. i love chiaki, she isn’t my favorite character, but she definitely gave so much and lost the chance to see a much more hopeful future, which fucking sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
