<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject39</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 17:45:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Según yo entiendo la empresa no puede despedir a empleados que han estado en ERTE los 6 meses posteriores a la reincorporación de esos mismos. No he leído ni escuchado nada de una norma parecida para los empleados, o sea, lo que tus compañeros quieren hacer no llevará ninguna sanción. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 20:19:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dad would do that as well. He also convinced me and my brother that they have machines inside the farms to shake cows... for milkshakes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 15:56:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That list is great! Something to work through the next couple of weeks. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 15:54:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! There are lots of things here to start with, some of these I know a little bit of and some I don't. Thank you for the tip about patents especially! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 18:40:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the advice! I'll definitely check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Learning technical SEO, where to start? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 14:39:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi guys, I'm looking for some advice on learning technical SEO. Basically, I know the basics of technical SEO, and bit more about certain aspects of it, but I really need to improve my skills.

This is what I know:
- HTML basics
- Structured data (theory, not so much practice)
- Crawling and indexing basics
- Sitemaps (again, theory)
- Redirects

I've learned all this stuff on the go, basically researching them whenever it was needed, but now I have this patchwork of knowledge with lots of big holes in it. There are so many classes, webinars and articles online that I'm overwhelmed with all the options and I don't know where to start. I hope you can give me some tips about good resources (can be paid).

Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 18:04:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn't know that! I'm gonna brush up on my jellyfish knowledge, there are lots to spot around here. Thank you so much for taking the time to answer my questions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 16:52:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interesting. We saw some fish in the white part just above the tentacles, that's why we supposed it was sticking around to eat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 16:26:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cool! It probably stuck around for a bit because of all the fish that were in the area then. I believe it was swimming around for about half an hour and then I lost track of it. Thank you for the info, very interesting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 15:12:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! I guess it's not that common to see one of them? We've never seen any jellyfish that big. Would you know why it was so close to the shore? We were about 15 metres from the beach, and the water was quite shallow too (waist deep). One lady said it probably came closer to shore to lay eggs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Can anyone tell me what kind of jellyfish this is? Spotted in South Spain near the shore, about 1 metre long </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 14:22:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Say cheese! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 09:45:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 18:56:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Al desayuno de media mañana lo llamamos así, desayuno de media mañana.

Sí, he escuchado a algunos malagueños decir desayuno de media mañana, o simplemente desayuno. Algunas personas no desayunan cuando se levantan (o se toman sólo el café) y toman el desayuno sobre las diez en el trabajo.

En cuánto a si es en toda Málaga, creo que sí. No soy española entonces no voy a decir que soy una experta, pero tengo amigos por toda la provincia y nunca me han mirado raro cuando digo almuerzo jajaja. Hasta creo que es así en toda Andalucía, pero no estoy segura. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 18:16:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Qué curioso. Vivo en Málaga y aquí llamamos a vuestra 'comida' el 'almuerzo'. Que yo sepa en Málaga no existe nombre para vuestro 'almuerzo'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-25 08:58:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stay with a host family. That's what helped me the most. If you can find a family with children of about your age even better, you can hang out with them and their friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-13 08:38:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have no idea about that, but you are right that 'u' is used a lot more in Belgium but not in the Netherlands, it sounds very formal to them. You could do an experiment and use 'je' on some pages, see how it goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-10 21:38:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hmm, it can't be semantics in that case. It could be that your competitors don't offer services in Belgium (free shipping and the like) which makes Belgians leave the site very fast. It could be that your brand is more known in Belgium and gets more clicks because of that. Honestly it could be anything. Without knowing what your industry is it's a bit hard to say. You could look at searchers' intent. Maybe the keywords you are targeting have an informational intent in the Netherlands and a commercial one in Belgium (or vice versa), and your content is more suited to the Belgian intent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-10 20:45:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi, Belgian SEO-er here. The person or people who produce content for you, and the people who work on SEO, are they by any chance all Belgian? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-10 17:25:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No problem :) I forgot to mention that the bus company in Malaga (EMT) has an app that shows you the timetables of their buses, and for each bus stop it shows you in how many minutes the next bus will arrive. Might come in handy when you're in town. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-10 17:18:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi! I've lived in Malaga for a couple of years now, here's my faves.

Favourite restaurant: restaurante Antonio in El Palo to have fish (it's out of the centre, but you can get there by bus: line 11 to El Palo, last stop). My favourite place for coffee/brunch/quick lunch is La Flor Negra near Plaza de la Constitución in the city centre.

Cool places to visit: this depends whether or not you'll rent a car. In the city, there are several historical/cultural places to visit such as the Alcazaba and the Gibralfaro, and plenty of museums about art and history. If you're renting a car, I'd recommend El Torcal de Antequera for hiking, Frigiliana if you'd want to see a typical white village and Ronda if you'd like to visit an old town with amazing views. The Nerja caves are also worth a visit.

Something interesting to tell: I'm not sure what you'd like to know :) Malaga has a rich hostory, you could do a free walking tour to learn some things. Alternatively, if you're into ghosts and legends, there are ghosts tours (I've seen some ads on Instagram for those).

Best way to move around: you can walk or rent a bike or e-scooter. If you want to visit places outside of the city centre you can take a bus, one trip is €1,30, and you could get a rechargeable card (it's 1 or 2 euros to get the card itself I think, and €8,30 for 10 trips. You can use it with multiple people and there are a lot of places where you can recharge it).

I hope this helped, and enjoy your holiday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-23 10:13:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for this! I completely missed that article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-20 20:18:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe... If it's schema related it must have to do with a markup that exists already. The company I work for is in it and we haven't added any new markup recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-20 20:16:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the reply John. I guess if it's here to stay we'll get some info in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-20 15:15:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm seeing it in both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Anyone know what this Google feature is? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-20 13:20:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Earlier this week I noticed this Google feature: [https://imgur.com/a/HmczOcP](https://imgur.com/a/HmczOcP)
Does anyone know what this is? First I thought it was something to do with the Hotel Ads, but now I don't think so. I also thought it might have to do with the organic ranking, but that doesn't appear to be the case.
Thanks for your help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is this new Google feature? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-20 13:03:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Earlier this week I noticed this Google feature: [https://imgur.com/a/HmczOcP](https://imgur.com/a/HmczOcP)
Does anyone know what this is? First I thought it was something to do with the Hotel Ads, but now I don't think so. I also thought it might have to do with the organic ranking, but that doesn't appear to be the case.
Thanks for your help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-13 09:56:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in Puerto de la Torre and I love it there. My neighbourhood is very calm and there is a nice park near my house where lots of kids play. However, there are some more decrepit parts in Puerto de la Torre. DM me if you'd like to know some specific streets/more info. One thing to keep in mind tho, you absolutely need a car if you live in Puerto de la Torre, especially for work. It's quite far from the city centre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-08 13:23:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The dates are quite complicated, especially because late December all prices for holiday homes go up because of the holidays. Why do you need to be near a post office? There are letterboxes throughout the city and you can buy stamps at the 'tabacos', which are small shops that sell cigarettes, stamps, sweets etc and you can find those everywhere as well. I agree with the other comment that a place on the coast outside the city would be cheaper, but expecting to pay 550 pounds for that entire period is quite unrealistic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-05 13:42:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! Unfortunately with this bus I would have a two-hour wait between my arrival at the airport and the departure of the bus so it won't work for me. I'll keep it in mind for the next time I have to go, it looks like the fastest connection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-05 13:41:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you, in the end I went with this link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Public transport from Billund Airport to Aarhus </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-01 13:20:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi guys, I hope I can get some help RE public transport in Denmark. I have to travel from Billund Airport to Aarhus, and I've seen on Maps that I have to take a bus to Velje (I think that's what it's called?) and from there a train to Aarhus. Can I buy tickets in advance for the train/bus or do you have to buy it on board? Is there anything I should know about how prices are calculated, does it go by travel zones or is there a fixed price? Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-09 11:47:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi, why do you say that you should avoid Squarespace? I've heard about Wix being bad for SEO, but is Squarespace bad too? Asking because I've been considering to use Squarespace to make a site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-06 08:47:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry, I'm not into clubbing so I can't really give you recommendations. I do know there is a soul festival coming up, and in the port area there's usually live music in the weekends. If you and your friends are into cards, a Spanish deck could be a good gift. It's also used in other countries, but if I'm correct it's originally from Spain. It looks like this: https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/8/89/Spanish_National_pattern.png/1280px-Spanish_National_pattern.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-05 23:38:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where I live (Malaga), people often give a mini bottle of the local wine to their wedding guests, maybe you could do something similar for your groomsmen? (If you want them to be able to take it home this probably won't work though) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-23 09:35:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, i agree an I'm from Malaga too. Especially Nerja, there's just not a lot to see. Malaga city itself isn't too bad to visit but Seville is more interesting and more beautiful. It's by far my favourite city in Spain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-14 09:58:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The same happened to me! I started listening to kpop around 2010 and I loved it, so I wanted to share it with my friends. The point is, I used to live in a rural area, everybody only listened to popular music in English or our own language, and they all thought kpop was super weird. I stopped taking part in conversations about music because they didn't want to hear about kpop. Last summer, I was visiting my village (I moved to a different country where kpop is a bit more known), and on this popular radio station I was hearing Fake Love. It was a surreal moment for me and I almost started to cry. Every time I think of that moment it makes me so happy I can't really describe it. It can't really be compared to seeing your favourite artist live or even interacting with them, but for me personally nothing will live up to that moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-20 09:33:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> La Bella Julieta and Julia's Bakery are both very popular options (both are in the city centre). La Canasta is also very well known, they have nice croissants and cakes but it's more expensive. Casa Aranda has already been mentioned for churros, but I also want to recommend Café Madrid. They offer churros madrileños which are a bit lighter than the churros from Casa Aranda. For a budget option, there is Granier, it's a chain of bakeries and while they may not offer the very best pastries, they have decent cakes and other baked goods for a good price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-10 22:59:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If your exchange is arranged through your university, ask your professor. There's always one of two who are in charge and they will be able to give you info on most universities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-06 18:08:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely do that. When you're planning on making such big changes, and a lot of them at once, it's best to talk worstcase scenarios and what you would do. If you wouldn't want to move back to your country, you could both live to a different place for example.

And the language thing: my husband and I also have completely different languages (mine is Germanic and his is Roman, so there is no overlap at all), and he is rubbish with languages, but he's still tried to learn some things in order to have short conversations with my family and friends. It's the decent thing to do when you're in a relationship with someone whose language is different than yours.

Btw, something else that may be good to talk about is interactions with his family. I also moved to a different country for my husband after 2 years of LDR. In his culture it's very normal to visit the parents' place at least once a week, one thing I am not ok with for a couple of reasons. We had a talk about the frequency of family visits and about not living close to his parents before I moved. If there's something similar that would be a definite dealbreaker for you, now is the time to talk about it, before you invest time and money in a move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-06 13:48:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree with all the other commenters, and almost wasn't going to comment until I read this. You don't say if he speaks your native language, but I'm going to suppose he doesn't. The fact that he is not interested in learning other languages, not even your own, concerns me. How will he communicate with your family? When you go visit your family in your country, will you need to translate for him all the time? For me that would be a dealbreaker. Also, he should at least be open to move to your country. What if you move, but you notice that you can't live that far from your family, or you don't mesh with the culture, or simply you don't like living there. Would he consider moving back with you to your country? If he wouldn't, what would that mean for your relationship? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-02-05 11:44:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Still, you shouldn't have gotten mad. He was tired when he came home and forgot to message you. I doubt he did it on purpose. That being said, his reaction is over the top, especially since you're LDR and can't just go over to see each other. You need to communicate respectfully with each other. If he doesn't want to open up communication on his end and pick up the phone, there's not a lot you can do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-28 11:37:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can only talk for certain about holiday rentals/hotels in Andalusia: here they need to have a scan or photocopy of the physical ID. In other Autonomous Communities it may be a bit different. That could also be the reason why this time they took a photo at that hotel but not at others (because you're in a different Autonomous Community). Anyway, it's definitely not out of the norm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-28 09:44:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly. This is also the case at holiday rentals. They need the copy because they would have to be able to provide it to the police if they are asked to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-23 13:28:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any foreigner living in Spain needs a NIE. WIthout you can't open a bank account, can't join the seguridad social, can't do an empadronamiento... As far as I know the NIF is the same as (or similar to) the NIE. Also, there's nothing "eventually" about getting a NIE, you have to apply for it, and it's best to do it as soon as you're able to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-21 12:05:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah yes, that's probably it, we are all EU citizens, so our ID cards from our countries are accepted. I would be interested in getting a more permanent, plastic card though, since the NIE is only a piece of paper and the ink on mine has faded a lot (and if you laminate it, it's not valid anymore). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-19 21:17:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> En caso de cambio de domicilio, documentación que lo acredite. >>> This is maybe the only thing that you would need a certificado de empadronamiento for...but I'm not sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-19 21:16:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Second one. I had no idea the first one even existed. I work in an office with almost exclusively foreign coworkers, and no one has a residence card. Never been asked one either. I got married this year to a Spanish citizen (so lots of paperwork) and I got everything done with just the NIE.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-19 09:51:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in Malaga, so I'm not entirely sure if this applies to Barcelona, but I didn't need any empadronamiento to get my NIE. In fact, having a NIE was required to be able to do the empadronamiento. So I think it's NIE first, empadronamiento later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-02 22:27:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My now husband and I were long distance for 2 and a half year. Apart from regular Skype dates (we had a schedule for that), we would write each other letters and exchange them at the end of each visit. Usually only one, but if we knew we wouldn't be able to see each other for months at a time, he would write me 4 or 5 and tell me to open one every first day of the month. I loved that. You could also write letters and send them through mail as a surprise, I did that a couple of times and he was always so happy to get them. It's inevitable that you feel sad as the visit comes to an end, but things like that can give you something to look forward to during the time apart :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-22 15:07:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely Instagram, especially for visual businesses such as photography. Instagram also draws a younger crowd. At my day job (which is digital marketing) I've noticed that the main demographic for Facebook are people over 40/45... Younger users are using Instagram a lot more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-21 10:29:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly, Facebook for businesses is dying. Organic reach is declining steadily, and virtually the only way to make money off Facebook is by advertising. It still is the norm for all businesses to have a Facebook page, so I wouldn't recommend deleting it. Keep it but don't put too much effort in, just have enough activity on your page that people see it's not dead. You could link it to Instagram so everything you post there shows up and Facebook too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-08 21:53:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Only if it rains a lot... There is a possibility but in the time I've lived here (4 years), there hasn't been a lot of rain in December, if any rain at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-12-06 09:55:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a linguist and got into SEO a couple of years after graduating. I think it's definitely a plus, especially if your company/your clients have sites in multiple languages like my employers does. Being able to grasp the mechanics of a language has helped me out a lot. And if you study a practical (applied) linguistics course, it will also help you with your writing skills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-30 10:10:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We did. We did an engagement/family session with them (photos of just the two of them and with their children), so they knew how we work and how we edit. I did tell my husband (he's the main, I'm second shooter and do marketing etc) to let it go, but he is quite stubborn and did not want to give up. To be honest, we did need the money to invest in equipment. At least we learned a lot from the experience about how (not) to handle clients, and our contract has tripled in length after this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-29 09:32:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh man, where do I start? The first wedding we did was paid (but at a reduced price because first wedding and all). They contracted us after having an engagement session, so they knew our editing style. After the wedding, the bride just got off the rails. First she wasn't happy with the edits and demanded re-edits, which we did but only the photos she wanted to go in an album. After that she still wasn't happy and came to use with 'examples' of photos of her niece's wedding saying that she wanted the photos like that. Those photos were completely different than ours because of lighting at the moment of taking the photos, so we explained that even though we could try to imitate the style, it's impossible to edit in that specific lighting. She just blew up. She hadn't paid us in full yet (also the last time we let a couple pay us part of the price after the wedding btw) and started demanding that we give her the originals, that she would have a family member edit them (as if an amateur could fulfil her request even tho a pro had told her it was impossible). She asked to meet up with us several times and was a no-show, wasting hours of our time. In the end we gave her the originals to get paid and to be left alone. It hasn't hurt us, we haven't seen any pics online, and we got her out of our hair, but the entire situation has left such a bad taste that we want to avoid anything that could lead to messy situations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-29 09:23:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely, we're never shooting without a contract again. Lesson learned! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-29 09:23:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We did one other wedding, and the bride was a regular bridezilla (late payments, requesting re-editing several times, requesting the originals so she could send them to family members for them to edit...). The situation got out of hand partially because we weren't firm enough with our answers and not having specific things in the contract, so we're working on that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-28 15:54:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The sister isn't in our country and doesn't speak our language, so it's not possible (but it is a good idea actually) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-28 15:53:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! As it turns out, there's even a subreddit with RAW files for editing lol. We will send her that one and the subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-28 08:46:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, that's what we're thinking. We would however want to help out the sister, but not with our photos (seriously, we got into such a mess the other time that we almost gave up on professional photography). I guess it would probably be best to go with: it's the norm of the industry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Our client wants the original, non-edited photos </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-28 08:38:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So... last weekend we did our second wedding ever. It was pro bono, as the bride and groom are refugees and did not have any money for the wedding (the entire event was organized by the community, everything was donated, it was pretty incredible to see this all come together). We were asked to shoot the wedding the night before by a friend who was coordinating the entire thing. Since we got this gig so last minute, no contract was signed.


The day of went pretty well, we got nice photos, made some contacts with other people from the wedding industry... But...


Yesterday the bride asked us to send her the original photos and the edited ones, because her sister apparently is studying photo and video editing but doesn't have a camera so she can't take any pictures to edit. Basically, the sister wants our photos to practise.


We do not want to send the originals, we did it once for another couple and it was such a mess that we decided not to do that again EVER. We include it in our contract, but obviously, since no contract was signed we can't refer to this.


Do you have any scripts to politely but firmly make clear that we do not want to share the originals? Alternatively, do you know of any resources that we could pass her for her sister (sites where she could find unedited photos maybe, or where she could find people looking for an amateur editor)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-22 13:38:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you don't want to do more chores than hovering and cooking, maybe consider hiring a cleaning service if it's possible. Your gf will have some (or a lot of) days where even putting away laundry will be too much for her, especially after working all day. Hell, my mom has chronic pain and fatigue too, and some days she's too exhausted to do that (and she doesn't even work like your gf). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-22 12:48:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> > edit: the credit cards that were opened in my name have been closed as far as I know and I was able to eventually take out student loans. I’m not sure how the process works but my dad said he took care of it

You should doublecheck it because your dad has proven that you can't trust him when it comes to your finances. Check that every card has been closed, check if there are other cards that you don't know about yet, and inform yourself about the process so you can see if he did it correctly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-22 07:32:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You are not being unreasonable. However... I personally would also feel uncomfortable with letting my SO pay for international travel for me, especially when we'd only been together for one year. Have you asked why he changed his mind? If you want to make a more pricey trip with him, maybe the best thing to do is to talk to him WAY in advance so he can save for it and contribute more (maybe you've done this already, but I can't deduce it from the post). Another option is to make closer and/or cheaper trips. For all the other situations you mentioned, yeah, that's him being too proud. He has to change his mind from "I have to pay for everything and if we can't do this thing that GF really loves bc of my finances, too bad" to "my GF really loves this thing I can't pay for, but it doesn't matter if she does bc her happiness is more important than my pride". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-16 13:00:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't do a surprise just because you want to prove something, do it because you think she will like it. Also, don't ask her in front of her family and friends if you're not 100% sure that she will like that. I love my family, but if my husband had done what you're planning, I would have said no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-08 13:36:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We spent 5 days in Seville and it was the perfect amount of time to see the city. We took our time exploring the city and we had enough time to see the most important sights as well as relax. Especially if you're going in summer it's worth staying a couple of extra days since it can get quite hot in the afternoon and you don't really want to go out in the heat (our tactic was going to the hotel after lunch and relax till 6 or 7 pm, and then go out again).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-07 00:16:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, there is a different accent and yes you will probably despair a bit at first. Andalusians tend to "eat" letters ("agotao" instead of agotado for example). They speak very fast too. But don't worry, most people will speak slower and articulate better once they notice you're a non native, and feel free to ask them to speak slower too. (Source: non native who went to Andalusia to learn Spanish, didn't understand a word at first but in the end left speaking Andalusian) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-01 10:59:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sometimes IVA is lower for certain items bc they are so called "essential items", that's probably the reason. (I have no idea about the specific percentage tho) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 13:59:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> En mi caso no me explicaron nada de eso. Yo en el momento de solicitar el NIE había encontrado ya trabajo indefinido (aunque no por cuenta ajena), y lo dejé claro, pero por alguna razón ninguna de las 3 personas que me atendieron me dijo que el NIE que estaba pidiendo era el temporal. La triste verdad es que hay algunos funcionarios que no tienen ningún interés en ayudarte lo mejor posible... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 10:38:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here in Spain it's required to give your ID and they have to make a copy of it. Actually, they have to see and copy the IDs of all the guests above 16. You don't get it back a few hours later as the original commenter said though, it only takes two minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 09:54:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Vivo en Andalucía, y lo que pone en ese gráfico no es verdad. La gente se llama católica sólo porque sus padres lo son/eran, no porque ellos mismos de verdad creen en dios. Las personas mayores sí son religiosas de verdad (la mayor parte por lo menos), pero de toda la población ellos son una minoría. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 09:47:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1.Honestly, I personally would split Madrid and Andalucia in two trips instead of combining them (with Madrid, Toledo, Segovia etc in one trip and Granada, Cordoba, Sevilla in another). However, you should look at what works best for you and go for it.

3. You can eat churros in the morning or in the afternoon, there are no rules about that. If you can, have churros in Madrid and in Granada, they are very different.


Some other comments:

Maybe a bit redundant, but if you haven't gotten your tickets for the Alhambra yet get them ASAP! It's the most visited tourist attraction in Spain so you need to get them well in advance. Also be aware that the tickets are only for the morning or the afternoon, not for the entire day.

If you can, visit El Escorial, it's really beautiful. Also, if you are in Madrid, try to visit Toledo like you planned or Segovia, both are definitely worth a visit.

To go from Madrid to Granada, look into flights. Usually flights are cheaper that train tickets, and it will save you a lot of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-30 09:13:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Todos estos pasos son los que yo seguí, aunque en mi caso no pude sacar cita para solicitar el NIE porque para poder solicitarla necesitaría tener ya el NIE (no tiene sentido, lo sé, bienvenido a España). Entonces comprueba si es posible sacar la cita, y si al final ves que no puedes, ve preparado para hacer mucha cola.


También un comentario adicional: cuando yo fui a solicitar el NIE, me dieron el NIE temporal que sólo es válido durante 3 meses. Tuve que volver para sacarlo otra vez. Entonces mira bien cuando te dan los papeles porque si no tienes que hacer todo el proceso de nuevo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-29 09:03:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Según mi experiencia, es mucho más fácil vivir en España teniendo el NIE. Para los trabajos en general hace falta que tengas un número de seguridad social, y no puedes sacar eso sin el NIE. Para abrir cuentas de banco también es mejor tener el NIE, porque muchos bancos simplemente se niegan a abrirte una cuenta si no lo tienes (eso me pasó a mí). Además, para pedidos online viene mejor tener el NIE, porque en la entrega te suelen pedir que les des tu firma y tu NIE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-23 10:19:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not working in a hotel, but for our last team building, we had pizza and after that went to an escape room. That was a pretty fun day. The other office did archery and rocket building. Just keep in mind that building a good work environment doesn't depend on team building exercises, it's got more to do with everyday interaction and communication.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-18 09:41:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >
>
>I proposed that we take turns doing what each person wants; I have Thanksgiving and he has Christmas one year, and then he has Thanksgiving and I have Christmas the next year.
>
>My boyfriend has been clear that he wants us to be with his extended family on his turns for both holidays, which is fine.

And when it's your turn, he should be fine with whatever you want to do for the holidays, whether that is going to your family or celebrating only with your nuclear family.


If you start going to his family all the times you can't go to yours, his family may start to expect that you'll ALWAYS celebrate the holidays with them.


I completely understand that he likes to be with his extended family, I come from a very close extended family myself, but it's only fair that you get to decide what to do when it's your turn, instead of defaulting to celebrating with his family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-18 09:14:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, water sports and beaches in general. Cabo de Gata is especially beautiful, with a lot of small coves. Though if you have to stay closer, you can't miss out on El Torcal (I mentioned it before). It's not really well known by tourists, but it's a very beautiful area and a great place to take photos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-18 07:06:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the best way to travel :) if you can, go down to Cadiz when the weather is a bit better and see the beaches of Tarifa. And Cabo De Gata is also very beautiful (it's in Almeria, but it's pretty doable to go there from Andalusia).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-17 23:43:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Playa El Chanquete is a beach in the El Palo neighbourhood. It's considered a more 'fancy' area of Malaga, but IMO it's not really that fancy (anymore at least). Google "Restaurante Antonio Playa Chanquete" and you should be able to see find it. We're regulars at that specific place, but there a lot of other restaurants along the beach and they're all good. Plus, you're not going in high season so the prices should be lower. Granada is definitely worth a visit for the Alhambra alone (get tickets online!), but as a city I personally like Cordoba more. In Cordoba you can't miss the Mezquita and the patios of the Palacio De Viana (though in October I'm not sure which plants are in bloom). There's also Seville of course, but compared to the other two the travel time is much longer and you'll be getting more out of your day if you go Granada or Cordoba.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-10-17 23:13:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go to Playa El Chanquete in El Palo for the best fish dishes. Museo De Malaga is a good museum if you want to get to know the history of the city, and the Museo Ruso often has good expositions too. The CAC is a nice museum if you like modern art. Alcazaba and Gibralafor are the usual suspects too. For nature, I suggest Frigiliana (nice white village with good hiking), Ronda and El Torcal De Antequera national park. If you are willing to travel a bit further, you can visit Granada or Cordoba by bus or train. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-25 09:34:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi! My husband and I are a photographer duo based in Malaga, but we wouldn't mind going to Seville for a shoot (we visited recently and there are some amazing places to shoot). If you want more info and see our portfolio, just drop me a message and we'll talk ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-12 08:52:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like you're in luck. Most supermarkets don't open in Spain, but the Carrefour website says that that particular Carrefour does (from 10 am to 10 pm). In case we're not talking about the same Carrefour, here's the address:  Avenida Circunvalación, s/n
Centro Comercial CostasolCentro
29620 Torremolinos


In the event that it is closed, most small grocers and Chinese food shops do open on Sundays.


((Disclaimer: I haven't been to that Carrefour ever, so there is a small possibility that the info I found may be wrong)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-07 10:05:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah, yes, that's right. I must have had a brainfart moment when writing the comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-06 13:19:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You don't need a NIE to travel, a valid ID (for EU citizens) or valid passport is sufficient.


Also, you can get a NIE that doesn't expire if you are living permanently in Spain (if you're only here temporarily it doesn't make sense to get one). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-31 13:18:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly, we only use natural light and whatever artificial light is present at the venue. We have mainly done afternoon weddings that stop around sundown though, so that hasn't come up a lot (the golden hour shots are usually the last shots for us).


The point is, we've noticed that in our region most photographers have this approach, or sometimes they use flashes to create contrast, they don't use a lot of artificial lighting. The few times they do it's usually a softbox. We want to take advantage of this and use artificial lighting to get more creative shots and generally to stand out amongst the crowd. Since we don't have a lot of experience with lighting and my husband sometimes has to shoot alone, we're looking for an easy system, which is why Magmod stands out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-31 13:13:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the pros and cons. We've watched some of those videos you mention, and also video reviews, but they were all too positive if you know what I mean... Good to hear their customer service is great. We agree that it's quite expensive, but then again, it looks so easy to mount that we think it could be worth it.


I'm not the main photographer of our duo, and my husband isn't here right now, but maybe in a while we'll get back if he has some more questions. I am interested to know what flashes you are using. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Looking for opinions on the Magmod lighting accessories </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-31 10:24:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My husband and I are starting out with a photography business (mainly weddings), and we are looking to invest in some lighting accessories. We stumbled upon the [Magmod system](https://magnetmod.com/), and honestly, it looks really promising: easy to mount and assemble, seemingly very good results. However... we'd like to get some opinions from people who are using it already in the field. Is it really that easy to assemble? Is it really universal as they claim on the site? We have Nissin i40 flashes, so any experiences with that flash in particular are appreciated. What do you think about price/quality? And lastly, are the results as good as the with traditional lighting accessories?

&#x200B;

EDIT: Wow, thanks for all your imput guys. For now, we've decided not to go for Magmod for a number of reasons. One, we're not in the States, and if we import such an expensive product we'll have to pay a lot of additional taxes, making it even more expensive. Two, we can't try it in a store which is something we like to do (we have searched for stores that sell it, but nothing in our area). Three, as u/dewthedrew90 and u/evanrphoto have pointed out, an expensive system is probably not the best way to start out if you're not that experienced with using artificial lighting. Well be following your advice and getting some less expensive equipment first (maybe we can get it secondhand through my job, so fingers corssed). Also thanks to u/kcdale99 for recommending van Niekerk's book, it looks very useful so that will be our starting point.

We still like the Magmod system and will most likely invest in it along the road, and maybe by that time some of the problems you've pointed out in the comments will have been solved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-30 11:12:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, Idealista for sure and Fotocasa is also a good site. Do NOT use Milanuncios, it's full of scams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-27 12:50:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bus tickets are generally cheap but you will lose a lot of time. Trains are fast but sometimes the tickets are more expensive than plane tickets. I'd say compare the prices of train vs. air and choose accordingly. For Barcelona-Seville I would choose to get plane tickets, even by train it will take a long time to arrive.


You can rent a car in Seville, but there's plenty to see to keep you occupied in the city. We visited in spring for 5 days, and still didn't see everything we wanted to see. If you do rent a car, check out the beaches of Cadiz or the Doñana Natural Park. Also, if you want to visit the Real Alcazar in Seville, you should get your tickets now, or when you're there book a guided tour. Lines are crazy, but guided tours and people with pre-reserved tickets get in faster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-27 08:47:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, great to hear it won't be for a limited amount of time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-27 08:47:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, definitely. Housing, food etc are all quite cheap. It's not bad up north either, but in my experience it's still a bit cheaper down here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-25 10:46:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will he he online all day, or does it start at a specific time? We don't want to miss this, but we're from Europe so we need to know when to connect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-24 12:58:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in South Spain. Two of my best friends are surfers, and they mainly surf around here (Costa del Sol and Costa de la Luz). They've told me that the Costa de la Luz is one of the best areas to surf. Up north, Asturias is definitely the best place to surf in their opinion. They try to go there each year to surf for about 3 weeks, but they go in September or October, and even then, they can't surf some days because of the bad weather conditions.


To give you an idea of the weather in Asturias: one of my other friends went to a surf camp up there a couple of weeks ago, and could only surf 2 out of 6 days because the sea was too rough (she is a beginner). This was this month, in the middle of summer. Doesn't mean that in winter the sea will be super rough and you won't be able to surf, but there's more chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-22 13:35:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> > We’ve tried to stop seeing each but then she finds ways to contact me again and tell me she loves me and wants to keep meeting me, and that I’m all she thinks about.

Sounds like she's using you. Your "girlfriend" doesn't care about her husband as much as you think (if she did, she wouldn't be with you), and she also doesn't care that much about you because if she did she would leave her husband to be with you, or she would respect you when you want to stop seeing her (sorry if it comes over harsh but it is what it is). My advice in this situation is to forget about her and decide what you want to do about your marriage, work on yourself and be the best possible parent to your son. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-22 12:26:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's not the university, it's the Ayuntamiento (city hall). The university building is just down the road. And yes, it is the coat of arms of Malaga. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-14 11:35:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Late to the party, but Alison from Ask A Manager can definitely help you with this. She can also give you scripts to deal with the situation of the two year commitment and the amount of notice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-14 09:24:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh man, I would love to have info on LR. I have a couple of Facebook friends that work with them, and while they are too far gone to listen to any reason, I'd love some info on compensation plans from them to inform people getting started.


About your questions... I'm fairly new to the anti MLM movement so my answer to your first question may not be entirely correct, but in my understanding, people at the bottom basically funnel money to the top. They invert a lot of money into buying the products, to a point where if you don't recruit you don't make any profit. Apart from that they also invert a lot of time and resources (transportation, extra costs for booths etc...). Basically, if you don't have a downline, you may break even, but you will mostly lose money.


I also have some dear friends who make a decent living with an MLM (Essens, in case you are wondering). I am very happy for them that it works, because their home situation is bad, and they can't have traditional jobs because of it (not going into details for privacy reasons). However, I will never buy anything from them. They were lucky to get involved with the company when it first started in our country, but people that start with them now can't make a living. I think your parents got lucky too, but the sad truth is that most people that get involved in MLMs lose money, and even end up with debt. If you're interested I can send you a BBC video I saw a while ago about MLMs, it's quite interesting.


Your last question... I personally will not buy any MLM products ever. I don't care if they are actually good quality products (which is the case with some MLMs like Tupperware), but the business tactics are unethical and very predatory. The job itself... I don't think it would be an unethical job if you refrain from agressively recruiting people, pressuring friends and family to buy your products and lying about your income/lifestyle on social media. Unfortunately, with MLMs, if you don't do those things, you probably won't be able to turn it into a steady form of income. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-13 13:43:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not sure how it works in the Nehterlands, but here in Spain you can't do that. All tourist accommodation (hotels, hostels, appartments etc.) need to keep a register of the IDs of all guests and be able to present it to authorities when asked. If you sneak someone in, the hotel could be in serious problems. As said, not sure how it works in the Netherlands, but don't try sneaking anyone in without checking this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-08 10:42:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Obey Your Body is not an MLM in my knowledge, they have representatives and sell at ridiculously high prices, but there's no recruiting going on. Their sellers are always pointing out flaws to anyone unfortunate enough to fall in their clutches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-08 09:31:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >there is a huge language barrier

But there isn't. They all speak English, they can talk to you. If they won't use English when you're standing next to them, they will the ones being awkward, because they would be choosing to exclude you.


You have met some people who will be there already, so you can definitely talk to them and take it from there. Yes, the people who are not in a conversation with you probably won't talk English, but that is actually logical and reasonable. What is important is that the people that you engage in a conversation are speaking in English.


Source: I come from a multilingual family and we have these situations all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-07 10:09:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's great that you made an appointment with your therapist, because regardless of the cause of your panic attacks and anxiety, it's something you need to address.

Now, on to the real issue here: your SO. He is being very inconsiderate, and by continuing to hang out with his friend for very long periods of time even though he knows how it affects you, he is saying that his friend is more important to him than you are. I don't know what you could do to make him realise that you are absolutely not okay with the situation (you having panic attacks about it should have made it obvious to him). If I were in your shoes, I would have ended the relationship, but I am not you and I don't want you to feel that you have to take the advice of an internet stranger. You will figure out what the best course of action is for you, I don't doubt that.

Surround yourself with people who love and care about you, don't be too hard on yourself, and don't give up therapy. Things will get better. We are rooting for you :)

(Edited because words are hard.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-06 13:33:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not safe. Where I'm from it's one of the worst MLMs around. Yes, some of their products are actually decent, but they are way overpriced and the company itself is very predatory and toxic. I had to cut people out of my life because of Forever Living.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 11:34:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To someone from outside the relationship, yes, it is very easy to come to the conclusion that she is cheating, because the way she is avoiding all conversations about it does point to something shady... BUT there can also be a perfectly reasonable explanation. You know her better than your friend so I say trust your gut. There is only way to find out what her errands are, and that is to have an honest conversation with her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 11:24:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, in that case it's really weird that she doesn't want to have lunch with you. The only other reason that I can think of is that the errands she runs are for something that make her embarrassed to share it with you this early in a relationship (no idea as to what it could be though). Your best guess is probably to be honest to her about how it makes you feel (and how her refusal to have lunch with you and even just tell you what her errand are make the situation look probably like something a lot worse than what it is). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-08-03 11:09:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly, to me it sounds like she doesn't want to attract too much attention to your relationship at work. If I were in the same situation, I would be worried that people wouldn't take me seriously as an employee, and that they would start thinking about me as \[BF\]'s girlfriend, and not as 'that employee that delivers good work' (especially if your position is higher/more important than hers).

Whatever her reasons may be, her behaviour and the fact that she doesn't want to talk about it is strange. I agree with u/airaqua, it's time to have an honest conversation about it. It may be a small thing for her, but for you it obviously isn't, and it could damage your relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-31 12:15:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> >I feel like marriage would be out of the question now and in the near and semi near future for me

In my opinion, you should be honest with your girlfriend. Communicate that you aren't thinking about marriage right now because of the things that are going on with your family, and that you prefer to wait.


You have clearly stated in your post that your family comes before your girlfriend, which to be honest makes it sound as if you aren't invested that much in this relationship. If I'm reading this wrong I'm sorry, but those are the vibes I'm getting.


> Financially not able to do all.

The point is, if you really wanted to, you could find a way. You could have a cheap wedding, set boundaries with your girlfriend's mom, look for scholarships for your sister... I'm not saying it would be easy, but it's not impossible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-30 13:59:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I ran with Appco for one day as some kind of 'training': just accompanying a girl going door to door selling contracts with an energy company. I was also at their offices. It is super shady, though it didn't strike me as an MLM, more like a sales company with very shady business practices that brainwashes their sellers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-12 08:13:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She doesn't, only on her chest and a little it on her paws! The neighbours have a ca that look a lot like her, initially we thought their cat was the father of ours, but then we discovered she is also a girl!


She isn't really black though, her fur has rusty undertones and in summer her fur gets lighter on the sides and looks orange.


Here are some pics (with a bonus one of her as a kitten): [https://imgur.com/a/hqlJ4rK](https://imgur.com/a/hqlJ4rK) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Patiently waiting for a bird to check out the bird house </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-11 13:18:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-11 12:08:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You've been together for 3 years but he doesn't want to introduce you to his family? That and his obsession with his friend are red flags to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-11 11:09:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in Spain and Essens is huge here. Sadly, I have a couple of friends who sell their products. Essens started out selling cheap imitations of high-end perfumes, but a while ago they moved to makeup and now they also sell skincare.

The prices in my opinion are as you say, not as high as most MLMs except for some products, and the quality of the perfumes is very good. I personally haven't bought any products from them, but I've smelled their version of a brand perfume I have and it's very hard to tell the difference.

That being said, it still is an MLM. Their website clearly states that though recruiting is not obligated, you can earn a lot more by recruiting and getting a bigger team (they say that you should at least get 10 to 15 downlines). They offer "free" holidays and BMWs (couldn't get access to that part of their site because apparently you need to be a member).

I've been looking for any income disclosures but I can't find any (if anyone else has found that info please pm me). I can say that it's exactly the same as other MLMs in the sense that only the people who get in early earn a good amount of money and extras, but they still have a lot of strings attached, and it's by no means an "easy" way of earning money.


ETA: one other thing they have in common with other MLMs: they claim their perfumes don't have any chemicals in them, which is a total lie. My MIL has an allergy to most chemicals and she cannot even smell their perfumes withouth having a reaction, yet still my friends insist that their perfumes are all-natural and that she can use them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-06 14:21:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also, I think that even in that case she should be paying rent. In a relationship, costs should be distributed evenly, or at least equally according to income. A relationship is not an excuse for one partner to live off the income of the other, especially if they themselves are able to contribute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-06 14:15:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree with you, a couple and 1 person in a 3 bedroom house is definitely not crowded and there's enough room for everyone to have their privacy. (tho I think with two roommates there will still be enough room for everyone, AND you would be able to save more money. Blows my mind that she doesn't see it the same way tbh) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-06 13:53:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think you are being unreasonable. One thing I do wonder: does she earn a lot less than you? Maybe that could explain why she doesn't want to pay rent.


The compromise I can see here is to treat it as if you both were moving to a rental apartment, and you would divide the rent 50/50 (or however you want), and have her pay that (so in the case of a 50/50 split, $450). I don't think you should ask her to pay $900 because she won't be occupying one room by herself, she will be sharing it with you.


Regarding the roommate situation: you are the owner, so ultimately it's your call, and I think you're absolutely right to keep having roommates and use that money for the mortgage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-05 13:45:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish I could help you a bit more. Good luck, and whatever happens between you two, I hope you'll both be happy :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-05 13:35:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I find it hard to believe that she hasn't got the slightest idea of what she means by saying 'cementing', but she could just have a gut feeling I suppose.


To me, 'cementing' brings to mind making the relationship official, introducing each other to your families and all that. This is me personally though. You could propose this to her (if you haven't done it already). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-05 13:23:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Since she brought up the 'cementing', my guess is that maybe there is something that bothers her/that she doesn't like/that preocupies her about your relationship. I would ask her to clarify the 'cementing' comment.


On the other hand, your relationship is very new. You're probably still in that stage where you're getting to know each other more and where you are getting used to each other, so maybe that sensation could be the reason why she said that the relationship needs 'cementing'. In that case, there's not a lot you can do but give it time (obviously this doesn't apply if you've been friends for a long time before starting your relationship). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-03 08:50:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the reason I suggested a sabbatical. I used to live in a different Northern European and there you could get a sabbatical and come back to your old employer, they would basically hold the job for you, no need to resign (disclaimer: I have no knowledge about visas, so no idea if that would also work with the visa OP has). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-03 08:50:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, I don't know anything about visas, so I have no idea how you would go about that problem... If there is no way around it, reconsider resigning. You shouldn't move back to your home country if you aren't sure, because then there's no turning back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-07-02 14:00:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you are having second thoughts, why don't you try taking a sabbatical year (doesn't have to be a year, could be less), and live in your home country for that time as a trial period? If it's not how you imagined it to be, you could always go back to London. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-27 10:45:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Could be that they also do independent sales reps. I remember when I was about about 8 years old my mom would get catalogues in the mail to order stuff, but I always thought this was bc we lived in a very rural area. Looking back this could have been some kind of independent consultant thing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-27 10:21:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a great gift /s. At least she didn't push you to buy after you told her no. Also, is Yves Rocher really an MLM? They have stores where I live, didn't think MLMs have storefronts... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-26 10:49:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> > I have this extreme thing with jealousy in general, even if it's towards me. Basically, I overreacted big time to her jealousy towards me, and felt a very big responsibility to stop it. I absolutely hated feeling like I was making her sad by being good, but looking back, I realize she wasn't feeling jealousy anywhere near the way I perceived, that it was never as deep or serious as I took it.

I think there may be a bigger issue here. I don't think this is a normal feeling to have, and the good thing is that you seem to have realised that too. You could definitely benefit form therapy (I believe everyone could benefit from a couple of therapy sessions). It won't hurt to try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-25 11:22:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Basically, you've gone from one extreme to the other, but neither situations are healthy relationships. What you state in your post (wanting to cuddle, wanting you partner to listen to you when you feel insecure or have something on your mind), those are completely normal expectations to have.

>Am I that needy/irrational/selfish to want some support from my partner, what he thinks is putting your problem on someone else


No you are not. You are not being needy or irrational or selfish.


> I don't know if, when we will talk again in the following days, I should give him a chance to change
 He had a relationship of 8 years before me but they never talked. Ever

You can try, but in my experience, people rarely change. If he gives you the excuse that his ex didn't need him to listen to her: you are not his ex. You have different needs and if he wants to be a good partner for you he has to change his behaviour.


OP, you deserve a relationship where your partner listens to you and respects your feelings. Right now, this is not that relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-22 13:04:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You don't have a communication problem. You have a boyfriend problem. He is putting you down and minimising your feelings.


On top of that, you say that he will be moving to Holland to be with you but he is not doing anything for the move (no tickets, no job applications...). It feels like he's stringing you along.


Rethink your relationship. Do you really want to be with someone who dismisses you and not gives you any support?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-21 12:28:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah. I'm a jw and very antimlm and I am very disappointed at the number of people buying into all of that crap, and almost all of my jw friends are too (especially bc the MLMers are constantly pressuring you to join/buy because they reason that members of their congregation MUST support them. Ugh). I'm working hard to educate people, especially when I see MLMers prey on them. It's very frustrating tho.


Note: not looking for discussions about my faith, just wanted to let you know my perspective as a jw and antimlm person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-21 07:46:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not Chinese but Spanish lol. I think u/bahhamburger has given a pretty good script to handle the situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-20 12:24:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's not rude at all, and if his parents are reasonable people they won't feel hurt or disrespected.


Is there any chance your BIL's family comes from a different cultural background than yours? I've noticed that my in-laws (who are from a different culture than me and my family) want to very close with my parents, but a close relationship between the parents of a couple is quite unusual in our culture and my parents have felt uncomfortable several times. I can't help but think this could be a similar situation, and that your BIL is just clueless that it's not something you like/are comfortable with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-06-19 13:54:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unfortunately, when someone has a brain tumor, their behaviour can and most certainly will change. My parents were in the same situation as you, although not as extreme. I suggest talking to his doctors to get some coping mechanisms (my dad told me this really helped), and therapy will definitely help too. Try looking for support groups as well, there are plenty for cancer patients and their families (the hospital should be able to give you some info on that I suppose). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-05-24 12:46:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ik denk dat het beter is om in het Nederlands te antwoorden. Bezie de tijd dat hij in NL is als een test voor de toekomst, en maak je niet te druk over de andere beslissingen die je denkt te nemen. Kijk eerst hoe het gaat tussen jullie twee, en maak dan pas een beslissing over de verdere toekomst.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-23 18:06:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Not at all, go ahead :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-04-23 13:04:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was in a VERY similar situation as you. My boyfriend and I were also young when we met (19 and 21) and were long distance, just like you and your partner.

I have known since I was 14 that I want to be childfree, and I didn't want to lose time in a relationship if he didn't feel the same way. We talked about this topic after 3 months, and guess what? He didn't freak out and run for the hills like I thought he would do.

The key is to have a calm discussion and clearly communicate what the both of you think. You could broach the subject this way: "Hey, I'm really enjoying spending time with you, but there's something I'd like to ask you before we move any further with our relationship. You've talked jokingly about being a father/having kids a couple of times, and I want to know if you want to have kids in the future?"

You can see what he says and explain how you feel about having bio kids. The sooner you talk to him, the better. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
