<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject29</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 02:51:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Or you can get your teeth fixed and skip the awkward “I think I look ugly while smiling with braces but it’s funny” laugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 22:53:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Robocock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 01:07:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This one made me laugh xD and it's still super cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 15:28:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> same here (edit) I waited for quite a while and it suddenly showed up... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 22:41:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It stopped working for me even after downgrading </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 23:10:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it ok If you use a pyrex with a plastic lid to cover it while it’s in the freezer, without the NPS touching the plastic? Do you mean OP’s would have some amounts of plastic because the picture shows it facing down? Would re-x-ing help getting rid of those amounts pf plastic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 05:29:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it’s Terence McKenna talking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-13 00:26:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it wasn’t until last season that pinup day was mostly terrible, like a curse... There’s been so many hideous looking pinups over the years but in my opinion, last season was the best ever.
Edit: and imo Angel’s pin-up should have gotten Tattoo of the Day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 01:44:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s great information, thanks for your comments. I also found this other product [Aguarrás Simil](https://imgur.com/a/zerrd8o)  and I’m doing an evap. test now. Will this be better than the lighter fluid? It’s supposed to be [NAPHTA](http://www.noriega.net/fichas_tecnicas/LISTA%20DE%20INGREDIENTES_SIMIL.pdf)  (PETROLEUM), HYDRODESULFURIZED HEAVY (< 0.1% W/W BENZENE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 01:28:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Naphta in a can? I’m guessing they don’t sell it as a varnish thinner, right? I could try in a pharmacy here but it’s kind of difficult to explain what I need and what for. I could try and ask for “Éter de petróleo” or “Nafta”
I think there’s gotta be something lost in translation here -see my comment on the difference between the ‘same’ Zippo lighter fluid’s SDS in Europe Vs. North America. It’s as if the word Naphta isn’t used in Europe.
I have this other product [Aguarrás Simil](https://imgur.com/a/zerrd8o)  which is used as some kind of turpentine and the components say “Nafta” - I’m doing an evap test with it now but I don’t think this is the right chemical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 23:58:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it’s this one: https://certification.zippo.com/Documents/Safety%20Data%20Sheet/English/Zippo%20Lighter%20Fluid%20-%20EU.pdf

Edit: I looked closely at the can trying to find the components but there wasn’t anything.

Edit: The SDS for the same product in the North America is this: https://certification.zippo.com/Documents/Safety%20Data%20Sheet/English/Zippo%20Lighter%20Fluid%20-%20North%20America.pdf
And one of the components mentioned in this version is Naphta, whereas Naphta doesn’t appear in the European version </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 23:38:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am in Spain and I can’t really find Naphta as is, but I’ve read mixed comments about this lighter fluid so I’m not sure; it’s quite unexpensive so I could just buy it and do an evap. test but I wanted to ask here first, also maybe there’s someone who knows a good Naphta here in Spain. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Would this work well? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 23:34:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 04:34:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here’s another picture: https://i.imgur.com/BDgAaLf.jpg

Could it be this? https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Albizia_julibrissin

According wikipedia article (under “Names”) there’s some confusion with Mimosa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Found in the streets of Barcelona </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 04:11:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 19:54:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sofi’s elevator death in “I Origins” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 01:36:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m just speculating here. Sometimes parents are present physically but not emotionally.
The father working long hours, yelling and being strict with academic/religious discipline sounds like an emotionally neglectful Dad -Never being enough to please your parents- also seems like part of the “black hole” PWBPD are characterized for.
I agree with some other comments that pointed out the mother maybe being emotionally absent.
The dynamics between the siblings could also affect the way he learnt to get what he wanted.
I don’t think trauma should be thought of as something very easy to spot but it’s easy to see it as a series of little wounds that biuld up with time.
I also agree that it could be a kind of NPD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 16:48:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This too shall pass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 16:42:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It sounds like we’re on the same boat here; keep working on it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 15:53:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “I hate all of my friends” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 20:58:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One was something like this:  （•_ㅅ_•）
And the other one: wecanhearyouhavingsex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-21 14:27:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This song is on my most repeated playlist for a long time now and the funny thing is last night while listening to it I thought this might be such a great track tonpost on this sub. What a nice coincidence!
I was also thinking this is maybe what Portishead would sound like if they dropped a contemporary album.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-19 00:10:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty nice! That beat is dope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-30 21:20:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A bit random? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-17 12:40:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> English is not my mother language and this is what I can decipher:

"check, check

hey, hey, hey, hey, hey

one

check, ok

hi

one

two, ok

feel

I feel like

I feel like you're coming when you're gone

it feels like so cold when it's over

it feels like so good and away

I feel like it's over when it starts

I feel like it's twisted and "????"

I feel you're always so cold

I feel like you're happy in the dark" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 23:58:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gian & Tiffer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 23:56:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kelly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-05 01:54:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Magnolia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Boy Harsher - Against The Clock </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-29 14:54:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
