<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject71</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 03:45:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the support and love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 03:43:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm feeling better, listening to 90s pop song. Nostalgia. Thank you, means so much to receive positivity when no one's around. Bless you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 03:18:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you so much!! Yeah I'll write no matter what. Atleast people can see and feel who I am after I'm gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 00:26:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too. Even if I'm not watching I play it for background sound. It gives me comfort especially HIMYM, I always get emotional. I feel it's deeper than just comedy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 23:31:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  Yea doctors do have to fill something on their notepad.. Writing has been therapeutic for me I won't deny. And doing too much research about my symptoms only worries me. Thanks a lot @tedmosley . I like your username btw, I'm a bit of a Smoshby myself lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 22:05:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for your reply in my moment of doubt. Tonight is harder I guess because my childhood friend next door hung himself to death this morning and turns out he was schizophrenic all along and no one knew till of late. And this makes me watch documentaries about schizophrenia and I learn some patients were diagnosed as bipolar before finally diagnosed with schizophrenia. Now my mind is super fucked. I don't hallucinate but I fear I'm soon gonna. I'm sorry to share all these negative thoughts but I'm scared. I don't know what to do, it's the middle of the night can't even go anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Am I really a musician or just my hypomania that makes me write all those music? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 20:37:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I write tons of songs, I used to write them with everything in me and I loved all my songs. Some got pretty decent YouTube views and feedbacks. But I am not sure about anything anymore, because tonight I for sure know I'm on my episode. And I feel all sorts of feelings and I wanna write so bad. But now I am aware about my hypo, and if I write and find it good again will it be just a delusion..or something else. Have people been laughing at my music behind me all those years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 20:36:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For 13yrs I have been dreaming about someone who I left after having 4yrs of relationship with. I was struggling with my mental health issues and we were young then. The dreams used to be so real that I can still feel the warmth of his hands on my palms as I open my eyes. Then I had to weep bitterly. Sometimes I used to even have a full on conversation about our future only to wake up alone.

Now over a decade later, he still haunts my dreams, I can feel his presence but he does not play the main character anymore I guess. But he's always there. I wonder what he dreams about tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 19:44:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guys thanks for taking the time to respond tonight. I think I'm just not in a good place rn.. I mean whole day I was trying to hide my tremors and today it's worse than other days. I guess it's taken a toll on me. I don't mean to whine so much. I'm sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 19:39:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've had lithium in 2014,the tremor eases after a week or so, I think I grew accustomed to it by then but now it's been months. I am troubled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 18:49:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the reminder..almost convinced myself this time (carried back sewing kits and shelving back the curtain material ..coz ah..I don't sew) 😂😅😅 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 18:40:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll be sure to consult my doctor for this 1st thing in the morning. It doesn't help that my mom tells me not to reveal my diagnosis to people. I understand where she's coming from though, and she still love me to shreds.. It'll help to have control over my body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 18:31:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And it is said getting off medication is not advisable, so pretty much forever I guess.. 😣 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 18:22:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The thing is I don't have tremors normally.. But are you telling me I'm gonna have this tremor as long as I take my meds? They won't go away after sometime? It's so uncomfortable and awkward too. 😣 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 17:40:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that made specifically for bipolar? I am taking Dicorate and Flumod but I'm having uncomfortable hand and body tremors.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 17:34:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is there a bipolar meds in particular? I'm just curious coz I think I should be taking that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Tremor </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 17:01:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does anybody have body tremors because of your medications and how long does it last? I started taking Dicorate, flumod and Modalert during daytime since mid June. Still I am getting tremors in my body especially my hands. Makes me wanna stop taking them even though it helps moodwise. Do share your experience. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 23:29:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just joined this group few hours ago but it gives me so much.. shall I say "joy" I don't know the right word for it, to learn that there are people like me, who are going through the same things as I do and to learn that this thing even has a name. And the delusional fogs.. I don't know if you have that too but..My goodness 😅😅😅 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 23:04:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup..when motivation comes you just gotta ... hypo or no hypo 😂😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 22:40:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh honey, me too..me too. I haven't spoken to my best friend from April..the reason is different for me although it springs from the same place. During that time I was 100%sure she was stabbing me from the back. Now I'm on Dicorate and Flumod..the delusional fog is getting clearer.
I have burned so many bridges in my life for various reasons. I always realize it after the "episodes" are over. Hang on tight. The storm is almost over. 🌼🌼 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 05:50:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Personally for me, I write in the aftermath. I can't write under the influence, be it alcohol, weed or heartbreak.. I look back to the situation and revisit with a clearer mind (for the sake of better phrase formation) and write.
Heartbreak's a bitch but it's what makes all my songs so can't complain 😊😊 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 02:08:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know this might sound insensitive and selfish but corona virus is a blessing in disguise for me. 7years ago I left my 4r old son with my mother and moved to another city 3000 miles away coz I can't stand to be in my hometown anymore. Too many deaths and too many scars in my life and I needed a change of scenery.
I was suffering from severe depression and anxiety that I couldn't have a normal relationship. Then shortly I got a job singing in clubs and living a different life from what I used to know.. I struggled a lot and got treated several times for my depression and Hypomania. During all these I miss my son terribly and although he doesn't say it I know he does too.
This year has been the last straw, I got ECT on June followed by mood stabilizers and anti depressants. I felt my mood has lifted and I can think clearly. Then I went home through many hardships on the way with quarantine and all, because the places where I perform were all closed down because of the pandemic, and the school which I teach music in switched to online classes which I can do from home.
Although I haven't taken my medication in over 2 weeks because of the border being closed, seeing my son, holding my son, small talk with my mom and sister, having a normal family meals on a table heals me from deep within. It took 7 long years but I'm home again ready to be a mother, a daughter and a sister this time.
"My heart swells with pride and thankfulness.. "


P. S If anyone needs to rant, cry, scream or express yourself because of your life's misfortunes, I don't have the solution but I can lend a listening ear. I know the feeling and I understand. Good day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
