<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject12</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 22:53:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unscrew something on the wall and then place it behind it and remount the item. Probably would work best with things that are not very accessible in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 17:17:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I wish it was free, guess I'll call them today and block minecraft transactions from happening </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [java] Minecraft Realms will not let me cancel, its been like this for 3 months </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 15:44:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 17:28:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He probably doesn't have it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 20:52:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> do you have any more info on how to do this or some youtube tutorial? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 03:34:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Check the owners manual perhaps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 22:13:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah must be a mod. I am unsure what mod though as I play on my father's computer and he has all sorts of additions to spice the game up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 16:49:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alright I used it and it seems to work flawlessly as I now have 24 rep and he hasnt left.

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Changing Alignments in EEKeeper </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 22:58:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was wondering if I would break my game, or the character Edwin if I made him neutral or good so he doesn't leave when my party reputation goes too high. I know I could just test it but thought somebody else might have already tried it. This is a good/neutral party in BGEE.

Edit: I have Edwin and Dynaheir in the same party by getting Dynaheir and then getting Edwin, which for some reason allows him to exist in my party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 19:29:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about hunting in the grocery stores. Nat Geo can make an episode on Karens and some half naked dude with a sawed off shotgun domes her at the checkout counter and then swings away on some Christmas lights as he makes loud chimp noises. It would make a boring day task become dangerous and exciting at the same time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 19:21:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well at least you remembered it, I only know it now because of the song 'I hate school' or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 19:18:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The only science I know is the mitochondria ism the powerhouse of the cell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 19:17:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> > This gets my goat so bad,

Does your goat game a lot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 19:13:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> are you monkey scientist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 19:03:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> hmm yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Monkey or Chimp. Which one is better and why? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 19:02:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 19:02:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hope the beauty community who create all the fake drama all get demonetized, all they do is create stupidly high beauty standards and get you to pay for makeup pallets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 19:28:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm in the same boat. I have traveled a lot going to Europe every summer but only to visit my grandparents. Other than family I saw no appeal and saw how much stress and anxiety it induced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 19:22:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha, I'm just imagining the scene from family guy where an asian lady is driving and says "I turn now, good luck everybody else" and then proceeds to make dozens of cars blow up in a pile. Here's the clip if you have not seen it yet

[https://youtu.be/LLuaPZWkvZ0](https://youtu.be/LLuaPZWkvZ0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 19:03:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you by chance know how much she was making? Is there a limit of how much you can make doing a sidegig before it must officially be made a business? (In Finland of course) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 19:01:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy fuck $400,000. I can't even fathom how much money that is. I'm glad to have $40 of money I can spend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 18:55:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spelling mistake on the word "opinion" in the third paragraph, first sentence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 18:52:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha I'm not even 16 yet and my back already hurts on the daily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 18:47:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Locked myself in a dog cage that was kinda small for like an hour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 17:31:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't forget the magnum condom!

\+250 resistance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In need of edgy username. Please send the funny? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 20:02:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anything funny as long as its not blatantly racist or something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 18:17:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lately, they haven't asked me to do much thanks to corona. Usually I am tasked with walking them since all I ever do is play video games and browse Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 17:13:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't Know as I have never seen one other than walking in the hills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 17:12:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean . . . , I never wanted the responsability that cam with them. My parents kinda forced it upon me. I now do weird things like always close every door in the house. Also I have been attacked by one before but I've been attacked by many animals so I don't think it matters too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 04:14:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I might get a cat after I finish school and whatnot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 04:12:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love cats too! I used to own one but sadly it died a few years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 04:05:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice dogs. I personally don't like the responsbility that comes with them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 04:03:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What breed are they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 03:21:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is exactly how I feel about dogs. Great Response. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 03:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Currently 6 chihuahuas, and some other one I don't remember off the top of my head. It can get loud asf especially since our house isn't the largest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 03:17:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the emoji thing is quite a common response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I don't like dogs AMA </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 03:11:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For context, I currently am in high school and both my parents have dogs. I get asked to feed them, etc, random bs tasks. I have never seen the appeal in having a dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 03:06:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Quarantine in a nut shell.

(pun intended) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 03:00:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also, what's up with all these bots saying I broke rule #23123 about how there isn't a question or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 02:58:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Alright I'll start one later tonight about liking dogs or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 02:55:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Seems like a cardinal sin to me anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Very new to Reddit. What are the do's and don'ts? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 02:52:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I am very new to Reddit. What are my do's and don'ts? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 02:51:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 02:49:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It amazes me how some people lack vital knowledge, especially common sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 02:33:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought so, but some people at my school, in my grade are doing the nasty already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 02:30:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At my age hopefully not, but I understand learning how to handle a relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 02:29:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Facepalm. I'm not even in high school yet and I know peeing after sex does nothing. (Don't get any wrong ideas though, health class) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 02:27:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Really seems like a 1/1000+ plus chance for that to happen. Best wishes in your relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 02:24:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't ever really thought about it that way. Really puts it into perspective IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is dating in middle/high school even a smart thing to do? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 02:20:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm very young (14m) and i hear all the time how people want a bf or gf. I just don't understand what is the appeal. I'm not asexual or anything like that, I just think "What is the point, it's gonna end anyway (most likely)" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 02:17:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am currently cringing. I have never thought of saying that they have an instruction book. Utterly hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 02:15:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks anyway. Hopefully I can find a way to politely ask them to back off a little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 02:09:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some kid at my school couldn't keep attending as his mom refused to get him vaccinated which was a requirement. Haven't seen him since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 02:07:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This one hits home, because my father is engaged with somebody whose family is extremely religious. The gifts they get for each other often include bibles and other religious texts. I'm not sure exactly, but I think they might be eastern orthodox christian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How far is too far for being an emotional crutch? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 02:02:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know multiple people who I still keep in contact with, which are mostly girls. They have recently started asking me for advice but I never know what to say, so I try to give them some generic response. It's getting a bit annoying and I don't know how to tell them that I don't want to be their emotional crutch any longer.

Suggestions?

Edit: I am we are all 14-16 age </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 01:56:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha this one makes me chuckle. I personally know somebody who thinks the earth is flat, and many other bogus claims. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 01:55:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interesting. I am too young (under 16) to really understand politics aside from people bickering about Trump in class. From some quick google searching, it seems he isn't great at arguing. If he is electable or not I have no clue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What is the stupidest thing somebody has tried to argue for but miserably failed? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 01:49:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
