<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject2</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-18 04:55:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hecho! Quería comentar ya que en la encuesta no lo pude especificar, que mi gato se lleva genial con mi perro, y no importaría que compartiera espacio con otros pero no estaría tan segura ya que dudaría del comportamiento de otros perros hacia mi gato. Por lo que respondí “si”, pero me gustaría asegurarme de que estaría cómodo y no se sintiera acosado o amenazado </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 14:16:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! We definitely still print on paper, it’s not as common but you can still go to gas station and any 24/7 and find newspapers. I’m from the canary island and we have a local newspaper that’s printed near where I live and know of people that work in that factory. As for your main question, tbh, I had never heard of it before, I’ll look it up and see if I can help you. Can you tell me which newspaper it was? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 03:21:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This reminded me of the time my dad magically teleported (as I recall it) to my 3yo sister to save her from being crushed by one of these old heavy TVs, he actually dislocated his knee but she could’ve ended really badly injured </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 03:14:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Heey! Just wanted to let you know, I followed your advise and I’m very happy! I wasn’t ready to commit to black hair yet but I knew I didn’t like the orange (the one I had when I posted this). Great advise, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 03:12:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Update: so I decided to go halfway, not completely black until I’m sure, so more of a brown shade [new color](https://www.dropbox.com/s/o1i908sqer4es5b/Foto%2014-10-20%200%2026%2033.jpg?dl=0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 03:39:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> El problema no es ser americano, es encontrar trabajo en España. Yo soy española y tengo un curso de formación profesional en gestión administrativa y llevo buscando trabajo desde que me gradué, solo he conseguido en Dunkin Donuts y una tienda de zapatos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 03:37:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We like to drink a glass of wine while we listen to music and cook together any recipe as long as we’ve never done it before, and then eat it like we where on our first date again. Sometimes it doesn’t come out as expected and we just laugh and order take out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 03:31:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It was kinda the opposite, I’ll explain:
My 76F neighbour used to be a seamstress and for a couple of euros she usually resizes my clothes, so one day I went over to her house, left a t-shirt there, explained her what I wanted done and left, but I got a bad feeling right when I was leaving and I turned around and something started smelling strong, turns out as soon as I left, her kitchen caught on fire, and she panicked so bad  that if I hadn’t been there she could’ve made the (oil) fire even worse or get intoxicated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-14 03:20:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can memorise large group of numbers, I know all my family’s license plates and number on their ID card. I could use that to my advantage some day, so far I’ve only impressed a couple of people and scared even more.
For example, one day my dad was sent a letter but he wasn’t home so in order for the delivery guy give it to me he needed both ID numbers, my dad’s and mine, I said both of them... he looked at me for a couple of seconds and even longer when he checked I was right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 16:49:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw the video but I was wondering, is it close to a kitchen? I saw myself in a kitchen looking out, like it wasn’t there but very close </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 16:46:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Spain you can work at 16 but with your parents permission, but they don’t hire you, so although it’s legal, nobody actually gets hired at that age. So basically: you have to be 18 to work, drink, and have a drivers license </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 16:41:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too, I started dating my now boyfriend and he introduced me to his childhood friends and they adopted me kinda as a little sister and we all spend great time together just drinking, partying or talking about life but I wish I had female friends to just go to the mall or spend a night together and vent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Which hair color suits me better? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 14:10:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is hair Botox a good idea? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-11 14:07:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I called my local hair salon telling them the condition of my hair and how I’d love it to be shiny again and they recommended I get hair Botox. I don’t know much about the product and I fear they only told me that because it’s one of the most expensive treatments they offer. Is it a good idea? I don’t want to damage my hair even further </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-07 19:27:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Choir, anchor, queue... as a Spanish who studied English I have an infinite list </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 03:11:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Merlí (it’s Catalan but in Netflix you can find it in Spanish), I don’t usually cry watching TV Shows but I did with that one. And also Vivir Sin Permiso, I personally didn’t enjoy that one as much, but my boyfriend loved it and the Spanish is very good to understand, good audio, pronunciation and speed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 14:01:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This actually happened last week. I had surgery on my foot almost a month ago and while taking the stitches out last Wednesday I was complaining it hurt, but the nurse said it was impossible, it shouldn’t hurt, until she pulled another one out and my skin opened because it wasn’t healed enough yet and I passed out and almost fell off the gurney apparently. Now I’m in risk of an infection but it doesn’t itch as bad anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 16:16:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’d end hunger at least in my town for a bit or I could start a croissant business and sell them... it’s ham and blue cheese if anyone’s interested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Coloring question </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 12:54:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had orange hair and I’ve decided to let my natural hair grow so I dyed it a similar shade, but now my roots are dark and the orange it’s peeking on the rest. What can I do to just cover the orange without dying the root? Is there a mask or something I can use or do I just have to be precise when dying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 12:48:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You too n.n </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 01:58:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ohh, I think I get it. Thanks!!! Really appreciate it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 01:48:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What exactly does that word mean? I’m Spanish but I’ve been fluently speaking English for almost 10 years and still don’t fully understand and looking for translation doesn’t seem to really help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 14:58:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I touched the protective rubber on a hot pipe, turns out it wasn’t that protective </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 14:01:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stuart Little. Maybe because of nostalgia but I love that movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 02:28:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would never stick it anywhere, I’d be too worried about ruining it and I’d want it everywhere, It’s beautiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 17:42:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I (F) have never had any sexual interest towards women, I like the feminine look and aesthetic but more as an inspiration, whereas towards man I’ve always showed interest and later on in life I wanted to experiment and try things and just like that I knew. I appreciate women but they don’t turn me on or spark anything else other than admiration </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 14:02:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Swimming, I’m 20 and I fear I’ll never swim but what if I need it someday? Will I just swim like babies do when thrown into water? I hope to never find out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This Persian carpet </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 13:57:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Continue watching </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 13:56:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 16:04:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If I’m on the internet I think in English (my 2nd language) because I’ll probably answer in English, like I’m doing right now, but otherwise Spanish (my 1st language) because I’ll probably be answering or talking to people around me. So I switch depending on what I need to use </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 14:25:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! My cat loves rubber bands, he also likes hair ties but prefers rubber bands. And my other cat likes bothering my other pets, there’s no toy she’ll choose over bothering my dog or first cat mentioned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> World’s largest turtle </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 12:41:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 01:36:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OMG! Today I got surgery and I saw them everywhere I looked, the bed I was in, the operation room, the hospital bedroom, and when my boyfriend came to pick me up, he had parked the car in front of a house with that number too! And these past few days too, we went on a road trip because we knew I’d be I bed for a few weeks and saw them everywhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 01:28:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Spain we have a similar dish, it’s only missing tomato sauce and depends on preferences some other ingredients. It’s called “ropa vieja”, a childhood memory! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Eli5: Gears on a plane </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 16:16:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do planes have gears? How do they work? If they were compared to cars, how many would there be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 15:55:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have to consider there are many types of lactose intolerance. In my case I can’t drink cow milk, but I can drink goat’s. It’s not exactly milk people can’t tolerate, but a component of it, and if it’s not present in other milks, then it’s okay to drink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 19:10:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had a math teacher that was so good at aiming that he threw pieces of chalk or even the eraser close enough to the student’s head to wake them up and scare them but not hit them. Never missed, luckily for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 13:50:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hercules for PS2, I used to play with my dad when he came home from work, that’s the only time we could spend together because he worked 12+ hours a day most of the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 11:34:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s a really good advice! Today I’m seeing him, I’ll tell him about the dream and see his reaction, I don’t want to make him uncomfortable or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 01:47:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t agree but that’s okay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-06 00:57:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t see how </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 22:25:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 21:59:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Monozygotic Mirror Twin. Our DNA it’s practically the same but I was born left handed and my sister right handed, my hair parts on the left and hers on the right, our cowlicks are the opposite direction and many other things! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 21:22:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m a rare kind of twin, out of every pair of twins, only 2% are like my sister and I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Should I worry? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 20:38:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Last night I had a dream that one of my friends had a pretty bad illness and hadn’t told us until it was too late. The thing is that I’ve had premonitory dreams before and this one felt like it wasn’t just a dream. My friend doesn’t look sick but I’d really appreciate if anyone here can help me. Maybe it isn’t an illness literally. Anyone has any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 04:25:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eating rabbit and duck as commonly as chicken </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 04:24:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No se si eres de españa también, pero estoy de acuerdo con lo que has comentado, bueno, más que carne barata diría que es la cantidad de carne que se consume y la de tipos disponibles que tenemos, lo cual ya de por si la abarata </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 04:16:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had never heard of this before! How can I crave something I’ve never eaten?! I really need to try it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 04:11:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ve never seen them in my life. And I live in Spain but I have also been to Ireland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 04:09:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in the canary island and I have lunch at 2:30/3:00 and dinner at 10:00/10:30. And I always have a snack, maybe a sandwich at around 5:00, otherwise I would be way too hungry for dinner time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 03:37:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ve been in a similar situation, I had a math teacher that allowed us to sit on the desk, on the floor, wherever we wanted, and made it feel like we where hanging out and just listening to cool facts, I think it actually worked, I’ll never forget him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This giant surfing Guan Yu statue has entered the chat </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 03:35:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 03:33:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The actor who plays Arturo (“Arturito”) in Money Heist
Edit: not a villain but definitely a character many people hate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 00:36:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where did it take off and where did it land? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 04:33:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My bf has a couple of ginger hairs on his dark black beard and I love them! It looks soooo good, and he hates them, he doesn’t like me mentioning it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 21:36:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I graduated from business school and got my drivers license!! And I figured out what I want to do next, what to study and the next goal to work for. So much time to think gave me that at least, also I think I underestimated some of my friendships and now I honestly value them more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 13:45:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Enlarge my left leg, I was born with a leg 3cm longer than the other so that has given me a lot of consequential health problems and other types, like how uncomfortable it is for me to drive my car sitting closer to the edge of the seat on one side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 01:25:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would be the goddess of the deserving. Kinda like karma I would reward those who do good to others (people or animals) maybe making them find 5€ while walking down the street but also the opposite, losing someone’s keys if they do something inconvenient for somebody else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-10 01:21:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My period. Every time it came I passed out because it hurt so much, I would cry, throw up, and not long after that just pass out, since I was 13 until I was 16, then I got on some pills that only make me cry and throw up, but it’s not as bad as before. They don’t really know what’s wrong but apparently it will stop once I get pregnant, I would call it bs but that’s actually what happened to my mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> La Galera </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 00:21:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Education is the key. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 17:51:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 05:13:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Forbidden tent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 16:29:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> E.T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Look, you learned something new </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 03:20:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 20:05:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [here’s gizmo giving his approval](https://www.dropbox.com/s/wd9ns1wugdmy3h6/gizmo.in.the.park.jpg?dl=0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 20:04:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [here’s Gizmo giving his approval!](https://www.dropbox.com/s/wd9ns1wugdmy3h6/gizmo.in.the.park.jpg?dl=0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Homemade park for disabled bird (explained in Spanish by my bf) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 19:30:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Homemade park for disabled bird (explained in Spanish by my bf) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 19:04:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-02 01:11:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It looks amazing!!! Could you share the recipe? I really want to try baking it hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 03:12:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just read your ring description and I think we have a very similar one. I lost mine once too and found it many months later, turns out it had fallen from my kitchen counter, or got caught on a towel, I’m not sure. I finally found it in the washing machine, check there just in case something similar happened. Best of luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 15:21:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too! And I’m Spanish but I always watched American tv series, I don’t know why I never gave my country’s tv series a chance and I honestly were impressed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 03:18:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Asking a question which answer could be followed by “tmi” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 03:07:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I feel like my body put me on pause. I’m still kinda aware but can’t do anything about it, until I’m okay again and realise what I felt where 30 minutes were actually 3 hours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
