<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject66</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-16 11:31:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NSV: I haven't lost any weight this last week. I haven't gained either. But today I wore this belt and [this happened](http://imgur.com/a/8ajWRpg)!

I've been regularly going to the gym lately so maybe I'm gaining muscle. I don't notice anything in the mirror yet, but there is no denying that I'm not as big as I used to be. I am motivated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-15 08:55:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And swimming in the pool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 21:35:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Podries haver fet crosspost enlloc de publicar-ho com si fos teu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-13 15:44:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly? This sounds like a cult member. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 15:28:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think at least Spain and Italy define ourselves more often as southern than western. TBH we never define us as western. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-12 15:27:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eastern Europe being more East than Eastern Asia is sending me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 16:53:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I lost 5 kgs in the last three weeks, I'm super happy and motivted! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> -5kg today (-11lbs) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 12:01:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe you remember [my last post](https://www.reddit.com/r/loseit/comments/j3a43j/its_starting/). Well. I stepped onto the scale this morning and it was clear: 100 kgs (220 lbs).

So I've officially lost 5 kgs in a month (11lbs)!

First goal: achieved. Like my therapist advised me some time ago, I like to set small goals and then achieve them one by one instead of setting a super big goal and stressing because I'm not getting there fast enough. So now onto -10kgs!

 I don't see much difference in the mirror, but there are some parts of my body that I feel smaller when I touch them (my hips, for example).

I'm happy! And excited for what's to come! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-09 09:55:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a nice city we live in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 08:11:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bye Friedberger Platz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 08:08:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice, good job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 18:56:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you for real? Have you ever been to any of those places you're so afraid of? You can perfectly live there without speaking or understanding the CO-OFFICIAL language. Just say you don't respect those cultures, it's quicker than writing a whole paragraph. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 18:51:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Són quatre: hivern, estiu, la renfe i autobusos. Però en anglès no queda bé :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 16:07:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is of course a language with its own grammar, structure and vocabulary. And from your opinion, what happens if speak Catalan/Spanish to someone from Portugal or Italy and they understand me? Are those dialects? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 16:05:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course, a culture does not equal a language, but a language does equal a culture. And they speak Spanish, not "kind of" Spanish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 14:59:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To me, a language is the basis of any culture. If the language disappears, the culture goes after it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 13:56:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. All languages in Spain should be official. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 11:39:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll never get why people change their last names anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-06 08:20:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> paraula=morena </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 14:15:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm in the same situation as you, I can't believe I've let myself get so big. If you need someone to talk or just share your progress with, DM me! We can do it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 08:29:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Lleida we have two seasons: very hot summers, very cold and foggy winters. We barely see the Sun in winter. I remember a december a few years ago we only got like 21 hours of Sun.

Edit: it was 34 hours. [Here's](https://www.segre.com/noticies/guia/2017/01/02/el_desembre_estat_mes_amb_menys_hores_sol_la_historia_lleida_9199_1111.html) the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 19:56:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep, I never felt at home in bodi-posi groups or fat acceptance communities because EVERYTHING is about extremely overweight people. Those of us who "only" were 10-60 lbs overweight couldn't find any representation in pictures, drawings, etc. There are some of us who have small boobs and have a size less than 20. We are not fat enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 09:39:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This. I celebrate them since, for example, I'm off work. But if they were placed in another day of the calendar I wouldn't miss them.

You can't "not celebrate" them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This mirror's message </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 09:33:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 15:36:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Koers!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 12:34:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks so much for these words, they felt like a warm blanket in a winter day. I have always loved my body and I usually think about everything it has done for me: it brings me places, it lets me see the world... Now it's time to give back and to be nice to it for once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 11:31:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> TúTubeas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 11:26:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Són el meu grup català preferit! Els recomano moltíssim. El meu disc preferit és Jo Competeixo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 10:39:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, I'm sick of excusing myself and blaming it all on my metabolism and the meds. I have a lot to blame on myself, too. I believe in you too! We can do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 10:37:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I go to the gym regularly, maybe doing more cardio and less weight training will help. Thanks! And I hope your lld doesn't escalate. If it does don't hesitate to take meds, they literally saved my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 10:35:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the tip, I'll try the app!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 09:07:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hola! Et deixo [una playlist que tinc a Spotify](https://open.spotify.com/playlist/7CifawSXRvSFm4qcBma1mp?si=uQ2YNh5uQ8SL0y6pQgowng) on hi ha gairebé 24 hores de música en català :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 19:48:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I saw one in Merianplatz a few weeks ago. I tore it apart immediately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> It's starting. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-01 16:55:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My story is like many others. Always been a bit overweight but not much. during many years I weighed 70-75 kgs (154-165 lbs), depending on the time of the year.  I'm 1,70 m (5,5 ft). I used to have a BMI of 26-27 and I had no problems. Was healthy, looked good, felt fine. When I wanted to lose weight I just stayed away from sugary things for a while and I went back to normal.

Well, 7 years ago, when I was 23 I started taking antidepressants for a chronic mentall illness (dysthymia, I'm fine and happy now but I still need my meds to stay on track). These completely slowed down my metabolism and since I had this excuse I started eating more without watching anything. The result, I put on 30 kgs (66 lbs). I weighed 105 kgs two weeks ago (231 lbs).

[This is me in 2013](https://imgur.com/iSnAc3r) and [this is](https://imgur.com/9rcAC2M) [me now](https://imgur.com/PvWW7sB).

I look at pictures of me and I don't recognise myself. I can't seem to understand why had I not realised before that I was getting so big. I don't like what I see. I've always been thick and "big-boned", but now I'm just full of fat. And my face, oh god. It has gotten SO UGLY. I am self conscionus when I smile or laugh.

And, cherry on top, last month my knees started to hurt. This was when I decided it had to stop.

I know where my problem is. My diet is healthy and balanced, I just eat too many snacks. So I've been cutting all of them and I've lost 2,5 kgs in two weeks (5,5 lbs). It's not much and I still need to lose a lot more, but it's a beginning, and I'm ready and willing.

Anybody here with the same experience? Recommendations? Support group? I'll be glad to read your stories and to talk to all of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 22:14:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep, more or less </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 17:33:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We drank that because it was the only thing in our parents' cabinet. I am 14 in that picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 14:58:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> you like plants and your apartment has white walls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 13:28:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> the worst thing is that it's dry martini vermouth. disgusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 13:20:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [16 years later](https://imgur.com/tPq3h20): kind is cool. be wholesome. love dogs and cats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> trying to look badass for my msn messenger picture. 2004 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 13:10:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 11:52:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jo us recomano totalment "Canto jo i la muntanya balla" d'Irene Solà </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 07:56:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good bot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-29 07:52:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Meetup.com holds monthly international meetups, it worked for me!! Also a couple months ago we were supposed to have a Frankurt reddit meetup, but it got canceled due to corona. Maybe it would be nice to get it going again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 10:00:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having joint pain is what actually changed my mind about HAES and FA. The first day I felt it, I knew it was time for a change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 08:05:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And Monegros </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 08:02:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can just watch La Vuelta every year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 08:01:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am from the Ebro river valley. I love to see it so clear im this map. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 08:00:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. Meseta means plateau. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 14:59:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lisboa - Barcelona - Rome - Berlin - Budapest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-26 08:44:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's "sueño". Dream. It's a quote from Calderón de la Barca's "Life is a dream". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Showing off </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-25 12:20:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 21:32:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spanish republicans = left, socialism, communism, anarchism, you name it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 13:59:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mine had 33 CP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 16:23:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A Pyrenees hiking trip is completely fine! Just don't be an idiot and follow all regulations. Hospitality workers will be happy to see you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 15:50:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They brought back the monarchy.... in 1975 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 15:16:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The coup side wasn't monarchist. Was Spain a monarchy after 1939 when they won? No. They were military fascists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 15:11:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spain neither </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 07:57:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I followed the second until my knees started to hurt. Then I switched </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 22:14:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> u/vredditdownloader </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 21:12:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> u/vredditdownloader </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 19:11:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [SUPPORT] Laptop acting up since latest windows update. Today I get this. It's a loop, I close it and opens again. What should I do? It has 4 years, no problems until now. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 12:48:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 14:18:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 13:55:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks so much! I love plants but I don't have much idea about keeping them healthy, I mostly just water them and they stay alive. I was worried because this one doesn't have any soil to grow, it's /just/ roots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This plant in my office. It was like this already when I started here. I keep watering it and doesn't die, what should I do? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 10:56:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-18 09:06:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait, it's always been egg? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-17 12:19:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I watched s3 of Druck and realised it was way better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 11:04:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I came here to ask the same thing, I was so confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 21:31:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I had an amazing childhood and teenage years, I had friends, family, support. When I was 23 a cousin died in an accident. I've never been the best at letting my feelings out so this was a lot to take. I started getting so paranoid about death that my doctor sent me to a psychiatrist. Two years later I got my diagnosis for dysthymia.

What I'm trying to say is that in my case there's a day and hour when I started going down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 21:26:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just listen to what he has to say and don't minimize the illness. Make sure he knows you're making an effort to be closer to him. He is not his illness, but the illness is an important part of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> A happy story for once </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 21:24:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I consider myself happy. This had not happened for seven years. After a very traumatic death in my family, I started getting lots of anxiety episodes and being generally sad. My doctor sent me to a psychiatrist and put me on antidepressants. After two years I got diagnosed with dysthymia (or persistent depressive disorder). It was 2015, when I was 23. Antidepressants made my moods back to normal but I just couldn't consider myself happy. I was apathetic most of the time, even in the moments where I was legit feeling loved or having fun or doing things I enjoy. It was so frustrating, because I had everything in life: friends, family, enough money, challenges, support... It didn't feel like I was missing anything. I find it quite difficult to explain, maybe some of you could do it better than me.

After a few rough months last year, I decided to spend some money and go to the therapist (All these years I'd been going to the psychiatrist included in my healthcare, paying nothing). Guys, it was the best decision I've made in my life. It's amazing how my life has changed since then.

I finished my university studies with a high grade and a 10/10 in my thesis and I moved abroad to work in a job I adore. I love living in a big city. I'm living the life I always dreamt of when I was younger. Sometimes I say it to myself just in case there's a glitch in the matrix and a younger me is having a peek into her future.

If fifteen years ago someone had told me or shown me this would be my life in 2020, I would have been extremely happy and content. It's the first time I'm writing it down to acknowledge it. It's been in my head for weeks, maybe a few months. I don't know how long this will last as I know that dysthimia is always with me. But for now: I am happy. Finally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 20:58:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not even gonna bother saying I'm sorry for English not being my first language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 17:36:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate that everyone is rooting for the turtle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 17:30:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pues que es un temazo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Forbidden pineapple </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 11:35:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 11:34:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/forbiddensnacks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 10:18:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You spin me right round baby right round </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 08:57:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hans from Druck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-11 15:49:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ho fan servir a Balears i València, i algunes varietats de l'occidental. Sa mare, sa germana. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 15:27:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 7322 7699 2070 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 15:18:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Will do!

7322 7699 2070 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-10 13:48:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And what about the car? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-09 14:01:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's my second time living in Germany. I lived here from 2013 to 2015 and this time I've been living here since January 2020. This time I earn more money than before, so I can fly home quite usually to see family and friends.

I love living in Frankfurt. The city is so lively and it has a very international atmosphere. Back in Spain I'm from a reallllllly small village (500 people) where we all know each other and which I absolutely adore and I am an active member of the community.

I still have more than a year of working in Germany, I don't know what I'm gonna do later. I'd love to go back home, but I'm not sure I can ensure a good job there. That might be easier in Germany. On the other hand, I know I'll never feel 100% at home here and I'll never be as socially active as I am in my hometown. I'll always be a foreigner in Germany and I don't know if I like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-08 23:31:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Catalan it's Finestra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 22:24:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course, they were never talking about his sexuality. It was foreshadowing via wordplay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 19:46:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I'm always straight" - "That's the bigger lie you've ever told" is a pretty good hint in my opinion.

I also like how Ronan being gay does not have an impact on the story at all. It's just a fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 07:27:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Im Spain? No one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-05 10:06:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The audacity of judging us AND comparing us to France in just one post???? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 15:11:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I loooooved Sumol when I was on Erasmus in Portugal. I had completely forgotten about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 07:10:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And BonÀrea if you're in the Lleida region! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 15:40:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Petrol in Spain is one of the cheapest in the EU. It's cheaper than in Portugal, France, UK, Italy, Germany... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-02 15:39:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always use the navigating app Waze, there you can sort petrol stations by price </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Fiends by Saf has been taken down </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 19:44:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I know we've all been worrying/thinking about Saf in the last weeks but the [Fiends by Saf website](https://fiendsbysaf.com/) isn't working anymore.

I just hope whatever is happening is something that can be fixed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-31 09:29:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm getting worrisome too, also: the [Fiends by Saf website](http://fiendsbysaf.com/) has been taken down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-30 10:59:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It does absolutely not. Some people might do it like "i", in Spanish it's called yeísmo and it's very common (tortilla > tortiya), but it does not happen to native Catalan speakers. It is one of the things people use to mock Catalan accent in Spanish, they exaggerate it.

I would say it sounds like the italian "gl", for example "torteglini'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 13:13:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's normally not a problem, best thing to do is calling and asking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 07:39:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Españita is my fave. I live abroad and I always refer to it like this when I miss it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 00:29:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Druck and España. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-24 01:53:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cook only for myself. 2 liters per month, more or less </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 11:39:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wth is that Catalan flag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 11:25:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, at least you can choose them. We can't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 09:45:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The fact that it is a Monarchy (and that they can get away with whatever they do) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 09:43:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Republic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-16 09:39:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I ride an old Kynast bike I got for 70€. It has a sticker that says "made in West Germany". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 19:04:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's my favorite theme. So good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-14 12:06:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same with Spain/Andorra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 12:54:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Battling pirates with insults </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-13 12:04:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty much all scenes from Aquí No Hay Quien Viva, a cult comedy series from the 2000s in Spain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 14:06:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beware of Darkness 💚 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 09:16:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Año (year) and Ano (anus) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 08:32:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gosh, I feel you. I come from Spain where it is a lot better and cheaper. Now I have to resign myself to 4gb for 12€ with aldi talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 23:09:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I actually worked there the Summer I was 17! But it was really not my thing. Besides, I live in another country now so it's a bit out of the way for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My dad went into retirement today! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 22:54:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Today my dad has turned 65 and has gone into retirement. It makes me feel old somehow.

He's been working nonstop as a welder and mechanic since he was 14. First as an apprentice, then as an associate and then he finally opened his own workshop with his brother (my uncle).

The workshop is gonna be empty from now on. It's gonna feel so weird walking by it and seeing it closed.

I'm very happy for my dad and proud of him. My parents might have not been able to give me everything I wanted but certainly everything I needed. And that is enough. Happy retirement dad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-08 16:04:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Further left than Sanders, I guess. There's more to US politics in the world. In Europe, what Sanders does is considered centrist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 23:02:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I honestly do not care at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-07 22:05:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. I just turned 30 and this has been on my mind a lot. From 10 to 20 everything I did I was doing it for the first time. From 20 to 30 it was just repeating things most of the time and it went by much quickier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-06 08:30:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> None </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 12:32:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Trial and error. Trying everything with everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 10:30:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In almost everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-04 13:40:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is crazy for me to think that an election is not on a Sunday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-03 07:44:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Die Wald in Oberursel, man kann dort mit der Ubahn einfach fahren </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 21:41:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For all monarchies to become republics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 21:36:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it really warm in your area? They do that because the metal is cold </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 14:42:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I Massalcoreig al baix Segre ✌🏼 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 13:18:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I've read but I can't find them anywhere, even in big rewes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 09:35:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Odd tinkering </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 09:23:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Which ones? Because I've looked EVERYWHERE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 09:18:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Spain we use them! But we might be one of the few countries. I live in Germany now and I can't find them anywhere, I just buy a lot of them when I go home and bring them back with me since non applicator don't work for me (sadly tho, they are much cheaper and good for the environment) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 15:55:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> EVERYONE, THE BALLOON IS FALLING </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-31 08:36:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sunflower seeds 💚 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 10:29:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I work for my region's tourist board, but in an office abroad. Our job is to bring tourists to our region and to show them how wonderful it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 22:34:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> PLAY JA JA DING DONG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 18:01:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My thoughts exactly, this is why I'm so curious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 18:00:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know, that's why I don't go to them (besides from this one time), but the second doctor I went to was a real doctor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 16:15:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have ten! Catalan, German, Japanese, Latin, French, Dutch, Maltese, Portuguese, Hungarian and English, and I'm expecting a Korean edition 💚 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 30F, can someone please explain what this doctor did to me. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 16:04:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've had scolisis since I was a child, so my shoulders are always very tense and I go to the physiotherapist quite often.

I went to an ostheopath who speaks Spanish since someone reccommended him. He didn't do what usually my physiotherapist does, he focused more on massaging and cracking my bones (never going back again). After three days, I started feeling pain in my stomach zone and in my upper right leg, like if I was about to get my period. I knew it wasn't that so I went the doctor.

Now, I'm from Spain but I'm living in Germany, and even though I speak German quite good, some medical terms are just too much for me. So I didn't quite understand what was happening.

I explained him my symptoms. He made me get up and put my feet together. He then noticed something unusual, checked my belly and made me lie on the stretcher and stretched my back and my legs. He told me that the osteopath had "blocked something" in my abdomen and that this was the reason of my pain. I felt perfectly well afterwards.

So, my questions are, what was he checking with my feet? What was this "blocking" thing? What did he do to "unblock" it? Was this all charades and placebo?

Help. I am extremely curious. Also, English not my first language so some terms might not be accurate :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 14:37:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Entonces Rosalía es Rihanna? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 14:34:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Entonces España va bien de Ska-P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 13:36:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Solo se vive una vez" de Azúcar Moreno es 'You only live once" de The Strokes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 20:41:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/agedlikemilk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 13:43:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My faves after Matteo and David. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 12:18:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're in for s wild ride 🧡 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 10:51:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> well, I'm trying to hold on too. I know this won't be forever, my illness is not going away. But I'm trying to enjoy this happiness while it lasts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 10:28:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's so nice!! Make him a nice gift so he knows you appreciate his efforts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> After a few years I think I can finally say it: I'm happy! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-28 10:07:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm happy. I consider myself happy. This had not happened for seven years. After a very traumatic death in my family, I got diagnosed with dysthymia (or persistent depressive disorder) in 2013, when I was 23. Antidepressants made my moods back to normal but I just couldn't consider myself happy. I was apathetic most of the time, even in the moments where I was legit feeling loved or having fun or doing things I enjoy. It was so frustrating, because I had everything in life: friends, family, enough money, challenges, support... It didn't feel like I was missing anything. I find it quite difficult to explain, maybe some of you could do it better than me.

After a few rough months last year, I decided to spend some money and go to the therapist (All these years I'd been going to the psychiatrist included in my healthcare, paying nothing). Guys, it was the best decision I've made in my life. It's amazing how my life has changed since then.

I finished my university studies with a high grade and a 10/10 in my thesis and I moved abroad to work in a job I adore. I love living in a big city. I'm living the life I always dreamt of when I was younger. Sometimes I say it to myself just in case there's a glitch in the matrix and a younger me is having a peek into her future.

If fifteen years ago someone had told me or shown me this would be my life in 2020, I would have been extremely happy and content. It's the first time I'm writing it down to acknowledge it. It's been in my head for weeks, maybe a few months. I am happy. Finally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 19:46:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> EVOO and salt! Maybe some species? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-27 12:44:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Add the Canary Islands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 18:44:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm in Germany. Female. Only medication I'm on is antidepressants, but I've been taking them for 7 years. Nothing has changed in the last few weeks. It itches sometimes, especially around the nose, but nothing major. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Been having this rash around nose and mouth for 2-3 weeks. I'm 30, I've never had acne, pimples or blackheads. Same skincare routine for 6 months. What is it!? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 18:41:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 10:57:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too! You're the first person I've met than can do iy as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 10:56:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can write calligraphy backwards, upside down and both (like mirrored) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 10:46:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! When I have a craving I just have to follow through, this has always been my baking process. O don't think much about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 18:36:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also my first time making lemon curd or meringue. I am astonished. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My first time making lemon meringue pie 🍋 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 18:35:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-23 07:21:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The 1997 graphics are my fave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 17:11:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The curse of Monkey Island </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 13:18:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're a champeon, little Eevee

and you're dead

you're the champion of death </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 09:22:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I still play them nowadays </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-22 08:54:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No hace falta estudiar una carrera. Puedes hacer FP. Ahí vas a estar dos años aprendiendo a programar.

Tengo varios amigos trabajando de programadores y cobrando muy bien que nunca han pisado una universidad, ni falta que les hace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 12:21:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Monkey Island. Always and forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-21 12:09:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Four actually: Hivern, estiu, Renfe i Autobusos ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 16:04:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why would anyone ever subscribe to this sub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-20 08:04:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lleida might be cold in winter but it gets extremely hot in summer, we go from 0° to 40° quite easily, there is no inbetween. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Art imitates life </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 21:15:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 20:48:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look up "Bar España" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 09:49:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah yes, when Portugal, the country with more neighbors and more political alliances won. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 09:01:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was 11, I remember it as if it were yesterday. I was with my family at a holiday apartment in the coast, getting ready to go to the beach. We had Antena 3 on, and all of a sudden Matías Prats started narrating everything. I don't remember making it to the beach. In the afternoon we went for a walk and everyone was talking about it. Crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 12:00:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I flew Frankfurt-Barcelona two weeks ago. It went as usual, no changes from pre-pandemic flights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 16:13:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've given English classes in a 500 people town </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-09 00:42:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dwight said it first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 16:46:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Skam España told it like it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 16:44:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. Matteo + David
2. Cris + Joana
3. Isak + Even
4. Lucas + Eliott
5. Robbe + Sander
6. Martino + Niccolò </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 10:15:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 08:18:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For me, apart from the stories, it's how she tells them. Her vocabulary is so beautiful and wholesome, it makes me feel so happy. And proud to call Catalan my mother tongue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 22:09:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We don't even wear them anymore! The word just got here a long time ago and it stayed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 09:28:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tippex, Celo, Donuts, also in my region we call trainers "Keds". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 09:01:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have been into Pokémon since 2001 and I have drawn Pikachu thousands of times. The brown in the base has always been there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 22:13:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lleida (in Spanish "Lérida"), the inner province of Catalonia, was named "Iltirta' by the iberians. The romans changed it to Ilerda. The arabs changed it to Larida. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 21:59:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Girl, leave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My sister just adopted this kitten. They seem comfortable in their new home. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 17:16:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> PAINTING SQUARES </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-27 11:48:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> PAINTING SQUARES </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-27 11:07:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I have an extremely low metabolism... </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 14:38:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey everyone.

I´m 29 (30 in a couple weeks), female. I am 1,70m tall (5,5 ft) and I currently weigh around 100 kgs (220 lbs).

All my teenage years and early 20s I weighed around 70 kg (154 lbs), which was perfect for me. There was a time when I gained 10 kgs, but I lost them quick with diet and help of a nutritionist and I went back to my normal. I usually stayed between 70-75 kgs. (154-167 lbs). When I was 23, I started taking antidepressants and my metabolism has slowed down so much that it has practically stopped. I gained 20 kgs in two years, and 10 more in the last two.

I can't get rid of them. I have tried keto, but I don't like the idea of cutting a whole family of nutrients and food off.

I'm not the sporty type, never have been (I hate running with a passion), but I am very nervous and I keep active. I go hiking sometimes, walk or bike to work, play tennis, I work out sometimes. All signs point that I'm gonna need my medication my whole life so I'm not planning on quitting - also they keep me from being sad and anxious which I am very grateful for. I eat out once in a week, some weeks I don't.

Btw, I am now living in Germany, which has a completely different diet from my home country (Spain). I try my best to stick to the mediterranean Diet, but there are many things that are very expensive here or sometimes inexistent (Mangold, I miss you! Sugarfree products, I miss you even more! Fresh fish, you too!)

CICO has seemed to work for me in the past, but now I just can't get it to work again. What am I doing wrong? Any advice? Help?

Thanks so much <3

Edit: typo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 09:41:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This was exhausting to read </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 22:01:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Qué se entiende por nativo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bi erasure in S2 of The Politician </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 09:37:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does anyone else think that in this new season they erased any visible evidence of Payton's or River's bisexuality?

Payton saying he was never sexually attracted to River and that he didn't think River was gay or bi felt like a little dagger in my heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 08:35:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> that's my haircut and honestly the one that suits me the most </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-19 08:32:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes to this. And many private hospitals send patients to the public ones when it gets too serious sometimes.

Edit to say that public healthcare in Spain is equal to everyone, you don't get an "upgrade" based on how much you earn / the company you work for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 08:53:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So comfy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 12:19:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Costa Brava is also very touristic tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 12:18:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then Tarragona is your place. It has everything a city has but it is very homey, has a strong mediterranean culture and is right by the sea. The harbor neighborhood is beautiful, and the food is awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 09:59:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually that's the Catalunya flag period. No independence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 09:54:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Salou and Cambrils are very touristic. I'd reccommend you Tarragona or Reus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 15:00:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My cousin, who was 11, died in an accident while playing with other kids. One of the kids was severely injured and no one thought she would make it alive or without any serious consequences. She was completely recovered in three-four days. Even doctors couldn't explain it. People said she had gotten some help "from someone or somewhere" (re: my cousin, who had died immediatley).

A few months, maybe a year later, I don't remember it well. I was in a store with my mom, and we ran into another woman and her daughter, around my cousin's age. I did not know them, but my mom did. The kid kept looking at me all the time. I was feeling some connexion and something weird. When they left, I asked my mom who they were. It was the kid who almost didn't make it and her mom.

I have questioned everything since then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-09 12:45:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No queda massa ja que el van enderrocar, però pots veure les bases de les cases, una mica els carrers... Tot plegat és bastant trist però molt interessant. El poble vell estava a la vora de l'Ebre i ara el nou està a la vora del Segre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 19:40:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Pantera Rosa](https://images.app.goo.gl/2PUtiHREN5WebxMo8) maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 11:52:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Et recomano visitar el poble de Mequinensa. Hi visc molt a prop i hi vaig sovint. Pots veure les ruines del poble vell i visitar els museus, són visites molt interessants! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-08 11:51:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Viatges i Flors" de Mercè Rodoreda, i després llegiré "Canto jo i la muntanya balla" d'Irene Solà </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 18:34:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> En mi pueblo está también Sotano </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 09:06:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hackeando la metrosexualidad en la sociedad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-06 08:57:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Que surti de Barcelona i vagi cap a l'interior, ja veurà com millora la salut del català. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 19:46:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Paquita is an amazing show and I love it so much! As a Spaniard I think it can be a bit weird to people who are not used to spanish pop culture and, how we call it here, mamarracheo. Maybe they'd miss a lot of jokes. But it can be a very good way to get into Spanish culture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-05 08:34:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It looks handwritten to me. A, S, T, N even the 2 are not the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-04 23:20:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I came in 2018 during my Erasmus in Lisbon, truly a paradise. Definitely going back someday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-04 23:18:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 💙💜❤️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-04 20:36:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you like crime I reccomend you "Bajo Sospecha", it has only two seasons! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 07:58:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ha preguntado por la diferencia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 15:02:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Merci! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 14:58:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Viri & Hugo and Kiki & Carlos. Basically because of their adaptation of the Magnus character. They do not treat him as a gross, woman-obsessed comic relief, but as a normal, intelligent guy with feelings and who respects women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 13:08:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know, I thought it was a basque name tho and not the adaptation of Ethan. The more you know... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 12:49:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am so glad that I studied ancient greek in high school </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 12:45:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Isn't Izan a basque name or have I been completely in the wrong my whole life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 10:32:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chiller </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 10:31:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, definitely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 10:20:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Publica esto en el sub adecuado - **Publícalo** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 09:38:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, she's giving you a roof, food, tv, internet, heating... And she's your mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 09:35:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NAH. But your wife maybe needs a break too. Try not to be more self-centered next time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 08:13:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rent in Barcelona is way more expensive than in Berlin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 10:28:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are other brands of hazelnut spread other than Nutella, you know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 23:00:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did my Erasmus in Portugal and everyone there talked about it as if it had happened two days ago and it was affecting their lives directly. When I learnt when it had taken place I could not believe myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 09:15:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Rednecks, basically </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 20:15:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agujeros de guión!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 20:03:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Donuts" is an actual donuts brand in Spain. The most popular one may I say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 20:01:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Corona beer is called Coronita in Spain because Corona is the name the royal family uses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-22 18:03:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. And in the rest of Catalonia we speak of "Barcelona" when we talk of the Catalan government </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-22 12:37:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> La Vida Moderna </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-22 11:22:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> És curiós, visc a Alemanya i ja he conegut dos persones d'Olot. Què ho deu fer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-22 11:21:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Circumval·lació </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 10:47:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My phone's wallpaper is [Francisco de Goya's "Perro Semihundido"](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/3/38/Goya_Dog.jpg/1200px-Goya_Dog.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How long should one stick to keto? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 09:38:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a friend who insists that Keto should be only followed for 2-3 weeks, if not it's dangerous. How much of this is true? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 09:30:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> At least four generations full catalan. I know for my first surname that my father's family comes from Aragon, but we must have moved to Catalonia pretty soon. My second surname is a full catalan one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 09:28:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know if Whatsapp is now more common in America, but a few years ago (like 3-4) I had american friends that never used it. They got it basically to get in touch with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 15:42:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [this! ](https://imgur.com/a/RXYkGlT) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ELI5: Why does tea not taste like it smells? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 14:38:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 20:04:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YES! I love the Azores. A paradise in the middle of the Atlantic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 20:03:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YES!!! To me it's like the Bible. And all that handwriting! Beautiful. I even got a tattoo from one of the scribbles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 23:13:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ángel Salvador... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 18:06:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maria-Mercè Marçal, Salvat Papasseit i Joan Maragall, són els meus preferits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 12:02:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Teresa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 21:09:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my opinion Druck and España are way better and handle things in a more accurate, realistic and unproblematic way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 23:39:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> One word: hemorroids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 16:06:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, it's a dorm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I don't know how to start </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-02 15:30:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey everyone. I've been reading a lot about keto / low carb for a while and I've even started eating according to this diet. The problem is, there's so much info out there that I don't know if I'm doing it right.

I'm a woman, 29 years old, 5'57 ft tall (1'7 m) and I weigh 225 lbs (102 kg). During many years my weigh was around 70-75 kg (164-175 lbs), but I've been taking antidepressants since 2013 and my metabolism has slowed down a lot.

My main goal is to lose body fat, so I don't know if eating the amount of fat this diet has is gonna take me to what I want.

Should I start with low carb and then switch to keto or go straight to keto? Any tips? Everything is welcome!

Thanks!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-01 10:01:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sorry. English is not my first language. Nephew, niece, whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-01 09:57:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NAH. Jealousy is a complicated feeling but it's completely normal that you're feeling this way, given the circumstances. I reccomend you go to therapy. Sometimes getting it all out helps. You should talk about this with someone, because if not you're gonna always carry this feeling and her child's gonna be in your life forever. Don't let anything stop you from loving your nephew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-01 01:23:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> POP POP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 16:21:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not German,  I'm not that used to it! But I'm checking it out and it has some cool stuff, I just wanted to look somewhere else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Where to buy used bikes? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 15:14:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does anyone know of a place where they resell bikes (besides Kleinanzeigen)? I'm interested in getting one. I know they sold some in the Flohmarkt by the river, but is it still taking place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 12:36:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep, totally right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 08:54:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Spain we have a president, Pedro Sánchez, head of the government, and the king, Felipe VI, head of the state (who does not do much) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 23:43:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lucy Lawless 💛 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 23:01:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fariña, Bajo Sospecha, El Ministerio del Tiempo, El Tiempo entre Costuras, Isabel, Paquita Salas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 23:00:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Came in here to reccomend this. So yes.

Also: they're gonna put the new season on HBO, I don't know if only in Spain or Europe/Worldwide. I personally watch it on the RTVE website (I'm in Germany) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 09:19:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you know where I live? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 23:17:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am mesmerized. I can even tell where the building where I live would be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-26 11:19:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The one in Battonstraße is open </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-25 16:01:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes, there are lots if ducklings right now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-25 13:18:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> VACA. In Spanish it means "cow" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-25 12:41:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I got most like Pablo Iglesias (who I always vote for) and least Donald Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 15:25:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's been like this for almost two weeks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 16:52:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Poner el alma en el ruedo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 16:51:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [Fuente](https://twitter.com/Gema_Chaparro/status/1252979674499727363?s=19) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 00:16:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love him so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 11:15:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I go to the Volkshochschule, it has good classes and teachers and it's not as expensive as a private center. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 09:57:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FFM is a city full of international people, before moving here (I'm from Spain) I wasn't so sure about it because I prefered Berlin, but I've been pleasantly surprised! There's always something to do, public transport is awesome, people are nice, there are lots of green areas, cafeterias and restaurants... It's not the most beautiful city in the world but it certainly has its charm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 11:34:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks tasty and healthy! What is it exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 11:26:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh my god. It sounds like brainwashing to me. O can't even wrap my head around it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 11:23:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Do you really do the pledge of allegiance every day in school? Why do you have flags in there as well?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 16:40:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the tip, I definitely don't want any homeopathy or alternative medicine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Physio/Chiropractor in FFM? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 16:12:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hallo zusammen, I'm looking for a physiotherapist, chiropractor or something similiar that helps me with my back pains and muscular tension. There are lots of them on google but I can't tell if they're just relaxing massages, reha doctors or what I'm looking for.

Could you recommend someone? I live in Bornheim-Merianplatz, so something close would be cool but I don't mind how far away it is. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-15 14:08:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Però és justament això lo que els fa tan especials i bons! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 13:07:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oils: Spanish extra virgin olive oil, sunflower oil

Spices: salt (duh), black pepper, sweet pepper, roasted garlic, basil, yellow curry, parsley

Vinegars: wine vinegar, modena balsamic

Also soy sauce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 13:01:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Si, i per cert, l'escut d'Aitona és un gall, suposo que per la mateixa història </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 12:40:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In 2013 I moved to Germany to work as an au pair

In 2015 I moved back to Spain to get my uni degree

In 2018 I moved to Portugal with the Erasmus program

In 2019 I moved back to Spain to finish my degree

In 2020 I moved to Germany to work here and here I am! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 01:34:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is my mom's hometown, it's a village with 300 inhabitants. So shocking to see it here!

The eyes come from a legend that says that God made all the roosters in a village nearby sing so loudly that the christian troops that were sleeping in Sunyer would wake up and be prepared for the attack of the muslims. They won and hence the eyes: they literally represent waking up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 01:26:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> El poble de la meua mare!

A Aitona els seus veïns tenien molta afecció a criar galls, i a la població nhi havia uns quants milers. Quan els moros envaïren Catalunya, damagat varen concentrar un gros exèrcit a Soses amb el propòsit de destruir lexèrcit cristià, que dormia a Sunyer. Déu volgué ajudar els cristians i féu cantar alhora tots els galls dAitona i van fer un soroll tan fort, que despertaren els cristians, que interpretaren el cas com un avís celestial, i van poder destruir a lexèrcit moro. Es per lexercit cristià que dormia a Sunyer que lescut té uns ulls que simbolitzen la son. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-11 22:49:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish this gif never ended </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 23:05:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ur damn right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 14:20:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I LOVE YOU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 14:15:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did not know this website existed, how wonderful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Oberschweinsteig </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-09 14:15:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-05 11:11:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My sister used to work at McDonald's and they actually weren't allowed to say "boy" or "girl" toy, it was just like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-05 11:08:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aye </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-05 10:54:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a friend who calls them "the being me pills" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-30 11:44:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm a Teresa, also named after my grandmothers Maria and Teresa (my actual name is Maria Teresa). I also used to think it's too much of an old woman, especially in here in Spain, but now I love it because it's quite rare for someone my age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-29 17:38:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People who buy things are idiots - Ron Swanson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-29 17:23:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Noooooo. All + Oli + Tomata + Sal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 13:02:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [La Senda del Tiempo](https://youtu.be/UftowLtrFVc) de Celtas Cortos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 19:58:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love it. The sunset was especially beautiful yesterday, I took the same picture from the Alter Brücke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 00:49:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chainsaw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 00:43:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Note: I think I should be more to the left when it comes to economy, but well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Well, I took the sapply one and this is definitely more like me </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-27 00:42:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 18:13:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm actually wondering the same myself, this test does not make the correct questions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 17:58:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good boy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 17:33:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Actually I'm not lmao I'm quite pro government </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 17:29:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well I took it and it is way more accurate than this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 16:39:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did an 8values! It's in my profile, and I agree with what you say. I'll do the 9axes as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> I kinda have survivor's guilt about COVID19. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 15:57:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey everyone. I am from Spain, from a very tiny village (population 600) in Catalonia. I am living in Germany now, a country that I love and I kinda have my dream job.

The thing is, Spain is being hit very hard with COVID-19 and even though I don't know anyone who has had the illness (and I hope it stays like this), I feel bad about being here, where we have relative freedom, and all my friends and family not being able to leave the house and to live in fear.

I am actually 0% worried about me getting the virus, but I am terrified of anyone of my family getting ill and not being able to go there, or them not telling me so I don't get worried. I've been offered by my job to go back home and work from there, but I just don't want to go there and have the possibility to infect them.

How are you all keeping up with this? How do you make bad feelings go away? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 15:45:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're absolutely right. I actually know what a Metropolis ist, I don't know why I put that "like" there. Thanks for your input :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Finally took the test, no surprises here </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 15:39:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 17:23:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Schrödinger's broken plates </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 23:22:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used to live there, in Essen. It's crazy, cities aren't even separated by land. They all merge together like a reay big metropolis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-22 18:11:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Finally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-20 23:50:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We'll see each other soon! Until then, let's all stay home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-20 08:52:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's.... Not true. My mother tongue is catalan but I am native in Spanish as well. I speak both of them equally fine. Maybe what you say was true in the 19th century, but certainly not anymore.

Edit: typo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-19 00:27:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Angry sign </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-18 14:50:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-15 21:19:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If people in Spain managed to understand that they have to stay at home, you germans definitely can as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-15 18:56:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is OC! I took it this afternoon. Thanks for your words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-15 16:52:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where is the head?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-15 16:48:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank god Michael Scott did the fundraiser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> This picture is upside down. Oberschweinsteig, Frankfurt 🇩🇪 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-15 16:47:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-15 11:33:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm from Spain and it was like this there a week ago. Look at the country now. Sometimes you don't need to wait for a law to make you stay home, it's just common sense and thinking about others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-13 16:19:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Es el vecino el que elige al alcalde y es el alcalde el que quiere que sean los vecinos el alcalde </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-13 09:01:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I made one for Adam a while ago, [here](https://open.spotify.com/playlist/5kdR6DDYmyOT9xRrOaI3ag?si=yzk0IXe2R62SXXMfh2Xh6w)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-13 07:48:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And Madrid still not in lockdown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Combinació de pronoms febles en la forma escrita </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 13:57:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 09:16:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Javier Ortega Smith is a politician from VOX, the Spanish extreme right party. They are completely against immigration and always use fake news to defend their racism-filled ideas.

To put a cherry on top, last Sunday [there was a meeting of the party in Madrid](https://english.elpais.com/society/2020-03-10/secretary-general-of-spains-far-right-vox-party-tests-positive-for-coronavirus.html), which more than 9.000 people attended. There are [images](https://twitter.com/InstaSamer/status/1237350609923309573) of him [coughing](https://twitter.com/EmilioCabrera7/status/1237342414974705664) in that meeting and still greeting and [hugging people.](https://twitter.com/EmilioCabrera7/status/1237343552767758336)

They also called the goverment "irresponsible" for not cancelling the women's day march that very same day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One of the leaders of Spanish extreme right got coronavirus after saying immigrants bring diseases to the country (more in comments) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 09:11:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 09:59:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I speak the northwestern dialect of catalan, I grew up with it and since I'm from a very small village, everyone around me speaks it.

 As a kid I didn't realise I was speaking a dialect even though in Catalan TV they speak the eastern dialect. When I started taking catalan in school it was when I realised that we spoke differently since most things didn't add up. Normative Catalan is solely based on the eastern dialect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 23:01:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't believe you're r/gatekeeping being ambidextrous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 21:39:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can someone explain what is going on there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 15:39:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm in! Probably gonna bring my roommate as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 09:57:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree completely. Nora's season has been one of the best seasons of all the Skamverse.

Also: watch Druck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 14:28:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA, but me personally I hate it the most when something wakes me up the days I'm allowed to sleep in. I don't care if I wake up twenty minutes before the alarm on workdays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 11:17:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lobster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 11:17:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I couldn't vote for him even if I wanted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 11:16:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're my faves yep, but I vote for PSOE because in my province Podemos has no chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 11:13:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA. Ask her to celebrate together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 11:11:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA, but please try to put yourself in her position and be more empathic. Old people feel lonely most of the time, and as time goess by, they also tend to feel that they don't matter or have a purpose anymore. You need to understand this and be the better person here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 11:07:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. Leave him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 10:05:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not scared 'cause I'm not a beet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 29F from Spain... Guess who I vote for! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-06 16:01:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Steuer ID </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-06 14:24:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hallo zusammen! I've been living (and working) in Germany since January. I haven't gotten my Steuer ID yet, which my colleague has (she started working at the same place the same day as me).
Where should I call/go/ask for it?

Also: I work in Germany but I work for the Catalan government, so I am Steuerpflichtig in Spain. Does this have anything to do with it? I pay the tv tax and stuff like all Germans tho.

Thanks!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 09:55:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pls come back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 13:55:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 46K a year in Spain is a shitton of money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-02 13:53:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> But you can buy a Chipkarte with the Monatskarte included in it. It's what I did, you don't have to go to an Automat to get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ITAP of a plane from a plane </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-28 20:06:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-28 07:26:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me! Dr. Ferreruela in Lleida. Absolutely reccomending it. They have the best team and the prices aren't extremely high. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-27 18:23:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I lived in my tiny village in Catalonia, it took me half an hour by car. I worked in another tiny village, so the roads weren't great.

Now I live in Frankfurt, Germany, and it takes me 10 minutes by metro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bockenheimer Landstraße, an hour ago 🌨️ </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-27 18:19:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-24 19:24:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Join Facebook groups, join language courses or if you already speak the language, any course that you find slightly interesting: dance, art... Try to stick to a healthy diet so you don't feel bad about yourself, keep in contact with your friends and family back home! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 21:48:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Venía a recomendar esto, así que aquí te dejo [la web ](http://www.rtve.es/alacarta) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-23 09:33:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Welcome to the city btw! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-22 23:46:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in Bornheim and I love it! It has everything and a very nice vibe. I see kids and Spielplätze everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 20:50:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are thousands of Miriams in Spain and I'm pretty sure not even the 5% are jewish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-16 23:19:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My favorite remake and characters so far, too. Nothing can compare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-16 09:41:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> [jean ralphio voice intensifies] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-16 08:39:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No hi ha cap dialectalisme del català central? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-15 06:57:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My german is not exceptionally fluent either. Wir können zusammen üben :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-15 06:56:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm in!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 13:44:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Juraría que veo mi casa y soy de Catalunya </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 12:13:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> r/expectedoffice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-05 10:02:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I usually don't like the closeted bully storyline (for example the Karofsky storyline on glee was so poorly managed) but with Adam it's different.

First, Eric actually lets him know very clearly that he has hurt him and that this is a very important issue in their relationship. They don't just jump into it without putting some thoughts in first. He doesn't forgive him just "because he was insecure of his sexuality".

Second, Adam actually acknowledges that he has hurt Eric deeply. When he tells Eric so, he doesn't expect anything in return. He is just ashamed of his past behaviour and wants Eric to know that. That is all.

When they get together it's after a very well done redeeming and self-acceptance arc.  He doesn't forgive him "just because he was insecure of his sexuality". Adam has changed, not only with Eric but with his attitude towards everyone, including himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-02 13:13:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The city locations make so much more sense on a map with the rivers on it. Missing the Ruhr, tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-27 14:28:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not all barcelonins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-26 09:50:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1917! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-25 11:13:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Gonna go to the market in Konstablerwache around midday, dinner at Bergstrasse and a movie in the evening </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> As of today I'm officially a Frankfurt citizen 💖 </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-23 22:56:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-23 19:10:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The tinder one screams anyway here's wonderwall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-22 14:21:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jim... James... Jimothy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 90 minutes in the train with this guy staring at me </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-20 17:16:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-19 09:00:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1. Druck
2. España
3. France
4. Wtfock
5. NL
6. Italia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 12:00:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tot i que "I aquest problema es diu tres per cent" és bastant mític també </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 11:59:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I tot és primavera:
i tota fulla, verda eternament"

Res no és mesquí, Salvat-Papasseit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-16 11:06:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tourism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-15 19:22:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aupairworld is the one I used </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-15 14:57:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Endlich sonnig 🌞 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-14 23:22:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Deliveroo. I was actually shocked with the speed of the process and the 0 questions they asked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-14 23:20:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Meetupp app works wonderfully, also joining language classes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Which actor/actress would play you in your biopic? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-14 12:19:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-09 17:08:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So people don't throw shoes at them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Good online banks? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-08 15:44:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm moving to Frankfurt on saturday! My employer is Spanish so I'll be getting my money in my Spanish bank. I'm looking for an option to be able to get money from ATMs with no extra fees, what could I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-08 15:40:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In Spain it's just numbers and letters in order of registration. The first one was 0000 BBB (there are no vowels involved), then 0001 BBB, 9999 BBB, 0000 BBC, etc. We're currently at letter L and everyone gets excited when they see plates with the new letter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-08 08:16:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First question: if there for example, 50 vacants for fine arts in University of Granada, the first 50 people with the best mark get in. If you don't get in, they try to get you into your second option, and so on.

Second: yes.

Edit: you can check each autonomous communities' "notas de corte" online (each year's lowest grade to get into the degree) online. Just Google "notas de corte Andalucía" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-07 20:26:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Each autonomous community has its own university system where you can apply. You basically rank your degree options from the one you'd like the most to the one you like the least, and you apply for the degree, not for the uni. For example, if you want to apply to two different degrees from the same uni, you need to list both on your preference list.
If you want to apply to unis in different autonomous communities, you need to make an application for each AC.
Wether you get in or not is based solely on your grades. You don't have to write an application letter or stuff like that. You just apply when it's due (mostly around may-june). It's almost always a 100% online process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-05 10:07:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She already is and I'm so glad for that. I'm hoping for a season free of relationship drama and for Alexia to be the supportive gf I know she is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-04 22:50:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for the reply. I take antidepressants so it's something I need every day and for a very long time, decades maybe.

I already know about the registering thing, but I'm still not losing my residency in Spain since I'll be registering just as a passerby residency ( I don't remeber the exact name for that).

I'll have to check public insurances in Germany to be safe tho. Thank u so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-04 15:03:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think Idealista has something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-04 11:02:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude she doesn't like you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Spain > Germany how to have access to medicine? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-04 01:59:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm moving to Germany for the second time and I take daily meds (paid by Spain's social security / universal healthcare). During my first time living in Germany I had my mom send them to me via mail but I'd like to know if there's a way I could get my meds in Germany without having a private insurance, just with my European health card. TIA 💛 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-04 01:46:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm in this picture and I don't like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-03 11:16:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I learnt all about german teenage slang by watching the show Druck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-03 11:09:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's a common thing in Spain to randomly sing out like the lottery. We do it a lot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-31 15:40:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They do, actually. I know many guys who did it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-31 14:58:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right, but it gives you the chance to look for jobs and opportunities there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-31 09:25:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Try au pair! It worked wonderfully for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-29 21:50:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Desatrancador de destinos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-29 01:23:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> HE IS SO HAPPY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-26 15:17:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ich!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-26 10:47:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Calvin's parents are such great role models for parenting. It would be so easy for them to laugh and dismiss everything silly their kid says but they decide to be patient and treat him with respect and kindness. We don't get to see much of that in the media and that's one of the reasons I like this comic so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-26 02:13:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks, I'll try! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 13:52:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Written by Arturo Pérez Reverte </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Two voice profiles in the same account? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-25 13:23:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I bought my parents an Echo for Christmas. I already have one myself and my parents' one is linked to my account because I have prime and therefore they can use my music, etc.

Is there a way we could create a different ~profile for my parents' one? So their Echo can call them by my mom's name and recognize their voice better, or should we create an amazon account for them? Will we be able to listen to two different musics at the same time?

Thanks and happy holidays

Edit: I live abroad and my Echo is coming with me after the holidays, I guess that won't be a problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-24 00:23:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I read Spiegel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-23 07:17:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just a tech </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-22 23:10:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just had it for dinner! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-20 16:30:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> lepública catalana </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-20 08:52:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you missed Ascó, in Catalonia! But I didn't know we had one so close in Valencia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-20 08:51:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Common man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-19 15:45:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My name is Teresa which I love in my dialect of Catalan, my mother tongue. I don't like how it sounds anywhere else so when I leave my area I'm always Tere (which is a quite common short form in all of Spain) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-18 14:20:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You will not lose them. I sent two years in Germany and when I came back to Spain, they were all there. People who care won't leave your life just because you moved countries. There's internet, social networks, whatsapp... It's very easy to keep in touch, but you need to make an effort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-18 09:24:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nooooooooooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-18 08:56:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'd say "Vaig construir la meva identitat al voltant dels que també ho van patir". I'm guessing this "too" refers to the struggle, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-16 01:03:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my area we use both, dos quarts de dues and la una i mitja, but we do not use "un quart i cinc", we just say twenty past or twenty for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-14 12:38:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks for fucking up my life since I won't be thinking about anything else when I speak from now on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-13 18:17:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, I wish it had... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-13 17:49:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I live in Spain and I'm pretty sure this has not happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-13 17:39:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 15:59:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cómo me alegro tía de verte ahí </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 11:49:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I agree with you, but in my country muslim people are much more integrated with locals than asian people.

Also: I hate separating the muslim from the locals because they're also locals, I did so for my point to be clear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 09:12:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where are Cris and Joana </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-11 09:08:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, it's Europe, there aren't many asian people living here, and most of the ones who do usually hang out within their own community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 23:50:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's exactly what they're for. You'll find them mostly in small villages.
P.s.: they work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 11:34:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Olive oil is the key. Stop buttering everything, you guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 11:33:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not that much anymore since the implementation of anti-smoke laws a few years ago. Smoking is more frowned upon every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 09:51:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> La única salvación posible para desatrancar España </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-09 21:12:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe in the most touristic zones, but it's not a language people tend to learn for fun. I speak it because I lived in Germany for a few years. When I came back and wanted to keep learning it, it was very hard to find a place where they offered a level higher than b2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-09 11:06:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am one of the 2% in Spain *stolz* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-09 10:56:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Masterchef! Also Masterchef celebrity if you want to get to know some famous spanish people.
I'd say Gran Hermano, our Big brother, but it's been really sketchy lately, has lost its essence and I don't like it anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-04 22:13:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly. And he doesn't realize Robbe has seen him, and yet he does nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Is anyone else having a hard time connecting with Sander? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-04 12:54:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm having a hard time with liking him. At first I adored him, he was quirky and nice, but ever since he started ghosting Robbe after the homophobic attack I just can't bear him anymore.

He didn't even tell Robbe he wanted nothing with him! He didn't even know Robbe saw him, so he was technically ghosting him. And the reunion scene looked more like a booty call than anything else. He didn't let Robbe say anything, and not even the morning after. Just making out.

And now it seems that he ghosted Britt as well, he didn't break up with her and told Robbe that they were over.

I really hope they're not going with the MI storyline because that would be such a bad rep. That's not MI, that's just plain rudeness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Constantino Romero en otro universo? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-04 09:11:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-04 09:04:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am from Spain and I would love for that to be my flag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-02 23:14:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Don't all of them do that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-02 23:13:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Believe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-02 23:07:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll dm you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-02 14:58:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My case exactly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-02 14:42:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I played Farmville. I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-01 18:19:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The salt in their kitchen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-29 23:58:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ay, una de las cosas que mas6me chocó cuando me marché de España. Al principio no entendía nada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-29 17:37:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A llorar a la llorería </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-29 17:36:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Keep in mind that the 8th of December is a national holiday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-29 17:34:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Read books, watch movies and tv shows and try to translate random things at random times. This last one I do it all the time with Portguese, which I learnt in Portugal during my Erasmus last year and I'm still fluent. With German I try to watch all shows on Netflix and watch movies and I read online press all the time. I also learnt it in Germany during two years, and now, four years later, I'm gonna go back there and I can say I haven't lost any fluency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-27 15:06:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Estará C. Blanco por ahí? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-27 00:15:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spoiler: they make it into the EU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-26 22:28:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yay, now as a woman I can finally use Duolingo.
Also: why assume that the green one was male? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-25 16:40:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lo hice con 23 por no poder encontrar trabajo de lo mío. Volví a España con 25 y ahora con 29 vuelvo a irme, esta vez por gusto y no por obligación. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Al pot petit hi ha la bona confitura </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-24 22:41:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-24 22:30:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sito Miñanco upgradeando la flota </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-22 13:58:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have the degree in tourism you talk about and it's not completely useless. Sure, if you wanna work as a hotel recepcionist you don't need any degree, just languages and common sense. But if you want to make it a frw steps further and get into tourism promotion or administraton you need to have certain knowledge of the market, history and sector that you acquire with this degree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-18 13:27:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mercadona es la mejor cadena de supermercados ahora mismo a nivel nacional. Mucha calidad a muy buen precio. Aunque lo de la charcutería no te lo discuto, pero elige bien. Que tampoco te la cuelen los bares/restaurantes especializados en jamón que hay por los centros de las ciudades turísticas, porque te van a cobrar mucho dinero por algo que en supermercados o charcuterías encontrarás por menos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-18 12:39:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> En el Mercadona (Supermercado) te cortan jamón y otros ibéricos y te los envasan al vacío, va genial para llevártelos porque ocupan muuuy poco espacio y aguanta el tiempo del viaje.
Y también te recomiendo polvorones y dulces de Navidad ahora que ya empieza a haber. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-18 01:12:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> #NoSePodíaSaber </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-17 14:53:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Este chico lo describe súper bien: https://youtu.be/ExhKqyzvhA8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-16 13:03:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally 50% of dogs in Spain are named Black </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-15 21:29:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How did you get a NIE without an address? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-15 19:24:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Einigkeit und Recht und Kartoffelspalten </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-15 18:42:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Wo dativ, wohin akkusativ" wird immer in meinem Kopf bleiben. Genauso "der das die die, den das die die, dem dem der den, des des der der" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-15 12:54:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank u so much!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-13 12:04:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am from Spain too and I lived there for two years a few years ago and going back again for work in January.

Our culture is very different to the German. They're polite, nice and amiable, but they're just not like we are used to in Spain.

The language barrier is a very important thing. Most German people don't speak fluent English (like in Spain I'd say), and German is hard to learn, so I get how this is a problem. I had a hard time adjusting my first time there, but once I was able to carry conversations it got better.

Maybe you could try moving to a different part of Germany with more internacional people? What I did as well was to get into expat facebook groups and meet people through apps.

Mucha fuerza desde Españita 💜 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-07 23:03:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In my country it's your employer who pays for your social security </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 15:57:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ich habe Depression seit sechs Jahren und ich habe 30 Kilo angenommen 😅 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Places to play padel tennis? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 15:56:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hallo ihr alle, I'm from Spain and I recently got a job in Frankfurt, I'm starting in January. I love to play padel, do you know if there's any club or group (I mean like Facebook or similar) in Frankfurt I could join to get more info?
Danke und ich freue mich sehr dass ich bald zu euch komme 💜 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-06 10:28:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lebensretter. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 20:28:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> na dann schön </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-11-04 18:34:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was about to post the same. I'm coming in January from Spain, and I'm just looking for a place in an area with good public transport connection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 13:42:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This will always be my favorite bi meme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 10:21:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Who took this picture of me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-29 10:19:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mátala Juan, por favor te lo pido, nunca te he pedido nada </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-10-23 08:58:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> ITS A COINCIDENCE I SWEAR </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-29 15:19:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-09-08 18:44:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A jo m'ha agradat molt. És un grup que evoluciona a cada disc però que no perd mai la seua essència. El vídeo és una meravella si entens què critica </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-02 14:53:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should stop in Lleida (halfway between Zaragoza and Barcelona) and visit the old cathedral "La Seu Vella" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-31 18:11:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been asked if I'm asian my whole life because my eyes are small. I'm 100% from Spain! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-31 13:56:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mercadona world domination 2k19 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 18:12:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am all of that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 18:11:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well none of that is true but that's one hell of a story, you should sell it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 18:10:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm 29. Not a lesbian, but bi. And no long term partner :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 18:09:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes to all (I'd like to think) except to the fact that I haven't travelled! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 18:08:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's not a guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 00:05:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well.... Kinda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 00:05:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yay!! I don't have the dogs but I wish I had. I love to sing but I'm awful at it tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 00:04:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope. But I did live there for a few years, and I love it with all of my heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-30 00:03:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can have a beer or two some days, but in my country it's a normal thing to do when you're hanging out with friends.
Definitely not a party all the time girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-29 20:24:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What a beauty, I hope it's nothing ❤️ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-29 20:13:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't even know what to say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-29 19:59:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lol so I've noticed. Love your username btw! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-29 19:54:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I recently got to work on that and it's quite working! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-29 19:54:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! I do makeup and contouring when I'm in the mood but rn it's too hot lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-29 19:53:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah, the glasses are getting old I know lol. I'm actually looking into getting surgery later this year so that wont be a problem anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-29 19:52:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I already know I'm fat, I was mostly asking about my face tho. I can change my body if I work v hard, can't change my face for free tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-29 19:49:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> U got the age right! I'm 29. I smoke pot sometimes but def not an enthusiast. I don't even know what Warped Tour ist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-29 17:38:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm way older that that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-29 17:38:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a healthy diet and I exercise. I take antidepressants which is why my metabolism is slower than usual. Nothing I can really do about it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Help a sister out [f29] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-29 17:12:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So I was ugly as an early teen and that really played with my confidence. Those days are gone now but I've always felt like "the ugly friend" and a bit inferior to everyone regarding to looks.

My pics: http://imgur.com/a/WLhQegj </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Okay, reddit, what's my story? Guess away!! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-07-29 16:50:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-20 12:39:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I classified it with s03e11 in my collection </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-06-20 12:36:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally agree with the setting up interesting stories! I think España and Druck are the only remakes that let us know more about the life of the characters that aren't the season's main. Like I never cared for what happened to Mahdi, Magnus in OG or Basile and Arthur in France, but I would die for Abdi and Carlos and Lucas and Viri. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-03 08:04:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then you'll love Druck. They're doing things very much their way, and España too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-02 21:22:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I legit cried while Matteo wrote that message to his mom. "Ich hab mich verliebt"... I have fallen in love. What a beautiful verb. I am so glad that I speak german so I can understand every undertone and shade of the words they use.

What do you think will go down tomorrow? I know episode 8 is the shitshow episode, but we haven't had the fluff week, so it would be nice to switch them and get a fluffy week instead.

Tomorrow they have the sports exam and David has already said that he had stress with the teacher, maybe something happens? I don't want anything bad to happen to my son but I'm thinking maybe he gets accidentally outed and everyone finds out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-02 14:04:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He almost came out to his mom! Come on Matteo, you can do it!!

I'm expecting he goes to visit her tomorrow and runs away to go to David. Or, he goes to David and then something happens to his mom and he gets a call, what would give us the episode 8 shitshow.

Anyways I just want him and David to get together for good already and go through whatever comes with each other's support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> The Druck youtube channel is now open to everyone! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-02 11:55:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Edit: they geoblocked it again. LOL.

&#x200B;

We don't know if it's a mistake or if they really went and decided not to geoblock anymore, but [the official Druck channel](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCr5zglOqHZAEfCcAx_nw1dQ) is now open to everyone!

Go give them some love, views and subs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-05-02 09:13:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I personally think Druck is the best one and I prefer it to OG, but I would reccomend you watching OG first and then Druck. Then España (two girls), France and the one I like the least is Italia, I just couln't relate to the characters at all (also they looked way too alike and old for high school) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-29 12:39:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love him so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-29 11:13:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am sick of people hating on Matteo and on Druck for not having reached out already, I have to stay out of the tumblr tags because I'm getting really angry.

It's a tv show, people, relax. We need the drama and the plot. I doubt they'll do anything slightly transphobic when they have Lukas there and knowing he has had some saying on how the storyline is going.

Matteo has JUST come out of the closet, with himself and with his friends and he said very specifically he likes men. He is now facing this whole new side of the lgbt spectrum that he knew NOTHING about and that had no plan on learning about. He likes (probably loves) David and he wants to be with him, he just has to read a bit about the matter and reach out.

Also, Matteo didn't "allow" David to leave. When David said he wanted to leave, Matteo shrugged. He knew David needed the time and the space, he had been distant the whole night/morning. So he gave him the space. He will reach out when he thinks they are both ready, and it will be sooner than later.

And one last thing, don't expect Matteo to post a romantic MatteoMonday or something like that. He posts stupid memes, and that's it. And we love him for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-27 14:17:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> > I am sure he is not transphobic but he needs to re-conciliate his attraction towards David with this new revelation, and then I am sure he will reach out to him

Amen to this. He has just come out of the closet, remarking it several times and saying he is attracted to men, "einfach auf Männer". He is also clearly uneducated on trans issues and has to read about it and spend a few hours thinking, but in the end he is head over heels about David and will reach out to him soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-27 14:09:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also, I loved that both drawings were on Matteo's bedside table. Even the one he tried to tear up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-27 13:46:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have so much love for David and for Lukas. Did you see [this interview](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o5ZiGczrt6M) about being trans? He truly is an angel. Also, the fact that Druck has so much secretism with its actors but is willing to create content about being trans warms my heart.

I don't think Matteo reacted badly at all. He was smiling when David explianed why he hadn't told him earlier, and I'm pretty sure he would have said something good if Hans hadn't interrupted them. After all, David was saying that he didn't want him being trans to break what they had. When David said he'd better leave, Matteo just shrugged, he didn't want him to go, he wanted to talk about things but decided to give David his space.

I love Druck and Matteo and David so much. This season is my favorite of all of Skam, including OG. I just have so much love for everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-26 23:10:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The reunion was perfect for them. Anything else would have been too rushed and unrelated to what happened between them and how they were taking things before David broke things off.

Lukas is such a great actor... I could see the fear in his eyes while he was hugging Matteo. And how he kissed his shoulder! Oh my god. He's still so afraid to talk to Matteo about whatever it is that haunts him.

I loved the scene with the Jungs, it was so real, just four friends hanging out and laughing and having a good time. Props to Abdi supporting Matteo a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-26 09:25:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Happy David day, everyone. Matteo is already liking posts on insta (he liked David's latest drawing) and we already have a FlorenziFriday pic. Today's gonna be a ride. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-25 13:33:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Aw, and Matteo has now liked the post! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-24 19:27:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally, I just want David to know that Matteo is head over heels about him and will love and cherish him forever, no matter what. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-24 19:26:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The moment Matteo realised he was being a cliché hugging a pillow that smelled like the boy he loves and chuckled KILLED ME. My heart can't stand all this love I have for this boy. I love him like I've never loved anyone. He is just the most precious, most caring, most amazing boy ever.

I can't wait for the reunion, Matteo deserves to be with David more than anything and David deserves Matteo as well. I hate that we can't see how David is doing, I hope he talks to Matteo about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-23 22:17:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My boy is reaching out and is so brave.... I love him so much.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-23 22:17:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> According to [this article](http://plusinsight.de/2013/04/johann-joerg-was-macht-der-fuchs-hier-um-halb-vier/) it's a quote by German scenographer Johann Jörg. He explains that he was once out in the street at 3:30 and he saw a fox standing next to a trashcan. The fox kept staring at him and he kept staring at the fox and he asked himself who was actually staring at who?

I've tried to look it up more, but this is everything I've been able to find. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-23 20:27:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude, I am totally expecting that it's gonna happen and I can't wait for it (and when they run into each other again after that) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-23 11:52:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, after being away for Easter holidays I am finally back and I want to say so many things! First and foremost, mein lieber Matteo is finally opening up to his friends and accepting himself. The scene with Hans meant so much. Only a week ago he would have heard the music and put on headphones so he could isolate himself from it - now he's getting up and going to talk to Hans. Btw, it was an italian song, maybe a way for Hans to invite Matteo to come?

I loved that scene so so much and the fact that they waited for Matteo to like David's post on IG after he had talked to Hans about giving David time. David's like to Matteo's post = Please don't be mad. I miss you, I still think about you. Matteo's like to David's post = I'm not mad, I am here to talk if you ever want to.

The scene with Amira!! So pure. Matteo ordering coffee for her, his way to apologise to Amira without words, and Amira forgives him, also without words. I can't wait to see their friendship develop more. I was surprised that Matteo didn't freak out when he read Kiki's message and then Amira mentioned homosexuality. Very very proud of my son.

Now give me David already, I miss my other son. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 21:08:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Students are on Easter holidays in almost all of Europe. But yes, I kinda like that they haven't run into each other. David's last message was way too harsh for a funny/quirky run-into like Isak and Even's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 20:29:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well, I am in tears. The music was the most spot-on music on Skam after "I'm not in love". Holy fuck, Druck. And Matteo's face of hope when he sent that message to Jonas? His face when he saw the drawing? I LOVE THIS KID SO MUCH. Also protect David at all costs, my other son :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 19:42:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Druck playlist on spotify has been updated and the last song on it is called "[Sandwishes](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XcTxesNVhAQ)"..... the lyrics have nothing to do with sandwiches but still (they kinda talk about rich kids and smartphones) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 18:49:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh man, I forgot about that. I watched Og while it aired, I gotta do a rewatch soon 😅
As of the other thing, I was referring to Leonie telling Kiki (or at least showing it to us), what's the point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 18:40:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree completely tbh, it is very important for Matteo to do so. But it's been the first time an Isak has been outed like this and I don't really understand why they've done it if it isn't for the plotline, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 17:52:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What I think will go down: Kiki tells Carlos, Carlos tells the boys, Jonas reaches out to Matteo to have a talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 15:01:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ugh, ugh, ugh. Leonie outing Matteo to Kiki. This was not the news I wanted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-18 12:38:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's been more than 24 hours since we got news from Matteo, where is he, is he okay, is he eating healthy and drinking water? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-17 10:47:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> and this, folks, is how you do a remake. I fucking love Druck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-16 19:48:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have dysthymia myself (a kind of chronic depression) and smoking weed puts me in such a bad mood after the initial high is gone. It's one of the most depressing substances out there, along with alcohol. Even my psychiatrist has adviced me not to use them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-16 18:37:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They're bringing the topic of smoking a lot, so I'm guessing this will be an important plotline in the near future. Sure, all the Isaks have smoked in all the remakes but none has done it as regularly as Matteo and none of them have had it brought it up by their friends.

I'm thinking maybe this will have something to do with the fallout in 3x08, assuming that David doesn't have any MI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-16 18:32:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> First of all, how dare you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-16 18:31:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hola! Primero de todo, que bien que quieras venirte a España! Me encanta Lisboa, estuve haciendo mi Erasmus allí no hace mucho :)

Barcelona y Madrid son bastante caras, sobretodo el alquiler, está por las nubes. Se paga unos 500€ o más por una habitación (almenos en Barcelona, no sé tanto de Madrid pero creo que más o menos lo mismo).

Galicia no es tan caro como Madrid y Barcelona y también se vive bien. Como tú dices no son grandes ciudades muy cosmopolitas, pero no les falta nada. A lo mejor te interesaría mirarte ciudades como Valencia, Bilbao o Sevilla, que son grandes y no son tan caras como Madrid y Bcn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 22:26:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The girls from Skam España tweeted pictures from the Women's Day demonstration and they also showed texts between them asking each other if they'd go. It's not the same, since they already knew this would be in schedule, but text messaging would be a good way to adress it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 17:58:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He said he comes back on Thursday so I guess it will have something to do with the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 16:15:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am veeeery happy with the new clip! Matteo told the boys he is tired of only hearing about sex and tits and that they only want to know if he has had sex with Sara. And Jonas said he definitely knows something else is going on and told him to talk to them when he's not angry anymore. THINGS ARE MOVING FORWARD.

Also, Matteo has cleared up his room, I would call this progress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 13:09:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ugh, I am from Spain and you can't even begin to believe how REAL that scene was. You hear comments like that everywhere, all the time and by everyone. What angers me is that most of the people who use it aren't even homophobic or wouldn't react badly if their children came out as LGBT, it's just the way people talk. It's roots down in our vocabulary.

Edit: grammar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 11:33:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Crying tears of happiness with that new screenshot from the group chat. The boys are worried about Matteo and will check up on him later on today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 11:07:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wonder what they're going for with that. David will definitely see it, what is he gonna think or do when he reads it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 11:06:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I mean, the phone "works", but the screen is broken so he can't see it or do anything with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 00:04:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lmao, same. I watched today's clip before lunch and I lost my appetite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-15 00:02:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I loved Lucas' season in SkamFr, but Matteo owns the 100% of my heart. I am enjoying this season even more than the OG. They're both just so pure and natural, no extra passionate scenery for the show or for the teenage audience, no model actors. Just two normal teenagers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-14 23:59:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So, no phone = no #matteomonday. I guess if this will be useful to the storyline? Maybe David can use it as a premise to say he misses it. Or Jonas realising something is going on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-14 22:32:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi! Been on meds for five years and I have to increase my dose every winter (and decrease it in the summer). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 22:45:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am from Spain and I think SkamEsp is actually very accurate. Everyone lives with their parents, drinks in the street (not many parties at home) and spends daytime in parks or wherever you can sit. I'm actually 28 and  I don't know exactly what teens are up to these days, but from what I've seen I think it's a quite accurate representation, at least of the ones who live in big cities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 22:41:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a Spaniard I can only say Skam España is showing the real Spain: drinking in the streets and having sex in cars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 22:38:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The last message David sent was way too harsh to believe he actually meant it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-12 22:24:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I am devastated. First of all, where does David even live? All I can think about is that he had to leave home when he came out and his sister went along with him and had to settle for the only thing they could pay. What I have no idea about is why David has been so harsh all of a sudden - just when that afternoon they had been shopping together. There has to be a familiar or health reason behind, same as why he didn't want to kiss Matteo in public or couldn't go to his place yesterday. And Laura, who seemed so nice at the party, is now so harsh at Matteo. ALSO - Matteo has already been to David's??? How dare they not show this to us. And what I loved about the clip is that Matteo just gets up and goes to his bf's house to talk it out, he is the first Isak to do so and I love him a whole lot more after this.

I loved Hans' speech, it is one of my fav scenes in all of the remakes. It has to be said, and it is said. Also, David gave Hans the salami? This boy, I swear.

I'm pretty sure there's gonna be a hiatus this week, with Matteo's phone broken and with the Easter holidays it makes a lot of sense.

Anyway. I can't even bring myself to think about Matteo isolating himself from the world and staying at home smoking and depressed and listening to Take me to Church on repeat. And what makes me even sadder, his friends are not even gonna realise he's missing because he always tends to isolate himself. I hope Hans or Mia see something and act on it. KEEP MY SON SAFE.

Good things are coming, good things are coming, it's all gonna be okay.

EDIT: THE CLIP FUCKING ENDED AT 21:21. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 11:49:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Totally agreed. What if David was in a relationship and got hurtly dumped when he came out, maybe even pre-T? I can understand him being worried about Sara if this has happened in the past.

(Sorry if "condition" is not an appropiate word, if it isn't someone pls educate me) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 11:34:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To me this is David seeing that Matteo wants something serious with him and being afraid of coming out to him because Matteo might not want him then. Expect a "we're going too fast" message from David any time now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-11 10:19:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Movistar+ on youtube. It's the official channel and not geoblocked 💙 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-04-10 20:50:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't think it's something major. It's just him liking a post in my opinion, nothing deep. David is just the nicest boy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sure Jan </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-03-07 15:09:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-21 13:55:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's Catalan rumba, which clearly has its origins in Latin America. Everything is connected! <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-15 20:07:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm just so afraid someone of the gang is gonna die that I can't enjoy this how it should be enjoyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-14 14:12:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What they said. I'm from a village with 500 people and it's very useful. They announce doctor hours, if there's any change on something that has a usual schedule, if something is happening, acts, events, the sellers that have come to the weekly market, etc. It's called "pregón" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-12 09:02:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My two moms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-01-04 14:48:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've never had any problem with SEUR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-11-09 13:17:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was gonna say the same, I watch it on Netflix every week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2018-09-30 10:35:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Keep in mind that in Valencia they speak Valencian as well! Madrid is very expensive in terms of rent, but the atmosphere is the best. And people in Teruel are very nice and welcoming and it's a city full of students. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
