<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject47</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-10 00:18:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Snacks, scented candles (I love scented candles), random little self care items, and I really like the idea of something I can do, like a little craft kit for something fairly simple but fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-08 09:40:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> By tracking my calories so I don't go overboard, and by using other activities to distract myself, like playing a computer game (I get super engrossed) or scrolling through reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 23:06:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is making my mouth water. It looks so good. Can you share the breakdown? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-05 12:30:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My chair. It was huge, soft and comfortable. It also happened to be slightly broken in the most convenient way so as to give me the perfect recline. Sadly I had to get rid of it a couple of days back (it was literally on its last legs) before it completely fell apart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-04 18:30:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congratulations! You look amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-03 12:02:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How to negotiate a better salary. I know that I'm very underpaid for the designation I have but salary discussions make me extremely uncomfortable.

Also, basic financial knowledge, like being able to read and understand balance sheets. I don't necessarily need it for my job but it occasionally comes up and I feel like an idiot compared to others in the room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-10-02 20:46:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There were pros and cons. I found that people (including my bosses) took me much more seriously and seemed to find me more trustworthy, but some of my peers (interestingly more the women than the men) thought I was stand-offish and cold. I don't regret it at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-28 21:10:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Art of Life - X Japan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-24 21:14:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I took accutane for acne a few years ago. It was a fairly low dosage and I was on it for about a year. It did wonders for my face (haven't had a pimple since). The only side effect I noticed was that my lips became very dry, so I had to get a really good lip balm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-23 22:58:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's crazy dedication, congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 19:16:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When I hear my parents laughing in the next room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 19:09:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When you join a company, look for some quick, tangible wins that benefit your peers and make your contribution known (humbly). People's first impression of you will be that you're someone who gets things done, and first impressions last incredibly long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 18:49:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This. I'd just roam around the city alone, maybe sit by the sea, late into the night. Impossible to imagine now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 17:48:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't speak for others but I've had no side effects. If I skip my period more than twice in a row I tend to get some breakthrough bleeding, but nothing other than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 06:09:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bit of a generalization there. Not only do I still live in my home country, I'm living at home with parents. I've lived and worked in other countries for a year or two, but when I came back to India a few years ago I moved back in with my parents because it's incredibly convenient, they're easy to live with, and I can save a lot more. I'm 30 now and have been under no pressure to get married (neither has my sister, or my several female cousins, all of whom are around the same age and unmarried or living in with their boyfriends). I focus on my job, getting healthier, and spending time with family, and I don't regret it one bit. At some point I will end up leaving to pursue my master's degree, but by no means do I look at it just as a way to escape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 05:58:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Couldn't agree more. For me, the preventing pregnancy part is a secondary benefit. The main one is being able to skip periods (or at least have them be very regular). It quite literally changed my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-22 05:50:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I did a solo trip to a Europe a few years ago. The main highlight was that it was in December. I love everything to do with Christmas but where I'm from, we don't celebrate Christmas on such a big scale, so the cold weather and Christmas markets made it the perfect holiday for me. It was also the first trip I took completely solo and I loved it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-21 06:55:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The Princess trilogy and Mayada: Daughter of Iraq by Jean Sasson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 21:38:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She's confident, well informed, and can talk to almost anyone about anything. She's also one of the most hardworking people I know, and always has the best advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 21:32:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Smiling. While walking down the road, I naturally smile at anyone I make eye contact with because it feels uncomfortable and unnatural not to, but some men have felt that it was flirty or some kind of invitation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-20 21:27:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anything but burial. I know I'm not going to notice since I'll be dead, but the idea of being enclosed underground makes me very uncomfortable. I'd be more than happy to donate my organs (though they probably aren't acceptable right now), or just donate my body to science. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What was your experience with laser hair removal and was it worth it? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 18:22:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 14:03:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty chewy. It's a substitute for noodles when it comes to shape and volume, but not texture at all. Also you have to separate the mushrooms beforehand or you end up with a big clump that you can't easily bite through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 11:19:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love soupy noodles but calories are always an issue. Recently I've been using enoki mushrooms as an insanely low calorie substitute (I don't get shirataki noodles where I am) and I've been loving it.

The 320 calories includes 80gm enoki mushrooms, about 100gm each of onion and cherry tomatoes, an egg, about 30gm of smoked cheddar cheese, spices, and my side dish, which is about 90gm of raw mango with a bit of salt and chili pepper.

Edit: just to add, skipping the cheese and the raw mango would knock off about 150 calories from the total. When I don't have them, my lovely, filling lunch comes up to a grand total of about 170 calories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Ugly but delicious. 320 calorie lunch using enoki mushrooms as a noodle substitute. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 11:14:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-19 10:46:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hello! I'm 30F (5'2", SW:230 CW:194ish GW:130) from India. I tried losing weight a few years ago, and although I lost 30lbs at that time I ended up gaining most back. I recently restarted in June this year and have lost about 25lbs since then, 12 of which were during the last challenge (I hit my goal on the very last day. I consider it to be one of my greatest achievements, academic and professional successes be damned).

I'm excited for this one. These challenges certainly motivate me to get my steps and activity minutes up. Looking forward to this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 16:54:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I rarely have a typical breakfast. While I like eggs, I generally prefer to have them as part of a bigger meal. If I have just plain scrambled eggs or an omlette, it feels like I haven't eaten anything. Nowadays I generally skip breakfast, but if I do eat something, it's usually something like popcorn or something snacky like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 16:51:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> These were quickly identified as stink bug hatchlings on r/whatsthisbug so they were just as quickly removed from my house, but I thought they looked quite cute, if a little creepy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Bugs making a pretty pattern on a leaf </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 16:49:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 12:54:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 12:46:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This happens with me frequently. I hover around the same weight for 1-2 weeks at a time and then drop a pound or two over a couple of days. It's been happening with me for a couple of months now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are these? Found these tiny bugs around what looks like a cluster of eggs on the underside of a leaf (Mumbai, India) </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-16 12:39:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-14 12:00:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get healthy now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-13 17:26:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chocolate spread (nutella and anything remotely like it, basically). For all my other weaknesses (pizza, fries, burgers) I've figured out substitutes, but not for this. After months of comfortably counting calories I thought I'd buy a bottle of chocolate spread and planned to have it 2 tablespoons at a time as a little treat after dinner. As you've probably guessed, that didn't work. I ended up finishing the whole bottle in 2 days (went hundreds of calories above my target, and definitely a bit over maintenance as well). Now I'm just keeping it out of the house until I think I have the willpower to try again.

Funnily enough, I don't have the same problem with normal chocolate, so that helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-12 07:16:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Super excited. I just about hit my goal on the last day of the last challenge but my weight went right up after and I've been hovering around there for a week now. Can't wait to do this again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 19:33:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh yeah. There's this kind of barley soup/stew I make that I have been told looks like it's been previously eaten and regurgitated. I have to say that's not inaccurate, but it tastes amazing. I normally keep cooked barley in my fridge, and I take about 70-100 gm of the barley, put it in boiling water with a mixture of spices (Indians will fondly know it as Maggi masala, which tastes like heaven). I then put onions, tomatoes (both cut into chunks), chilies and garlic in it. When the onions have softened, I usually add an egg (depending on my mood I'll either mix it in so it becomes like an egg drop soup, or I won't so it becomes like a poached egg). When the egg is cooked, I pour it all into a bowl and add fresh coriander, Tabasco, oregano and anything else I feel like. There are a lot of other random things I put in depending on what I have in the house (spring onion, enoki mushrooms, cheese) but it always tastes amazing.

Looks like utter shit though.

On a side note it has the added benefit of being like 250 calories max and insanely filling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-07 19:18:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love these comparisons. There are so many days when losing 5 or 10 or 15 lbs doesn't seem like that much, but when you pick something up that weighs the same, it's crazy to think that we were previously carrying it around and lost all of that.

Congratulations on your progress! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-04 04:14:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Popcorn with soy sauce, and raw mango with salt and chili powder. The latter is something I have almost every day. The more sour the mango the better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 06:21:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love this sub. I'm mostly a lurker, but I've found so many recipes to try and I honestly don't think I would be able to stay on track without it. I've always been a volume eater, I just didn't know there was a word for it until I found this sub, let alone so many others who are similar. It was so encouraging to find. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-03 06:12:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Natalorian

Always happy to see others' progress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 18:43:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I made a dip today with canned tuna, a bit of cream cheese, mustard, spring onion, chilies and some seasoning (salt, pepper, garlic). You can also replace the cheese with a bit of sour cream or yogurt, or skip it altogether. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 18:40:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's so convenient! Where I am the smallest pringles pack is almost 300 calories. I enjoy pringles, but I can almost never justify spending a quarter of my day's calories on something that won't fill me up even a little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 06:39:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That dress looks fantastic on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 06:20:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The first time I tried to lose weight was a little over 3 years ago, and I lost about 30 lbs in 4-5 months by eating pretty much only salads everyday. Then I stopped, maintained for a year or two, and then gained most of it back until June this year when I started actively losing weight again.

There are only two things I wish I knew then. First, that I should've tried to lose weight sustainably rather than quickly. I wish I knew that losing weight doesn't have to mean suffering and being hungry all the time. I was unhappy with my diet and always felt deprived, which led to my giving it up completely. What I'm following now (calorie counting and occasional light exercise) feels much more sustainable. I'm enjoying planning and eating my food, I don't feel deprived, and I feel better than ever.

Second, that whether I had a bad day or two or ten, not to give up. It's fine to go back to maintenance for a while, but not to completely give up trying at all. After losing my initial weight and getting frustrated with my diet, I just figured that if I can't eat salads everyday I'm never going to lose weight. Sounds silly, but I didn't know any better. 3 years later I know that even if I'd slowed down my weight loss and eaten better, I'd probably be at goal by now. That's why this time I'm committed to keeping at it, whether I'm losing 1lb a week or 1lb a month. The time's going to pass anyway, so I may as well do my future self a favor and stick with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-29 02:24:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's happened a couple of times with me in the past few months, even though I generally quite enjoy the food I make. What I ended up doing was ordering takeout and just having one meal that day. That way I could have a little treat that excited me but not go over my calories for the day.

Just one word of caution. Don't do this if you think it'll set you off on a binge. Thankfully whenever I've done this I've gone back to my normal food the next day without trouble, but it can be a slippery slope.

It could also help to sometimes look up and try different recipes that fit your calorie goals until you find some that you like. I try out different things, but I have a set 4-5 meals that are around 4-500 calories that I know I can always fall back on and enjoy. I don't think I'd be able to sustain a long term thing if I didn't enjoy my food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-28 12:08:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I barely even look at macros. I have quite a bit of weight to lose (lost about 30lbs so far and have at least another 60-70 lbs to go) so I'm just focusing on calories for now. The meals I make are quite satiating and I've been able to stay pretty comfortably within my calorie goal, so for the moment I'm not going to worry too much about the macros.

I do occasionally look at my protein and if it's particularly low, I'll try to have a higher protein meal, but that's only once in a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-27 17:27:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a big achievement, and I'm saying that as someone who often struggles with getting into a normal, healthy sleep cycle. Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 18:25:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's an interesting thing to think about. If I think about it completely objectively, fat is a factual term. I am fat. I know that, and using other words (larger, heavyset, stocky, etc.) is just sugarcoating.

That being said, I don't believe that almost any person I know would use that word so objectively (with the exception of a couple of people, like my family doctor, who can use the word fat just as a matter-of-fact term without meaning it as an insult).

I guess what I mean is that, as a word, 'fat' is as insulting as the person who is using it. If they're using it as a fact with no ill intent, I wouldn't mind. Unfortunately the majority of people I know of would use it as an insult, or in a mocking/pitying way, so I would still be pissed off if almost anyone else called me fat, and I wouldn't call anyone else fat either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-21 19:34:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't log herbs, spices and most seasonings (unless I'm using a large amount, like taco seasoning on my chicken mince, which is some 40 calories) and things that I am using small quantities of that are very low calorie (lemon on a salad, chillies, tabasco, vinegar). Other than that pretty much everything gets logged, including dressings, hot sauce, vegetables, etc. Oh, I also don't normally bother logging a small bite I've taken from someone else's food unless I think it's more than 10-20 calories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 18:16:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have zero scientific knowledge about this, but in my case I have seen a drop in weight a couple of days after having a cheat day (particularly when it came after 2 weeks or more of being strict with calories). One note is that on my cheat days I normally stick to maintenance calories, or at most a couple of hundred calories over, so nothing really crazy.

This could just be a coincidence, but it's happened at least the past 3 times with me so I'll probably keep doing this every couple of weeks to see if it continues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-20 18:04:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I haven't had any issues with hunger in quite a while now and I'm hoping it stays that way. I'm not a breakfast person, so I have lunch and dinner (anywhere between 300-700 calories each, usually) during the day, and that usually leaves me enough calories to snack a couple of times in between if I want to. I keep several snack options between 100-150 calories handy and I have them whenever I feel like it so I don't ever get very hungry. My dinners are typically the heaviest meal I have, so I don't wake up hungry either.

That being said, I've also gotten better at identifying when I'm actually hungry and when I'm just bored (which was a huge factor in how much I used to binge earlier), and it turns out I'm hungry a lot less than I used to think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-19 18:06:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're amazing! Congratulations on a huge milestone. It's so inspiring. Also I love the snoopy t-shirt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 04:00:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm 30F (currently about 202 lbs), I've lost about 18lbs since June so far, and I definitely feel like I'm jigglier in my inner thighs and under my arms as well. Not a big fan of it, but hey, it's progress. I'd rather have the jiggly bits and eventually loose skin than the extra pounds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 03:53:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been overweight since I was a baby. In school it wasn't too bad because I was, at least, active, but I was always heavier than almost all of my schoolmates. In high school and after, it just got worse and I've been obese ever since (I'm 30 now).

I always knew I was the fat kid (my parents didn't shame me, but random extended family members certainly loved to make jokes and comments about it). It's definitely affected my mentality towards food, but honestly I don't blame my parents for it. 20-30 years ago the knowledge they had about nutrition, weight loss, health, etc. was limited. They did gently try to talk to me about losing weight, but I don't think they really knew any more than I did about how I could do it in a healthy way that didn't make me feel deprived.

At this point I know I have an uphill battle against years of bad habits with food, and there are lots of things I want to blame for it (the fat shaming from other family members, toxic friends during high school/college years that led to a lot of insecurity, my own apathy towards what I was doing to myself, etc.) but I try not to dwell on it so I can just focus on the future. It certainly helps to see posts on here to see that I'm not alone, and that it is possible to overcome a lifetime of being unhealthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-18 03:27:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This happens to me occasionally and honestly I wouldn't overthink it. I chalk it up to little issues with the scale (slightly different position, old scale/battery so possibly a little inaccurate sometimes, etc. ). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-12 17:20:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some days are just like that and honestly it's fine. As long as days like that don't happen too often, enjoy them without guilt (easier said than done, I know) and go back to your normal plan the next day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 19:26:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congratulations! There's such a big difference in your face. Also, I love your smile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 18:37:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're doing amazing! Maybe taking a day or two break where you eat at maintenance will help if you haven't taken any days off since you started.

I didn't have blisters, but I did face some pretty painful skin issues when I first started exercising a few weeks ago which made me want to stop. I talked it out with a doctor who said it was due to friction and sweat while exercising, and most likely some vitamin deficiencies, so she helped me figure out what supplements I needed and I changed up my workout clothes a bit (more breathable materials mainly) and it's helped a lot. Perhaps a change of shoes would help for blisters, or maybe you can consider going barefoot and doing home exercises on a yoga mat. If the blisters are very bad, see if you can speak to a doctor about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-11 17:50:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm in, too. Would be great to have a small group to talk about this with, especially those who have similar-ish stats. F30 5'2" SW: 230 CW: 203 GW: 130 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 00:20:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope. I usually use a tsp or less, so I don't normally bother. I also tend to round up other calories (eg. If I've used 9gm of oil, I'll round it up to 10) so I figure that cancels it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-01 18:03:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi there! Most of my details are very similar to yours except age and height (30F, 157cm, SW:99.5kg CW: about 93.5kg) and I started on 1st June. I had almost the exact same experience as you. I was sticking to about 1200-1400 calories and was losing at a steady rate, and then a couple of weeks ago it just kind of stalled and my weight was yo-yoing between 93.5 and 94 for a little over 3 weeks. It was frustrating as all hell because I hadn't changed my eating habits so I should have kept losing.

I've lost some weight in the past and I know that I retain water really easily (if I do an exercise that leaves me sore the next day or have a little too much salt, it is at least a few days before I go down again) so I didn't change anything. I decided to keep at it and stick to my process for at least 1 or 2 more weeks and if my weight still didn't move I was going to reevaluate what I was doing and figure out what changes to make. I didn't ultimately need to because a couple of days ago I finally broke out of it and went down to below 93.

If you're confident you're tracking your calories accurately and you're not eating too much or too little, give it a little more time. If there's still no movement in a couple of weeks, see if changing something up with your exercise routine or macros helps. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 07:43:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's awesome. So happy for you 😃 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 07:42:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you! You're more than halfway there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 07:42:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's crazy, congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-30 07:41:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's such a fun idea. When I actually start dropping sizes, I'm definitely going to keep at least one piece of clothing from my biggest size. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 19:58:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 20% of your starting weight is amazing, congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 19:49:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha, a lot of your words could have come out of my own mouth. If I lost just 3 lbs a month when I tried to lose weight for the first time in 2017 I'd be at my goal weight too. I use Libra to track my weight and it recently showed my projected goal achievement date in February 2024 (last month it showed July 2021). I spent some time lamenting about it but then I realized that, honey, that time's going to pass anyway. Would I rather be at my goal weight in February 2024 or never? Pretty easy answer, that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> What are you proud of? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 19:33:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been in a bit of a plateau for 23 days now (yo-yoing  back and forth, but I'm at the exact same weight today as I was on the 6th of July, which is 94 kgs). It's frustrating, but I've been sticking to my calorie target regularly, tracking everything I eat, and exercising at least a few times a week. I know this will pass and I'm trusting the process because I've done this dance before.

Still, it's difficult not to feel a little down when I see the number on the scale each morning. So I decided that today, instead of going into my usual self pity mode, I'm going to note down all the ways in which I have progressed and what I'm proud of, even if they're minor.

- despite my current stall, I've lost 5.5 kgs since June 1st
- I've been doing a YouTube workout (chloe ting's 2 week shred with every possible low impact modification). I had finished it at the end of June and recently decided to do it again, and I am so much better at it now than I was when I first started. I have better form and while the workout still exhausts me, I get sweaty and tired later than I used to and I hurt much less.
- possibly my biggest achievement is that I've completely stopped late night bingeing. Calling it my Achilles' heel would have been an understatement. I used to binge every night after a full day of eating for years. For the past two months, I haven't done it at all. My new habit is getting into bed at most an hour or two after dinner. After that I can muck about on my phone for hours and hours, but I no longer feel the need to get out of bed and eat. I love this.
- I've found so many new and exciting recipes to try, and have even got my parents asking about calorie counts and starting to make healthier choices. Tbh it warms my heart every time it happens.

Just typing all that out put me in a much better mood. I know that so many people face a plateau at some point, so for anyone who's feeling down about it or just wants to put it out there, take a moment to celebrate your hard work and what you have achieved rather than what you're yet to achieve. If anyone would like to, feel free to use this space to toot your own horn a little. You deserve it, and I would love to hear about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-29 18:46:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed.

I've been thinking a lot about pizza recently, so I decided that out of my 1400 calories for the day tomorrow, 1000 is going to be a pizza from Domino's which I've already looked up (4 slices for lunch, 2 as a snack, and 400 calories remaining for dinner). Craving satisfied with zero guilt.

That being said, I had about 2 days in the past month where I've gone up to or a little over my maintenance calories, but I make sure it doesn't happen more than once every 2 weeks, and I stay as close to maintenance as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-26 07:14:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The brand is called Haim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-26 06:05:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here. It's so motivating to see people progress with similar stats (I'm 30F 5'2" SW 230 CW 207). Also that dress looks amazing on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-25 11:00:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pita bread and thick rice cakes have worked well for me as pizza bases. I've also used tortillas and eggplant slices, but neither of those will give you the substantial pizza base feel. They taste delicious, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-24 17:25:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I ordered this a month or two back and was super excited about getting it, but days later I got a message saying my order was canceled and I was so bummed. Probably time to try again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 21:12:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The tops were maybe a little soggy, but the rice cakes are fairly thick so most was still crispy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 17:31:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! I think I put them in at 410 for about 15 minutes. I wasn't too particular about the temperature and time since nothing really needed to get cooked. I just wanted the cheese to melt enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 17:09:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don't know whether it looks less natural in person, but in the picture it's gorgeous. I can't stress enough how good it looks (I'm know I'm gushing creepily, but I have very thin hair and that is the kind of hair, both cut and color, that I've dreamed of having). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 17:03:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's fantastic. I also have to say that I love that haircut. It looks amazing on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 17:00:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I try to eat at maintenance or at most 100-200 calories over. Occasionally in the past when losing weight I have gone all out, but then I've limited it to one meal in the day rather than the whole day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 10:56:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 3 rice cakes (99 cal), 30ml homemade pizza sauce (29 cal), 71gm tomatoes (13 cal), 34gm onion (14 cal), 17gm mozzarella (42 cal).

The rice cakes held up surprisingly well in the oven. Will definitely be making this again, maybe even doubling it for a meal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> In a bid to make every meal pizza, here is the 200 calorie rice cake pizza I made for breakfast. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-19 10:53:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-17 17:17:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's such an exciting milestone. Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 17:45:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tortilla base for normal sized pizzas and eggplant for mini pizza bites. I've been obsessed with them for a few weeks now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-15 00:27:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed. That's absolutely gorgeous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-14 00:39:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I swear I'm not a creep, but look that that definition on your butt! Congratulations on 7 months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-13 11:07:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You already know it's not fat you gained, but hoo boy, I empathize with how annoying it is to see your weight increase on several consecutive days. I just came off a 4 day streak when my weight kept going up despite being well within my calorie limit and even though I had no doubt that it was temporary, it still bothered me. I did briefly think about reducing calories further before I gave myself a (metaphorical) slap in the face and told myself not to be an idiot and to trust the process, and thankfully yesterday and today I had a significant drop back to what I expected it to be. Hang in there. As long as you're eating at a deficit, it'll adjust itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-12 17:40:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's a combination I haven't heard of before. Can you taste the cauliflower in it or do the other flavors cover it up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 05:36:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1 egg omelette, 10gm hot sauce, 80gm sauteed onion,  25gm mozzarella, 3gm olive oil, bit of pizza seasoning and Tabasco. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Simple but yummy 200 calorie breakfast </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-11 05:34:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-08 10:50:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't speak to the effects on weight loss and health as a whole (not an area I'm very knowledgeable about) but I do have a similar habit in my home, where we almost always have something sweet after meals. On an ideal day, having a bit of fruit would be ok, but that doesn't always do it for me. So I keep certain things around that satisfy my sweet tooth and for which I know the calorie counts. For example, I have a bag of mini Snickers bars and each one is 50 calories. I also have a bottle of butterscotch candy, and I know that 20gm is 100 calories. Depending on what I want, I always make sure to spare some calories for these little treats.

It's also worth noting that after about a week or two of pretty healthy eating my cravings for sweet stuff reduced a lot, so now I only have the chocolate/candy when I really feel like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 23:44:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn. Those are some arm goals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 23:21:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, it's amazing the difference that 10lbs made. Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 15:18:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm not sure if it's the same for you, but where I'm from we have instant noodles that are about 300 calories for a single serving. I usually bulk them up by adding onion, tomato, garlic, chilies, and either some cheese or an egg, and it's pretty comfortably within 500 calories. It's not the healthiest, but it's an option and it's really quick and easy to make.

Other than that when I don't feel like putting in too much effort I'll just sautee a lot of mushrooms with some onions and maybe peppers. It's super low calorie so you can have a huge amount within much less than 500 calories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-07 02:20:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I eat back a part of my exercise calories. I know the calories burned estimate is super unreliable and since I'm pretty unfit, I don't always know how to judge the intensity of my workout (everything feels high intensity to me), so I always lowball how much I've exercised when putting it into MFP. If I've exercised for 45 minutes at what feels like medium/high intensity, I'll log it as 30 minutes low intensity.

Usually this increases my calorie limit by about 100-200 on days I exercise. I don't eat them back if I don't get hungry beyond my normal calories, but if I do I leave myself that extra bit of leeway. It keeps me motivated to exercise and I've been losing at a pretty steady rate, so that's working well for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-05 23:04:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use the recipe option in MFP. You can weigh your final dish and put the total weight of the cooked food under servings. Then when you add it to your diary, just weigh the amount you took and put it in. Eg. If the ingredients for your dish comes up to 1000 calories and your cooked dish weighs 250gm, put 250 under servings, then all you have to do is weigh whatever you take in your plate (say 50gm) and it will calculate the calories for that amount (200 calories). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 18:42:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like them. They make you look younger! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 05:01:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What worked for me was identifying when I got the urge to snack and heading it off if possible. I spend a lot of time indoors on my computer, and I had gotten used to eating something everytime I was watching a movie or tv show. There were two things I did that helped.

1) If I got hungry I would pause the show and play a game instead (can't eat if both my hands are occupied with the game). I love gaming so I usually forgot about my craving fairly quickly.
2) I did my nails. It distracted me, took a fair amount of time, and you can't easily eat without ruining the nailpolish for a while. It became quite a habit, and an unintended side effect was that I got really good at doing my nails and got a ton of compliments on them :)

There are, of course, times when I end up giving in and snacking, but for those times I keep pre packaged snacks in my house which are not too high in calories (small bags of crisps, popcorn, crabsticks, etc). I do CICO, so I snack if I must as long as I'm within my calorie limit for the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 03:21:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi, 30F here. I've been overweight pretty much my entire life (obese from my mid-teens onward). I started trying to lose weight in 2017 when I hit my high weight of 230lbs through a kind of modified keto diet. I lost about 30lbs in 5 months, but found that way of eating too unsustainable for me. I stayed at that weight until mid-2019 but since then had gained almost all of it back. I restarted my efforts about a month ago and have lost around 9lbs so far.

This is my first challenge so I'm super excited for it. Hoping it helps me stay accountable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-04 02:39:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Congratulations! This is awesome.

I've been thinking about moving to a weekly target as well for the same reason. Some days I'm more than happy with just 1000, other days I feel hungry at 1400. A weekly target would definitely help me relax a little instead of feeling like I'm under/over eating on different days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 14:35:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not sure. I got it unpackaged from a friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 08:07:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha, some others have recognized it as well from a different post. It must be a pretty common set. A lot of people seem to have had it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-03 08:04:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sure you can cook it on any base you want as long as the calories work for you.

You can definitely do cheese and then veggies. I know a lot of people normally do cheese on top of veggies, but for some reason I've always preferred veggies then cheese. Most of my veggies are already pre cooked or can be eaten raw, so I like piling the cheese on top and having it get extra brown (didn't happen as much as I'd like in this case because of the vegan mozzarella sadly). There are a few exceptions (like ham, pineapple, pepperoni, etc.) which I put on top of the cheese, but mainly I prefer my toppings to be under it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 23:18:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Smart background idea. The mousses also look great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 23:03:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I cut it into 6 slices and I could pick each one up fairly easily. I had baked the tortilla for a few minutes before adding the toppings, so the bottom was a bit crispy. I think that helped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 17:29:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> After seeing these multiple times, I finally decided to try it out and did not regret it one bit. Super filling, and completely satisfies my pizza craving.

Mission tortilla (couldn't get the 70 calorie one, so had to make do with the 140 calories), homemade pizza sauce, tomatoes, onion, jalapenos, olives, smoked cheddar cheese, and vegan mozzarella cheese (low calorie but wasn't a fan of the taste and consistency.. will probably stick to normal mozzarella next time).

Note: getting the lower calorie tortilla and using less cheese can easily knock about 200 calories off this total. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> One more for the tortilla pizza bandwagon. 590 calorie veggie pizza. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-02 17:25:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 20:43:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "Cheat moments not cheat days". That's really admirable. Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 20:41:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's awesome. I'm a similar height and starting weight and I have to say that even in the before pic you carried the weight extremely well. Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-01 20:38:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That, sir, is a beautiful beard. A+ transformation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 18:54:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I normally up my intake a little on the days I exercise by about 100 calories. It helps motivate me to exercise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 18:49:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not ugly at all, although I would suggest getting a different haircut. Also you seem super broody in your pictures which isn't the most approachable look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-30 11:51:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is so logical but it's unbelievable how difficult it is to think logically after a binge. I think I need to print this out and stick it on my ceiling so it's the last thing I see before I sleep and the first thing I see when I wake up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 21:53:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow, look at that bone structure! Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 17:43:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's so pretty. I love the colors (of the food and the plate). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 06:15:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Have mentioned it in the steps in one of the other comments. You put salt on the slices to draw out the water first and then use paper towels to remove the water and the extra salt. It's the most annoying step but it's worth it to avoid a soggy base. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 06:13:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Any other toppings you'd normally put on pizza, I would think, but since it'll only be in the oven for a short amount of time and not at as high a temperature as you'd normally bake a pizza, it might make sense to pre-cook some of them. Off the top of my head, the ones I can think of are sauteed mushrooms, onions, pepperoni, ham, peppers, jalapeno, pineapple (yeah, I really like pineapple on pizza). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-29 00:05:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Haha, no kidding. My family's had them for as long as I can remember and the damn things don't break easily so I think they're probably going to outlast me and my children (which don't even exist yet). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 20:03:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cut the slices, sprinkled coarse salt on them and let them sit for about 20-30 minutes. That draws out water. Dabbed them with paper towels to remove the water and brushed away the salt. Then I brushed the slices with some olive oil and baked them plain for about 15 minutes at 210C. Then flipped them over, added the sauce, tomato, cheese and herbs, drizzled a little more olive oil over them and baked them at 200C for 20 minutes or so.

It takes a bit of time, but my understanding is that it would be very wet and soggy if I tried baking it on raw slices. Never tried doing that so I don't know how it would turn out like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 19:51:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are a ton of videos and channels on YouTube for indoor workouts which don't need any gear. One example is popsugar fitness. Do a little digging and I'm sure you'll find something that you like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 19:28:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This was over 500gm of food and was delicious. I had half for dinner and kept half for tomorrow.

500gm eggplant,
120ml homemade pizza sauce (tomato puree, garlic, herbs, olive oil),
200gm sliced tomatoes,
90gm cheese
18gm olive oil

Can be made with less cheese and olive oil for lower calories, and of course with tons of different toppings. Could barely taste the eggplant itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> 653 calorie plate of eggplant pizza </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 19:25:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 19:17:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is gorgeous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-28 10:26:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That looks really good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> How has exercising while losing weight benefited you? </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-27 14:51:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just to clarify, I'm talking about light/moderate exercise, not heavy lifting or super intense exercise.

I (30F, 5'2", 211 lbs) restarted my weight loss journey about a month back with CICO and exercising about 30-40 minutes 5-6 days a week and I've lost a few pounds so far. However even though I switch up the exercises and try to find workouts that I enjoy, there are many days where I feel extra lazy and have to drag myself up to do it, and I know that those workouts are very low intensity and probably don't burn a lot. I know that losing weight is more dependent on diet than exercise, and I've been able to fairly easily stay within my calorie limit each day (average of about 1400 per day throughout the month). On many days I feel like it would be easier to just eat 100-150 fewer calories than get up and exercise.

I want to keep myself motivated to exercise because I do want to be strong and healthy along with losing weight, but recently I've been reading about gaining muscle and a lot of what I've read seems to say that it's very difficult to gain muscle while in a caloric deficit (unless you're lifting a lot and eating a lot of protein) and that sometimes makes me wonder what the point is to huffing and puffing through these workouts if I'm not going to be gaining any muscle (please tell me if I've misunderstood how this works). I was hoping some of you who have incorporated some exercise into your journey could tell me how it's helped you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-27 09:19:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What an exciting achievement. Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-27 04:48:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do add the exercise calories back in, but I only eat them if I'm actually hungry. Also I under-count by a bit (eg. If I've done 45 minutes of medium intensity, I'll count it as 30 minutes of low intensity) just to be on the safe side. I also prefer to look at weekly averages, so if I eat a few more calories on some days and fewer on others, that's just fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-25 08:02:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's the right number of regrets :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 18:33:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can't say whether or not your goal weight is good or not, but what I can say is that pretty much everyone's goal weight is an arbitrary one initially. Just because you've picked a goal weight doesn't mean it's set in stone. When you get closer to it if you think you want or need to lose more, lower it. If you feel strong and healthy and good about your body at a slightly higher weight, you can stop there. It's all up to you.

Don't give that one number so much power. You choose it and you can change it whenever you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 11:47:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's nice. I have a chat group with a couple of my closest friends and they're the most supportive bunch ever. We've been inconsistent about staying in touch over the years, but every time there was a big life event (eg. weddings) we've come together and it's like old times. We've been talking a lot more in the past few months because of the lockdown and all. It's comforting to know that if I ever need advice, help, or even just an ego boost, they're always there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-24 11:18:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NAH. You're pretty young and, over time, as all of your interests develop and you know yourselves better, you may grow apart and find that you're happier hanging out with different people. There's nothing wrong with that. It's just life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 19:29:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That there is such a thing as heaven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 10:31:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup, agreed. Keto worked faster but just wasn't sustainable for me. Even though it's slower,  I'm much more comfortable now, knowing I can eat whatever I want as long as I keep an eye on the calories. I do love my carbs dearly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 10:11:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing more annoying for me in this past week than deciding to have an indulgent meal, coaching myself mentally to not feel guilty about it, saving up as many calories as possible, and then have the meal be badly cooked and super unsatisfying (soggy fries, dry burger... that kind of unsatisfying). It feels like such a waste! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 10:05:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's so nice! Even though you both have to approach it in different ways, the eventual goal is the same, to be healthy. It's lovely to have that kind of genuine support.

On a side note, your black lab and picky cat comparison made me laugh. It's absolutely spot on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-23 09:57:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It may have something to do with what you're eating. A couple of years ago when I first lost some weight, I started with keto, and I think that resulted in a pretty big drop in the first 3-4 days. This time when I started with just cico (no specific carb restriction) I've been losing weight at a fairly steady 2lbs per week with no dramatic drop in the beginning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-22 05:21:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've gotta say I greatly admire your restraint with the cheese. That's normally my biggest downfall when making a pizza, even one that's otherwise low cal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Father's day dinner. Homemade burger buns with chicken patty, colby cheese, tomato, sauteed onion, jalapenos, bacon, mint mayo and a ton of butter </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 20:47:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 20:40:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 20:34:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm sorry you've had such a rough time. Breakups can be really difficult but don't get disheartened. You're a handsome young man and you have a lot ahead of you. Hang in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 20:31:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You look like a lovely person. I'm sorry things have been so tough for you, but don't lose hope. Adulthood isn't all that bad. You'll have the freedom and opportunity to make new friends and the best part is that you don't have to be friends with a group of people just because they happen to be the group you're stuck with in school or college. You can be close to those who value you, and distance yourself from those who don't. It's incredibly rewarding and freeing. I'm over 10 years older than you and most of my closest friends are those that I made in my late teens and early twenties. Hang in there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 20:24:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You have a lovely smile. It's so infectious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 20:13:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's awesome. My height and starting weight are very close to yours. It's so motivating to see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 20:11:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's fantastic progress, congratulations. The change in your face especially is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 19:49:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh lord, there have been so many times I've fallen down that rabbit hole wondering what my teens and twenties could have been if I were healthier/prettier/smarter, etc. But ultimately I realize that there's no point in dwelling on it, and I try instead to visualize myself a year or two from now, when I'll be thanking the me of today for not obsessing about the past but working on the present. That makes me happy :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-21 19:43:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I started cico 3 weeks ago after having fallen off the wagon for almost a year (I had previously lost about 30lbs and then gained most of it back). Initially I craved salty stuff a lot, and occasionally sweet stuff. For me the cravings reduced after about a week or so. I didn't cut them out completely, I just made a rule for myself that I can only have those things if they're within my calorie limit, which is currently 1500. That helped a lot.

Also, I'm a very all or nothing person with food. If I open a packet of crisps or a chocolate bar, I can't have just a few or one piece, I have to finish it, so what really helped was keeping individually packaged snacks around. For example, I have a huge bag of mini Snickers by my bed. Each of them are individually wrapped, and I know they're 50 calories each, so if I have a major sweet craving and I have spare calories, I'll have one or two. Not cutting out foods completely has been a lifesaver and has really helped me to not feel deprived (which is usually what leads to my cravings). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 22:05:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The browning on the apple pieces looks divine. Could you give me the quantities you used? I want to try this out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-20 14:10:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love mushrooms and they're very low calorie, so sauteeing a bunch of mushrooms with some onion, maybe some bell peppers and garlic normally makes the perfect side for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 18:41:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It's great that you're making so many positive changes, and that includes leaving behind people who don't make you feel good about yourself. Also, you look really young. Interviewing for a position like general manager sounds like success to me, whether you get it or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 18:36:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not at all. You're young and have so much ahead of you. I hope things look up for you soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 18:34:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 50lbs is a huge achievement. Congratulations! Also I love your tattoo (at least the part that I can see) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 17:40:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'll make a man out of you in any scenario. Instant badass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 17:35:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not ugly, but I'm not a fan of the blond hair. You look much better with dark hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 07:03:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Both are pretty, but I'd go with bangs. No bangs makes your hair look flatter and thinner, and your forehead looks larger. Bangs cover up the forehead and look fluffy and voluminous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-18 06:38:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Pretty. What have you used as a base for the pizza and the sandwiches? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 19:19:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hard to explain, but you look a bit like you're glaring at whatever you're looking at and you seem to be giving a very tight smile. Then again, that might only be the case in this one picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 19:07:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nope, not ugly in the least, but you do have a kind of intimidating, super intense look.

On a side note, anyone who says 'ew' when asked out really doesn't seem worth the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 18:23:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not exactly. There are some 5 different videos, each somewhere between 12 and 15 minutes long (approximately), and each day is a different combination of these videos. On some days there are just two videos you need to do, on some there are up to four. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 17:43:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're a cutie. And there's nothing wrong with enjoying video games. I'm almost twice your age and I remember spending many years playing video games (was not the most social kid), and I don't regret a second of it. Work on your studies, but always make time to do the things that make you happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 17:33:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your skin is flawless, and you've chosen an unusual color for your hair that really suits you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 10:49:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same. I don't think I'd have the motivation to get all sweaty twice in the day. Also I'm quite unfit, so I'm spreading the workout over several weeks. I'm doing 2 days of her workout, 1 day of lower intensity cardio/dance, and 1 rest day, and then I repeat the cycle. It keeps me same. I'm currently on day 11 of her 2 week shred. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-17 10:42:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Horse riding. I used to absolutely love horse riding when I was younger (in my mid-teens), and was starting to get pretty good at it. I was overweight at the time,  probably about 75-80kgs, and looked quite fat since I'm very short. Still, I used to ride big horses that could carry me very comfortably. Then one day when I was riding with a friend, we passed some kids around my age (complete strangers) and one of them made a comment about how there was an elephant (me) riding a horse and they all laughed (including my friend). I brushed it off at the time, but it absolutely crushed me, and that was the last time I sat on a horse. It's been probably about 15 years since then. I really want to get back to it but I feel like I can't until I get to a lower weight.

Apart from that, I really enjoy adventure sports, but I'm just not fit enough to enjoy them right now. That's why I want to be able to get healthier, so I can do the things I love without feeling like my weight is holding me back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 17:18:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is that you, uncle iroh?

You look great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 11:45:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup, water won't add calories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 11:28:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The USDA database. You can see it here - https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/fdc-app.html#/food-details/170284/nutrients </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-15 11:08:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've been using MFPs calculation which is 100gm uncooked = 352 calories. I usually weigh it uncooked since the cooked weight can vary depending on how long you boil it for and how much water is absorbed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-14 04:59:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm about 2/3 of the way into S2, and honestly I'm trudging through most of it because I've heard S3 and 4 are great. The only thing I've really liked about this season is the avatar wan story. Other than that, there's too much time spent on pointless relationship stuff, and so many characters are frustratingly unlikable and act stupidly, especially Korra. Just a few episodes more and we can move on. I really hope S3 and 4 are worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 10:33:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Keto worked well for me for a short while. I lost about 30lbs in 5 months and was over the moon. But it was completely unsustainable for me. I started to feel deprived (oh, how I missed those carbs) and ended up gaining most of it back. I'm doing calorie counting now and am much happier. I don't feel like I'm living for cheat meals like I was when I was on keto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 10:27:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish I could say quality, but at this point it's quantity that gets me through the day, so that's what I'd go for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-10 01:40:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi, my stats are very close to yours (30/f, 216lbs, 5'2") and it sounds like you're doing everything right (though the calories seem quite low). I wouldn't expect to see too much difference in appearance or inches just yet, but I would have thought there'd be at least a small shift in weight. There are only three things I can think of (and I'm no expert).

1. Calories might be tracked inaccurately - are you weighing and tracking absolutely everything? Even foods with low calories can add up, and we tend to underestimate the weight if we're eyeballing it. Also add ons like a tbsp or two of salad dressing, olive oil, etc. can pack quite a punch in terms of calories. You should be weighing everything with a scale and tracking it all. The only things I don't track are herbs and small amounts of dry spices. Other than that, everything goes into MFP. Also keep in mind that it's difficult to estimate the calories in restaurant food, so if you're eating out or ordering in a lot, that might be an issue.

2. Overestimating and eating back exercise calories - not sure if you're doing this, but sometimes apps and sites can overestimate how many calories we're burning during exercise, so if you're eating those calories back, that might contribute to not seeing a loss.

3. Any other underlying conditions - pcos for example can make it difficult to lose weight. Have you tried speaking to your doctor about other possible reasons? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-04 22:55:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I recently started following exercise videos that were way too hard for me. The workouts were about 20-30 minutes long and I was huffing like crazy less than 2 minutes in. I pushed through and did it the best I could (by modifying some things I just couldn't do and taking lots of breaks), and, as expected, I woke up with terrible soreness the next day so my workout was even worse than the previous day.

I felt like utter shit, but while following a random cool down video, the trainer said something along the lines of 'don't worry about getting it right immediately. It's about progress, not perfection'. That really smacked me in the face, because I've always been an all-or-nothing person with both diet and exercise, and I realized that's what holds me back and made me gain back most of the weight I've lost in the past.

After that I decided to just do the best I can, whatever that is. If that means I take 60 minutes to finish a 20 minute workout, that's fine. If I can't do the intense workout, I'll just dance or something for 30-40 minutes. And if I feel really bad, I'll take a rest day (which I did just yesterday, and I feel much better physically and mentally for the next workout today).

I guess that's about it in a nutshell. Each day aim for progress, not perfection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 18:15:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm doing one of the Chloe Ting workouts (the two week one on her website). It's way above my fitness level, but I do the low impact versions and take breaks and it still kicks my ass. It's very structured and, most importantly, free. Today I was really sore so I just did about 50 minutes of not-very-strenuous dancing and might have a rest day tomorrow if it's not better. I'm not aiming at doing any of it perfectly. I just want to make sure I'm getting in 30-60 minutes of any exercise at least 4 or 5 days a week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 17:44:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Photos are everything. A few years back I lost almost 40lbs (from about 230 to 191) in about 7 months. I couldn't see a difference in the mirror at all, even at the end of the 7 months. However in pictures I could clearly see a huge change, especially in my face, from about 3-4 months onward. That was also when some people started commenting on it, so others could see the difference, even if I couldn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-03 17:33:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That's not a small accomplishment at all! It's tough to break out of a binge eating habit. It sounds like you're doing great. I had lost about 18kgs a few years ago (out of a total of 40 kgs that I wanted to lose) but have gained a lot of it back because of binge eating. I just restarted my calorie counting and exercising a couple of days ago, and it's really motivating to see the progress everyone's making. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 21:41:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For the first issue, it's tempting to say Y T A because it's messed up to be glad someone's in a situation like that, regardless of how you feel they wronged you. However, there isn't really a conflict to judge, because it's a thought you had, not something you acted on or gloated to others about (I sincerely hope).

Regarding the second issue, I guess NTA, but I don't know what you hope to achieve by doing that. You seem to be holding on to a lot of anger. I can't imagine he's going to roll over and accept responsibility (I could be wrong, but it doesn't seem likely) and if he doesn't respond in a way that you'd like, it could just lead to further escalation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 21:03:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup, you'd definitely be the AH. You've already told her once. Keep at it and you're going to piss her off. It's her hair. YTA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-29 18:37:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. It's your property and that's all that matters. But if this is happening often, it sounds like you don't have enough (if any) signs up specifying that it's private property. Maybe it needs to be more clearly visible and obvious that they're on private property. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 21:19:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. Yes, they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 18:28:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I want a friend like you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 18:21:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. That's weird and overly controlling of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 18:19:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly your boyfriend sounds like the only one who wasn't an AH in this situation. The woman was being overly aggressive, you escalated it by flipping her off. Your boyfriend was trying to calm her down. That sounds like support to me. Did you want him to try and intimidate her instead? That would only have made things worse. YTA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 17:53:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. If he's said that he's going to, it's reasonable to expect him to follow through. If he has no intention of helping out financially, he should at least be up front about it from the start so you could take that into account while planning your budget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 17:47:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hard YTA here. Puppies aren't Amazon purchases you can buy and return for no good reason. If you hadn't been clear and up front about having any breed restrictions earlier, it's an AH move to now tell them to get rid of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 17:39:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA. While her saying that 'no one thinks she's Indian because she isn't black' is pretty tone deaf, I don't think it's your place to decide how much she should embrace her culture. It doesn't sound like she's doing anything intentionally insulting, and it's her choice what she wears. I understand that you may have faced challenges yourself, but don't take it out on her just because you think she has it easier. It's not her fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 02:16:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm gonna go with ESH. It was honestly a little dense on your part to think that she wanted to have a conversation just an hour after she had specifically asked not to be messaged all day. If someone asks for space, give it to them. On the other hand, it was also quite the overreaction on her part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 02:10:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. Dear lord, why on earth does she think she has a say in how you spend your money? Sure, supporting local businesses is a worthy thing to do, but it's not her place to try and dictate what others do. You didn't owe her any explanation, but you still gave one to her (which makes sense). She should have backed off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 02:03:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your first line says that you've been secretly dating him. If it's a secret, why would you expect that your mom would invite him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 00:19:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NAH. It's your business so it's up to you to decide who you want to employ. You don't owe it to anyone. That being said, your friend wasn't an AH all that time ago either. It's perfectly understandable that they didn't want to work for no pay, even if they didn't need the money. That shouldn't be held against them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 00:16:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA. Why is it B's problem that you feel the teacher's being unfair? What do you expect her to do about it? It seems like you're bitter about this whole thing and are taking it out on your friend because you don't know what else to do. I don't blame her for getting pissed off at you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-28 00:09:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ESH. Your SO certainly sounds like she was being a bit hypocritical, but if you were going to call her out, it probably would've been better to do it privately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-26 17:59:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have a hard time believing some of these scenarios. YTA. Your boyfriend sounds insecure and is a real AH for asking you to choose between him or your friend, and you're an AH for choosing to break off a years long friendship over text even though she did nothing wrong (she just truthfully answered a question you asked her). On the other hand, she's probably better off without you as a 'friend'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-21 20:29:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are you married or are you roommates? 3/5 is not unreasonable if you're making double. YTA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-21 08:56:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. Even if she didn't like receiving a letter, the was a ridiculous overreaction on her part. Any decent human being would have a little sympathy for your situation, but she sounds like that's beyond her capability. I would keep my distance from someone like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 21:02:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tell them anyway. It should be checked out. A doctor would be a better judge of what the cause is. You don't want to keep shut about it until it's irreversible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 20:57:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. If you find it boring, it doesn't make sense to continue with it since your parents will only be spending more money on something you'll eventually quit anyway. However, why would you tell your parents you want to quit only because it's boring? If you genuinely think it's injured you in some way, you need to tell them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 20:52:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ESH. Yes, him trying to spit water at you is disgusting, but you're daft for doing it the second time and not expecting him to retaliate. Both of you need to grow up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> First time shaping dinner rolls into anything other than a ball </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 19:43:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 10:06:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hard to give a judgment honestly, because it sounds like your sister's keeping the rabbits herself and is just having your daughter visit them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 10:01:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> INFO. Were the rabbits a gift for your daughter at all? It just sounds like she got two rabbits and is keeping them herself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 20:27:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. This whole thing sounds shady as hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 20:23:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My water literally just came out through my nose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 20:10:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> To be honest you probably do need to let it go, but you're NTA for feeling a bit annoyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 19:03:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. It's your stuff. Even if he was careful and considerate with your things (which he clearly wasn't) you'd have no obligation to let him continue using them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 18:54:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. Irene needs to back the eff off. It's not her business in the least and if you need to be a little rude for her to get the point, so be it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 18:49:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Truer words have never been spoken. NTA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 18:47:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> "I do play with the dog and take care of it when M is doing something". Sorry, OP, but that says it all. You feel like your mom is primarily responsible for the dog's welfare and that you need only pitch in when she's busy with something else. Help your mom out and split the responsibilities (which, yes, include playing with the dog now and then). She's not being unreasonable. YTA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 18:28:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. She demanded. You asked her to ask nicely (although asking her to piss off would have been an equally suitable response). She didn't. If she can't ask for stuff politely, she probably doesn't deserve it.

On a side note, your dad "doesn't believe in autism"? What the everloving hell?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 17:29:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I'm following a recipe for dinner rolls. In the recipe it says that the dough will make 8 rolls and should be baked at 200 degrees Celsius for 20 minutes. However based on the pictures, the rolls look much larger than I'd like. If I want to divide the dough into, say, 12 small rolls instead of the 8 large, would I need to adjust the baking temperature and/or time? If yes, how should I calculate it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 05:36:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ESH, but you guys are married. Is this really the hill you want to die on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 05:28:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this for real? You sound ridiculously overprotective and overbearing. YTA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 02:54:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. Maybe calling him out on a group chat was harsh, but honestly it's a dick move on your dad's part to snoop around their house and then share information they obviously decided not to share themselves at that point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 17:00:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NAH. I can understand her feeling let down about this because it's probably something she was excited about and had put some thought into, but you have good reasons and it sounds like you told her gently enough. Tough break, but I don't think you're an AH for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 14:47:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NAH. You were a kid. A smartass and probably a pretty annoying one, but a kid nonetheless. I don't think you left too much of a lasting impact on your teachers. Don't worry about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 14:41:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You're NTA. He is. Honestly he sounds like a terrible friend. Who makes jokes like that and refuses to stop, and then has the audacity to expect an apology from you for confronting him about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 14:35:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. If you genuinely wanted them on because you couldn't follow it otherwise, he's being childish. I know a lot of people prefer watching without subtitles, but it wouldn't be the end of the world for him to be a little accommodating if not having them on literally means you won't understand half the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 14:25:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. It's natural to be curious about this, especially if you feel you haven't gotten the full picture from your mom. You would certainly not be the AH for asking her more and wanting to meet him, but do be careful to manage your expectations. You've gotten two such opposing accounts of the kind of person that he is. He could be either of the two extremes, something in the middle, or something totally different. Either way, can't blame you for wanting to know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 13:03:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> In that case, in the nicest way possible, it's his problem and he should know that. If he wants to fix things with her, it's his responsibility to do so. Nobody else should do it for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 12:09:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA. The relationship between your husband and his mother is clearly very complicated. I understand you wanting to fix things, but you've said yourself that he has a good reason for distancing himself from her. While it was ok for you to try once or twice, at this point it seems like you're completely disregarding your husband's feelings on the matter. While you may want your child to know their grandmother, please consider that she may be a bad influence and that keeping her away may be what's best. I would trust your husband on this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-18 06:07:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. There are red flags all over this situation. Don't share your address unless you feel comfortable doing so. You don't owe her anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-17 21:33:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA. I can understand that the lockdown isn't easy on anyone, but from what you said, your mom has a full time job as well. All three of you have full time commitments, but your mom seems to be doing a majority of the house work. Doesn't that seem unfair? Maybe it's her way of asking you both to help out more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-17 19:10:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. While it's ultimately her decision, she asked for an opinion and you told her the truth. There's nothing else to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-17 18:57:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA. Sounds like you have strong beliefs. That's fine, until you start pushing them on to others and expecting them to conform to your idea of what's right. It's sad that you can't be happy for your sister and show a little support just because the attention's on her. Also, it's great that you adopted a dog, but it should be enough to be happy with your choices instead of expecting praise and getting pissed off when you don't get a pat on the back for it. Your sister doesn't sound like the selfish one to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-17 18:28:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. There was enough food to go around. The kid chose not to eat any of it. He sounds extremely spoiled. His mother may choose to cater to his every whim and encourage this behavior, but it's unreasonable of her to expect you to do so, especially if you have several others to feed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-17 18:21:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA. Their relationship is between them. You seem to have inserted yourself into it for no good reason. You don't have any solid reason to assume he was cheating other than reading into some comments he made (which you most likely didn't hear first hand but through your friend). Also bringing all this up after she's already broken it off doesn't serve any purpose other than to hurt her further. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 11:16:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. She is your mother, but she gave up any right to be a part of your life long ago. Reading your post actually made me angry when you wrote that she thinks she's been a great mother. She deserves nothing from you. Don't feel even an iota of guilt about this and frankly, if your dad knows about what went on and that she did nothing, it's baffling that he's pushing you to involve her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 20:10:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA at all. It's your wedding and your big day. If she's cut you off in the past and hasn't made any effort to reconnect or even respond to you,  don't feel guilty about inviting others but not  her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 19:57:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably not the best thing to do legally but I'm going to go with NTA. It just doesn't seem like a good idea to give that amount of money to an unreliable addict. I don't know what your parents would think about it, but I feel like they should be the ones to handle the money, especially if they're covering her expenses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 19:52:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 'I told her to stop sending them to me, that this is too much'. YTA if that's how you told her. I'm not saying that you shouldn't have said anything, just that it could have been put in a much better way.  It sounds like she's only trying to be nice, even if she is going a bit overboard. You've said yourself that some of the things she's sent have been helpful, so it may have been better to be appreciative of everything she's sent but explain that it would be unfair to your roommates to continue to take up more than your share of space. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 19:42:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. If you've told him clearly that you don't like it and he doesn't stop immediately, he's the AH. Weight is a sensitive issue for a lot of people, even those that aren't overweight or underweight, so he should really be a little more understanding and drop that particular nickname. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 19:20:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. It's competitive out there and I don't think it's fair to blame anyone for doing everything they can to get ahead (as long as you're not hurting anyone). Advancing a worthy cause is a good thing, even if it may not be your passion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 11:37:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA. You've chosen which daughter you prefer and have made it very clear to her. I'd wager that a large part of your daughter's actions are because you pretty much gave up on her and made it so clear that your stepdaughter is better. It's great that both of them got in to good colleges. Treat them the same and support them equally. And for God's sake, stop comparing them so much. They're different people and have had different experiences that have made them who they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 11:27:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. Avoid away. You should spend time with people who you actually enjoy spending time with, not people who make you uncomfortable, especially if you've voiced your discomfort and they've dismissed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 11:13:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. The family gave her away willingly and you've taken good care of her since. It's your cat and as long as you're treating her well, it's fair to keep her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 11:05:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Took the words out of my mouth. ESH, and how. Joe sounds an AH, Lisa's 'prank' was an incredibly shitty thing to do, and the rest of you sound like you want to milk this drama for all its worth by getting yourselves involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 10:37:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA. I get that you want to help sort things out, but ultimately it is between them. You expressed that you didn't think it was fair and that's fine, but don't push it further. You can't force Sam to get over it just because you disagree with how they're handling it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 07:17:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. If this were unsolicited, it would be a different situation, but your brother has asked you for help and seems to be responding favorably to this style of training. If he doesn't like it or seems to get frustrated, you will have to change tactics, but right now it sounds like it's going well. Now that it's been a month, maybe have a sit down with him and go over the progress he's made and whether he's happy with how it's going and wants to continue in the same way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 20:03:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. 'Let bygones be bygones' works for times when you've had a silly argument or your mom's been a bit petty about something. Being used as a drug mule, being stolen from and being psychologically abused and manipulated goes way beyond that and, in my book, is pretty unforgivable. This isn't a one time lapse of judgment, but a toxic pattern of behaviour.  If you feel the need to reach out and give her another chance, please do so (but be wary), but you would absolutely not be the AH if you decided not to have any contact with her again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 19:16:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. It's entirely up to you whether you want to accept their terms or not, but this seems less about whether you'd be an AH and more about whether it would be smart for you to turn it down right now. From my perspective it would make more sense to accept their best offer (after as much negotiation as you feel you can do) and if it's not enough, continue to look for a job while you still have this one. Given the current job market it doesn't seem well advised to leave or turn down a job unless you have something else in hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 18:43:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mild YTA. I get how this would make you feel ignored. That being said, everyone has different ways of dealing with a stressful day and most of them probably aren't fun for the partner. I assume it would be just as annoying if he completely shut you out and refused to meet you, or if he met you and complained the entire time you're together.

His method of dealing with it seems to be withdrawing into himself and needing a little quiet time, but he still wants to be close to you, possibly because you being there gives him some measure of comfort. In a relationship it seems reasonable to expect that you would both be there for each other during bad days (to a reasonable limit... twice a month doesn't sound too bad) even if it's not the most fun thing you could be doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 18:23:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ESH. She overheard the worker, got the impression that he made a racist assumption and felt that she needed to say something. She could have spoken in a nicer way and the matter probably would have been clarified quickly. Similarly, you could have told her what the situation was (without all the insults) and that her assumption was incorrect, and she probably would have backed off.

It sounds like both you and the lady got confrontational without even trying to be civil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 18:12:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. It's your decision who to and who not to give the discount, and you've never even met her. I can understand her asking why the price was higher for her than for your friend, but once you answered (whatever the answer), it should have been enough. She should have either accepted it or decided not to place the order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 17:26:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YTA especially because the tantrum happened in front of everyone, but it looks like you already knew that. I'm sure it was irritating for you but it sounds like it was an honest mistake on his part, forgetting to pick you up. It's not his fault and he had no way of knowing that you were having a bad day. It's good that you apologized and he accepted it, because being embarrassed in front of others (especially his students) is not easily forgiven. Best thing to do would just be to move on and not do it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 17:15:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Soft YTA. It is completely your decision to choose not to do so, but it doesn't seem like a very big ask from them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 17:04:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NAH. Your wife probably didn't realize how important it was to you. Possibly to her it's just a story they were talking about, but to you it was a memorable experience that you missed out on sharing with your daughter.

For people who don't get too invested in movies, stories, TV shows, etc. it can be difficult to understand why spoilers are such a big deal. Maybe it would help to explain to her (without getting worked up) that things like this had an impact on you when you first watched it and you want to be able to create those kinds of memories with your daughter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 11:49:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. There's nothing wrong with wanting to keep yourself safe and it's baffling that the family would hold that against you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 11:39:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Absolutely NTA. He's being overbearing and pushy and the shower jokes seem super weird, especially if you made it clear that they make you uncomfortable. A good friend wouldn't be so dismissive of your feelings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-14 10:14:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> NTA. It's understandable for him to be concerned about a loved one's health, but pushing you to do this when you've so openly said you don't want to will lead to a lot of resentment and insecurity down the line. Doing too much because someone else is nagging you to is unlikely to keep you motivated in the long run, which will be needed if you want to lose weight and maintain it at some point. Doing crazy workouts for a few days or weeks is not sustainable unless you're motivated to do it yourself. It's also pretty widely known that nutrition plays a bigger role in weight loss than exercise (although both together is the best), so figuring that out together may help.

I can't comment on whether your looks bother him, but it's worth giving him the benefit of the doubt, especially if he's never brought it up before. If fitness is important to him, it seems most likely that he's only worried about you. That being said, he's going about it the wrong way and is only going to end up pissing you off more if he doesn't ease off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
