<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>erisk2021-T3_Subject76</ID>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-30 00:09:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I've picked my lips till they bleed or it triggers a cold sore since middle school. I'm a senior in college now. I feel your pain. Also, I have a question, since this related to anxiety disorders when would be the time to see a psychologist for this, if at all? Asking for myself, thanks. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-09-01 19:27:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just tell people I’m California sober </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 18:11:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck them kids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 18:03:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Huh, I’m in a long term relationship and can still do all these things. I guess you’re referring to marriage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 17:56:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dorm room doesn’t have a fucking lid so I literally sprint out of the bathroom when I flush.....so nasty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-26 17:48:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t wear one pieces because I want my torso to get sun. The tan line is weird to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 19:09:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wall-E is one of my favorites. It’s mainly aimed at kids but I think that the overall message sits well with adults too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-25 19:08:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wall-E!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 21:54:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No I haven’t. I sent an email to Depop though to see if they could help. If not, I told my buyer to give me a few days and they were understanding about it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 19:13:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuckkkkkk I don’t wanna upset my first buyer :(( but thank you for your response I just sent them a message letting them know the issue and offered a discount on their next purchase. Hope they’re cool with that <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> SHIPPING ISSUES </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-08-05 19:01:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hi I’m new to depop and have just sold my first item. I can’t view my shipping label but I’ve already verified my PayPal account so I’m pretty annoyed and confused. This needs to get shipped today it’s very urgent. Even though I chose to ship with depop, could I just handwrite the address and ship that instead of using the label since I can’t fucking see it? Thanks guys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 17:49:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People are obsessed with sex 🙄 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 17:46:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So is IVF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 17:41:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Jada smith fucked her sons friend who was going through addiction issues. If will smith did that he’d be labeled a predator. Also I’ve only seen people backing up Will not making fun of him. I guess it depends on which platform you’re on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 17:37:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude @ me next time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-07-16 17:34:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This shit never crosses my mind because I would never be committed to someone who doesn’t work. It’s hard to get by on a one income household. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-06-12 01:52:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can’t even laugh at this she’s so dumb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-26 18:34:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You’re not needy. I dont know what your girlfriend’s problem is but complimenting your partner is not hard unless she really can’t think of anything positive to say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-26 16:21:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I felt like a whole dumbass trying to press play. C’mon man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-26 16:11:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There are other cute girls out there who won’t hookup with their exes. Go find one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 16:18:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree this makes me cringe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 15:45:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You two need counseling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-25 15:21:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup that’s how opinions work. A lot of others agree with me as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 22:54:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No one should be allowed to in public, imo. There should be designated areas for nudity as I stated previously. I think it’s a win win for everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 22:45:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t think people should be allowed to walk around half naked. I don’t think it’s flawed logic because it’s pretty vulgar to flash yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 22:32:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> There should be designated areas like beaches or parks where people can go nude/topless. I don’t believe women should be allowed to walk down the street topless. Not everyone wants to see that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 21:14:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. Everyone grieves and deals with death and tragedy in different ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 19:08:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yessssssssssssss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 18:43:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m not sure how to link a photo without making another post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 18:40:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tomato pie recipe:

Pre-baked pie crust 9”

5 Roma tomatoes

1/2 cup of chopped red onion

5-8 basil leaves

1 cup shredded mozzarella

1 cup shredded cheddar

1/2 cup of plain Greek yogurt

1/4 cup of light mayo

Salt n pepper

Pre-heat oven to 375.
Peel and slice tomatoes. Place in a strainer and salt, let sit for 10 minutes. (Very important step - this draws out the water in tomatoes.) Lay tomatoes on paper towel and pat dry. (We don’t want wet tomatoes.) Layer the tomatoes, onion and basil in pie crust. Salt and pepper to your taste. Mix together cheeses, yogurt and mayo in bowl. Spread on top of the tomatoes. Place in oven and bake for 30 minutes. Let cool for 15 minutes and enjoy!
This is my healthy version of tomato pie! Other recipes use sour cream and regular mayo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 18:30:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont care about any pregnancy honestly but I do think puppies and kittens are cuter than infants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 18:26:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get some flavor up in there! Looks good tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 17:58:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes. You can 100% find healthy food for cheap. You just have to know what to look for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 17:57:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Healthy food is actually relatively cheap. Most people who are low income are just uneducated about what is healthy and what is not. Processed foods are not good for you. If you buy mostly veggies and meat, it’s much cheaper than buying a bunch of processed foods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 17:52:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She honestly had no choice but to accept it. That was her fate once she decided to go on the trip. Pelle’s whole purpose was to bring victims back for their sacrifice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 17:35:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t follow hot guys because I don’t get “turned on” by people’s looks. If I follow a guy who is deemed “hot” by society it’s usually because of his hobbies or other attributes that aren’t physical. The only guy I follow who I personally think is physically attractive is a gay man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 17:28:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t bathe to get clean, I bathe to relax. Showers are for hygiene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 17:07:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love my Lexus. Japanese cars are top tier imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 17:04:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 17:03:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fiji is where it’s at </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 16:54:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No thanks I can just wear a sports bra or a crop top without a shirt instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [Homemade] Southern Tomato Pie </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-24 01:45:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 21:31:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People should be pushing women to enter any field they choose. Regardless if that’s STEM or another field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 16:37:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get more upset when people value the life of a dog over the life of say a pig. People flip their shit when other cultures eat dogs but don’t give a rats ass about farm animals. They’re all animals. They’re all equal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 16:32:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wear glasses/contacts and never had a problem but I know this isn’t practical for everyone. Try goggles! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 16:27:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I get what you’re saying now. By “vs” you mean when they post side by sides of the bad angles vs the full make up pic of the same person? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 16:23:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What do you mean “they just take a decisively bad angle Vs a post with full make up”? So full make up posts deserve to be criticized over bad photoshop? I don’t get your point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 15:53:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They’re just exposing the photoshop trend. It’s not ripping apart girls’ appearances because that’s not even what they look like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 15:41:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 07:04:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This guy knows how to have a good time. Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 02:17:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is this “potato bun” you speak of </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-23 02:15:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn sounds spicy!! Would love to try that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-22 20:35:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s just you. She’s obviously an athlete. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-22 16:22:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ve never had pierogi before but it looks so delicious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-22 01:29:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Boiled eggs with avocado toast or tomato sandwiches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-20 05:10:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-19 18:42:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’d still rather be a Phoenix </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 21:41:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where tf are you if you don’t mind me asking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 19:02:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Man..... that was really sad to read. Remember to fake it till you make it. Good luck out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 19:01:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 18:56:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You kind of blame women for your troubles in your post. I saw some say to be the person you would wanna date. I like that and think you should follow that advice. That being said, confidence is something women look for in a man. I’m sorry, but if you go around with the mentality of “I’m a good guy woe is me,” women aren’t going to find that attractive. If it’s hard to be confident in yourself then fake it till you make it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 18:36:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No I’m being serious, you sound extremely insecure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 18:33:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude what? You’re insecurity is showing. Just be confident and the girls will come. Seriously. Not trying to be mean but try and be someone YOU would date. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 18:29:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh, I would be livid as well. The best revenge is to be better than you were before. I say, try and find someone else and forget about this girl. She’ll realize she fucked and may try to win you back but guess what? You’ve already moved on, you won, you’re happy now. I say forget about her and let her live with the choice she made to date this loser. Good luck to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 18:24:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you do continue this friendship/relationship just know, the whole dynamic was build on lies. Is that really someone you want to be friends with? Much less in a relationship with? You’re obviously a kind person, you’ll find a girl who respects you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 18:21:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude, please go find a girl who doesn’t view you as second best. Everyone deserves someone who is their number one choice. You deserve much better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-16 18:10:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I know it hurts right now, but in time, you’ll see you’re so much better off without an alcoholic bringing you down. Time will heal, just try and focus on yourself. I’m sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 18:40:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s great you should find the time to watch it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 18:39:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Take this to r/legaladvice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 16:50:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was in a sorority because I was my moms legacy. I was absolutely miserable even tho I was in “the most coveted house.” I ended up dropping this semester and I’ve never felt more free in college. Some people love it, but to me, they cared more about their image and numbers than the actual people in the chapter. It was extremely superficial in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 16:35:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Careful, your envy is showing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 14:55:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s pretty easy for me to burn bridges and move on, but I still think about the fun moments I may have had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-15 01:48:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do this too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 16:31:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ewwwww hahahahaha took me a minute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 15:19:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes they do but thank god for the castle doctrine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 03:31:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t care if my boyfriend goes through my phone because I really don’t have anything to hide. Also, to me it’s not really an invasion of privacy in a relationship but that’s just us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 03:03:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I like Purple Haze, but other than that I really only love this one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 01:41:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ll have to try that sour sometime! I also love a good tropical IPA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 01:28:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why does food turn me on.....I’m drooling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 01:08:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s really good! Next time it crosses your path I encourage you to give it a shot :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Great seasonal by Abita! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 01:05:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Abita! Perfect beer for the beach, wishing I was there right now. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-13 00:50:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 18:20:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Stop it, I’m horny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 18:17:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dudes that’s fucked but also what an idiot to not clear your iPhone before selling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 16:01:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go cry me a river Darnell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 04:11:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit yum!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 01:51:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yet, here you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-12 01:38:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If I’m working out I definitely think wireless is better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 17:24:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m telling you not Every. Single. Guy. in a relationship thinks about other women while masturbating or having sex. We can go back and forth on this as long as you want but you’re wrong for grouping every man into that category. People aren’t black and white like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 17:07:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lmfao not all guys are slimy like that while in a relationship. YOU may be and that’s fine but not Every. Single. Guy. Do you know every single man on the planet? Have you had this conversation with them all? Nope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-11 00:33:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Heyy, I did this in Germany at the Englischer Garten! Very efficient </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 22:23:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lmfao no, why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 21:25:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is NOT a girl thing. Do not let her manipulate you into thinking this is normal behavior for girls. If the tables were turned, I’m sure she’d be livid. Tell her to cut this shit out or leave the relationship because this is not healthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 21:22:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You’re right, next time I’ll try harder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 21:19:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s really just a cultural thing, especially in the Southern United States where I’m from. We’re extremely polite but in a passive way. It’s not right, I agree, but it’s just how we are down here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 21:13:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hot legs, dog! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 21:01:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You could call it a thirst trap :) lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Sittin’ poolside with a tall glass of water </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 20:56:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 20:09:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Right? It sounded like he got pissed at OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 19:54:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s not weird if you look at it from her perspective. Your ex does not allow your wife to treat her step children like she would her own. She probably feels like an outcast in the family and wants someone she can bond with naturally, fix her hair how she wants, teach her French and talk about their racial history. Heritage and culture, such as Juneteenth, is very important to black people in America and you should be understanding of this since you are her husband. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 19:48:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your ex is blatantly racist towards your wife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 19:42:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s Americans for ya. We don’t actually care but we don’t wanna be rude either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 19:34:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lil weed and lil drank. Best combo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 18:29:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I don’t condone telling people to kill themselves over it (unless it’s beastiality, pedophilia or necrophilia). If it’s not hurting someone no need to be vile but laughing at them for it is okay in my book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 18:26:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My thing is why tell people, who you aren’t fucking, what your kinks are? Like I get it would hurt if your partner made fun of you, but friends? If my friends tells me that she can’t get off unless some guy sucks her toes, I’m gonna laugh at her and poke fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 18:23:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ah, so shaming is not the same as making fun of in this sense. What would be shaming if it’s not the same as making fun of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 18:21:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I stopped reading after “my wife and her boyfriend.” Sorry bro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 18:20:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me either, so why tell people? Keep it to yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> There’s nothing wrong with kink shaming. </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 18:18:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you have a weird ass kink and tell people about it (especially over the internet) people have a right to laugh if they think it’s funny. If it’s that sensitive to you then don’t tell people you aren’t having sex with. No one needs to know what you get off on. If your partner makes fun of you then you’re obviously with the wrong person. Some kinks need to be shamed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 18:14:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Kink shaming is my kink. How dare you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 18:04:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If you’re insulted then maybe stay off Reddit? Or the internet in general? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 17:59:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tomatoes go between the lettuce and the burger so no soggy bread! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 13:29:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People are stupid. We do more damage to nature than fucking cats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 13:27:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My cat used to the same thing with birds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 06:49:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thanks! Gotta show my momma I appreciate her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Baked my mom a blueberry lemon pound cake for Mother’s Day. First time baker right here! </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 04:04:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-10 03:20:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just made a blueberry lemon pound cake!! I love lemon desserts :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-09 17:13:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’d eat that everyday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 19:01:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good luck kid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-08 16:57:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe stop texting people who obviously don’t want to talk to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-07 18:09:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When you say “alcohol comedown” do you mean a hangover? Genuine question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-07 17:24:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Deli meats, cured meats, sausages, hot dogs, baloney, bacon and things like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-05 03:15:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Would’ve eaten a whole one if I didn’t have to split it with my bf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> [homemade] filet mignon with fries </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-05 02:58:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-04 23:54:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dad did the same thing with my fake ID! Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-03 23:11:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For sure, I’m the exact same way! I also think I’d be a better parent IF I have kids in my 30s, as I’d be more mature than in my 20s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-03 06:42:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Very true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-03 05:40:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Didn’t say it was a problem. I just like the term “toughen up” better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-03 05:22:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They remind me of myself. That’s why I love them <3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-03 05:15:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think we should say “toughen up” to both sons and daughters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-03 05:04:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would consult r/legaladvice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-03 05:00:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this unpopular? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-03 04:02:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A lot of porn stars commit suicide it’s sad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-03 02:30:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Where then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-02 23:52:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree 100%. I wish they allowed animal gore not that I condone it but it’s just as interesting as human gore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-02 23:42:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ve always wondered how handicapped people fucked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-02 17:37:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I read the title as “parents” 😅 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-02 17:36:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Beautiful! I’d hang this on my wall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-02 17:33:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> More like people fart in it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-02 17:25:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hold up.....you may have done something here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-02 17:22:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t understand why people push others to have kids in their early 20s?? That’s so young! Enjoy your youth and your new home! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> My dog Bear </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-05-01 17:26:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 15:34:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Interesting. So would you say kinks are more common than fetishes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 15:30:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You can contract serious diseases and other illnesses. It’s not necessarily because I find it gross (which I do). You or someone else involved could die from it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 07:32:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahahahaha! I’m in that sub too and I can attest to that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-30 07:09:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also long as people don’t have sex involving feces, bugs, dead bodies or children I don’t give a rats ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 22:04:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True dat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 16:30:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I grew up hearing, “If you’re early, you’re on time. If you’re on time, you’re late.” I live by that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 16:17:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agreee 100%. Blackberry and peach are my absolute favorite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 16:02:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Repost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 15:54:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is this a show or something?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 08:31:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DAS WHAT I THOUGHT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 02:46:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She more than likely shoved him by the way he fell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-29 01:48:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> USA USA USA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 22:41:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All the super hot ones are gay sighhhhhhh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 20:32:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck yeah you did </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 19:12:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 19:12:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I hate male sluts and female sluts. I don’t discriminate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 06:31:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s a pitcher with a built in water filter. Reduces plastic use! They also make faucet filters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 06:29:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Get a Brita ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-28 05:43:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s a sausage party up in here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 22:41:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hey he didn’t catch on to my sarcasm either. This dude is S-L-O-W. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 22:28:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah I’m 21. Just fucking with you since you get so upset and angry lmfao. Easy entertainment. But yeah I’m done with this convo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 21:46:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ding ding ding we have a winner!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 21:33:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You’re a pussy then. Wah wah wah wittle baby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 20:59:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> We’re all a little fucked up :) zippy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 20:10:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You’re definitely on the wrong sub. We don’t discriminate here we’ll take animals, humans and even babies! Nothing is safe from eye blechh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 05:32:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I love seeing men complain about how tough they have it in life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-27 05:25:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow three days of “withdrawal”. How terrifying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 22:17:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep! My roommate said the same thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> BLT with avocado </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 20:53:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 18:28:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Anddddd here comes all the crazy dog people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 01:33:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Does whatever a spiderfetus does </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 01:06:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I give up. I’m making tacos and margs for my roommates right now. Kind of have better things to do. Tootles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 00:56:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> HAHAHAHAHAHAH a you’re arguing for the sake of arguing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 00:41:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yep! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-24 00:33:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No amount of pig lives could be equivalent to a human life. And this also for my own entertainment lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 23:40:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You missed my point that animal suffering and human suffering aren’t equivalent in my opinion. Therefore, I don’t see 72 billion land animal deaths and 1.2 trillion aquatic animals deaths as being a “Holocaust”. You’re arguing with someone who has seen what goes on in slaughterhouses and chooses to turn a blind eye. I’m not saying I’m right. I’m just giving you my view on the topic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 22:54:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> this guy knows what’s up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 22:16:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My moral compass tells me that animal suffering is no where near the same as human suffering because we have a higher conscious and are self aware unlike animals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 22:13:43 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just think animals are lesser than humans, sorry boot it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 21:31:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks like a human spider hybrid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 19:34:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t think you can compare animal suffering to human suffering but that’s just me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 17:12:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oop nvm I found it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 17:11:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What was the video titled </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-23 05:28:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 😂😂😂 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 01:02:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You mean different *yolks* for different folks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-22 00:56:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is hilarious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 23:14:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look man just giving you the vibe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 23:12:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Being ungrateful and acting bratty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 22:03:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was asking what would happen without the stitches. Can you read? Stop being a patronizing asshole because I asked a question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 21:54:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do, thanks. Do you not see all the replies? I didn’t know what tore during child birth cause I’ve never had a kid and wasn’t educated on it in school. I know the difference between the taint and the pussy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 20:13:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not if it makes the school look bad no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 19:23:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahahahahaha yes I’m very educated on the topic now. Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 19:07:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s about imagine. A school’s imagine may be tarnished if they allow students spread hate speeches whether that be on or off campus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 19:04:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My boyfriend and I are quite literally the same size. Im 5’9 1/2 and he’s 5’10 and I weigh around 120 he weights around 130. We both slender beans but sometimes I feel heavy when I sit in his lap or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 18:32:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sooooooo if there were no stitches would it grow back normal or? I guess what’s the point in saying it goes back to normal size if you need stitches to do that? I dont know just sounds super shitty and painful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 18:29:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought you have to stitch the vagina up sometimes after birth? So it does loosen and doesn’t go back to normal size? Sorry not trying to argue here just a 21 year old American girl with no kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 18:21:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some people can’t have children of their own. My parents adopted me. Sure I’m “some random child to raise” that’s what everyone’s mentality is on adopted children. I don’t want to be a parent personally but don’t be so dense like your last statement. You know damn well why people would want “some random child to raise.” It really sounds like you are saying adopted children are unloveable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-21 17:35:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She looked the best in 2015 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-20 20:49:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> How did that get past security? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 21:59:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Here comes all the animal rights activists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 20:52:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I use two towels. One for my hair and one for my body. I’m a girl and have longer hair so I like to wrap it up to towel dry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 17:45:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look I’m 5’10 so I would turn him down just because I’m very tall for a woman but you’re like 5’3? Seems kinda superficial </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 05:47:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Definitely talk to them about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 00:20:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-19 00:17:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just because someone makes an “adult decision” doesn’t mean it was a good decision by any means. I think people are in the right to express how they feel about her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 22:11:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> IT WAS A POMEGRANATE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 19:22:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> YALL STOP WITH THE FRUIT AND CONDIMENTS PLEASE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 19:19:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Unless you fart ON me then you’re gonna catch these hands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 19:08:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t know any high schoolers who gangbang lmfao you’re in a whole nother world man. Peace out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 19:03:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh and I don’t think the preference is childish. It’s pretty adult themed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 19:02:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh I got what you were saying :) I just wanted to keep reiterating my point. I like hearing myself talk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 18:55:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t wanna marry someone who lied about a gangbang? That’s fine if you’re cool with marrying someone who has no respect for you. I guess I’m childish because I wouldn’t want to marry a lying sloot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 18:41:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Are children lied to by their fiancés about a gangbang? Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 18:38:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Preference bitch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 18:34:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hopefully your ex finds someone better who respects him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 18:08:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please stop. Get some help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 18:07:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends on what kind of school. Public? Yeah maybe you’re right. Private? Hellllllllll no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 18:05:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nice one haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 06:12:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yay!!! Mississippi! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 06:07:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit this is the ultimate high snack. Gimme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 02:54:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That pit bull analogy was shit just like your parenting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-18 02:24:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit I didn’t know dogs could be intersex!!! That’s so cool tell Bug I love him.. or her:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-17 19:24:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What about smoking weed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-17 19:11:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why the fuck would you even say that to your partner tho? What’s the point? The benefit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-17 18:44:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just saw something further in the thread that made me think this. Guess I should’ve responded to them instead of making my own comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-17 18:40:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do people not believe that a woman might actually want to work and be the breadwinner? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 17:52:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is actually really cute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 17:48:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some people have a scat fetish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 17:38:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I didn’t even have to read the paragraph to know that’s a baaaad idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 17:34:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What was on the playlist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-16 01:25:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This person is just ignant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-15 20:29:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me too teehee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-15 18:07:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why does reddit hate college? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-15 17:39:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was thinking the same thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-15 17:38:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just wondering but do you clean yourself well? Were you just on your period? Are you stressed? Hormones and hygiene can be a huge factor in how you taste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-15 17:25:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think it’s how you were raised because my dad always gives Coca Colas to the landscapers and pool guys. So it’s a given we offer drinks or food to guests who come inside. I’m glad I was raised that way!

Edit: I’m from the Southern United States </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-15 03:52:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Let’s see if y’all will still be calling each other “mates” after he finds out the truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-15 03:45:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I understand her behavior is abhorrent but I really don’t like when people call those with a mental illness psycho or crazy. That being said yeah definitely leave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-15 00:36:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> OH SHIT HE GOT THE FUNNY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-15 00:33:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whenever I make jokes like this I get downvoted. Hmph. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 23:37:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I never subscribed to Team Piñata either but I enjoyed watching them with DissociaDID. Oh! And DissociaDID recently posted to their Instagram addressing the situation. I would go check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 23:24:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah we probably aren’t looking at the same thing. I didn’t see any of that stuff on the link I was on. I just saw naked adults sneezing. It’s really shocking because I loved DissociaDID and Team Piñata as a couple and I just can’t believe it ya know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 23:12:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I see no CP on the threads. Am I missing something?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 22:29:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “I trust him with everything except her..” So you don’t trust him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 22:24:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s prime entertainment! Pussy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 22:22:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well when and if that time comes then maybe I’ll consider if he’s a true friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 22:15:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It is offensive if you’re treating me nicely just so you have a chance to get in my pants. It’s not genuine respect as a beloved friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 22:00:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Disagree heavily. I’ve never had a guy friend that didn’t want to fuck me and I find that offensive and non friendship material. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 18:18:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Just go be a vegan and stfu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 18:17:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahahahaha true. That’s his moral justification you need to eat to live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 18:10:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed. Plus people rush into marriage and children without fully getting to know the other person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 04:46:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Look up sunk cost fallacy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 03:21:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This will happen again OP. You can’t trust him anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 03:17:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> paprika is also a good one if you want a lil extra flavor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 03:09:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I always season my food with at least salt, pepper, garlic powder and onion powder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 02:57:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My boyfriend and I are rising seniors at different universities. 2 1/2 hours away from each other. We’ve been together for 4 years and it’s been great. Most people don’t want to put effort into things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-14 02:09:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Your boyfriend wants to pass you around his friends like that? He has no respect for you OP. You deserve much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-13 21:28:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can you link the photographers insta handle? I’d like to give him a follow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-13 21:26:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You wanna fix this? Fix yourself crazy bitch. Ruining an innocent mans life? I hope your boyfriend runs fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-13 20:02:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You really need to work on yourself before this relationship can move forward </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-13 01:17:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Me toooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-12 18:37:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Agreed. Where’s the gore? If I wanted to watch porn I’d join a porn subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-12 18:34:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn wtf?? That’s assault is it not? I’d break up with her you don’t want your wife beating you because that’s where this is headed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-12 18:29:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’ve wanted to try this sooooo bad. How does it taste? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-12 18:27:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It does tho. Ever heard of birds of a feather flock together? The people who you hang around affects you and affects how others view you if you’re hanging around a toxic person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-10 18:49:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Opening a relationship is always a sign of it ending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 06:10:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lmfao it’s okay. Sorry I told you to fuck off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 06:06:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “Assholes like me” that’s funny you don’t even know me and I’m not even disagreeing with you I’m just saying that other people view things differently. Also, where did I say women should be ashamed of their pasts? Oh that’s right I didn’t. Fuck off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 05:55:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think what the problem is is that some people lie about their experimenting early on in the relationship. That then sets a foundation of mistrust. Just be honest from the get go and things should go smoothly, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 05:52:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You should want to change for yourself not for someone else. It may get her back or it may not but either way you’d come out a different (maybe better) person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 05:44:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It definitely might change someone’s view on how you treat sex. Other people hold different values over sex and that could be a sign of sexual incompatibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 02:37:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I only get pissed when he starts screaming that is just unacceptable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 00:16:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Maybe six months to a year? We’ve been together for 4 years now. Still going strong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 00:10:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You need a better boyfriend. That’s probably why you feel so anxious and insecure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-06 00:07:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This sub is literally about opinions. If you’re gonna get offended by unpopular opinions you’re definitely in the wrong place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-05 23:56:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly, I was about to comment this. It doesn’t matter which console you use that’s how each animal crossing game works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-05 09:19:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> All the negative comments are the sluts who have been shamed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-05 09:16:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahahahaha you can be with a good girl who knows what she’s doing, knows what she likes, can communicate and has a high sex drive. Just cause you’re not a slut doesn’t mean you suck at sex!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-05 08:58:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Of course it’s not necessary. Don’t try and fix something that’s not broken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-05 04:24:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Second grade </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-04 23:29:10 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> compatibility and preference are important to some people seeking long term relationships </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-04 23:27:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have no problem with friends of mine doing what they want sexually. More power to them. However, when it comes to a long term relationship I wouldn’t want someone who had a promiscuous past. It comes down to preference and compatibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-03 00:52:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Then the sub needs to go on private </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-02 22:51:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why doesn’t she just move in with you? If she’s going to work and living with older family members she is putting them at risk. Seems safer to just quarantine together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-02 19:25:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tylenol is no where near the same as antipsychotics so one shouldn’t compare the two. Also OP’s gf won’t apologize or take accountability for her actions. She seems to only say “I guess you can’t take a joke anymore. Got it.” It sounds like the relationship is over in my eyes. Sorry OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-02 17:22:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eating ass is pointless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-02 17:13:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> FINALLY someone said it!! Two birds one stone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-01 21:31:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m normal I just think death and gore is interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-04-01 17:45:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Okay but like do you change your sheets...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-29 22:49:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do this and agree so I’m downvoting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 17:59:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree. I can’t get horny if I don’t know you at all. Weirds me out to the extreme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-28 08:33:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s a southern thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 23:19:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> SAME </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 17:18:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Most people on this thread are just a bunch of horndogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 17:04:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No? Lots of us hate the idea of casual sex or it makes some uncomfortable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-26 03:08:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why does this offend people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-25 00:46:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> True true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 22:43:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t understand people who think water is gross. It tastes like nothing and is so quenching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 22:39:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No. No they do not. A lot of people are uneducated about food in general which affects their diet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 22:15:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> The thing about height is you can’t change that but you can definitely change your weight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-24 16:30:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Either way pregnancy sounds shitty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 22:55:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally me rn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 22:41:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s a gore subreddit I really have no shame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 22:36:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Please link the vid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 22:15:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> IKR?? They’re massive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 22:11:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> And this is why I’m having a C-Section IF I have a kid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 20:36:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> He’s just straight vibing y’all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 20:26:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God hers was the absolute worst. And I mean painful to watch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 19:17:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Guns N Roses starts playing in the back ground. Imagine THAT being the last thing you hear....chilling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 18:59:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought they were gonna draw and quarter it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 17:09:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t even want a fucking kid so? That won’t be a problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 17:03:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit you’re retarded </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 08:13:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Did you slap her in the face or?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 06:23:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I guess we’ll just have to agree to disagree. I’m just glad I still have my right to an abortion regardless of opinions like yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 06:11:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You people really expect couples to just not fuck if they aren’t ready to be parents? Ridiculous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-23 05:50:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Men should keep their dicks in their pants then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-21 16:20:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> God I love a milky geeb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-21 08:50:13 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Depends on the couple </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-20 18:05:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My athletic season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-19 01:04:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why....Just why ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-17 21:11:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes I don’t see why that’s a problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-16 22:04:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> For my wisdom tooth holes to heal up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-15 20:09:54 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wouldn’t know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-15 19:51:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Logic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-14 20:53:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My tiny bong! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-13 04:31:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I tried percs at 14 only once tho never again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-13 01:05:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s soooo easy just soak it in a salty rubbing alcohol mix (use at least 90% isopropyl) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-12 18:07:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Bong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 20:51:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 20:44:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What is DADT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 18:14:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ewwwww really:( I’ve never had guts. What’s a good tasting one for someone who has never had offal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 16:54:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck dem kids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 16:44:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> INTP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 06:35:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spent his whole spring break with me after my wisdom tooth surgery. He got me chick fil a mac n cheese and chocolate shakes, Popeyes mashed potatoes and gravy and watched all my favorite kids movies with me. He’s the sweetest ugh I’m like getting butterflies just thinking about him!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 06:30:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What does “HL” and “LL” mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 05:56:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah it seems like a lot to me as well but I try not to judge. My body count is 2 and I’m 21 but that’s mainly because I don’t get horny for people I don’t have an emotional connection with. I’m definitely not a 1 night stand type gal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 05:52:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> An unconscious person cannot consent tho? It’s rape? Just because you are married does not mean you have a right to sex 24/7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 05:46:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck off. Having sex with an unconscious person is rape and definitely out of the ordinary. ESPECIALLY since they already had a conversation about how she is a victim of sexual assault and she does not feel comfortable with it. If you and your gf consent to this and it’s y’alls kink then do you man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 05:22:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I agree that people are allowed to have preferences. This should’ve been a conversation to have before marriage considering how hostile OP’s husband is being about something that happened years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 05:20:28 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same. 12 for a woman in her 30s is so normal it’s wild to me that her husband is being such a dick?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 05:18:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why would you marry a man who speaks to you like this, OP :(( I’m sorry you’re having to deal with this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-11 05:17:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have friends whose body count is in the 30-40s so you are NOT out of the ordinary. Your husband is just insecure and this probably should’ve been a conversation to have before marriage. Ya know since it’s such a big deal to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 18:15:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I would honestly go you two could both have a great time together. Plus FOMO is no fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 18:10:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> MLM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 18:02:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I can see that actually. Her character is pretty quirky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 17:49:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You’re 100% right I do because it doesn’t line up with my values or morals but you do you! To each their own ya know? And yeah you’re definitely not my fam either I take that back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 17:11:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She literally said she’s end things if he fucked other girls. Lmfao that is cheating and hypocrisy at its finest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 17:06:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nah fam you don’t actually love them if you’re fucking other people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 16:07:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I deadass think Lucy is into it too tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 16:06:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s called compromising and being respectful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 16:05:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You either have shitty roommates and just deal with it or you are the shitty roommate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-10 14:33:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I dont know much about Artificial Sweeteners because I’ve heard how bad they are for you (I haven’t done any research myself). I typically use stevia sweeteners for my coffee and tea and it’s soooo good! I don’t have to worry about the side effects of artificial sugar or real sugar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 20:05:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Lmfao I don’t know anything about fishing either I just see it a lot off the Gulf of Mexico. Seems to be a regional thing I guess :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 19:09:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You’ve never seen people fishing on the shore? Maybe it’s a southern thing but it’s very common on Florida beaches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 17:58:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Nothing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 17:52:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s not love that would be lust </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 17:48:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly why I don’t want children </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 17:46:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Suicide </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 17:40:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Because I can afford it and like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 17:37:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No because I’m attracted to cis males </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 17:26:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I think you mean *worst*. And yeah it’s hard to insult someone you literally know nothing about lmfao. I’m very calm thank you tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 17:25:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I wish I could </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 17:01:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fuck awf with these stupid sex questions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 16:45:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 16:37:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My brother and his wife do this and they are thriving. This is also how I want my financial situation to be when I’m married. Keep doing you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 16:23:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Honestly tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 15:46:06 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ‘Tis so funny!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 15:44:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t believe in astrology lmfaoooo it’s just fun to mess around with. Who hurt you for real? An ex gf? You poor thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 15:41:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awe boo hoo some reddit loser told me my opinion doesn’t count. Well guess what opinions are like assholes everyone’s got one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 15:11:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> She asked his opinion tho? Was he suppose to lie to her? Honesty and communication are important in a relationship </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 15:03:46 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Having a child sounds awful but having a child with a man like this sounds not as awful but still pretty shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 14:57:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the dopest shit I’ve seen in a minute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 14:40:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-09 14:33:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You’re disgusting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-08 15:51:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So anyone who is smaller than plus size doesn’t have a normal body? Choose your words carefully. Smaller women exist and their bodies are normal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 23:55:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Grave of Fireflies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-07 03:43:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 21 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-06 23:54:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Good luck to you!! Glad I could make you smile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-06 22:43:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I smoke everyday and I’m on the Dean’s List at an Honors college while also being a successful student athlete. It’s all about control and having a healthy mindset. It’s totally possible to be a stoner and be successful and professional. I also only smoke at nighttime during the weekdays and do not go to class/practice high. Weekends however are for boolin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-06 22:41:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wait for her. My boyfriend and I were in a similar situation when we were 17. My parents despised him and we had to date in secret which caused a lot of drama in my household. My parents ended up letting me date him (mainly as a “I told you so” if things didn’t work out). Well fast forward 4 years and we are currently finishing up college together and totally in love. Just hang in there. Everything gets better with time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-06 22:36:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> British people be like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-06 20:14:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Curly Dick Road in Australia lmfao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-06 16:07:51 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Men carry the pregnancy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-06 06:56:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> LMFAOOOOOO I did this to my best friends belly button when we were 14 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-05 18:44:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why don’t you learn to spell correctly then ask your weird sex questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-04 18:30:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Cat or a fox </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-04 16:04:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally nothing it was all an act lmfao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 22:14:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Go ask a track/sprints coach. They’ll give you the answer you’re looking for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 05:53:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude anything below 50 is freezing Hahahahahahahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-03-03 02:35:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahahahahaha I was so confused when I started reading this thread. the fun facts I always heard and told were about oneself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-28 23:43:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Great! The sun is shining, it’s 60 degrees out and our first track meet of the season is tomorrow at our home field. Gonna be another beautiful day tomorrow:)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-27 04:16:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 100,000 tomorrow so I can invest that money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 23:59:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> So this was actually a time when my parents thought I was gonna die. I was around 3 years old and had a tonsillectomy, well a couple days after I started coughing up blood clots and basically my throat started hemorrhaging. It was so bad the doctor had to come to my house to try and treat me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 22:08:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Tony chachere’s creole seasoning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-26 21:34:30 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah apparently there is a gas leak at my house so I have to pay a $500 gas bill that I can’t afford for gas I didn’t even use </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-25 17:33:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Literally any fruit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-24 23:31:56 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “That’s your boyfriend??? You’re too hot for him”  keep in mind the bitch that said this knew me for two weeks and I had been with my boyfriend for two years at that point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-24 23:28:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When you say skidmarking up up a toilet you mean in the inside of the bowl correct? What is someone suppose to do then? Stick their hand in toilet water to clean a public restroom? No way there are custodians for that. Shit happens, literally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-24 23:25:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I thought it was a girl who does anal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-24 23:16:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> A million dollars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-24 02:57:39 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Emily </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 05:36:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m 21 and a lot of this is me right now hahahahaha especially the tea and loving when plans cancel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-21 01:36:45 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mosquitos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-20 19:47:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Chargrilled oysters are the best!!!!! Love me some raw oysters but nothing beats being cooking in butter yummy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-20 18:32:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Probably why coworkers should stay coworkers.... seems to make things difficult and awkward </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-20 18:20:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have found that cocaine doesn’t really effect me. I think because I have ADD it just stabilized me or something because I do not feel wired or anything really just a bad taste in my mouth. So yes I think coke is overrated in my mind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-20 16:51:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> People obviously realize it’s a joke. They also realize it’s not funny jokes. Plus this doesn’t even fit the sub it’s not even close to technically the truth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-20 16:23:31 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is not technically the truth. Doesn’t fit the sub. Plus lots of creeps in the comments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-20 16:20:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Courage the Cowardly Dog!! I still watch it to this day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-20 16:18:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> When egg yolk runs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-20 02:32:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Animal crossing and sims </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-20 02:25:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Drive stick shift </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 21:28:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Ayeeee we have the same birthday also I’m a Gemini rising and I didn’t drive till I was 17 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-18 04:48:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My dad told my boyfriend not to walk down the stairs in a pool because that’s gay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-17 23:08:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is why I don’t need/want kids bc I definitely would turn them against my cheating husband lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-17 16:22:53 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why do I want the caption to say “Ratatouille” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-15 17:32:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I used it to triangulate my high jump approach in college. Pretty neat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-14 21:32:59 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Veterinarian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 23:10:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn, yeah that’d scare the hell out of me as a kid! But alas, I was educated in the southern United States. Can you link that video? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 21:19:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow I have so many childhood memories of my friends and I walking around the neighborhood and playing in construction zones after hours. It was so entertaining as a child I didn’t even realize the dangers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-13 16:04:22 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I don’t see how that correlates but okay dude! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 22:59:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I ask others in the restroom to hand me toilet paper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 22:54:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oop! I found the misogynist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 22:53:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Why? I call my boyfriend dude all the time? I call my girl friends dude? Everyone is “dude” !! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 22:19:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Spyro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 16:59:48 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Oh wait I read that question wrong. No my mom and my dad are both my legal guardians. So they both adopted me. I probably didn’t make that clear in writing, sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 16:58:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I was adopted at infancy from a different region and my brothers were in their early teens at that point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 07:54:08 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> What Does The Fox Say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 03:39:17 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just get defensive because I love my family so much!! No worries :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 03:33:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> They aren’t my step brothers at all. We share the same father so they are my adoptive half brothers. But I don’t call them anything but my brothers because of the bond we have. They are my family. No one is “adoptive” anything. So the story goes - my dad married this woman had my brothers and they divorced. My dad remarried my mom when my brothers were around 8. My mom had a hysterectomy so she couldn’t have children and adopted me. My brothers aren’t my step siblings as we share the same dad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 00:46:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “That’s your boyfriend of 2 years?? Wow you’re too hot for him.” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-12 00:42:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yeah I’m adopted and this was the approach my parents took. I don’t see them as my “adoptive” parents they’re just my parents. I wasn’t treated any different than my older brothers (technically they’re my half brothers as my mom is their step mom). I appreciate my parents even more knowing they were honest with me from the get go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-11 23:53:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> If celebrities would just be honest with us about the work they get done this wouldn’t be such a big deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-11 23:50:47 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Damn!!! She’s a huge female!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-11 21:30:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I have mine set to only three people can see me on my snapmap. My boyfriend and two besties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-11 21:23:29 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sims language and animal crossing language </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-11 19:29:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Is it possible to link the video?? I have to watch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-11 19:28:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Also I would LOVE to see some of these people do their make up. Shade matching is hard as shit and your skin changes color based off seasons too. I have three different foundation shades 1 for summer, winter and a transition for spring/fall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-11 04:10:20 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahahaha well something is working because we are both happy and going on 4 years. Do you have advice? I’m just trying to be a better girlfriend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-11 01:17:21 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I really wanna watch the rest of this video lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 23:03:52 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yes! Definitely an option </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 22:36:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> French </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 22:35:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That shit hurts and is pricy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 22:18:32 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> “But you’re still the one pool where I’d happily drown” </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 20:41:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m confused about the sexual nature of you and your husband. I’m sorry if these are rude questions but I didn’t know asexual people were interested in relationships like marriage? Do you have/want children? Is it more of a platonic relationship than romantic? Please tell me to fuck off if these are rude questions I’m just ignorant about asexuality! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 20:31:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Internal monologue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 20:25:26 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It doesn’t seem like anyone’s business but my own. I really value privacy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 20:24:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> ME TOOOOO I’m so glad other people are like this. I don’t want someone talking about me in bed so why would I talk about someone else? Also it’s just weird and makes me uncomfortable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 20:19:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> No Ragrets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 16:44:42 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Mortar and pestle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 16:15:07 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hahahahaha yes! but I also hear I’m very intimidating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 04:59:14 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Fried calamari or charcuterie boards
, I still love both hahahahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 04:56:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Wow those look amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 04:49:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My boyfriend and I are going to eat crawfish with a bottle of champagne </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-10 02:02:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Asking if we can do anal. It seriously ruins the mood and I just start thinking about taking a backwards shit which is NOT sexy to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-09 18:10:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sweet thank you! So I wasn’t saving them for nothing! Yay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> WEED TEA </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-09 16:41:41 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Such a dumb question but I gotta ask...can I brew tea with weed stems?? Is that a thing and would it get me high because for some reason I save all my stems in a jar so I just have like 2gs of stems </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-09 16:34:25 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Love the story bc it involves crawfish and a relatable scenario lmfaoo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-09 16:32:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Went to my friends house last night and he had made dinner for us which was so random and kind!! We then hit a couple dabs and geebs drank a lil wine and watched the office. Supa chill night 10/10 would recommend (maybe not watch the office for 3 hours tho Hahahahahaha) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-09 16:13:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Well thank ya! I don’t enjoy talking about sex first of all but also I really value my privacy even with my closest of friends, I still need space and boundaries. And yes I don’t like/need my friends unsolicited opinions about my intimate life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-09 08:03:11 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> DS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-09 04:47:23 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> 1,860 miles
I’m adopted so :) I also grew up that far away from my birth state </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-09 04:41:00 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Animal Crossing New Leaf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-09 00:16:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Not necessarily true, I don’t talk about my sex life with anyone but my partner but I dont know how many of us are like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-08 05:28:44 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Dude I think about this when I’m sober.. so no resin lungs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 08:06:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> This is the content I subscribed for LMFAOO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-07 01:21:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Awwwwwwww he’s got a stick stuck in his wing :(( I hope it doesn’t hurt him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-06 17:54:02 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> RIGHT ON RED </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-06 17:49:24 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Can I ask what MLM company she is trying to sell ?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-06 16:13:57 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I just everyday because Im a collegiate high jumper Hahahahahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-02-04 16:15:01 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I’m sorry but this is NOT botched. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 16:07:27 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> It’s beautiful!! Looks like a sunset </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-29 16:06:37 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Hell yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-26 07:20:36 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Looks good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE> Perfectly juicy chicken with summer squashes. [homemade] </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-25 04:41:19 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-10 20:26:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> You from the ‘sip? He’s from there I’m pretty sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-10 20:24:50 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Was coming to comment this exact thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-10 18:58:03 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Sims 2 is my childhood and I still play to this day!!! I’m 21 now lmfao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-10 07:05:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> I do the same but with blush!!! Sorry I do realize this was posted 6 days ago lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-09 23:46:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Same here got them touched up twice maybe three times and just didn’t like spending the money especially since no one noticed I’d gotten them done lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-09 23:33:34 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Some people get permanent fillers!! That might be what this woman had done.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-07 20:22:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Eating food on trips weirds me out the food looks like it’s crawling and wiggling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-07 20:16:04 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> That’s a WIN in my book!! Free mojitooooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-07 01:32:55 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-02 22:07:40 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Exactly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2020-01-02 17:38:09 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy CRAP I need this in my life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-18 19:15:18 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yup! Love writing papers and doing my assignments high af. Helps me focus and makes my work more interesting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-12 07:28:16 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Marijuana </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-12 07:20:38 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Def an eighth since you said them nugs dense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-10 07:49:12 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Whoa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-01 21:39:33 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Incredible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-12-01 16:52:49 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 07:35:58 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> As a collegiate high jumper this is amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 04:33:35 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> My athleticism and loyalty to those I love/care about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 04:23:15 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Holy shit this is the coolest thing I’ve seen all day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
<TITLE>   </TITLE>
<DATE> 2019-08-15 03:38:05 </DATE>
<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
<TEXT> Yummy :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
